<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Yeongdeungpo-gu on Every Corner of Korea</title>
    <link>https://codecorea.github.io/tags/yeongdeungpo-gu/</link>
    <description>Every Corner of Korea (Yeongdeungpo-gu)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 03:28:50 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="https://codecorea.github.io/tags/yeongdeungpo-gu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Yeouido 1st, Elementary Tour 1st National Assembly &amp; Constitutional Memorial Hall - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/yeouido-1st-elementary-tour-1st-national-assembly-constitutional-memorial-hall-216/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 03:28:50 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/yeouido-1st-elementary-tour-1st-national-assembly-constitutional-memorial-hall-216/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;yeouido-1st-elementary-tour-1st-national-assembly-constitutional-memorial-hall--216&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;View of the main assembly hall of the National Assembly Building - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/216/2e67aea9-21d3-4de1-b9a3-caeec5d5e973.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    View of the main assembly hall of the National Assembly Building
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Yeouido 1st, Elementary Tour 1st National Assembly &amp;amp; Constitutional Memorial Hall
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    It is the &#39;President of Minui&#39;, but it is the place where the ordinary people cannot easily access. However, it is easy for anyone to visit and visit here if they want. However, if you make a reservation 3 days before the tour. A place that will be a good experience for adults as well as children&#39;s performance evaluation. In addition, it is closely related to the contents of the textbook, so in many ways it is worth calling it “the number one elementary field trip”.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Tours of the National Assembly are divided into the Constitutional Memorial Hall (the National Visitors Center) and the National Assembly. Previously, it was separate, but now it is possible to watch “one stop”. The Constitution Memorial Hall, which displays materials and artifacts related to the National Assembly of the Republic of Korea, can be freely visited, and the National Assembly Building must be gathered as a group at the time of reservation for guidance.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    The dedication memorial hall is composed of the ‘Minister of the National Assembly’, ‘Temporary Assemblyman ’s Hall’, and ‘National Assembly Tour’. At the &#39;Temporary Court House&#39;, you can see the materials related to the provisional court and the first constitutional assembly, which is the legislative institution of the Korean Provisional Government. Space.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Upon receiving the guidance of the National Assembly guide, the House of Parliament listens to explanations of what the National Assembly is doing, and actually visits the main venue where the bill is being processed. The advantage is that all explanations are made to fit the eye level of the children. Rather than letting parents know something more by studying separately, it&#39;s a good idea to research the National Assembly with your child in advance and summarize your child&#39;s questions and ask the guide.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Then, let&#39;s go on a full-fledged tour of the National Assembly from now on. First, when you enter the entrance of the National Assembly, two Haitai greets visitors. Originally, Haitai is a legendary animal that judges fertility and good and evil. Because of this symbolism, it was a symbol of Saheungbu, an organization that inspects officials in the Joseon Dynasty. Perhaps the National Assembly stood in front of the National Assembly in the sense that the National Assembly would act on behalf of the people to monitor the government and correct the errors. Let&#39;s tell the children that this is the meaning of the name of the cookie maker.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Haitai Statue at the entrance of the National Assembly Building - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/216/bd0b74be-646f-4ca5-b01a-83bb7982a177.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Haitai Statue at the entrance of the National Assembly Building
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Facing Haetaesang and walking to the right for about 5 minutes, today&#39;s first destination, the dedication memorial, appears. You can enter by entering the National Assembly Visitor Center on the right side of the entrance and confirming the reservation. When you open the three glass doors, you can see the portraits of the former National Assembly Speakers to the right of the large hall. The main hall is always in a &#39;special exhibition&#39;, but it is good to start watching by watching a promotional video about the functions and roles of the National Assembly right in the public relations video theater on the right. Robot Taekwon V comes out and kindly explains it to the eye level of children. If your father tells you that rumors of a robot Taekwon V secret base in the Capitol were spinning when he was a child, how would the children react?
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Dedicated Memorial Lobby - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/216/59da69f9-0386-48bb-b034-390ec251f419.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Dedicated Memorial Lobby
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you go across the re-emerged central hall, you are the Minister of National Assembly. One thing you shouldn&#39;t miss here is to take a cyber authentication shot against the backdrop of various parliaments. The history and activities of the former National Assembly Speakers and the variety of souvenirs they have received from overseas are bonuses.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Minister of Parliament - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/216/315310c2-c32e-4b34-8bc1-c146f918c5e2.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Minister of Parliament
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The provisional courthouse, which is naturally connected to the Minister of National Assembly, is a place where you can see the process and activities of the provisional courthouse, which was the National Assembly of the Provisional Government of the Republic of Korea. If the Government of the Republic of Korea took over the provisional law of the Provisional Government, it can be said that the National Assembly was the authenticity of the Provisional Court. Another advantage is that you can see the activities of the temporary courtroom through panoramic images as well as photos and records.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Exhibition of the National Assembly - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/216/a4e5166e-9c8f-4d1d-b054-1a6cb7a73936.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Exhibition of the National Assembly
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Next is the “President&#39;s Office produced by the Parliament,” which literally introduces the activities and achievements of the President of the National Assembly. Don&#39;t forget to take a commemorative photo here in a space that reproduces the president&#39;s office. Nowadays, children whose dreams are presidents will be rare, but when they were young, they told them that most children&#39;s dreams were presidents.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox type2 clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Temporary Court House - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/216/ce56abe9-4e76-4f72-a260-bd934356eb9b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Temporary Court House
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;President&#39;s Office produced by Congress - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/216/186a0f97-eada-4099-8531-cbb2b1778679.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     President&#39;s Office produced by Congress
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The children&#39;s experience room, decorated with colorful primary colors, is a place where children can have fun. You can experience the functions of the Korean National Assembly and the principles of democracy while touching, turning, watching and enjoying. There is also a corner in the subsequent National Assembly of the Republic of Korea that informs the operation principle and composition of the Korean National Assembly and at the same time looks around the world&#39;s parliament. It would be interesting to compare our parliament with other parliaments. Looking at the Constitution Hall, the last exhibition room of the Memorial Hall, the supplementary explanation of the father is necessary. It explains what the Constituent Assembly is, and why it was necessary to convene from the Constitutional Assembly to establish a country after liberation.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;14&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Constitutional Council Miniature - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/216/03fc0729-60ee-4c6a-b52c-549bb68eb55c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Constitutional Council Miniature
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   “The Constituent Assembly is a parliament gathered to make a constitution. In order to establish a modern democratic country, we must first have a constitution. So, it was called from the Constituent Assembly before the establishment of the Korean government. Here is the day when the first constitution of the Republic of Korea is released. ” Isn&#39;t this enough?
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;16&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Children&#39;s Experience Hall - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/216/f6f79d7f-d27c-4d28-8f37-a66d79a6e367.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Children&#39;s Experience Hall
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It takes about an hour to tour all of the Memorial Halls. Then, in front of the Memorial Hall, take a shuttle bus to the National Assembly to head to the National Assembly Building. Unfortunately, the red carpeted staircase, which appears in the news every day, is an exclusive entrance to the National Assembly. Visitors must enter the parliament building by the back aisle. From here, the guide of the National Assembly staff begins.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;18&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;National Assembly Visitor Shuttle Bus - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/216/5d2f630c-7f87-4da0-b33d-050c0ed778f4.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     National Assembly Visitor Shuttle Bus
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The first stop is the National Assembly Hall. It is a space under the dome that looks like a symbol of the National Assembly Building. The marble on the floor and the lighting on the ceiling dome create an exotic atmosphere. After walking around the main hall for a while, we move to the 4th floor exhibition hall to hear brief explanations and see various activities of the National Assembly. This is a review of what I have already seen from the Constitutional Memorial Hall. The dedication memorial hall summarized the contents that were divided into various exhibition halls into a panorama on one wall. After looking around the exhibition hall, we will finally head to the highlight of today, the main assembly hall.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;20&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Inside the Capitol dome - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/216/58abacf4-3598-41cc-839e-558ac7ec367d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Inside the Capitol dome
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The first impression I see in real life on a daily meeting of the main assembly hall on TV is &#39;it&#39;s less than I thought&#39;. It is a phenomenon that many people use wide-angle lenses when trying to show the entire conference hall. While sitting on the second floor of the auditorium, looking at the main conference hall, we hear a full explanation of the functions and roles of the National Assembly.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;22&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;National Assembly Main Building 4F Exhibition Hall - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/216/cfc370a0-b855-473d-802f-c56096287e43.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     National Assembly Main Building 4F Exhibition Hall
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The most important thing that 299 members of Congress do in the National Assembly is legislative action that makes the law. People&#39;s lives are determined by what laws the National Assembly makes, so it is a very powerful authority. Next, the enactment activities to deliberate and inspect the country&#39;s livelihood. It is about deliberating and deciding on a country&#39;s budget for the year. In addition, the National Assembly is responsible for checking the administration. All these things are called ‘politics’. So politics is so important and essential that we can ignore it as dirty. This is why children should look around at the National Assembly and pay attention to politics.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;24&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;First Parliament House - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/216/87d005d2-bcee-49dd-81a3-7886ea2a809c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     First Parliament House
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Constitutional Memorial Hall and the National Assembly Building are not the only highlights of the National Assembly. Along with the National Library of Korea, the National Library of Korea, the representative library in Korea, is also a place to go with children. In order to go with your child, you can visit the Internet three days before the desired date of visit.
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.nanet.go.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;국회도서관 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
     www.nanet.go.kr
    &lt;/a&gt;
    ) Must be applied in advance. If the weather is good, it is good to take a walk in the National Assembly. You can take a rest for a while after climbing the Uiwon Garden, where the wonderful hanok is located. If it is unfortunate to come to Yeouido and see only the National Assembly, the tour hall of the nearby broadcasting station is also a place that children will like. No reservation is required unless you are in a group.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox type2 clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;26&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Capitol facade - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/216/5245afa9-29af-413b-983f-e834e89f843c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Capitol facade
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;26&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sculpture in front of the capitol - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/216/e87b85f4-88f3-4dfc-ad49-5b401adc4a6d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sculpture in front of the capitol
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    * National Assembly Visitor Center
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Address: 1 Capitol Road, Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Contact: 02-788-3656,
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.assembly.go.kr&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     www.assembly.go.kr
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    1.Access
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    * Self-driving
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Olympic Boulevard → Yeoui downstream IC → Turn left at the intersection in front of the House of Representatives → Parliament House
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    * public transport
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Get off at National Assembly Building Station (Subway Line 9), and 7-minute walk to Dedicated Museum
    &lt;br/&gt;
    City bus 1, 162, 261, 262, 263, 360, 362, 363, 461 and get off in front of the National Assembly Building
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    2. Delicious
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Modagoda: Noodles and Bossam / 30, Gyeok-ro, Yeongdeungpo-gu / 02-786-8787
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Other profit press: Thai food / 23, Gukhoe-daero 70-gil, Yeongdeungpo-gu / 02-783-3101
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Donghae: Conveyor-belt sushi / 25, Ginkg-ro, Yeongdeungpo-gu / 02-761-6300 /
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.donghaedo.com&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     www.donghaedo.com
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    3.Accommodation
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Lexington Hotel: 16, Gukhoe-daero-gil 76-gil, Yeongdeungpo-gu / 02-6670-7000 /
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.thelexington.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.thelexington.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Yeouido Hotel: 62, 82, Gwangjin-ro, Yeongdeungpo-gu, 02-782-0121 /
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.youngdonghotel.co.kr/hotel/korean/index.htm&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.youngdonghotel.co.kr/hotel/korean/index.htm
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Conred Seoul: 10, Yeongdeungpo-gu, International Financial Street / 02-6137-7000 /
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://conradseoul.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://conradseoul.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    ※ The above information was created in May 2013, and may change later, so be sure to check it before you travel.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A unique alleyway ‘Munrae Art Village’ where an iron man and an artist coexist - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/a-unique-alleyway-munrae-art-village-where-an-iron-man-and-an-artist-coexist-204/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 09:05:10 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/a-unique-alleyway-munrae-art-village-where-an-iron-man-and-an-artist-coexist-204/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;a-unique-alleyway-munrae-art-village-where-an-iron-man-and-an-artist-coexist--204&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Seoul scenery over the Han River - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/204/a3740b03-71d6-40fb-a2a3-694cd0aa5ad4.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Seoul scenery over the Han River
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   A unique alleyway ‘Munrae Art Village’ where an iron man and an artist coexist
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    There are a lot of buildings and apartments when you walk around the Han River and look around. Excluding the ridges of Mt. I hope that the Bukhansan Mountain is not covered by the building. When you escape from the Han River, the scenery of the low world, which was hidden in the big building, unfolds. The sidewalk block is stuck like a ruler and the square sign is dizzy.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Flyers such as lodging, rent, charter, and Gosiwon are posted on the alleys of a university town. Alleys with a high smell of people are better than the monotony of building forests. Suddenly, memories of Munrae-dong are revived. &#34;Jiing ~&#34; The sound of iron splitting, the mural on the alleyway that you don&#39;t know who drew it, the dazzling Daegutang ... , I looked back on the journey.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    From Exit 2 of Munrae Station on the Seoul Subway Line 2, go straight for about 200m, and there is a junction of 128 roads between Dangsan-ro and Dorim-ro. You can easily find direction signs and signs related to the Munrae Art Village in the vicinity. Based on Dorim-ro 128-gil, the high-rise building area and the low-rise building area have different atmospheres. This itinerary is a course that walks around the area with mostly low buildings.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The place where the alleyway begins is the famous seat of mural - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/204/d4a6a848-aa62-4b29-b188-826acf9e1e64.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The place where the alleyway begins is the famous seat of mural
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Munrae-dong is a place where the relationship with the factory deepened as a spinning factory entered during the Japanese occupation. At that time, the spinning machine was called &#39;Mullae&#39;, and the place&#39;s name, &#39;Moonrae-dong&#39; was said to have been established. Since then, steel factories and iron statues have been concentrated here, and now artists are flocking to this place, where art and ironworks coexist.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Walking using the map app on your smartphone is only in the early stages. If you see an alley next to the ironworks, you can go through the other side and enter the alley again. Even if you go back to the alley you came from, the fun is more intense than the embarrassment.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Booth at the point where Dangsan-ro and Dorim-ro meet 128 - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/204/0170e6b4-bc43-45e4-86b6-7f996a98ca4d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Booth at the point where Dangsan-ro and Dorim-ro meet 128
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Outside the alleys, murals are drawn without any rules or entanglements in a space where the proper words do not come up. It might be an unexpected scenery. Whenever I walk down an alley and turn my body toward the bent, I can feel like stopping at this sudden stop several times. It would be okay to call it a museum without a roof.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox type3 clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;mural - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/204/dd7af467-2e43-43b4-8486-b7563608c46d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     mural
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;mural - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/204/37091d71-383b-473e-97d2-dfdd642cf77c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     mural
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;mural - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/204/40c862fc-70f0-4b0c-a274-f2fbfcc0baf9.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     mural
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    It would not be an order to skip the story of the past where there could be a current Munrae-dong and take it in an alley atmosphere. Let&#39;s take a brief look at the past years here. Seoul&#39;s old industrial complex is a trace of modernization, where the industry began to prefer treatment over agriculture. In the 70s, where factories were more concentrated than now, Munrae-dong was a world of workers, machinery and iron. So far, the scenery of the world remains in every corner of the alley. On top of that, someone drew a brush and colored it. It would be a moment when the artist&#39;s hand began to transform into a unique neighborhood rather than a common neighborhood in Seoul.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    If you listen a little to the back of the mural, you can hear the harsh breath and the smell of sweat. The energy of iron that fills the alley, &#34;Jieing ~&#34; The creepy sound of iron grinding &#34;Bang!&#34; The sound of heavy iron bumps through the alley without even attempting it. It is a space where wild nature and weeds coexist.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The reputation of the old Mullae-dong steel mill was rusted. - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/204/31a91011-0441-4b99-927d-e36be40f16b8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The reputation of the old Mullae-dong steel mill was rusted.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    On the one side of a sunny alley, the clothes are roughly lined with wrinkles left over from the woven traces. The color of the clothes has faded, and the cotton gloves are open to seams. There is a shabby pajeon in the corner of the alley. Makgeolli here would have cooled the night of those who spent the day hot with iron.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Tough jeans fit well in this alley - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/204/50b68fbd-f6a1-4427-9c5a-23eddc5a9742.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Tough jeans fit well in this alley
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    How did Moonrae-dong, the mecca of the steel industry, now become famous for the Moonrae Art Village? In the late 80s and early 90s, Munrae-dong was one of the most serious areas of air pollution in Korea. In line with this period, the city of Seoul attempted to move the steel sales districts around Munrae-dong and Dorim-dong to the outskirts. Since then, the steel industry in Munrae-dong has gradually declined and the number of vacancy has increased. Around the same time, artists who were looking for inexpensive work spaces began to fill the empty spaces here. Currently, there are about 100 workshops in Munrae-dong and about 200 artists are active, but the issue of redevelopment is said to be reducing the scope of the artist&#39;s activity as it reaches the Moonrae-dong.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox type2 clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;13&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;radish - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/204/fc86757a-6546-4836-b8a4-a7b8a749ad9a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     radish
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;13&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A deer walks on a gray fence that would be colorless and odorless - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/204/4baf1e38-47c0-4f03-bccc-bec65ca21a8d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A deer walks on a gray fence that would be colorless and odorless
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Based on the Yangnam Intersection, let&#39;s turn to the northeast block and then cross the southeast block. Mural paintings are also painted on the backside of the post office in Munrae-dong and in a dense alleyway. In some murals, the feeling was so intense that I had to look for a while, and in some murals, I felt like a graffiti on my desk as a child. While looking at the murals, each element of the alleyway approaches meaningfully. The atmosphere of this place, such as green water flowing over cement, broken tiles, and small simple doors, has a rather rough texture.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox type2 clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;15&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The padding and padding will crack as time goes by. - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/204/cf68d8e9-4d13-4d25-a72a-1f5769e6a0ce.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The padding and padding will crack as time goes by.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;15&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;One of the murals that impressed me - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/204/c671a84a-2111-4485-9e35-b0e1ed9630a9.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     One of the murals that impressed me
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    My heart gets eaten before I press the camera shutter. The scenery that came into my eyes through the viewfinder was like the wrinkles of the swings that happened again even though I lived and wasted. . Nevertheless, the reason to remember Munrae-dong with warmth and brightness is that a child with a smile and a light step was holding flowers in a mural, and the door in the mural painting the village was wide open.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox type2 clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;17&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;mural - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/204/aef417a9-af6f-444e-b95c-3f94b996d300.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     mural
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;17&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;mural - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/204/772490b8-ac58-49ec-a79a-18c27e81c282.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     mural
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    There is a Daegutang specialty store (Moonrae Daegutang) to decorate the beauty of this journey by going west from Munrae Post Office and crossing the southwest block of the Mullae Park intersection. The moon tastes like Daegu and Munrae Daegu-tang, which were in season when Munrae-dong was suddenly remembered. The menu that the reporter enjoys is Daegu Gonitang, which has spicy soup and hearty Goni.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;19&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Daegu Gonitang in Munrae Daegu Bath House - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/204/a981a364-4e42-4691-8b74-076e6bca68bb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Daegu Gonitang in Munrae Daegu Bath House
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    How long it has been since I pledged the New Year&#39;s pledge, my feelings have faded and aesthetically pleasing. As I walk in the Han River Dunchi, I hope that the space of coexistence of iron and art and workers and artists in the Mullae Art Village will continue to look like the hope of continuing to see the Bukhansan Mountain.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;21&#34; id3=&#34;15&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Daegu Gonitang in Munrae Daegu Bath House - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/204/281f54d7-2b46-40f9-9987-417523251f44.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Daegu Gonitang in Munrae Daegu Bath House
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Exit tips
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   1. It is good to use weekends and holidays when iron workshops and steel malls are closed. On the day off, you can see the pictures drawn on the shutters that fall down, and it&#39;s more suitable for weekends than on weekdays for leisurely walking around.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   2. If you want to put a mural on a narrow alley, take a wide-angle lens. Smartphones with a panorama function are also useful.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   3. You can access information related to artists&#39; exhibitions and events at nearby cafes.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    1.Access
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    * Self-driving
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Yeomui-daero IC of Olympic-daero (To Yeongdeungpo Rotary) → Yeongdeungpo Station → Munrae-dong Intersection (turn right to Yanghwadaegyo Bridge, Yangnamseo Street) → Yangnam Intersection
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    * public transport
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Seoul Subway Line 2 Munrae Station Exit 7 → Go straight 200m → Munrae Art Village
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    2. Delicious
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Mullae Daegutang: Daegutang, 02-2633-5529
    &lt;br/&gt;
    English / Japanese style: Kalguksu, 02-2636-9817
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Garlic Whole Chicken: Whole Chicken, 02-2637-3480
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    3.Accommodation
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    M Hotel: Yeouido-dong, Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, 02-783-2271
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Petra Hotel Motel: Yeongdeungpo-dong 3-ga, Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul 02-2631-6686
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Yeongdeungpo Tourist Hotel: 02-2678-4265, Dangsan-dong 5-ga, Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Sejong Motel: Yangpyeong-dong 1-ga, Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, 02-2633-2838
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    ※ The information above was created in February 2013, and may change later, so be sure to check it before you travel.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finding the taste of everyday life in China, Daelim 2-dong Chinese Village - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/finding-the-taste-of-everyday-life-in-china-daelim-2dong-chinese-village-143/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 12:19:13 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/finding-the-taste-of-everyday-life-in-china-daelim-2dong-chinese-village-143/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;finding-the-taste-of-everyday-life-in-china-daelim-2dong-chinese-village--143&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Chinese Village Street in front of Exit 12 of Daelim Station on Subway Lines 2 and 7 - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/143/a57f90e0-adc6-4458-a13c-da4f956f53ca.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Chinese Village Street in front of Exit 12 of Daelim Station on Subway Lines 2 and 7
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Finding the taste of everyday life in China, Daelim 2-dong Chinese Village
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you walk around Daelim Central Market in Daelim 2-dong, Yeongdeungpo-gu, you will experience illiteracy unintentionally. Eight percent of the language you see and hear is Chinese. It is a place where the lives of Chinese people can be seen as if they were thought of as Korean villages in China, not Chinese villages in Korea. Let&#39;s meet a variety of different foods that Chinese people enjoy everyday in a Chinese village located in Daelim 2-dong.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Daelim 2-dong, a daily scene in China
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Usually, the residential area is quiet during the day and has a busy time during commute. However, the streets of the Chinese village in Daelim 2-dong are a little different. As more and more Chinese people live in Daelim 2-dong, Chinese merchants entered one another. As Koreans begin to visit, the day and night of Daelim 2-dong is an ordinary week.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;People enjoying a midday meeting - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/143/5656aa3c-4fd1-4e8c-98b3-4c604fcf824f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     People enjoying a midday meeting
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Daelim Jungang Market is located inside the alley in front of Exit 12 of Daelim Station on Subway Lines 2 and 7. The scenery here is different from any traditional market in Korea. Every other house sells Chinese-style ingredients, so it&#39;s hard to tell whether this is China or Korea when you walk around the market. medium
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Chinese vegetables commonly found in Daelim Central Market - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/143/e2862853-6536-4a30-b13a-bf07577acdfc.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Chinese vegetables commonly found in Daelim Central Market
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It is also common for shops to sell a variety of smoked meat, including Sochang, Daechang Sundae, and dried pork, on a board and sell them by weight. A Chinese-style tofu shop, which looks like a general tofu store, has a thick but soft tofu that rises in the middle of the seat.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Shop selling various kinds of smoked meat - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/143/2f543988-4585-4132-9d49-846bf0d4d288.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Shop selling various kinds of smoked meat
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Various main beaks stimulate curiosity along the way. Chinese dumplings, steamed buns, and steamed pears look similar to Korean hotteok, croquettes, and bindaetteok. However, whatever Chinese style is large, the texture, flavor and taste are completely different. Menus that I&#39;ve never seen before are fragile. Although it looks like a tray of eggs of only one size, the bread that is cut into the shape of a pizza like a pizza, a pimento glutinous rice cake filled with glutinous rice in green peppers, and even the food with rice in thin tofu, the name and taste are unfamiliar, but there are things that you can try lightly It&#39;s very thick.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Spicy rice cake filled with glutinous rice - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/143/5ca73979-b897-4ba6-9c29-d69fba10f2a7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Spicy rice cake filled with glutinous rice
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   You can choose what you like and feel the taste of mainland China. There are so many varieties that I am greedy, but let&#39;s be patient. Now, you can go to a restaurant that does not speak Korean well, order Chinese food, and taste Chinese food.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;It&#39;s also common to be hot-teak and pretzel. - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/143/b5a14c22-f3d9-4007-bf54-5e122fe7b521.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     It&#39;s also common to be hot-teak and pretzel.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Chinese shabu-shabu, hot pot
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   ‘훠 냄비’, which means ‘hot pot’, is a Chinese-style shabu-shabu, which is cooked by boiling various ingredients over broth. It is a common hotpot eaten in most parts of China, but the ingredients used in the hot pot vary depending on the ingredients from each region.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;One mandarin duck - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/143/cb9e3c2e-a78c-4acc-aa3e-fc4d7e669520.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     One mandarin duck
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you taste mainland Chinese food for the first time, it is good to cook Yuantang. Mandarin duck is a type of bird that is commonly known, and here means ‘pair’. This is because clear white and spicy red hot broth are served together in a divided pot.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Boil it in a pot with a compartment and eat it. - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/143/811660d6-f745-49f8-9d4d-2fdada1d9ecf.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Boil it in a pot with a compartment and eat it.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The broth has a unique scent, and the amount of ingredients is very generous. Put the ingredients in the bath and wait until they are cooked, so you must prepare them to eat the ingredients. When ordering a hot pot, give the peanut sauce, minced green onion and coriander mixed with various seasonings. On the table is a Chinese spice, Tsuran. Tsuran is a spice made from the seeds of the apiaceae cumin. It is bitter, spicy and has a strong aroma, and it removes odor. Of these four, mix them with one that suits your taste and the sauce is complete. Coriander and Tsuran can be burdensome with their unique scent, so check the taste and scent beforehand.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Make the sauce by steaming it with peanut sauce, chopped green onion, coriander, etc. - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/143/ea805e53-7024-4c7d-8d85-6218cd1b33d3.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Make the sauce by steaming it with peanut sauce, chopped green onion, coriander, etc.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &#39;Daesikdae&#39; and &#39;Eusseonbang&#39; are divided into 1st and 2nd floors, but they are connected to each other. They sell a variety of Chinese foods, from traditional to fusion cuisine. The hot pot shabu-sha of this house
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Tsuran is always on the Chinese restaurant table - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/143/5b0d1dcb-bcdb-47f2-ae73-53b830a111ab.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Tsuran is always on the Chinese restaurant table
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In the opposite building, there is a restaurant called “Soonpung Seafood Shabu Shabu”, which costs 35,000 won per set for 2-3 people.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;‘Daesikdae’ and ‘Eonseonbang’ which sells various Chinese foods. - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/143/005feb52-fb90-4631-8070-c0d857a72af5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     ‘Daesikdae’ and ‘Eonseonbang’ which sells various Chinese foods.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Sweet and sour pork is perfect for the popular noodle soup!
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you have Champon in Korea, there is Maratang in China. Maratang refers to ‘tang hot enough to be paralyzed’, which is considered one of the hottest food in China. Pork bones are chopped with over 20 spices and seasonings. Various vegetables, dried tofu, and vermicelli enter there, but it is difficult to count them even with your own eyes.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Maratang, spicy noodle soup popularly eaten by Chinese - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/143/a9548c8e-3d0e-4875-9a77-67b7c7bec56b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Maratang, spicy noodle soup popularly eaten by Chinese
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   When ordering, there are places where the chef takes care of it, and there are also restaurants where customers choose the ingredients that go into the bath. ‘Bongseon Maratang’ is a specialty store that boils after ordering. There are basic (6,000 won) and lamb (羊肉) marathon (9,000 won). There are also several restaurants that order ingredients. Buffet over the window
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#39;Bongseon Maratang&#39; panoramic view - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/143/0edbb42a-7e4d-4df3-92b6-6adf537f6b15.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     &#39;Bongseon Maratang&#39; panoramic view
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The dish that goes well with the spicy and fragrant marathon is definitely Kwabaru. Cucumbero is a Beijing-style glutinous rice soup. The sourness beyond the sour taste and the sweetness wrapped around the tongue make the mouth clean even though it is a fried dish. What is different with Chinese sauce is the thickness of the meat and the tempura.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#39;Maratang&#39; is written in various places in the restaurant. - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/143/164a1295-94a5-44c8-90c4-425c3f6a4496.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     &#39;Maratang&#39; is written in various places in the restaurant.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In recent years, many restaurants have Korean menus, but some do not speak Korean at all. In that case, don&#39;t panic and find another Korean-speaking guest and ask for help. It will be another pleasure to experience foreign food. The Chinese village of Daelim 2-dong is hard to find and there are many passers-by, so it is better to use public transportation.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Chewy and crispy - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/143/2a267a82-c615-4a87-a416-8ca113520f0e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Chewy and crispy
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel info
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;font color=&#34;#000001&#34;&gt;
      &lt;strong&gt;
       Contact us
      &lt;/strong&gt;
      &lt;br/&gt;
      -Daelim Central Market Daelim 2-dong Community Service Center 02-2670-1419
      &lt;br/&gt;
      -Daesikdae &amp;amp; fishing boats Daesikdae 02-836-7555, fishing boats 02-849-7555
      &lt;br/&gt;
      -Bongseon Maratang 02-2637-4005
     &lt;/font&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;/font&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Nearby attractions
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Boramae Park: 33, Yeouidaebang-ro 20-gil, Dongjak-gu / 02-2181-1181
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Gwanaksan Ecological Park: Mountain 117-3, Sillim-dong, Gwanak-gu / 02-880-3675
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Gwanaksan: Gwanak-gu Daehak-dong / 02-879-6561
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Rooms
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Lifestyle F Hotel: 8, Gyeongin-ro 108-gil, Yeongdeungpo-gu / 02-2675-1984
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.lifestylehotel.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.lifestylehotel.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Bobos Motel: 41-18, Gukhoe-daero 54-gil, Yeongdeungpo-gu / 02-2676-7118
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Hotel The Designers Yeouido: 24, Gukhoe-daero 68-gil, Yeongdeungpo-gu / 02-786-5511
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://hotelthedesigners.com/yeouido/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://hotelthedesigners.com/yeouido/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was updated in June 2019, and may be changed later, so please check before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ The information such as text, photos and videos used in this article is copyrighted by Korea Tourism Organization, so unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 burning flavors to blow away your stress - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/5-burning-flavors-to-blow-away-your-stress-117/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 22:35:27 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/5-burning-flavors-to-blow-away-your-stress-117/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;5-burning-flavors-to-blow-away-your-stress--117&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Spicy Grilled Feet of &amp;lt;Changsin-dong Spicy Feet&amp;gt; - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/117/25a1c472-f7d8-4e3d-a331-72867b2f670a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Spicy Grilled Feet of &amp;lt;Changsin-dong Spicy Feet&amp;gt;
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   5 burning flavors to blow away your stress
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    In fact, &#39;taste&#39; has nothing to do with the season. Didn&#39;t find hot food in the summer because of the heat. The same is true for winter. The cold noodles called &#39;cool noodles&#39; were a winter delicacy in the north of Korea. Nevertheless, there is a ‘taste’ that crosses the season. The hot taste of the tip of the nose, the whole body getting hot, and the drops of sweat springing up one by one. Here&#39;s a spicy taste that will blow you away from the stress that comes up behind your neck even when you&#39;re in tears.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   #One. Singil-dong Spicy Champon
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The spicy taste of Seoul, the best champon restaurant that comes to mind when you first think of it.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Originally, the food itself has a spicy taste. Among them, spicy is one of the nation&#39;s wards, so be prepared. No matter how urgently the champon is, you should prepare a drink that will soothe the extreme spiciness.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    When you enter the store, there is a warning saying &#39;Please don&#39;t try Wanpong&#39;. &#39;Empty, pregnant women, senior citizens, high blood pressure, gastritis, gastric ulcers, bad condition champon absolute envoy&#39; is added. I want to try spicy jjamppong. The appearance is not much different from the champon I&#39;ve seen so far. Suffering, the pain begins as soon as you take the broth and take it to your mouth. It&#39;s spicy and spicy. But my hand keeps going. It is the same as those who ate champon with tears and runny noses. Not much seafood, but good for the price. It&#39;s hard, but it&#39;s spicy when I turn around. When it&#39;s complicated, it disappears as soon as it finds it. It&#39;s better to remember the hot soup season. However, be sure to include udon or gimbap for our stomach. We are precious.
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   #2. I shed tears, spicy pork cutlet, Shindaebang warm pork cutlet
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Enjoy pork cutlet for all ages. To what extent can you think of the spicy taste of pork cutlet that is perfect for a weekend family outing? The champon, jokbal, chicken feet, and tteokbokki that are introduced as `` Seoul spicy &#39;&#39; are spicy in the seasoning itself, so it is not difficult to imagine the spicy taste. On the other hand, the cutlet taste is only remembered, but the spicy taste is not well associated. This prejudice (?) Disappears naturally when you look for &#39;Honjeong Dongas&#39;, which is famous for its spicy pork cuts near the Sindaebang Intersection.
   &lt;br/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Spicy pork cutlet of &amp;lt;warm pork cutlet&amp;gt; - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/117/89f55143-8d39-45db-81eb-3858f07717d4.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Spicy pork cutlet of &amp;lt;warm pork cutlet&amp;gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Onjeong Dongas, already introduced several times on TV programs, is a tonkatsu specialty store. From authentic cutlet and fish gas to spicy seasoned cutlet and spicy cutlet. Up to this point, you can not find much difference with the general pork cutlet shop.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Authentic pork cutlet boasting a generous amount at an affordable price - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/117/0813eebe-fc99-444a-a823-2c4e913852c0.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Authentic pork cutlet boasting a generous amount at an affordable price
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The point is spicy cutlet which is not on the menu. If you eat everything within 20 minutes, you have to pay for free. You can&#39;t eat spicy, but if you&#39;re a big eater, you can try the giant tonkatsu. If you eat it within 20 minutes, it will be free. If you inhale two inexpensive pork cuts within 10 minutes, you can taste pork cuts for free for 6 months if you inhale within 2 minutes and 5 minutes.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Spicy Pork Cutlet - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/117/299aab5d-0378-4c0b-a569-311fbac34cd0.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Spicy Pork Cutlet
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Rather than ordering spicy tonkatsu from the beginning, try the pork cutlets on the menu. Spicy pork cutlet service to all customers. A quarter of pork cutlet is put in your mouth and spicy. Sweat on your forehead will heat your neck and face. The warning &#34;Galphos + Milk Required&#34; was not okay. It&#39;s better to taste this tasting pork cutlet and decide whether to order one.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A piece of spicy (dinda) pork cutlet for tasting - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/117/1c33d151-fa12-4cf6-a1c0-80b575df1cef.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A piece of spicy (dinda) pork cutlet for tasting
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   For reference, the reporter ate only one piece, but struggled to shake off the spicy taste that goes through the head and torso. After an hour or so, my stomach started shaking. The first point is to try and taste spicy pork cutlet.
   &lt;br/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Comparison between regular cutlet and spicy (dish) cutlet - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/117/d820a074-124b-4bb1-80ae-ac38a82ff156.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Comparison between regular cutlet and spicy (dish) cutlet
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   # 3. Delicious spicy, Changsin-dong hot pork feet
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   What would you have thought about adding spicy sauce to the pig&#39;s feet? I think it&#39;s a dish equivalent to &#39;donuts with donuts&#39;.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Changsin-dong Spicy Pig&#39;s Feet - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/117/a79847f8-269b-4b2b-94fb-4d1073eb1347.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Changsin-dong Spicy Pig&#39;s Feet
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Just jogbal does not feel a bit boring, spicy jokbal has no place to think. The meat is as strong and chewy as it is. It also adds spicy rice balls, which makes it a good choice for meals and snacks. Governor Giza also had plenty of food to eat. It&#39;s a spicy flavor that keeps going.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Changsin-dong Spicy Pig&#39;s Feet - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/117/95efade1-8781-4422-8fec-5cf0a4924f74.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Changsin-dong Spicy Pig&#39;s Feet
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Get off at Dongdaemun Station or Dongmyomae Station, enter Changsin Market, and go out at the entrance. This is the main store. From the beginning of the market, the smell of grilling seasoned pork feet vibrates. The smell is amazing Even when I see it, my stomach becomes full and strong.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Spicy grilled chicken feet. I added rice balls to reduce the spiciness. - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/117/4cf6a571-6898-405c-89f5-cc6f062ed650.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Spicy grilled chicken feet. I added rice balls to reduce the spiciness.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you like lean meat, you can order miniatures if you have better collagen areas with grilled pig feet or assorted pig feet. There is a cool piece to reduce the spiciness.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Spicy Mini - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/117/6db5d528-583b-46ad-997a-821e564a7ae8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Spicy Mini
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Instead of &#39;strong medicine&#39; where sweat oozes out of your head like &amp;lt;Shingil-dong Spicy Jjambbong&amp;gt; or &amp;lt;Ondondon Gas&amp;gt;, the smoky spicy taste that makes your lips tingle is attractive.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Spicy Chilled Coolpeace - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/117/98b1b1c5-d6bf-4088-b289-fc4941ad1998.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Spicy Chilled Coolpeace
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   #4. Eat red pepper, Dongdaemun Yeopgi Tteokbokki
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you really want a spicy taste, there is Dongdaemun Yeopgi Tteokbokki, called `` Yuppteok. &#39;&#39; The tongue tastes spicy but can&#39;t stop eating. After eating, you should be ready to walk in and out of the bathroom for about a day. Some people are angry that they are spicy, but once you step here, you will come back to the taste. The addictive spicy taste is a powerful taste that makes modern people suffering from stress forget all of it.
   &lt;br/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Spicy Tteokbokki Representative Celebrity &amp;lt;Dongdaemun Bizarre Tteokbokki&amp;gt; Basic Set - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/117/f4ef5b53-e959-444e-873a-36fbc64b8e66.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Spicy Tteokbokki Representative Celebrity &amp;lt;Dongdaemun Bizarre Tteokbokki&amp;gt; Basic Set
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Steamed eggs and rice balls are a must, and add slush to your mouth. As you sweat, your annoyance disappears, leaving only the mouth and lips pain. Still, the idea of delicious does not disappear. However, no matter how motivated, do not eat soup with a spoon.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Thank you reinforcement spicy, rice balls and steamed egg - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/117/1c1fa0b0-e9b4-475a-ab1a-0a7e73c29861.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Thank you reinforcement spicy, rice balls and steamed egg
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Tteokbokki is high on price but high in quantity. Add one saree, enough for three to four people to eat. If you choose set menu, you can taste it a little cheaper.
   &lt;br/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The most spicy noodles in Tteokbokki - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/117/700fcf8e-ab12-4c1e-a8f4-212a260a5530.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The most spicy noodles in Tteokbokki
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   # 5. Delicious spicy Bangi Binja chicken feet
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Do you like chicken feet? It&#39;s very mysterious and gross, but once you taste it, the slight stipples that the appearance gives you are gone. It is understandable why so many people found chicken feet. delicious. Bony chicken feet are fun to eat with bones, and boneless chicken feet are easy to eat in a bite. Although there are differences depending on each person&#39;s taste, I think the whole bone is better to feel the natural taste of chicken feet. Spicy seasoning was added to these chicken feet. Spicy chicken feet are great as both side dishes and side dishes. Dudong!
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;5&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&amp;lt;Ijinja chicken feet&amp;gt; grilled chicken feet - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/117/840ee580-f106-4398-b706-69151c61f303.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     &amp;lt;Ijinja chicken feet&amp;gt; grilled chicken feet
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Like spicy pork feet, chicken feet are a must for rice balls that will reduce the spiciness and prevent heartburn. `` Ijinja Chicken Feet &#39;&#39; is located at the end of Bangi-dong Eat Alley. If you call 20 minutes ago, the chicken fried chicken soup is also good. The chicken feet that are just coming out are spicy, but if you want a stronger spicy taste, you can adjust them when you order them.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;5&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;15&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Seasoned Chicken Feet Before Roasting - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/117/a29a5dd9-5c2e-404d-9557-26cdb2d0fbde.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Seasoned Chicken Feet Before Roasting
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Chicken feet dressed in seasoning are grilled over the grill. Dishes Cooked Roasted chicken feet boast a strong spicy taste with added fire. President Lee Jin-ja, the owner of the restaurant, accepts orders, cooks and pays, so wait. In addition, the opening hours are flexible, so it&#39;s a good idea to check beforehand. The system is not equipped, but the chicken feet are known as one know. It is located in the alley next to Bang Middle School.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;5&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;16&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Grilled chicken feet for grilling - Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/117/2117a7cf-b7db-46da-9b97-adfe775447ed.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Grilled chicken feet for grilling
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel info
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Nearby restaurants
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Singil-dong Spicy Champon: Exit 1 at Singil Station / 010-5395-1151 / 13: 30 ~ 24: 00 (Closed 23:00 Sunday) / Spicy Champon 8,000, Udon 6,000, Gimbab 2000
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Onjeong Don Gas: Sindaebang Samgeori Station Exit 3 / 02-823-8589 / 10: 30 ~ 21: 00 (Free on success)
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Changsin-dong Spicy Bun: Dongdaemun Station Exit 3 or Dongmyomae Station Exit 8 (Changsin Market) / 02-3675-9689 / 10: 30 ~ 24: 00 (Closed on Mondays) / Spicy Grilled Pig Feet 28,000 won, Coolpeace 2000 won
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Dongdaemun Yeopgi Tteokbokki: Sindang Station Exit 10 (15, Toegye-ro 75-gil, Jung-gu, Seoul) / 02-2234-8592 / 24 hours / Yeopgi Tteokbokki 14,000 won
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Ijinja Chicken Feet: Mongchontoseong Station, Exit 2 (61-10, Ogeum-ro 11-gil, Songpa-gu, Seoul) / 16: 00 ~ 03: 00 KRW, boneless chicken feet 13,000 won, chicken dung house 12,000 won, fried chicken soup 30,000 won
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Accommodation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    24 Guesthouse Jongno Tower Branch: Jongno 31-gil, Jongno-gu / 02-747-1002
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://24guesthousejongnotower.com&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://24guesthousejongnotower.com
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Center Mark Hotel: Insadong 5-gil, Jongno-gu (Kwanhoon-dong) / 02-731-1000
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.centermarkhotel.com/kor/main/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.centermarkhotel.com/kor/main/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was updated in March 2019 and may change afterwards, so please check before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ The information such as text, photos and videos used in this article is copyrighted by Korea Tourism Organization, so unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>