<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sinan-gun on Every Corner of Korea</title>
    <link>https://codecorea.github.io/tags/sinan-gun/</link>
    <description>Every Corner of Korea (Sinan-gun)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 07:43:04 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="https://codecorea.github.io/tags/sinan-gun/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A beautiful island called Soheoksando, Sinan Uido - Sinan-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/a-beautiful-island-called-soheoksando-sinan-uido-226/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 07:43:04 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/a-beautiful-island-called-soheoksando-sinan-uido-226/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Sinan-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;a-beautiful-island-called-soheoksando-sinan-uido--226&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Sonam Jeongjeong Village from the exile site - Sinan-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/226/6c56a0de-cd9f-4ed7-b069-623cb97c789b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Sonam Jeongjeong Village from the exile site
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   A beautiful island called Soheoksando, Sinan Uido
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Sinan-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Uido, named after the ears of a cow, is an island about three and a half hours away from Mokpo by boat and is well known for its sand dunes. It is a beautiful island not only with clear and clean beaches such as Donmok, Seongchon, and the beach beyond the band, but also the scenery of the tea ceremony on the top of Sangsanbong. It is also the exile site of the Sonam Jeongyakjeon and remains a dock in the Joseon Dynasty that retains the old image. Let&#39;s take a look at the history of Uido along with the unexplored Uido.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Fragrance of Jeongyakjeon in Truth Village, 《Pyohae Shimsal》 and Uido Dock
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    A ferry to Uido departing from Mokpo Coastal Passenger Terminal arrives in Uido in three and a half hours via Tochodo. Kaido, which serves as the gate of Uido, greets the passenger ship first, and the ship arrives at Uido Port, where the truth village (Ui 1 District) is located. On the other side of Uido Port, where the truth village is located, you can see East and West Souido and Songdo. Uido is the name given to Dori and Mokseom, which protrude to the west of the island, resembling the shape of a cow&#39;s ears. Other names are called Sogu Island and Ugaedo Island. Uido is mostly dependent on fishing because it has very few farmland due to the development of mountainous areas around Sangsanbong, the highest elevation on the island, 359m above sea level.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In Uido, there are quite a few historical and cultural heritages. In 1801, the brothers Son Jeong-jak and Dasan Jeong Yak-yong went on their way to Guiyang after spending the last night at Yuljeongjeom intersection at Geumseongsan Mountain in Naju. The exile site of Jeongyakjeon was Uido, which was called Soheksando Island. Heuksando is well-known as the place of exile in Jeongyakjeon, but Jeongyakjeon seems to have loved Uido more. He first settled in Uido, and only in 1807 went into Heuksan-do, 40 km from Uido. There is also a record that the Jeong Yak-jeon was caught secretly at night to go to Ui-do near the land.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   During the exile in Daeheksan-do, Jeong Yak-jeon, who left behind 《Assassin ’, left a book titled‘ Pyohae-shim ’during his exile in Soeuksan-do. The story of Pyohae Shim-moon tells the story of Moon Soon-deuk, who lived as a spearfisher on Soheksan Island. Moon Soon-deuk, who learned of Jeong Yak-jeon during his exile, went to buy a redfish on a nearby Taesado Island and drifted to meet Pung Rang. He survived fortunately, and returned to his hometown in three years and two months through Okinawa, the Philippines, Macau, Nanjing and Beijing. In the 9th year article of the Joseon Dynasty, there was a record in the article of the 9th year of King Sunjo, saying, &#34;I order you to repatriate the drifter of the country of transit.&#34; He unveiled the full story that he experienced while traveling around the world different from that of Joseon to Jeong Yak-jeon, and the book he wrote based on his dictation is the poetry. In Uido, there remains the birthplace of Hong Soo Jangsu, Sun Soon-deuk, along with the exile of Son Am Jeong-jeon.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sonam Jeongjajeon Exile - Sinan-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/226/d2e1a81c-ea5f-41ae-a4a5-c198c4fe8022.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sonam Jeongjajeon Exile
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    At the entrance to the Truth Village, there are traces of Uido&#39;s strategic importance in the Joseon Dynasty. This is the Uido dock. Uido was also used as a naval base during the Joseon Dynasty, and it is said that there was a gwan-a and a hill at the foot of the truth village. The Uido Dock was created in 1745 during the Joseon Dynasty. He was responsible for the function of the muzzle to anchor the ship, the breakwater to prevent waves, and the shipyard to build and repair the ship. In fact, it is said that the boat was cut from a nearby mountain in the mountains. The Uido dock is made by stacking stones at a height of 3m. In the center of the dock, there is also a relay line that binds the boat. The Uido Dock is the oldest and most intact dock in Korea, and was designated as Monument No. 243 in Jeollanam-do.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Uido dock built in the Joseon Dynasty - Sinan-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/226/b7dd3a57-9439-4475-8db9-3f2d7d25027d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Uido dock built in the Joseon Dynasty
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Meeting the Unexplored Uido Islands
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Where to stay in Uido is Truth Village in the east of Uido, Donmok in the west, and Seongchon Village. If you want to look around Uido, you have to bear the inconvenience of moving on foot. The mountain and sea can be enjoyed at the same time, making it a very attractive place for travelers who have plenty of time or want to enjoy nature.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The beach beyond the band, located about 1 km away from the truth village, is not well known due to the popularity of Donmok and Seongchon Beach, but it is the most beautiful beach in Uido. Beyond the band, the beach is a place that has many belts used instead of rice straw when connecting thatch roofs. The belt reaches the beach only when it crosses a hill that forms a colony like a field.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox type2 clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Way to the beach beyond the band - Sinan-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/226/42e4ad3b-3e4f-4181-995e-bc8c9428410c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Way to the beach beyond the band
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The band that came from the beach beyond the field - Sinan-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/226/21c6a1b4-10f2-43c6-8ad1-2366d83da757.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The band that came from the beach beyond the field
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    If you climb the uphill road about 500m from the crossroads over the band, the beach spreads out over the band down the hill. On the hills, there are piles of rainrooms (stone walls) built to prevent wind. When you descend the hill, the beach beyond the band, about 1km long, reveals itself. The foot of the mountain, which descended from Sangsanbong, fell to the beach, separating the beach beyond the band and the Seongchon beach beyond. It is a fault that the waves are strong, but it is perfect for swimming in the sea because it has a fine and hard white sand.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox type3 clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Beach Beyond a Beautiful Band - Sinan-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/226/8adb4518-1ca8-4a97-a27e-0487318b70f0.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Beach Beyond a Beautiful Band
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Beach Beyond a Beautiful Band - Sinan-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/226/11d515c7-485e-4f0d-a285-5751b8d3c5de.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Beach Beyond a Beautiful Band
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The sand dune that meets at the edge of the beach beyond the band - Sinan-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/226/28ec644c-312b-4de8-91a9-1157e48a88b7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The sand dune that meets at the edge of the beach beyond the band
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    When you come out of the crossroads over the beach and go up the road to Donmok and Seongchon villages, you reach the truth hill near the water supply source of Uido people. The truth hill is a way to climb to the highest peak in Uido, Sangsan Peak. The road is not rough, so you can climb without hesitation. After about 10 minutes, the mountain peaks around Sangsan Peak slowly appear. Uido&#39;s appearance is clear along the border between the island and the sea. As you climb the Sangsan Peak, the breathtaking view of the tea ceremony unfolds so that your heart can pierce. To the east, the truth village is not visible due to the peak in front of Sangsan Peak, but there are more and more islands off the coast of Sinan, including Uido Port and Gado, Songdo, East and West Souido, as well as Bigeumdo, Tochodo, Hauido, and Sangha and Hataedo. . To the west, it overlooks Donmok Village, Seongchon Village, and the Donmok Beach filling the gap. In the mountains, traces of villages are also found. It is the first town in Uido, but it is now the ruins of Daechori Village.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox type3 clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Donmok Village, Seongchon Village, and Donmok Beach from Sangsanbong - Sinan-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/226/953fc3c6-51e8-4150-a71d-9ef38df58a6a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Donmok Village, Seongchon Village, and Donmok Beach from Sangsanbong
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The scenery seen from the way up the mountain - Sinan-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/226/27ab2069-abce-41a2-b544-d0bd5c1ca793.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The scenery seen from the way up the mountain
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;From the top of Sangsanbong, toward the truth village - Sinan-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/226/1ad806f5-b163-44b2-99a7-7c969c83aaa5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     From the top of Sangsanbong, toward the truth village
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Uido&#39;s real exhaust, sand dunes and Donmok beach
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    camp
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   After passing Daechori Village, you will reach Donmok Beach. The left side of Donmok Beach is Donmok Village and the right side is Seongchon Village. The sand dunes on Donmok Beach are Uido&#39;s representative spots. It is also the place where the protagonist, Democrat Kim Ji-soo, was found in the film &amp;lt;Autumn&amp;gt; for a documentary filming. The sand dunes are 100m above sea level and 20m wide, and are known as the largest Pungseong sand dunes in the East. Between Seongchon Beach and Donmok Beach, the beach and sand dunes go well together. Right now, it is forbidden to enter the park to protect the sand dunes, but it&#39;s a painful effort to get back to the old look. At the moment, you can&#39;t go in and out to protect the sand dunes, but the scenery of the sand dunes looking over the Donmok Beach changes from time to time.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox type2 clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Daechori Village - Sinan-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/226/64967c20-1c43-4785-9890-b6c1c8cd8589.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Daechori Village
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The restored Daechori well - Sinan-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/226/8eda2b48-8bea-4e7d-ab9c-4c6a0710f159.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The restored Daechori well
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Located between Donmok Village and Seongchon Village, Donmok Beach has a long beach about 1.5km long. This sandy and hard beach is the most popular beach in Uido. In particular, this year, it was selected as one of the cleanest beaches in the water quality test of 187 beaches. Dalmulge is full of people&#39;s feet on the beach of Donmok. It is said to be the largest dwelling colony in Korea. When it feels popular, the crab quickly runs away with cute side steps.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Uido Sand Dunes and Seongchon Village seen from Donmok Beach - Sinan-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/226/dac6e4dc-5350-4006-b2a6-8c5869674bb9.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Uido Sand Dunes and Seongchon Village seen from Donmok Beach
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The ferry to Uido departs once a day from Mokpo. The trip is a bit unique, so if you take advantage of it, your trip to Uido will be easier. When you depart from Mokpo at 11:40 am, you will first arrive at the truth village of Ui 1-gu via Tochodo, and then arrive clockwise through East and West Soido, Yeri, Donmok, and Seongchon. The ship departs at Tocho-do for one day and departs at 6 am. After passing through the opposite directions of Seongchon, Donmok, Yeri, Dong-seoso-ido, and Truth, we go to Mokpo through Tocho-do.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox type2 clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Uido Sand Dunes seen from Donmok Beach - Sinan-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/226/557f913d-cef1-4fd7-844d-9462cfdd1972.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Uido Sand Dunes seen from Donmok Beach
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;15&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Dalrang crab I met at Donmok Beach - Sinan-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/226/833dc49c-0783-4196-b77d-4074ecb0e465.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Dalrang crab I met at Donmok Beach
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    1.Access
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    * Self-driving
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Seohaean Expressway Mokpo IC → Turn left at Yeonsan-dong Intersection → Go straight about 4.3km → Mokpo Coastal Passenger Terminal
    &lt;br/&gt;
    ※ Passenger ships to Uido depart from Mokpo Coastal Passenger Terminal at 11:40 am (approximately 3 hours 30 minutes via Tochodo)
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    2. Restaurants around
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Seolhee Neminbak: Home-style Baekban / 34-7 Uijin-ri-gil, Tocho-myeon, Sinan-gun / 061-262-7056
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    3.Accommodation
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Seolhee Neminbak: 34-7, Uijin-ri-gil, Docho-myeon, Sinan-gun / 061-262-7056
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Damoamine Park: 33-1 Donmok-gil, Tocho-myeon, Sinan-gun / 061-261-4455
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Seongchon B &amp;amp; B: 33 Seongchon-gil, Docho-myeon, Sinan-gun / 061-261-5187
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    ※ The above information was created in July 2013, and may change later, so be sure to check it before you travel.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Camper misses island &#39;Shinan Amtaedo Mongdol Sea Campground&#39;</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/camper-misses-island-shinan-amtaedo-mongdol-sea-campground-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2020 16:04:57 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/camper-misses-island-shinan-amtaedo-mongdol-sea-campground-6/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-title=&#34;camper-misses-island-shinan-amtaedo-mongdol-sea-campground--6&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Mongdol Sea Campground overflowing with blue sea - Sinan-gun, Jeonnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/6/8db5f7f8-e620-46fb-a922-e3d33a2f5466.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Mongdol Sea Campground overflowing with blue sea
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Camper misses island &#39;Shinan Amtaedo Mongdol Sea Campground&#39;
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Sinan-gun, Jeonnam, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Summer is crowded with people everywhere. If you&#39;re looking for a camping spot to enjoy the summer, head to the island. A day of bathing on a secluded beach, picking up seashells, walking and paddling, and falling asleep in the sound of calm waves. And when you open your eyes until the morning when the blue sea is full of tents… . The summer you dream is there.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Fluttering on board a tent
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Sinan is a country on the island. The island is composed of 1,004 islands, including 72 manned islands and 932 uninhabited islands. Among the countless islands as the stars in the night sky, the dark attitude is attracting attention among campers. This is because the Mongdol Sea Campground, which is popular with camping families, is located on the island.
   &lt;br/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Mongdol Sea Campground is different from the journey. First, put a tent and body on the boat. And he goes through the scenery of the archipelago. Even if you are overwhelmed, you will leave the Songgong Dock and travel for about 25 minutes. 5 minutes drive from the marina to the camping grounds. Along the way, the landscape of the nostalgic island spreads out. It is accompanied by a salt field with the sun&#39;s passion and a tidal flat engraved with an S-shaped waterway. Beyond the salt fields and tidal flats, these islands cast shadows.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Carry a tent and a body and go through the landscape - Sinan-gun, Jeonnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/6/dfcd050d-ac82-4a7c-b146-9c428bd908ed.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Carry a tent and a body and go through the landscape
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   ‘夢 -bar’ campsite telling dreams
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Mongdol Sea Campground is set on a hill leading to the beach. The cascading site on a steep hill overlooks the sea. Against the sea, I can&#39;t wait to play tents.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Overlooking Mongdol Beach is a camping beach - Sinan-gun, Jeonnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/6/87fc72ee-c51c-45b1-adf3-d03624e0d498.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Overlooking Mongdol Beach is a camping beach
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The island had a thousand faces. 365 days of changeable island weather offers a different landscape every day. Ocean view of Mongdol Sea Campground is nothing to be bored during your stay. The ocean view of an expensive hotel is not envious.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Happy to wash dishes at Mongdol Sea Campground - Sinan-gun, Jeonnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/6/d09c50b1-1656-47b9-951c-d8ee989330fe.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Happy to wash dishes at Mongdol Sea Campground
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The Mongdol Beach overlooking the tent is a private camping beach. Even if the 24 sites of the campsite are full, the beaches are generous.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;An ocean view no less expensive than a hotel - Sinan-gun, Jeonnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/6/440edb75-cc38-4e8d-aa97-a250a69347ec.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     An ocean view no less expensive than a hotel
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The fun is endless. Rias beaches are safe and enjoyable beaches. The drained and exposed tidal flats are transformed into ecological experience sites. Sea crabs, shellfish and fry fill the tidal flats. When you play with her, your whole body will improve with a natural mud pack.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sora is a fist - Sinan-gun, Jeonnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/6/59fd5f73-c353-4a7e-9d6d-9a764faf1b36.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sora is a fist
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Between the drained and exposed tidal stones, the seashells with only bumps and knuckles are the best. It&#39;s fun to catch, but the taste of boiled beef and seashells is also good.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Living Eco Experience Center - Sinan-gun, Jeonnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/6/8b09bbb1-8595-4283-b685-5607d313b7ed.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Living Eco Experience Center
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The offshore campsite is a fishing spot. Various fish are caught depending on the season such as black sea bream, rockfish and conger eel. That&#39;s why fishing camping enthusiasts line up.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Living Eco Experience Center - Sinan-gun, Jeonnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/6/1250af6b-456f-4214-b0dd-4a2c4cfccd18.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Living Eco Experience Center
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The Mongdol Sea Campground opened in 2012 and is celebrating its third year. Captain Choi Myung-sin wandered around the country for a year in search of a camping site and met there. It was the place where my son and I sketched and dreamed.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;14&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;“夢 -bar” campsite for dreamers - Sinan-gun, Jeonnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/6/e8a3d760-c252-4a88-9da0-e208b21c10ac.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     “夢 -bar” campsite for dreamers
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The Mongdol Sea Campground is more commonly referred to as the &#34;Monba&#34;. Mongba is also a short word for Mongdolsea, but it is a compound word of dream “mont” and the adverb “bar” which means “can” in German. In other words, “夢 bar” means you can dream. It is a camping ground where people dream and they want to be a camping ground where people can design their dreams and go back.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;16&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Beautiful Mongdol Beach - Sinan-gun, Jeonnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/6/3c1bb2cc-690d-474e-814f-a0d531f35175.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Beautiful Mongdol Beach
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Evening sunsets at Mongdol Beach are sweet as dreams. You fall asleep with the gentle sound of the waves, and when you open your eyes, the sea flows in front of the tent. The laughter of the children spreads like the sun.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;18&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Evening sweet sunset - Sinan-gun, Jeonnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/6/321fb45f-156c-4c83-9334-8588f7ec7c42.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Evening sweet sunset
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Happiness to enjoy four islands at once
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Dark attitude is also the starting point for island trips. Four islands are connected by bridges: Amtaedo, Jaeundo, Palgeumdo, and Anzado. You can enjoy all these islands by boat. Crossing Eunam Bridge is Jaeundo. Jaeundo, which means “kind and gracious,” has picturesque beaches running along the island. Particularly popular are the sloping beaches with gentle slopes, lush pine forests, white sandy beaches with white sand beaches, and dune villages where you can experience lily digging and frying nets.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Amtaedo finds a lot of Chupo beach. The 2.5km outcrop that appears at low tide is a landmark of Chupo. Both sides run out of the outcrop. Crossing Jungang Bridge to the south from Amtaedo leads to Palgumdo. There is a three story stone pagoda at the entrance of Eupri village, located in Palgeum-myeon. It is believed to be a pagoda of the Koryo Dynasty, and a small island is approaching greatly in the face of more than a thousand years.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Kim Hwan-ki&#39;s Birthplace - Sinan-gun, Jeonnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/6/eae57f40-5030-4887-a0a4-4b58f1060ce6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Kim Hwan-ki&#39;s Birthplace
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Andzado Island, located at the bottom, is the most hidden area of the four islands. Kim Hwan-ki, called “Picasso of Korea,” was born and raised here. His birthplace is in Eupdong-ri, where his childhood memories of nourishing his work are difficult. In Bangwol-ri, there is a dolmen, a bronze age tomb. Beyond the dolmen, the village stone path naturally follows.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Bangwol-ri Dolmen - Sinan-gun, Jeonnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/6/eeb401da-8471-41d1-b72e-e78268f6d4bc.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Bangwol-ri Dolmen
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The beauty of Anzado is “Angel&#39;s Bridge. Anzad is also a bridge between Park Do-do and Banwol-do. It is 1,462 meters long. Walking on the bridge makes you feel like you&#39;re walking on the sea. It is good to see sunrise and sunrise.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sights of Anzado, Angel&#39;s Bridge - Sinan-gun, Jeonnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/6/9f144a5b-87d9-465d-92df-ba600bf7bb56.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sights of Anzado, Angel&#39;s Bridge
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The boat going to Amtaedo operates from 7:00 am to 7:50 pm every hour. If you take a car with you, line up the car first, following the sign for Amtaedo, and call the car number to go to the ticket. You must bring your ID. If you have a lot of cars to board, you have to wait a few hours, so it is best to use the boat early. The fare is 3,300 won each way, and the fare for passenger cars is 15,000 won (inquiry: Sinan Agricultural Cooperative Ticket Office 061-271-0090). Currently, a new millennium bridge that connects Abroad and Amtaedo is under construction to be completed in 2018.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Another nostalgic island scenery - Sinan-gun, Jeonnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/6/802bf0dc-d5d4-4ddb-aa0d-6915cdd1ec44.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Another nostalgic island scenery
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel info
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p style=&#34;COLOR: #7b1f42&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Mongdol Sea Campground
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Address: 139-63, Jinjakji-gil, Amtae-myeon, Sinan-gun, Jeonnam
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Contact: 061-262-8872
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p style=&#34;COLOR: #7b1f42&#34;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.bada-camp.com/&#34; style=&#34;COLOR: #7b1f42&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;[새창열림]‘몽돌바다캠핑장’ 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
     www.bada-camp.com
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p style=&#34;COLOR: #7b1f42&#34;&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;topmr&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Nearby restaurants
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     New Breeding
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    / 1795, Jungbu-ro, Amtae-myeon, Sinan-gun / 061-271-6767
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     New Sea Ash Town:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Yeonpo-tang / 1848 Aphae-ro, Aphae-eup, Sinan-gun / 061-271-1270
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Island Village Restaurant:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Island Baekban / 832, Jungbu-ro, Anjwa-myeon, Sinan-gun / 061-262-0330
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Accommodation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Blue Motel:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    669-12, Bokyong-ro, Abhae-eup, Sinan-gun / 061-271-8966
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Yousung Motel:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    833, Anjwa-dongbu-gil, Anjwa-myeon, Sinan-gun / 061-261-1223
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Charcoal Kiln Jjimjilbang:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    200-5 Daebul-gil, Abhae-eup, Sinan-gun / 061-271-0774
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    ※ The above information was written in July 2014. It may change afterwards, so please check before you travel.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    ※ Information such as text, photos, and videos used in this article is copyrighted by Korea Tourism Organization, so unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>