<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ulleungdo on Every Corner of Korea</title>
    <link>https://codecorea.github.io/tags/ulleungdo/</link>
    <description>Every Corner of Korea (Ulleungdo)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 08:18:18 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="https://codecorea.github.io/tags/ulleungdo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ulleungdo hotspot looking around the road - South Korea Gyeongbuk Ulleungdo</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/ulleungdo-hotspot-looking-around-the-road-258/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 08:18:18 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/ulleungdo-hotspot-looking-around-the-road-258/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;South Korea Gyeongbuk Ulleungdo&#34; data-title=&#34;ulleungdo-hotspot-looking-around-the-road--258&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;View from Taeha Lighthouse - South Korea Gyeongbuk Ulleungdo (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/258/1c1cf1a5-1366-4f10-a459-40d8209c2d1a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    View from Taeha Lighthouse
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Ulleungdo hotspot looking around the road
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    South Korea Gyeongbuk Ulleungdo
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Ulleungdo is not an easy to find destination. Thanks to this, there are those who prepare as carefully as they find it because they are shy and different. Group products for travel agencies are inexpensive, and single trips can be moved according to your preferences. Introducing the hot spots on Ulleungdo&#39;s roundabout road, which is a must-see during the visit to Ulleungdo. Coastal drive, an excitement of the island trip, is a bonus.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    In an accurate sense, Ulleungdo&#39;s Round Road is not yet a round road. This is because it is not possible to operate a vehicle in the section of about 4.7km from Naesujeon to Seokpo (seommok). The section we call ‘Ulleungdo Iljudo’ refers to the pavement from Naesujeon ~ Dodong ~ Jedong ~ Namyang ~ Taeha ~ Hyeonpo ~ Cheonbu ~ Seommok except Naesujeon ~ Sukpo. It&#39;s not a complete round circle, but it&#39;s not awkward because it&#39;s a road connecting all of Ulleungdo&#39;s coastline except for the unopened section. Let&#39;s know though. In 2013, it is said that it is impossible to drive around the road along the “Ulleungdo Island Round Road”.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   A gateway connecting land to Ulleungdo and Dokdo, Jedong, Dodong and Sadong ports
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    First of all, the starting point was set at Jeodong and Dodong ports, Ulleungdo&#39;s entry port. From Ulleungdo, I plan to depart from Naesujeon and run clockwise to Seokpo (seommok). Of course, you can move in reverse. Let&#39;s take a look at the domestic observation deck, which is considered the sunrise point. The Naesujeon Observatory, which touches the Naesujeon ~ Sokpo Old Road, is only a 15-minute walk from the steep stairs and uphill. The slight strain on the joints disappears as the snow melts in the cool spread. Jeodong Port and Jukdo Island at a glance greet people. Even if you haven&#39;t set the sunrise time, don&#39;t miss it.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Jeodong Port from Haengnam Lighthouse - South Korea Gyeongbuk Ulleungdo (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/258/42639f77-5591-4c2f-b641-aba3c3675a71.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Jeodong Port from Haengnam Lighthouse
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Now head to Jeodong Port. The sunrise rising against the backdrop of candlestick rocks is a gem. Before dawn, Jeodong Port is full of boats that have been squid fishing all night. It is not boring to see and see the squid harbok work of Ulleungdo ajimae. You can taste fresh seafood in the sea breeze with a sea breeze.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Dodong Port, Ulleungdo&#39;s best downtown - South Korea Gyeongbuk Ulleungdo (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/258/1a1e09ee-5409-4059-9ce7-061f9c4d43ae.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Dodong Port, Ulleungdo&#39;s best downtown
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   When squid is a boiled fish, it is sold at around 5000 won per head, and when it comes back, about 20,000 won (3 heads) per dish. If it is not packaged, it costs about 9,000 won including a bottle of soju. It is full of fresh sashimi including horns, sea squirts, and dongs. The spicy spicy soup is also popular among lovers. The Jeodong Port Passenger Terminal has ships to and from Gangneung, Gangneung and Dokdo. It is better to avoid ship time because it has a lot of floating population after Dodong Port.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Jeodong Port where squid is dried - South Korea Gyeongbuk Ulleungdo (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/258/6e9171b0-64f5-4662-9ef5-ca0fd6625221.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Jeodong Port where squid is dried
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The coastal road next to the candlestick rock of Jeodong Port leads to Dodong Port. The coastal road with strong snow is a path that can be walked without difficulty by all ages. However, if part of the section is under construction, you can&#39;t look back at once, but you have to walk a little from Jeodong Port and a little from Dodong Port. If it is possible to complete, it does not matter where you start.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Haengnam Trail which connects Dodong Port and Jeodong Port - South Korea Gyeongbuk Ulleungdo (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/258/2cc6d782-29ea-4ca0-bbd4-32cebfce16a4.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Haengnam Trail which connects Dodong Port and Jeodong Port
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Dodong Port, where boats depart from Mukho, is the busiest space on Ulleungdo. It is a lodging facility, and most of the convenience facilities are gathered from restaurants, convenience stores, banks, and PC rooms. Behind the newly renovated Dodong Passenger Terminal is a coastal walkway that leads to Jeodong Port. The view from the Haengnam Lighthouse is a point that cannot be missed. Around Dodong Port, there are restaurants where you can taste mulleap, barnacle rice, and squid intestines, which are delicacies of Ulleungdo. It is better to taste the above delicacies when traveling on this section. If you go further south from Dodong Port, you will reach Sadong Port (Ulleung New Port). There are ships to and from Dokdo, as well as passenger ships to and from 뭍.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Haengnam Trail which connects Dodong Port and Jeodong Port - South Korea Gyeongbuk Ulleungdo (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/258/5b3555d3-2786-4fd3-8bdf-3d0907ebcf1c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Haengnam Trail which connects Dodong Port and Jeodong Port
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   From Namyang, still quiet, to Taeha, a pioneering history in Ulleungdo
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    After passing through Tongmi, you reach Namyang Port. Is it because it is located in the southwest of Ulleungdo? It has a southwest sunset observatory. The construction of Namyang New Port is in full swing. Here, &#39;Ulleung Pharmacy Specialty Store&#39;, a specialty of Ulleungdo, is gathered. &amp;lt;Solar Restaurant&amp;gt;, which is considered to be a barnacle restaurant, is also located here. In addition to restaurants, there are some amenities such as &amp;lt;Namyang Nonghyup&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;Daegu Bed &amp;amp; Breakfast&amp;gt;. If you don&#39;t like the bustling Dodong Port or Jeodong Port, it&#39;s okay to get a lodging here.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;If you walk about 10 minutes on a monorail, it is Taeha Lighthouse. - South Korea Gyeongbuk Ulleungdo (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/258/db200a99-1a78-45fd-b396-9124c65b7742.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     If you walk about 10 minutes on a monorail, it is Taeha Lighthouse.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    From Namyang to Taeha, located on the northwestern tip of Ulleungdo, it runs for a month. It is an indispensable space in the history of Ulleungdo, bearing the Taeha Coastal Road, which is regarded as a double-headed carriage of the Ulleungdo Coastal Trail along with the Haengnam Trail. In July 1883, the following year, when the pioneering order of Ulleungdo was issued as the capital of the old Usan Island, Taeha, the land of Ulleungdo closest to the Korean Peninsula, 54 pioneers took their first steps here. Before being moved to Dodong in 1907, Taeha was the administrative center of Ulleungdo for over 20 years. Let&#39;s stop by Seongsindang, located in front of the Taeha branch of Namyang Elementary School, and listen to the sad legend of the Southeastern sister born by Taeha.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;If you walk about 10 minutes on a monorail, it is Taeha Lighthouse. - South Korea Gyeongbuk Ulleungdo (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/258/9a094825-a60d-43b4-a143-fa855d55fad4.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     If you walk about 10 minutes on a monorail, it is Taeha Lighthouse.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    It dates back to 1417 (17th year of King Taejong). Appointed as a choreographer on Ulleungdo, In-woo Kim arrives here on a mission to move Ulleungdo residents to land. The day before leaving with the villagers, a sea god appears in a dream and asks to leave a pair of Southeast Asians on the island. Ignoring this, I tried to depart, but when the waves were so severe that I could not leave the island, he left with two false children on the island. After returning to Ulleungdo eight years later, Inwoo Kim finds the children&#39;s white bones and builds a small shrine to comfort them. It is a legend embraced by the Holy Ghost.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A great feeling of waiting for the wind to send home - South Korea Gyeongbuk Ulleungdo (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/258/a43af140-5fb9-4a7c-92a9-5bb57accb254.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A great feeling of waiting for the wind to send home
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The 200-year-old highway policy at the expense of young children led to General An Yong-bok&#39;s talks about Dokdo, and their ambition toward Dokdo remains in the 21st century. Once you&#39;ve looked at Seongshindang, take the monorail to Taeha Lighthouse. You can go up on foot, but remember that even if you get off the monorail, you have to climb the dirt road for about 10 minutes. Next to the Taeha Lighthouse, there is an observatory of great wind. The sense of great wind that refers to the perforated rock means &#39;a place waiting for the strong wind&#39;.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Taeha&#39;s Holy Shrine, which embraces the sad legend of Ulleungdo - South Korea Gyeongbuk Ulleungdo (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/258/72a461f5-642b-4d43-8209-20701fe47299.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Taeha&#39;s Holy Shrine, which embraces the sad legend of Ulleungdo
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Ulleungdo, famous for its juniper trees, is a good place to build a boat, so many people came to the old boat to build a new boat. When the new ship was completed, it was a place to wait for the strong wind blowing in the direction of the mainland by attaching sails and anchor lines in the rock holes. When the wind blows, it breaks the anchor and goes to the land in a month. At the observation deck, squids are relaxingly shooting the sea breeze. Squid, which is considered to be delicious on Ulleungdo Island, is probably due to the wind here. If you saw the great view of the viewpoints that photographers and travelers say are beautiful, don&#39;t miss the ocher cave at the beginning of the Taeha Trail. Choreographers dispatched to Ulleungdo, who had to run on the rugged sea path, had to prove their granularity by taking ocher and juniper trees from this island.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Taeha&#39;s Holy Shrine, which embraces the sad legend of Ulleungdo - South Korea Gyeongbuk Ulleungdo (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/258/bee3fe8c-c09e-4206-9649-274c7e152faf.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Taeha&#39;s Holy Shrine, which embraces the sad legend of Ulleungdo
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Ulleungdo&#39;s wild beauty at a glance, Buk-myeon
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    I climb the road again. It is time to run on the north coast of Ulleungdo, which leads to Hyeonpo ~ Cheonbu ~ Sommok (Sokpo). It is a section where you can taste the secret flesh of the wild island. After passing the Hyeonpo Observatory, where you see the Hyeonpo Village at a glance, greet the senior citizens and reach the heavens. The bus stop departing from Jeodong Port and the starting point of the bus heading for Nari Basin and Seokpo ~ Seommok are Cheonbu Stop.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Hyeonpo Village and Senior Citizen&#39;s Peak as seen from the Hyeonpo Observatory - South Korea Gyeongbuk Ulleungdo (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/258/0a7589f9-2626-4c47-9843-92bf046bfdb5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Hyeonpo Village and Senior Citizen&#39;s Peak as seen from the Hyeonpo Observatory
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    If you travel to Ulleungdo by public transportation, you should be aware of the Cheonbu Station. Just remember it as a transfer stop. The road from Seokpo, which is considered as an outback in Ulleungdo, to Ismok is steep and winding. The front of An Yong-bok Memorial Hall is the best point to see Jukdo Island. You can go to the An Yong Bok Memorial Hall by car. Before going to the memorial, it&#39;s okay to run along the coast to Gwaneumdo, the last point of the current coastal road. Gwaneumdo Island, where Yeondogyo Bridge is located, is emerging as a new destination for Ulleungdo Island.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Anyongbok Memorial Hall - South Korea Gyeongbuk Ulleungdo (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/258/7fbaa300-8c53-4906-840e-67e9ef78f8b5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Anyongbok Memorial Hall
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Gwaneumdo Island is under construction on a round road. Until the pavement road is formed between Seokpo and Naesujeon, the only way to connect the two is to walk through the old road or use the island mok ferry. To return to Naesunjeon by car, you have to go back to the round road or use the island mok ferry (054-791-9905). However, ferry operation in winter should be confirmed in advance.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Jukdo Island from the An Yong-bok Memorial Hall - South Korea Gyeongbuk Ulleungdo (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/258/b2e4582a-489c-4c3d-97cf-df2454c72e2d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Jukdo Island from the An Yong-bok Memorial Hall
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Return to the road you came back to and go to the Russo-Japanese War Ruins (Seokpo Sunrise Sunrise Observatory). From the intersection of Seokpo Observation Deck and Naesu Observation Deck, you must walk the pavement and dirt road for about 15 minutes toward Seokpo Observation Deck. It is the best point to see everyone at sunset. It could have been useful as a fortress during the war, as you could see the sea from all sides. What happened on this peaceful sea?
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Point on the north coast, Samseonam - South Korea Gyeongbuk Ulleungdo (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/258/a0895b7c-285f-44cb-b572-205a3e990e6d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Point on the north coast, Samseonam
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    For reference, the tunnel construction in Ulleungdo Island, which has a total length of 4.7 km, is in full swing in Ulleungdo. Construction including three tunnels and observation decks from the pipeline to Cheonbu, Cheonbu and Jeodong tunnels is planned to take place over the next few years. Why don&#39;t you enjoy a trip to Ulleungdo that retains its old appearance before the completion of the roundabout road of Ulleungdo?
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;15&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sea seen from Russo-Japanese War Ruins (Sokpo Sunrise Sunrise Observatory) - South Korea Gyeongbuk Ulleungdo (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/258/9e58d154-9e44-4595-8eab-94cf67f5e606.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sea seen from Russo-Japanese War Ruins (Sokpo Sunrise Sunrise Observatory)
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   tip. Explore Ulleungdo
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     ▶ Ulleung-eup
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Dodong Port, the gateway to Ulleungdo. There are restaurants and lodging facilities as well as county offices. There are Haengnam Trail, Haengnam Lighthouse (Dodong Lighthouse), Naesu Observatory, Bongrae Falls, Jeodong Port, and Dokdo Museum and Cable Car.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     ▶ Writing Rights
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    You can enjoy a drive to the southwestern area of Ulleungdo, and see coastal rock formations such as Lion Rock, Helm Rock, Gom Rock, and Manmulsang. At the west end, there are attractions such as Taeharien Seongsindang, Taeha Lighthouse, and Daegunggam. If you&#39;re past Taeha-ryeong, take a look around the tombs of Namseo-ri and the colonies of pine nuts and beech trees.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     ▶ North Korea
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    It is a place where the scenery of Ulleungdo, full of power, unfolds. Gongambong and Songgotsan, Gongam (elephant rock), Samseonam, and Gwaneumdo also unfold as shown. Compared to the southern hemisphere of Ulleung-dong, there are fewer people looking for it, but it is a space that shows the &#39;secret island of the wild&#39;, so don&#39;t miss it.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p style=&#34;COLOR: #7b1f42&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Ulleung-gun Office Culture and Tourism Sports Department:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    054-790-6393
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p style=&#34;COLOR: #7b1f42&#34;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.ulleung.go.kr&#34; style=&#34;COLOR: #7b1f42&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;울릉군청 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
     www.ulleung.go.kr
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Dodong Tourist Information Center:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    054-790-6454 (calls are available from 9:00 to 5:00)
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Jeodong Tourist Information Center:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    054-791-6629 (December to February, during the off-season, work only on boat days)
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1.Access
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
     * Ulleungdo passenger ship operation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34; style=&#34;MARGIN-TOP: 0px&#34;&gt;
    The ships operate from Gangneung and Mukho in Gangwon-do, Pohang in Gyeongbuk and Ulpo in Uljin to Ulleungdo. During peak season and off season, time is flexible depending on the season. Homepage or telephone inquiries required. It takes 2 hours and 40 minutes from Gangwon area, starting at 49,000 won.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34; style=&#34;MARGIN-TOP: 0px&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     - question -
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Daea Express Shipping:
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.daea.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;대아고속해운 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
     www.daea.com
    &lt;/a&gt;
    , 1644-9602
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Seaforceville:
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.seaspovill.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;씨포스빌 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
     www.seaspovill.co.kr
    &lt;/a&gt;
    , 1577-8665
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Ulleung Dodong Terminal: 054-791-0801
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Ulleung Jeodong Terminal: 054-791-9330
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Gangneung Passenger Ship Terminal: 033-653-8670, 033-653-8671
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Mukho Passenger Terminal: 033-531-5891
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Pohang Passenger Ship Terminal: 054-242-5111
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
     * Local transportation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34; style=&#34;MARGIN-TOP: 0px&#34;&gt;
    If you travel on Ulleungdo alone, the buses in Ulleungdo are the most economical. Route buses (054-791-8000) that run on a round-the-road route between Naesujeon ~ Jedong ~ Dodong ~ Sadong ~ Namyang ~ Taeha ~ Heonpo ~ Cheonbu have an average interval of 40 minutes. If you want to see many places on Ulleungdo with low cost and high efficiency, you can also take a tour bus. If you pay only 15,000 won, you can take a tour of the A course that goes around the coast from Dodong to Seommo, and the B course that includes the Bongrae Falls and the Inland Observatory. For three or four people, a taxi is fine. There are private taxis (054-791-2612) as well as Ulleung taxis (054-791-2351). Course A costs 150,000 won and course B costs 60,000 won. It can be adjusted according to the schedule. You can use a rental car if you want to explore every corner freely. Hanjin Rent-a-car (054-791-5337) and OK Rent-a-car (054-791-8668).
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Restaurants around
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Nari Basin Camping Restaurant:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Nari, Buk-myeon, Ulleung-gun / 054-791-0775, 011-553-0270
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     San Village Restaurant:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Nari, Buk-myeon, Ulleung-gun / 054-791-4643
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Camping restaurant:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Nari, Buk-myeon, Ulleung-gun / 054-791-0773
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Neulpuran Mountain Restaurant:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Nari, Buk-myeon, Ulleung-gun / 054-791-8181
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     3.Accommodation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Adult Bon Motel:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Dodong-ri, Ulleung-eup / 054-791-2677
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.uld-sunginmotel.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.uld-sunginmotel.com/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Ulleungdae Resort:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Sadong 1-gil, Ulleung-eup / 054-791-8800
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.daearesort.com/main/main.php&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.daearesort.com/main/main.php
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Ulleung Marina Tourist Hotel:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Sadong 2-gil, Ulleung-eup / 054-791-0020
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.ullungmarina.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.ullungmarina.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;red&#34;&gt;
    ※ The above information was created in November 2013, and may change later, so be sure to check it before you travel.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;m not lonely anymore, Dokdo, South Korea - South Korea Gyeongbuk Ulleungdo</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/im-not-lonely-anymore-dokdo-south-korea-253/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 08:18:13 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/im-not-lonely-anymore-dokdo-south-korea-253/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;South Korea Gyeongbuk Ulleungdo&#34; data-title=&#34;im-not-lonely-anymore-dokdo-south-korea--253&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Dokdo at sunset - South Korea Gyeongbuk Ulleungdo (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/253/fe766011-64b4-4f6e-a9ac-0f4fda23c7f7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Dokdo at sunset
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   I&#39;m not lonely anymore, Dokdo, South Korea
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    South Korea Gyeongbuk Ulleungdo
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    I visited Dokdo, our land that I would like to visit someday. Even on Ulleungdo, which is located about three hours from Gangneung, Ibaekri is the most easterly island on the Korean Peninsula. The appearance of keeping a seat in the middle of the sea is daunting and vague. Even if you go to the front of your nose, you can&#39;t keep your eyes on them, so you can only look at them like an unrequited love. Once you set foot on Dokdo, the sky has helped you, so let&#39;s go meet it with gratitude.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p style=&#34;COLOR: #036071&#34;&gt;
    Ibaekri along the waterway to the southeast of Ulleungdo
    &lt;br/&gt;
    A lonely island, the home of birds
    &lt;br/&gt;
    No matter who says it&#39;s your land
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Dokdo is our land
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Islands on the way to Dokdo - South Korea Gyeongbuk Ulleungdo (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/253/28729dc7-bc67-4692-9f2f-b20251995106.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Islands on the way to Dokdo
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The song that comes to mind first when you say “Dokdo” like the first love that comes to mind on the first snowy day. I don&#39;t remember trying to memorize, but seeing humming naturally, we seem to be quite friendly. Dokdo is considered to be the youngest island because it is far away and serves as a gate for the East Sea on the Korean Peninsula, but cannot erase the feeling of “small rock island”. Looking at the situation, Dokdo, which rose 2.5 million to 4.6 million years ago, is the older brother than Ulleungdo and Jeju Island, which was born 1.2 million years ago.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Seodo, Dongdo, and Dokdo, with 90 islands around - South Korea Gyeongbuk Ulleungdo (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/253/8b5ec64d-91e6-4ef9-92e8-eb6a3727f53d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Seodo, Dongdo, and Dokdo, with 90 islands around
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Even in Ulleungdo, Baek-ri, good to know Dokdo
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Because of its small size, and because of its distant location, it seems like it is receiving attention from the nation or during the “Dokdo dispute”, but in fact, there is a “Dokdo&#39;s room” in each chest. Each person may have different sizes, but it is an automatic option to catch up with any political reason for those born and raised on this land. The rocky island formed by hardening of lava rising from 2000m below sea level millions of years ago is not a good place for people to stay, but under the sea he harbors is a golden fishing ground and abundant underground resources. The abundant seafood that can be eaten right now, and the future energy that will be useful after the current energy, such as coal and oil, is exhausted. The face and mind are pretty, and they are also smart, and the desire to make the wife of another person who looks great is also similar.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The people who visited Dokdo are shooting &#39;authentication shots&#39; - South Korea Gyeongbuk Ulleungdo (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/253/64f95d57-b631-4be7-a691-0575f94ea3c9.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The people who visited Dokdo are shooting &#39;authentication shots&#39;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    I would like to investigate from aquatic products caught in Dokdo to every corner of the sea, but only 30 minutes are given to those seeking Dokdo. It is not long to stay in Dokdo, which was designated as a natural reserve in 1999 (registered as a natural monument in 1982).
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The people who visited Dokdo are shooting &#39;authentication shots&#39; - South Korea Gyeongbuk Ulleungdo (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/253/e1041771-6b7f-4270-ad5c-f9f472da1599.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The people who visited Dokdo are shooting &#39;authentication shots&#39;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    In order to go to Dokdo Island, it is in order to find it from Ulleungdo. Passenger ships to Gangneung, Gangneung, Mukho and Pohang, Gyeongbuk travel to Ulleungdo. It usually takes around 3 hours to go from Ulleungdo to Ulleungdo and from Ulleungdo to Dokdo as little as one hour to as many as two hours. After running from Ulleungdo to Dokdo and staying at Dokdo for a while, it takes about 2 hours 30 minutes to 4 hours 30 minutes to get on the cruise to Dokdo. The speed varies by boat, so be sure to check the time required when heading to Dokdo.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The Dokdo Guard&#39;s guard post is unfortunate, but access is restricted. - South Korea Gyeongbuk Ulleungdo (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/253/f8fbce3e-1d12-4cb8-b50e-114442dfe6e8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The Dokdo Guard&#39;s guard post is unfortunate, but access is restricted.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    And one more thing, if you&#39;re planning a trip to Dokdo (probably only once in your life), a weather check is a must. Although the island travels, Dokdo is particularly affected by the weather. It is better to check the weather forecast in advance to secure a boat. Also, remember that after the peak season, ships to Dokdo do not operate every day. I arrived in Ulleungdo, but if the weather is good, I recommend going from Dokdo. It&#39;s an island climate that doesn&#39;t know when and how to change, so if you have a good day while on Ulleungdo, head to Dokdo that day. Of course, there are enthusiasts who visit Ulleungdo a number of times, but most travelers are mostly by age regardless of age. It is better to make preparations so that you can go to meet Dokdo without missing it, as you have visited Ulleungdo Island.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The vast ocean is full of various rocks - South Korea Gyeongbuk Ulleungdo (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/253/9ea6d394-224c-4fa8-854e-0e865d81012f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The vast ocean is full of various rocks
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Ships from Ulleungdo to Dokdo depart from Jeodong Port and Ulleung New Port (Sadong Port). Ships arriving from Ulleungdo to Ulleungdo enter Jeodong Port, Dodong Port, and Ulleung New Port. If you entered Jeodong Port, you can get a boat to Dokdo from the Jeodong Port Passenger Terminal. Sea Flower, Dokdo Sarang, and Dolphin also operate at Ulleung New Port. The charge is the same as 45,000 won, but the time required is different, so be sure to check. It is here that it took almost 5 hours to meet Dokdo. One more thing, even in November, the ship heading for Dokdo is the best. When it gets cold, the ship to Dokdo stops operating and then heads to Dokdo again next spring.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The vast ocean is full of various rocks - South Korea Gyeongbuk Ulleungdo (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/253/eb8f440f-de18-42af-819a-c7333d2fc225.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The vast ocean is full of various rocks
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Along the way that General Silla Isa
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   I ran to Dokdo about two hours. Dokdo is not an island, but consists of Dongdo and Seodo and 89 surrounding islands. The boat docks at the Dongdo dock. There is a shelter for fishermen on the steeper west island. Fortunately, today&#39;s ship docks safely at the Dongdo dock. When the weather is rough due to the waves, even if you try to go to Dokdo, you will not be able to dock and come around. Finally, we set foot on Dokdo, the easternmost part of Korea. Nice to meet you, Dokdo.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Dokdo Isabu-gil, which is immediately accessible from the Dongdo Pier - South Korea Gyeongbuk Ulleungdo (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/253/18bb5257-dda1-4a9d-8156-057dc85b425e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Dokdo Isabu-gil, which is immediately accessible from the Dongdo Pier
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Thanks to its natural monument, it is possible to walk only a part of the East Pier. In 512, “Isabu-gil,” named after General Isabu, who absorbed Usan-guk (now Ulleungdo and Dokdo), an independent army into Silla territory, welcomes people. I don&#39;t know how much time it takes to see the scenery drawn by fan rock, whetstone rock, candlestick rock, etc. My heart jumps with my feet on the floor of a few square feet allowed to walk.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Dongdo from the ship to Dokdo - South Korea Gyeongbuk Ulleungdo (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/253/ca5b6974-77cf-405e-bfa8-9cee50c89ddc.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Dongdo from the ship to Dokdo
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Just because they came to Dokdo, the people who were reminded of it a lot have no time to take pictures. It is a scene that does not go well with “獨 島,” a lonely island. People who have migrated to Ulleungdo from the southern coast of Jeolla-do called &#39;Dolseom&#39; as &#39;Dokseom&#39; to become &#39;Dokdo&#39;.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Dokdo is starting to set out - South Korea Gyeongbuk Ulleungdo (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/253/a53f3b95-123d-4595-b4cf-b0c2215ad2cb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Dokdo is starting to set out
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   I don&#39;t look lonely at this moment, but I feel a little bit lonely when I think of a scene where I am defending the vast sea alone. Still, I don&#39;t have much time to stay, so I move diligently again. Unfortunately, the space where Dokdo Guards stay is restricted.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Dokdo is starting to set out - South Korea Gyeongbuk Ulleungdo (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/253/0a4a507c-4d2d-4252-aec1-03c5ddf9ef12.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Dokdo is starting to set out
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   You can&#39;t miss the view of the sea evenly picking up the green and blue colors. After a brief meeting with Dokdo, where 꿋꿋 is located in the vast ocean, a horn sounds to inform you of the time to return. Time to go back now. The road to Ulleungdo, leaving Dokdo Guard&#39;s offense behind, reveals Dokdo&#39;s side profile.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Cover stone to mark the end of the east of Korea - South Korea Gyeongbuk Ulleungdo (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/253/70818d7a-0b5c-49a1-8040-7c886903fef2.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Cover stone to mark the end of the east of Korea
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Describe the location of Dokdo An Yong Bok-gil, named after the fisherman An Yong Bok, who made the Japanese shogunate admit that Dokdo was Chosun land during the Joseon Dynasty. What do we have to do to protect this land, which is settled through the vast sea alone?
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Dokdo Guard - South Korea Gyeongbuk Ulleungdo (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/253/dd493f34-6cd7-490a-bd0c-a56c6c01248e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Dokdo Guard
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;topmr&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     ▶ Dokdo Passenger Ship Flight Timetable
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34; style=&#34;MARGIN-TOP: 0px&#34;&gt;
    Ships from Ulleungdo to Dokdo depart from Jeodong Port and Ulleung New Port (Sadong Port). Ship times vary from day to day, so be sure to check in advance. Some ships return to the origin in three hours, such as &#39;seaflower&#39;, and sometimes four hours and 30 minutes, like &#39;dokdo love lake&#39;. The charge is the same as 45,000 won, but the time required is different, so be sure to check it. In winter, ships to Dokdo do not operate.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34; style=&#34;MARGIN-TOP: 0px&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34; style=&#34;MARGIN-TOP: 0px&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
     * Ulleung New Port (Sadong Port)
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34; style=&#34;MARGIN-TOP: 0px&#34;&gt;
    Sea Flower, Sea Flower 2 (070-8675-9191, 070-8675-9192, 070-8675-9193), Dolphin Lake (054-791-8111, 054-791-8112), Dokdo Love Lake (054-791 -9901, 054-791-9902, 054-791-9903) operate irregularly (07:20, 08:00, 12:50, 14:00). It takes 3 to 4 hours and 30 minutes and costs 45,000 won. Sadong Port
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34; style=&#34;MARGIN-TOP: 0px&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34; style=&#34;MARGIN-TOP: 0px&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
     * Jeodong Port
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34; style=&#34;MARGIN-TOP: 0px&#34;&gt;
    Seastar 1 and Seastar 3 operate irregularly at 13:50 and 14:45. It takes 3 hours and 30 minutes, the rate is 45,000 won in general, 49,000 won in honors. The regular flight ended on November 17th. Winter Flight is expecting a weekend. For inquiry, Seaspoville (
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.seaspovill.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;씨스포빌 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
     www.seaspovill.co.kr
    &lt;/a&gt;
    ) And Ulleung Jeodong Terminal (054-791-9330).
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    ※ The above information was created in November 2013, and may change later, so be sure to check it before you travel.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>