<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Songpa-gu on Every Corner of Korea</title>
    <link>https://codecorea.github.io/tags/songpa-gu/</link>
    <description>Every Corner of Korea (Songpa-gu)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 09:54:40 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="https://codecorea.github.io/tags/songpa-gu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The museum is alive! Hanseong Baekje Museum - Songpa-gu, Seoul, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/the-museum-is-alive-hanseong-baekje-museum-115/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 09:54:40 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/the-museum-is-alive-hanseong-baekje-museum-115/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Songpa-gu, Seoul, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;the-museum-is-alive-hanseong-baekje-museum--115&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Pungnaptoseong Wall Section of Hanseong Baekje Museum Lobby - Songpa-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/115/d66ae9d1-89cd-4323-956b-ee67787362af.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Pungnaptoseong Wall Section of Hanseong Baekje Museum Lobby
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   The museum is alive! Hanseong Baekje Museum
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Songpa-gu, Seoul, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    It&#39;s been a while but it&#39;s still cold. However, as the morning dawns, spring is waiting for the end of winter. It is the season that shows the passage of time. As we move from winter to spring, we left to meet Baekje, which once took center part of the land. The main character is the Hanseong Baekje Museum, which bears the history of Baekje, which occupied the Han River.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The Hanseong Baekje Museum is a space where you can see &#39;Hanseong Baekje&#39; at first glance. With the focus on Hanseong Baekje, it has embraced the ancient history of this land beyond the times of Woongjin Baekje and Xabi Baekje. Let&#39;s take a time trip to Baekje, along the foot of Mongchontoseong, a defense facility of Hanseong Baekje.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   How did the Baekje live?
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Hanseong Baekje Museum is free. Feel free to travel to ancient Baekje. The museum is open from 9:00 am to 9:00 pm on weekdays and from 6 pm (November to February) and 7:00 pm (March to October) on weekends and holidays. Closed day is every Monday. The parking fee is 2,000 won for up to 2 hours, after which it is added to 150 won every 5 minutes. Card payment is possible. It is also easily accessible by public transport. You can find it at Exit 1 of Mongchontoseong Station (Line 8) or Exit 3 of Olympic Park Station (Line 5).
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Hanseong Baekje Museum Lobby - Songpa-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/115/f0bd7aad-3afe-41fd-95ef-6de3f4cfd13e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Hanseong Baekje Museum Lobby
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Baek jae. The first country of the Three Kingdoms occupied the Han River. Let&#39;s start with the name. &#39;Baekje&#39; comes from &#39;People have crossed the sea&#39; or &#39;Baekjehae&#39; or &#39;People have enjoyed&#39;. This is easier to understand when following the founding myth of Baekje.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#39;Prehistoric Seoul&#39; held by Exhibition Hall 1 - Songpa-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/115/68ee7c94-f517-42c4-bde1-c00e30ba967a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     &#39;Prehistoric Seoul&#39; held by Exhibition Hall 1
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   King Onjo of Baekje is from Goguryeo. His mother is Sosono, who is married to Jumong who founded Goguryeo. Onjo&#39;s new father, Jumong, was established by marrying Sossano, the daughter of a powerful patriarch. Jumong cared for Sosono&#39;s son Onjo and his brother Liu, but he passed down the throne to his son Yuri from Buyeo. Onjo and Biryu leave their hometown with Sosono, where Biryu is located in Michu Hall, Incheon, and Onjo is located in Saori, which belongs to Mahan Land.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Onjo, the Liu brothers and their mother Sosono - Songpa-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/115/7e0b8cbb-2e9d-41d0-b6b3-13a3f1968188.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Onjo, the Liu brothers and their mother Sosono
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Baekje, which started in the small country of Mahan, developed and developed in exchange with Japan and China based on the fertile land around the Han River. Baekje&#39;s first capital is Wiryongseong, south of the Han. It is the old name of Hansung. Hanseong means Bukseong (Pungnaptoseong), which had palaces, and Mongchontoseong, which had a palace. It is so solid that it has survived for more than a few decades.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Pungnaptoseong built by the stem of the Han River - Songpa-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/115/cdccedcb-c3e4-481f-83ac-e7c635d22afc.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Pungnaptoseong built by the stem of the Han River
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The northern province of Hansung, Pungnaptoseong, is an ancient castle built on flat soil. It is also quite large. The Han River flows north and west of Pungnaptoseong. Climbing to this stream, Baekje would have developed civilization by interacting with various countries. It is estimated to be 43m wide and 11m high. Some remain (except 2.2 km) except for the collapsed western wall. When you enter the Hanseong Baekje Museum, the first person you encounter is the soil layer made by removing the cross section of Pungnaptoseong.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Soil layer which removed actual pruned soil section - Songpa-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/115/8133254b-0f37-46e6-b311-035b3da3468d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Soil layer which removed actual pruned soil section
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It was restored to the Pungnaptoseong castle, which was unearthed in 2011. At first glance it&#39;s huge. Hanseong Baekje Museum commentator said, &#34;Though tens of centuries have passed, it means that it has been built up so firmly.&#34; &#34;They built it and buried it together.&#34; Looking at the cross section of Pungnaptoseong castle wall in the museum, the situation is drawn by itself.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;13&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Exhibition Hall 2 introducing Hanseong Baekje era - Songpa-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/115/7f806b86-3c33-4d57-b958-2c3c44136f65.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Exhibition Hall 2 introducing Hanseong Baekje era
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Korean Peninsula Ancient History of the Museum
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Passing through the lobby where the Pungnapseong cross section is located, you will naturally see the prologue and head for the exhibition room. In Seoul, Seoul, which was known only as the capital of Hanyang and 500 years of Joseon, recognized the capital of Baekje a long time ago. Kings, royalty, nobles, and people lived and died in Pungnapto (North) and Mongchonto (Male) and were buried in Seokchon-dong burial mounds.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Exhibition Hall 1 introduces the prehistoric era of Seoul. Stone Age - Songpa-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/115/cc14b659-76bf-4efa-8311-eb056c204a2c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Exhibition Hall 1 introduces the prehistoric era of Seoul. Stone Age
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In Exhibition Hall 1, you can meet &#39;Prehistoric Seoul&#39;. From the Paleolithic period to the Neolithic and Bronze periods, Mahan, Jinhan, and Hanhan&#39;s alliance are shown. The history of Baekje Empire, which started as one of Mahan&#39;s 50 countries, begins here. Baekje, which occupies the Han River, integrates Mahan by rapidly accepting and developing China&#39;s iron culture.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;We show life of Neolithic clearly - Songpa-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/115/7c7769fa-2c30-4f36-a789-f3bb7b45969e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     We show life of Neolithic clearly
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you move to the second exhibition room, you will begin to explore the royal road Hanseong. A kind explanation of the history of Baekje is known. Baekje, which was founded in Seoul in 18 B.C.E. and survived until 660 C.E., started out as the first capital Hanseong (Seoul) and reigned in Woongjin (Princess) and Xabi (Buyeo). Among them, Hanseong era accounts for more than 70% of the 600-year history of Baekje. During this period, Baekje enjoyed its heyday, expanding its territory from the present Hwanghaehae Island to Jeolla-do and Jeju-do.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Representative of Baekje. Seven map - Songpa-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/115/15af771b-5aab-4a58-9fe7-2fcf3bec4910.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Representative of Baekje. Seven map
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   After the heyday of Baekje, the third exhibition room, “Actualism of the Three Kingdoms,” will emerge. Baekje&#39;s first royal Hanseong was captured by the attack of Goguryeo Jangsu King in 475. For more than 70 years, the owner of the Han River was Goguryeo. In 551, Baekje reunited with the Silla to find the Han River basin again, but for a while. Silla, who became the new owner of the Han River two years later, has occupied the area for over 300 years. Baekje moved to Woongjin after the fall of Hanseong. Although the Han River was lost, Woongjin and Sabigi Baekje bloom unique cultures and influence Japanese ancient culture. A variety of attractions await you along with the ship model that was in charge of the trade of the Baekje era.
   &lt;br/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Baekje Geumdong Hyang-ro excavated from Buyeo Neungsan-ri - Songpa-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/115/a2000c37-c153-46de-90e9-37c533a6a598.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Baekje Geumdong Hyang-ro excavated from Buyeo Neungsan-ri
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   After the Three Kingdoms era, Epilogue ‘Seoul, to the world! To the future! ”Begins. Seoul, the capital of the Korean peninsula for 2,000 years ago, is the main character. Seoul, which was the capital of Baekje and a key point during the Goguryeo and Silla eras, served as the second capital to supplement the geographical weakness of the opening of the capital of Goryeo. Since then, it was chosen as the new capital of Joseon in 1394 and has been serving as the capital of the Republic of Korea.
   &lt;br/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Stone Beast excavated from Royal Mausoleum - Songpa-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/115/b612f468-7d0e-4928-bddf-3c7450307812.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Stone Beast excavated from Royal Mausoleum
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The Hanseong Baekje Museum shows the ancient history of Seoul, focusing on the Hanseong era of Baekje, the first capital city of Seoul on the Korean Peninsula. Along with the history of Baekje, ancient history of the Korean peninsula can be seen as a vividly embodied material, which is perfect for studying history. Do not know history, difficult to answer children&#39;s questions? Do not worry The rich and diverse materials of the Hanseong Baekje Museum will solve all the children&#39;s curiosities. Oh, if you are still burdened, you may want to take advantage of the six-day commentary. Why don&#39;t you take a trip to a living museum and join a child in spring break?
   &lt;br/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;13&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Geumdong Gwanmo excavated from Gongju Suchon-ri Tombs - Songpa-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/115/6759d823-da29-4ee9-91d3-0e49fffc2e3b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Geumdong Gwanmo excavated from Gongju Suchon-ri Tombs
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel info
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
     &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Hanseong Baekje Museum
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Address: 71, Wiryeseong-daero, Songpa-gu, Seoul (In Olympic Park)
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Inquiries: 02-2152-5800
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Free admission, 2000 won (up to 2 hours, 150 won every 5 minutes thereafter)
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Closed: Every Monday, January 1, closed by the market / closed, but not closed if Monday is a public holiday
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://baekjemuseum.seoul.go.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://baekjemuseum.seoul.go.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Nearby attractions
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Mongchontoseong: Olympic-ro, Songpa-gu / 02-2147-2001
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Pungnaptoseong: Pungnap-dong, Songpa-gu / 02-2147-2800
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Seokchon-dong Ancient Tombs: Seokchon-dong, Songpa-gu / 02-2147-2816
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Restaurants near
     &lt;br/&gt;
     One-way Tteokbokki: Seongan-ro 3-gil, Gangdong-gu / 070-8950-1019 / Tteokbokki
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Self House: Olympic-ro, Gangdong-gu / 02-476-7063 / Garlic Tteokbokki
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Binja Chicken Feet: Bangi-dong, Songpa-gu / 02-425-6292 / Chicken Feet, Chicken Stir-Fried Tang
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Rooms
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Seoul Olympic Parktel: Olympic-ro, Songpa-gu / 02-410-2514
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.parktel.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.parktel.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Lotte Hotel World Olympic-ro, Songpa-gu / 02-419-7000
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.lottehotel.com/world/ko/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.lottehotel.com/world/ko/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was updated in February 2019 and may change afterwards, so please check before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ The information such as text, photos and videos used in this article is copyrighted by Korea Tourism Organization, so unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>