<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gwangju on Every Corner of Korea</title>
    <link>https://codecorea.github.io/tags/gwangju/</link>
    <description>Every Corner of Korea (Gwangju)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 08:48:44 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="https://codecorea.github.io/tags/gwangju/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Along the frozen stream, &#39;warm exhibition&#39; Gwangju Gyeongancheon, Bunwon-ri - Gwangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/along-the-frozen-stream-warm-exhibition-gwangju-gyeongancheon-bunwonri-203/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 08:48:44 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/along-the-frozen-stream-warm-exhibition-gwangju-gyeongancheon-bunwonri-203/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Gwangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;along-the-frozen-stream-warm-exhibition-gwangju-gyeongancheon-bunwonri--203&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox type3 clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Gyeongancheon to join Paldang Lake - Gwangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/203/e64c9479-9f35-4f74-9f11-89c986389c32.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Gyeongancheon to join Paldang Lake
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Scenery of the face museum - Gwangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/203/c1262be6-18d8-4af6-bb8e-c20674d8f5a5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Scenery of the face museum
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Gyeongancheon Wetland Ecological Park - Gwangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/203/5ca3b2a7-16e1-4b60-a6d3-7649d4b1e295.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Gyeongancheon Wetland Ecological Park
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Along the frozen stream, &#39;warm exhibition&#39; Gwangju Gyeongancheon, Bunwon-ri
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Gwangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Even if the water path is tightly frozen, the warmth of calm emotion is transmitted. Road 337, which runs along Bunwon-ri and Gyeongancheon, is a path that blends history, exhibitions, and walking spaces in history. Namhan River, Paldang Lake and the clean path leading to the exhibition halls, old kilns and ecological parks await.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Marsh Ecological Park and the last kiln of the royal family
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The corner towns where Gyeongancheon and Namhan River meet are separated from the world for a moment. There are no boats and people on the water that has become a water resource protection area, and the local road No. 337 that bypasses to Yangpyeong is even the best.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   When you pass the Toechon Intersection along the path that crosses the Gyeongancheon River, the Gyeongancheon Wetland Ecological Park reveals a calm look. The wetland ecological park, belonging to the eight views of Gwangju, has a different winter walk. The white trail connecting the riverside and the wetland extends for about 2km. There are friendly guides to the flora and fauna inhabiting the ecological park. Gyeongancheon River, where you can meet elk and migratory birds, is also the wintering place of Koni. The riverside leading to the bird&#39;s eye view is also popular for family walks and dating dates for lovers. There are shelter everywhere, helping to remember the winter.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The way to the White House - Gwangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/203/309c64eb-42a5-4b44-af66-424377f1a646.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The way to the White House
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   As you enter Namwon-myeon Bundwon-ri, downstream of Gyeongancheon, time flows slowly. Although the surrounding villages are quiet, the spirits contained in them are high-class. Bunwon-ri is where the last kiln of the Joseon Dynasty was located. The village name &#39;Bunwon-ri&#39; is also named after the white porcelain branch of Saongwon, which was responsible for the food of the court. Good clay and firewood were needed to bake a bowl used in the palace, and an old kiln was created where the river stem meets the Han River.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Wooden deck walkway at Gyeongancheon Wetland Ecological Park - Gwangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/203/3240e3c2-f5d9-428e-b6d8-652e25ca6e18.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Wooden deck walkway at Gyeongancheon Wetland Ecological Park
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Branch of the White Porcelain Museum (031-766-8465,
   &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.bunwon.or.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;분원백자자료관 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
    www.bunwon.or.kr
   &lt;/a&gt;
   In terms of scale, even if it lags behind Gwangju Ceramic Museum in Gwangju, it is still different from the story. Located on a hill behind a secluded village, the museum remodeled the school and raised the building. It is a warm consideration not to damage the white porcelain that was buried in the elementary school site. The Japanese Imperial High School was established at the place where the royal bowl was to be cooked, and the site was revealed through excavation work in the early 2000s. The refurbished museum is strongly surrounded by iron plates.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Pieces of white porcelain found in Bunwon-ri - Gwangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/203/1094e3ea-33b5-40d6-9a24-b91f773532b8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Pieces of white porcelain found in Bunwon-ri
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   On the way to the museum, the names of the discovered whites are engraved, and the selection fees of Saongwon are lined up side by side. Inside the museum, white porcelain from the time of excavation is displayed. In the museum, you can decorate a postcard by stamping it, and if you make a reservation in advance, you can experience making a bowl yourself. It is a small space, but the friendly atmosphere with commentary is also friendly.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   The winter scenery overlooking the front of the museum is as elegant as white porcelain. Gyeongancheon and Paldang Lake blend smoothly over a large tree. The Bunwon White porcelain museum is free of charge, all year round.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Bunwon white porcelain museum - Gwangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/203/eb4b2aa2-cb9d-42e1-b3aa-eca12aa98552.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Bunwon white porcelain museum
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Bizarre and historical museum full of stories
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    In Bunwon-ri, a unique museum attracts attention. The face museum behind Namjongmyeon Office (031-765-3522,
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.visagej.org/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;얼굴박물관 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
     www.visagej.org
    &lt;/a&gt;
    ) Is a space where dolls, masks, etc. from around the world are exhibited using faces. Founded by a theater director, this museum decorates the courtyard with hanok and stone statues in Namdo, and has a shelter for a cup of tea. The Face Museum will be closed until February 12th to replace the exhibits and will be reopened from the 13th. Mondays and Tuesdays are closed, and Wednesdays and Thursdays must be reserved in advance to enter. It is always open from Friday to Sunday.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Face-themed face museum - Gwangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/203/74da2b61-3a56-44dc-8f00-5e4f2ea73aad.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Face-themed face museum
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The quiet exhibition halls continue along the waterways. To get a good view of Paldang Lake, which is in contact with Gyeongancheon, we will go to the Water Environment Exhibition Hall (031-8008-6937). On the 9th floor of the renovated building, there is an exhibition hall overlooking the Paldang Lake. On the other hand, when you look at the observation deck on the other hand, you can see the beautiful views of Paldang from Sonae Island, Yogja Island, and Yebongsan Mountain without interruption. A telescope is also provided so you can closely observe traces on the river that are easy to miss on the ground. From the past of Paldang Lake, it has been decorated as a scientific experience space where you can feel the preciousness of plants and animals and water.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Water Environment Exhibition Hall - Gwangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/203/2bec63dc-5928-4d1d-bd05-8a734fe55f32.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Water Environment Exhibition Hall
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In the vicinity of Gyeongancheon, there is also a meaningful space where you can calmly organize your excursion. This is the nest and history of Japanese women&#39;s comfort women who entered Wondang-ri. Here, the comfort women&#39;s grandmothers lived in a community, and the Human Rights Museum with the theme of comfort women also opened. Just looking at the pictures and statues of the grandmothers who filled the walls, it makes me heartbroken. Every spring, a memorial service is held at the History Museum.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   Filling the quiet Gyeongancheon and Bunwon-ri with a solid sense of fullness is the local specialty of steamed carp. Downstream of Gyeongancheon has been famous for true fish. There are over 20 restaurants specializing in steamed carp in Bunwon-ri, and some restaurants boast a tradition of over 20 years. Fishing for crucian carp was banned to protect water resources, but the legend of crucian simmered with various secrets such as rugs continues to this day.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Statue of the comfort woman - Gwangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/203/f9b9c4ce-1d9a-4a18-bdc4-b4a75ca18ffd.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Statue of the comfort woman
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    1.Access
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    * Self-driving
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Jungbu Expressway Gwangju IC → Doma Samgeori → Turn left at Toechon Intersection, turn to Bunwon-ri, and turn right to Gyeongancheon Wetland Ecological Park
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    * public transport
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Take bus No. 13-2 to Toechon from East Seoul Terminal. From Toechon-myeon to Bunwon-ri, use an autonomous circulation bus
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    2. Delicious
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Hometown Maeuntang: Namjong-myeon Bunwon-ri / Steamed fish / 031-767-9693
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Toechon Mill Noodle House: Toechon-myeon Dosu-ri / Milmyeon / 031-767-9280
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Chestnut House: Jungsan-myeon Sanseong-ri / Tofu Octopus Hotpot / 031-746-9643
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Dongseo Someori Gukbap: Konjiam-eup, Konjiam-eup / Suyuk / 031-763-1949
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    3.Accommodation
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Gwangju Hanok Village: Mokhyeon-dong / 031-766-9677
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Konjiam Twin House: Jangsim-ri, Konjiam-eup / 010-2253-3757 /
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.twinhouse.pe.kr&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     www.twinhouse.pe.kr
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Jeongon Pension: Gwaneum-ri, Toechon-myeon / 031-768-3917 /
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.jo-house.co.kr&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     www.jo-house.co.kr
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    ※ The above information was created in January 2013, and may change later, so be sure to check it before you travel.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>National Gwangju Science Museum where light, art and science are combined - Buk-gu, Gwangju, South Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/national-gwangju-science-museum-where-light-art-and-science-are-combined-159/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 16:04:27 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/national-gwangju-science-museum-where-light-art-and-science-are-combined-159/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Buk-gu, Gwangju, South Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;national-gwangju-science-museum-where-light-art-and-science-are-combined--159&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;dock - Buk-gu, Gwangju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/159/9793b9f7-1fdf-4852-9908-cd83dce38164.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    dock
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   National Gwangju Science Museum where light, art and science are combined
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Buk-gu, Gwangju, South Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The summer of Gwangju, the town of light, is hot. I visited the Gwangju-Kia Champions Field, a stadium of dreams boasting excellent facilities and the National Gwangju Science Museum to cool the heat. The science museum with the theme of light and art is good for avoiding the midday heat, and the baseball field starts in the late afternoon, so you can watch it cool.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Gwangju Science Museum
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The National Gwangju Science Museum opened in October 2013 under the theme of &#39;light&#39; and &#39;art&#39;, the symbols of Gwangju. Children are especially fond of the hands-on exhibitions, which are directly manipulated and touched. It is exciting for middle and high school students as well as adults. The 1st and 2nd exhibition halls are located on the 2nd floor, and the children&#39;s hall for children and the 4D theater are on the 1st floor. It is better to go up to the 2nd floor after checking the 4D theater time in advance.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Inside the Science Museum from the second floor - Buk-gu, Gwangju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/159/f9c737f8-25c7-4307-a384-9442edec230a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Inside the Science Museum from the second floor
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   1 The exhibition hall is about light and art. How would you respond if your child asks, &#34;Mom, why does the shadow keep following me?&#34; The answer, &#34;If there is light, a shadow is cast.&#34; Shadow is a phenomenon that occurs because the light goes straight. When a straight light encounters an opaque object, a shadow is created. What if the light doesn&#39;t go straight and it&#39;s meandering? Even if there is an object, it can bend to the back of the object, so there is no shadow.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;There are many experiential exhibits, such as snowboarding, windsurfing, and hang gliders. - Buk-gu, Gwangju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/159/12a72e00-1b6d-4375-a89e-96650cfe7003.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     There are many experiential exhibits, such as snowboarding, windsurfing, and hang gliders.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   2 The exhibition hall explains the principles of science encountered in everyday life and shows the science that meets the future, the universe, and the ocean. It is a space to experience and understand the science behind life, sports, and play. You can see why the roller coaster does not fall when it is flipped over, and what is the secret of moving the snowboard.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Some games arrive at a set time using real equipment such as windsurfing, snowboarding, and hang gliders. Through this, you will learn how to control the ship&#39;s direction with sails, the secrets of moving a snowboard, and the principles of hang gliders.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Shall we spin like Yuna&#39;s sister? - Buk-gu, Gwangju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/159/e718403b-eddc-49f2-a6b4-3581896fa78c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Shall we spin like Yuna&#39;s sister?
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The children&#39;s house on the first floor is open only to preschool children and their guardians. It is a space where you can meet interesting science principles in the universe, nature, the human body, and life. You can roll the ball over the shape of a giant tongue to see where it tastes and how you can get into it.
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;It tastes different depending on the location of the tongue ~ - Buk-gu, Gwangju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/159/bec9b194-a75f-4640-9de6-e6099049a662.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     It tastes different depending on the location of the tongue ~
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Inside the mini observatory, you can watch animations of space exploration, and it is full of experiences tailored to the eye level of infants and toddlers.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Press the pin to complete your own picture - Buk-gu, Gwangju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/159/2beaecef-aada-4d37-8fe0-bee6ec5c68d4.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Press the pin to complete your own picture
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Let&#39;s check the screening time of the theaters located in each exhibition hall in advance. 1 In the exhibition hall 3D theater, &amp;lt;Rocket Launch&amp;gt;, &amp;lt;Becoming a Space Flight&amp;gt;, and &amp;lt;The World Created by Light&amp;gt; are screened. Astronomical theaters, 4D cinemas, and 4D simulators, which require separate tickets, show more vivid and interesting images.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   There are many things to see outdoors. With a observatory facility moving on the bus, Lucerium Staka is a space where you can observe the sunspots and red flames and meet the solar system. Playgrounds that shape the universe and planets are also popular with children. From the playground side, the exterior of the science museum as if it were a space creature is also impressive.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    During the peak summer season, the Water Science Experience Center is operated. There is an admission fee separate from the Science Museum, and there is an object experience every Monday.
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;16&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Outdoor children&#39;s playground with the theme of space and planets - Buk-gu, Gwangju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/159/714d71b2-ee71-4086-a99f-c2d04a1a788a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Outdoor children&#39;s playground with the theme of space and planets
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Gwangju-Kia Champions Field, Dream Ground
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The closing time for viewing the science museum is 5:30 pm, and the summer sun is still in full bloom. Gwangju-Kia Champions Field is recommended as a great place to enjoy a late afternoon. It&#39;s hot, but I want to play some baseball, but when I go to the scene, it&#39;s different. When the heat of the day cools and the evening breeze blows, you can watch the game full of passion.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Gwangju-Kia Champions Field - Buk-gu, Gwangju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/159/d3424bf9-a51e-4207-82e9-91792f39cdb6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Gwangju-Kia Champions Field
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Gwangju-Kia Champions Field opened in March 2014 and boasts state-of-the-art facilities. Of the 22,000 seats, 19,246 are infield seats. It reflects the culture of Korean spectators who like to watch infield. The distance from home plate to spectator seat is 18.5m, which is the shortest among the national baseball fields. Various convenience facilities were installed in 229 seats for the handicapped, and they were also certified as a living environment without disabilities (BF).
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Hat slide found on the way to the outfield - Buk-gu, Gwangju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/159/1ad8cc1f-c901-490e-8471-d6e34cd11c56.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Hat slide found on the way to the outfield
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   There are several table seats for family visitors, and it is a spectator-friendly stadium with a sand playground for children, a hat slide, a playroom, and a nursing room.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;It is popular with family visitors because it has lawns and a playground for playing with sand. - Buk-gu, Gwangju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/159/a505ef49-3b18-447a-bc32-11f1841b0033.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     It is popular with family visitors because it has lawns and a playground for playing with sand.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you bought an outfield ticket, pack a mat and go in. Of the 2,754 outfield seats, about half are grass. Sitting here requires laying mats to protect the grass and prevent exposure to pests. If you don&#39;t have a mat, you can sit on a long bench-shaped seat. Since there are two playgrounds in the outfield, children who are not interested in baseball play in the sand, and parents who play mats nearby enjoy family outing and baseball. In addition to chicken, a menu that is indispensable to the ballpark, the outfield seat is the best for spreading and eating food. In the summer, most of the game starts at 6:30 PM, so we eat dinner while watching the game.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Playground for kids who are not interested in baseball - Buk-gu, Gwangju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/159/48f2c2d5-749e-4c91-a820-cbc3b16aa177.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Playground for kids who are not interested in baseball
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The outfield seats are originally unpopular seats, but the Gwangju-Kia Champions Field is the preferred space for families or those who want free viewing.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Children on the outfield fence - Buk-gu, Gwangju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/159/8634a1ba-b5f5-489e-bc2a-87e82c55af05.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Children on the outfield fence
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      National Gwangju Science Museum
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Address: 235, Advanced Techno-ro, Buk-gu, Gwangju
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Contact: 062-960-6210
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.sciencecenter.or.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
      http://www.sciencecenter.or.kr/
     &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Gwangju-Kia Champions Field
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Address: 10 Seorim-ro, Buk-gu, Gwangju
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Contact: 070-7686-8000
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.tigers.co.kr/main.asp?ssl=on&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
      https://www.tigers.co.kr/main.asp?ssl=on
     &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Nearby destinations
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Gossang Play Theme Park: 2, Gossang-ro, Nam-gu / 062-374-3839
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Gwangju Museum of Art: 52 Haseo-ro, Buk-gu / 062-613-7100
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Uijae Art Museum: 155 Jeungsimsa-gil, Dong-gu / 062-222-3040
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Restaurants near
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Ilsongjeong: Hanjeongsik / 12-9 Geumnam-ro 132beon-gil, Buk-gu
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Yeongmi Oritang: Oritang / 126, Gyeongyang-ro, Buk-gu / 062-527-0248
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Seokam Stone Pot Rice: Stone Pot Rice / 8-1 Daecheon-ro 139beon-gil, Buk-gu / 062-262-2222
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Rooms
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Byeolmung Guesthouse: 8-6 Gyeongyang-ro 147beon-gil, Buk-gu / 010-7197-7228
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Sejong Hotel: 30 Gyeongyang-ro 165beon-gil, Buk-gu / 062-528-0071
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Midas Tourist Hotel: 43, Imbangul-daero 825beon-gil, Gwangsan-gu / 062-973-5000
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was updated in July 2019, and may be changed later, so please check before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Go into the past! Gwangju Yangrim-dong Penguin Village - Nam-gu, Gwangju, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/go-into-the-past-gwangju-yangrimdong-penguin-village-151/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 15:17:55 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/go-into-the-past-gwangju-yangrimdong-penguin-village-151/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Nam-gu, Gwangju, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;go-into-the-past-gwangju-yangrimdong-penguin-village--151&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Penguin garden filled with all sorts of miscellaneous things - Nam-gu, Gwangju, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/151/06249576-87cb-4389-bc52-4b63d99b595f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Penguin garden filled with all sorts of miscellaneous things
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Go into the past! Gwangju Yangrim-dong Penguin Village
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Nam-gu, Gwangju, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   2019, 2013, 1994, 1988 ... As soon as you step into the penguin village, the clock starts to turn upside down. Every step of the way I feel like I&#39;m going back to the past more and more. You don&#39;t even need a time machine here. All you need is a camera for fun photos and a hat to block sunlight. Let&#39;s go to Penguin Village in Yangrim-dong, Gwangju, a memory playground for adults.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Explore another time in time travel
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Yangrim-dong, Gwangju, Jeollanam-do, is a time machine travel destination to the past. Gwangju is a popular destination for modern history, and there is another time travel destination that evokes old memories. The penguin village is also very interesting. Although penguins do not live, there are many other eye-catching things to see. It is a place that emerges as a unique destination in time travel.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Gallery under the eaves of Penguin Village - Nam-gu, Gwangju, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/151/a0efff55-6570-4eb1-9879-70a00de5675a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Gallery under the eaves of Penguin Village
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The alleyway next to the Yangrim Community Center is a secret passageway leading to the time of the 1970s and 1980s. It is small and narrow enough to be easily overlooked, if not carefully examined. From the moment you find a penguin made of recycled gas cylinders at the entrance to the alley, the memories of the penguin town begins with a smile.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Penguin Village, with an unusually large number of watches - Nam-gu, Gwangju, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/151/3e5fa54f-e24c-4705-a493-6c27e806dbc6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Penguin Village, with an unusually large number of watches
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The old, shabby wall scenery that appeared as soon as one step into the penguin village jumped the time back a decade. The old, dark stained concrete fence is filled with all sorts of graffiti written in the old movers center advertisement, town map, and colored chalk. After a few more steps, I stop at all and burst into laughter. The amount of pan should be in the kitchen, and frying pans and colanders glisten as if they were sunbathing.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Wall with a silver pan and a frying pan - Nam-gu, Gwangju, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/151/6942fad1-4f8e-4e73-a39e-e172c62bc9f0.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Wall with a silver pan and a frying pan
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   After a fun wall exhibition, a full-fledged village tour begins. The small village garden with small flowers and trees is a resting place for residents and a great photo zone for travelers. Of course it is not an ordinary garden. A guitar and a mirror ball are hung instead of the tree fruit, and the key that turns the grain between the flower fields occupies one place.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The wall of Penguin Village is an exhibition hall of memories. - Nam-gu, Gwangju, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/151/b3d5a548-0c19-4431-a5d7-76533111d16c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The wall of Penguin Village is an exhibition hall of memories.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Why is the name Penguin Village ?!
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   At this point, we cannot help but wonder why the village name is &#39;Penguin Village&#39;. The Penguin Village contains the characteristics of this village, which has a high age among residents, including the elderly living alone. The old man&#39;s walking image resembled a penguin that was faltering and was called as an alias, and it became the name of the village. It is an affectionate nickname to make the atmosphere of a quiet village more enjoyable and energetic.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Kim Dong-gyun, the self-proclaimed penguin village chief - Nam-gu, Gwangju, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/151/2de266f6-47a3-4170-b07d-168f38d52db3.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Kim Dong-gyun, the self-proclaimed penguin village chief
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Along with the nickname, the Penguin Village began to look like it is now about 5 years ago. It started with Kim Dong-gyun, the self-proclaimed mayor of this village, decorating and decorating his hometown as a hobby with all sorts of old objects and junk stuff piled up in a vacant neighborhood. In the meantime, as the residents brought together the old objects they had and worked together to build a village, the garbage here became a great driving force for the time travel. It&#39;s all used in real life, so it makes me feel better. Perhaps this is the charm of Penguin Village. The ordinary town was reborn as a time machine travel destination, one of the hot places these days due to the &#39;conversion of ideas&#39;.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Time machine destination decorated by villagers - Nam-gu, Gwangju, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/151/fc32ee3f-981a-494c-8fc0-4befad2da5f5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Time machine destination decorated by villagers
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   An exhibition hall of memories that stops in alleys
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The old objects packed in every alley reminiscent of the exhibition halls of memories that have compressed decades of time. The pace of the steps here is proportional to the amount of memory each person has.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Faded old movie posters on the wall - Nam-gu, Gwangju, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/151/a2571408-5541-4987-938c-85e1ba967ec9.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Faded old movie posters on the wall
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   A middle-aged gentleman stops walking in front of a faded old poster and stands for a long time, and the old couple who leaned on each other for a long time reflects the years passed in front of the sculpture of the bride and groom stained with hands. The children are excited as if they have found something novel, and the young travelers have no choice but to take pictures of these alleys.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Groom statue and flower rubber shoes with traces of time - Nam-gu, Gwangju, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/151/6612cb42-fc57-4715-b682-76727a66556e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Groom statue and flower rubber shoes with traces of time
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Penguin Village is enriched on Saturdays. This is because the alleyway flea market with handmade products, snacks, and a simple henna experience is opened from the morning. Although it is small and does not open regularly, the atmosphere of the flea market in the alleys of memories is more warm and warm than anywhere else.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Penguin village souvenirs made by villagers - Nam-gu, Gwangju, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/151/e4432bf7-069c-43b9-b10f-705a16482a2c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Penguin village souvenirs made by villagers
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It&#39;s fun to play with soap bubbles of memories that you&#39;ve been struggling with when you&#39;re only going to blow alone.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Soap bubbles of memories that children and adults will enjoy - Nam-gu, Gwangju, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/151/8bba9db8-9d3c-46c6-a57e-bf162c8f032c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Soap bubbles of memories that children and adults will enjoy
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   You should also pick up some souvenirs from the Penguin Village. Another precious time is engraved on the annual rings of life with the sunshine.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Dissolve sugar and add soda! Fun and delicious talgana experience - Nam-gu, Gwangju, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/151/b8aa6644-6ccb-4ebc-b542-97853ff4dd11.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Dissolve sugar and add soda! Fun and delicious talgana experience
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Han Hee Won Museum of Art and Holly Tree Hill Guesthouse
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   A good place to visit Penguin Village is the Han Hee Won Museum. The neat and neat Hanok building at the end of the alley is impressive. It is easy to find because it is located near Choi Seung-hyo&#39;s house. Opened last year, the Han Hee Won Museum of Art is a great place to enjoy a tea and chat after a picture. You can enjoy wonderful works with the charming atmosphere of Han Hee-won, and the cafe is operated unmanned.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Han Hee Won Art Center, a neat Hanok building - Nam-gu, Gwangju, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/151/36fe9735-fe8a-4134-bf3c-7a3af43eaa6d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Han Hee Won Art Center, a neat Hanok building
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   You can spend one night in Yangrim-dong. A hollyhock hill guest house is located on the hillside of Yangrim-dong, where hollyhock trees that are more than 200 years old grow. It was a historic space built by Western missionaries in the 20th century when they founded modern schools and hospitals.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Holly oak tree hill guest house using missionary residence - Nam-gu, Gwangju, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/151/5aa3f34a-466f-4e02-ad9a-b7dce2890796.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Holly oak tree hill guest house using missionary residence
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The antique atmosphere of the 70-year-old brick building calms the mind. The fresh green color filled through the window is very beautiful.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Greenhouse guest house kitchen - Nam-gu, Gwangju, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/151/4d510e71-d214-4993-beff-eac9a143089c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Greenhouse guest house kitchen
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel info
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Gwangju Yangrim-dong Penguin Village
     &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    -7 Cheonbyeonjwa-ro 446beon-gil, Nam-gu, Gwangju
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Han Hee Won Museum
     &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    -Address: 27-6 Yangchon-gil, Nam-gu, Gwangju
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Inquiries: 062-653-5435
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Horangashi Namu Hill Guesthouse
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Address: 20 Jejung-ro 47beon-gil, Nam-gu, Gwangju
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Inquiries: 062-654-0976
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.horanggasy.kr/wpage/index.php&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.horanggasy.kr/wpage/index.php
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Restaurants near
     &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    -Geomok Hanjeongsik: Hanjeongsik / 3-6, Cheonbyeonjwa-ro 364beon-gil, Nam-gu / 062-672-0333, 0444
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Daeheung Banjeom: Chinese cuisine / 16 Hoeseo-ro 22beonna-gil, Nam-gu / 062-223-6131 ~ 2
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Hanwoo Flower: Hanwoogui / 67-2 Baekun-ro, Nam-gu, Gwangju / 062-368-9292
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Rooms
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Hotel here, Gwangju Baekun Branch: 23-1 Independence Road, Nam-gu / 062-655-7955
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Hotel Arts Center: 2, City Hall-ro 20beon-gil, Seo-gu / 062-600-9999
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Yoro: 16-17 Donggye-ro, Dong-gu / 062-227-8815
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was updated in June 2019, and may be changed later, so please check before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ The information such as text, photos and videos used in this article is copyrighted by Korea Tourism Organization, so unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The face talked, the story came out - Gwangju, Gyeonggi, South Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/the-face-talked-the-story-came-out-116/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 22:35:26 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/the-face-talked-the-story-came-out-116/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Gwangju, Gyeonggi, South Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;the-face-talked-the-story-came-out--116&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Portraits of Japanese Military Comfort Women Victims - Gwangju, Gyeonggi, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/116/a7e06964-5175-430a-b214-a7711aa82a6a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Portraits of Japanese Military Comfort Women Victims
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   The face talked, the story came out
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Gwangju, Gyeonggi, South Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The grandmothers of the Japanese comfort women history have nothing to say. Tell the past years with your face. The grandmothers in the paintings are deeply stacked with sad stories in fan folds. There are about 1000 faces on the face of the museum. Some faces seem to want something, while others seem to realize the uselessness of emotions over time. Seeds of time and woven faces of stories. He visits Gwangju, Gyeonggi-do to listen to the myriad faces.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   The tears on her face have wrinkles
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The fluffy white girls of the 1930s became gray-haired grandmothers in 2019. It has been 80 years since the victims of the Japanese comfort women. Of the 238 grandmothers who were registered with the government, only 22 survived. Their average age is in their 90s. There may not be much time left. We need a place where we can better remember our grandmothers. So good news. The Japanese military comfort women&#39;s museum in Gwangju, Gyeonggi-do was newly expanded.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   “We must leave in history the work we did not overcome.” It was first opened in 1998 on the back of Grandmother Kim Hak-soon, the first to testify to the damage of the Japanese military &#39;comfort women&#39;. Since then, in late 2017, a relic exhibition hall and memorial archives have been established. It is a memorial to the back of the sharing house, passing through the entrance where the girl&#39;s flower, which is a symbol of victims of the Japanese military &#39;comfort women&#39;, and the bust of grandmothers. It is a two storey building with tiled walls. The memorial building on the first floor is divided into three parts. There are grandmothers portraits in the exhibition hall, the relics of the grandmothers in the relics exhibition hall, and about 20 paintings painted by grandmothers in the paintings exhibition hall.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Grandmother bust of `` comfort women &#39;&#39; at the entrance of Japanese comfort women history museum - Gwangju, Gyeonggi, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/116/2516da00-b15e-427c-93f3-63a5cfc984a4.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Grandmother bust of `` comfort women &#39;&#39; at the entrance of Japanese comfort women history museum
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   There are 10 paintings side by side that are more than 1 meter wide. It is a picture of grandmothers by performing artist Poppin Hyun-joon. He said. &#34;I painted it again with the hope that my grandmother&#39;s face would not be forgotten.&#34; Every grandmother has a different look and mood. Grandmother Park Ok-ryon of the white hair shut firmly on the date of her mouth, and Bae Choon-hee raised her mouth as if smiling. Kim Gunja grandma soon said, &#34;Did you eat?&#34; It&#39;s playful eyes like I&#39;m talking. Instead of opening up their mouths to explain themselves, grandmothers spend much of their lives with expressions of lines and colors. The girl&#39;s tears dried up and became her grandmother&#39;s wrinkles. The grandmothers in the painting closed their eyes without receiving official Japanese apology.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Portraits by Grandmother Poppin Hyun Joon - Gwangju, Gyeonggi, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/116/f690d635-3432-4580-9aa7-5e40b6e25a88.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Portraits by Grandmother Poppin Hyun Joon
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Older girls talked and painted
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &#34;I don&#39;t know why things are so vivid, even if I can&#39;t remember what&#39;s near.&#34;
   &lt;br/&gt;
   Kim Soon-deok says. In the exhibition hall, there are seventeen grandmothers&#39; life histories, photographs, and items they used during their lifetime. &#39;Live a life together&#39; is the title of the exhibition. It was a life where there was something more lonely than something pleasant, something more than something to remember.
   &lt;br/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Exhibition of exhibits - Gwangju, Gyeonggi, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/116/14e787b9-5b54-45dd-ba58-ef0f4a221613.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Exhibition of exhibits
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &#34;All of my friends are dead and I&#39;m just living back.&#34;
   &lt;br/&gt;
   11 years old, the youngest of the &#34;comfort women&#34; registered with the government. Grandma Kim returned home alone from Hokkaido, Japan. Kim Ok-joo was deceived by a Japanese landlord saying she had a job. The arrival was a comfort station in Hainan Island, China. Each story is long and long to abbreviate in just a few lines.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Relics Exhibition Hall - Gwangju, Gyeonggi, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/116/5fe48300-e034-4b44-99a6-47d7c9248f44.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Relics Exhibition Hall
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The things you used in your life are so simple. Magnifying glass, Hwatu, Hangul textbooks, passports that would hold &#39;Dandy&#39; in hand . I was crying and angry, and I was slowing down as I calmed my heart.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Grandma&#39;s Rustic Keepsakes - Gwangju, Gyeonggi, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/116/1c1c8a53-08d4-468d-8f7c-732b65019f63.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Grandma&#39;s Rustic Keepsakes
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   There is still music in the picture exhibition. Seochon Alley, it seems that you entered a small gallery. Grandmothers have been painting since 1993. At first, I was drawing along things around me, but as time passed, I began to express the past.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A picture exhibition featuring over 20 paintings painted by grandmothers - Gwangju, Gyeonggi, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/116/3edb3da8-e174-4710-909f-42e272d8055f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A picture exhibition featuring over 20 paintings painted by grandmothers
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Maybe fifteen? A girl in a white jacket is drawn to someone&#39;s arm. The wild flowers that bloomed in her homeland were so beautiful that she could not hear the girl&#39;s cry. Kim Soon-deok&#39;s &amp;lt;Attracting&amp;gt; vividly depicts the moment she was taken to the comfort woman.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Grandmother Kim Soon-duk&#39;s Work - Gwangju, Gyeonggi, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/116/55e9f81e-0926-4b31-8b83-fddd16ebdbbd.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Grandmother Kim Soon-duk&#39;s Work
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Most of the girls in the paintings cover their faces with their hands, their eyes closed, or they have no expression.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;13&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Grandmother Kang Deok-gyeong&#39;s work - Gwangju, Gyeonggi, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/116/5477ba55-5205-4f27-b7d0-bf36b02ac27b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Grandmother Kang Deok-gyeong&#39;s work
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Yes. The only thing a girl could do in front of the Japanese soldiers waiting in line and waiting for one person to lie down.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;15&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Kang, Deok-Kyung&#39;s work &amp;lt;Penant Officer&amp;gt; - Gwangju, Gyeonggi, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/116/30d3acf7-dc62-4e55-aecc-f75919eb0c7e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Kang, Deok-Kyung&#39;s work &amp;lt;Penant Officer&amp;gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    In the memorial hall, you can see the hand-printing of the victims, photos of 105 victims of domestic and foreign “comfort women” and a list of 280. It is the face of courageous accusers of Japanese war crimes. If you want to know more about the history of the Japanese military &#39;comfort women&#39;, you should also look around the existing history. The background of the establishment of the comfort women system, a record of activities on finding out facts, and a map showing the location of the Japanese military comfort station are arranged in detail. In the third exhibition space, there is a comfort station model with reference to victim testimony. The side room is 5 ~ 7㎡. I was upset at the moment, but I put up with it. Don&#39;t lose your composure and vow to see the historical truth.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Don&#39;t turn around. Don&#39;t forget to not forget even in the midst of your busy life. Face the pain of your current grandmother. The grandmothers in the painting are handing over.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;17&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Photos and lists of domestic and foreign victims of comfort women - Gwangju, Gyeonggi, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/116/0d82ad7d-06a3-4f08-a3af-b23cb2f00865.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Photos and lists of domestic and foreign victims of comfort women
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Huge archive of faces
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   With a deep tingling feeling, he heads to the museum face to meet more diverse faces. Should it be like a junk or a loft that gathered all kinds of miscellaneous secrets? This is the first impression of the museum&#39;s face in Namjong-myeon, Gwangju, Gyeonggi-do. This museum is the first time. The exhibits are not organized by age or have friendly explanations. Faces sway across the times and regions. There is a picture of actor Audrey Hepburn next to the shamanism and James Dean next to the Buddha. The museum&#39;s face exhibits more than 1,000 facial sculptures, from photographs, paintings and portraits to masks, puppet and stone statues. It&#39;s a huge archive of faces. It has been collected by senior theater director Kim Jong-ok for over 50 years.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Inside view of museum face - Gwangju, Gyeonggi, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/116/25a47c8c-bc8f-4204-8890-82a3d8d16c78.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Inside view of museum face
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The center of the first floor is empty. It&#39;s like a theater stage. It is the architectural intention of the director who thinks that the works of the museum are actors on the stage and wants to make a festival ground with the old people. There are colorful masks on the left wall and pictures of theatricians on the right wall. Traditional masks have a slightly different look just by the eye. Eyes that are raised uphill are biting impressions, and eyes that are gentle like downhill are sullen. Stone Buddha has nothing but a peaceful face. Actor James Dean is keen on something.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Various face sculptures including masks, sculptures - Gwangju, Gyeonggi, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/116/439b4165-8138-44f8-b92d-3f4c2dc0dd4e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Various face sculptures including masks, sculptures
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Unlike the first floor, which is a mix of East and West works, the second floor is rich in oriental colors. The exhibition focuses on bonuses and marionettes, especially the various marionettes.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Kiln to carry dead body to grave at traditional funeral, bonus - Gwangju, Gyeonggi, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/116/c1567aef-a491-4825-ae4b-9570992a0c73.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Kiln to carry dead body to grave at traditional funeral, bonus
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The puppet was decorated with bonuses at traditional funerals. A friend of the road that sees the souls of the dead. There is no saddening puppet. He is dressed in colorful clothes and smiles. &#39;Let me forget all the hardships of my life and have a good memory.&#39; I pray for the paradise birth of the deceased.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Cheerful expression of puppet to accompany dead man&#39;s journey - Gwangju, Gyeonggi, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/116/7f0614b6-f448-4b72-a82b-20426874dd81.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Cheerful expression of puppet to accompany dead man&#39;s journey
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   “Don&#39;t frown, everything will be washed away”
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The highlight of the museum&#39;s face is the stone gardeners in the outdoor garden. A stone man is a stone in the form of a man who was built at the entrance of a tomb or village. Jangseung acted as the patron saint of the village, and the gates and copper seats in front of the tombs honor the dead.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;15&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Stonemason in the outdoor garden - Gwangju, Gyeonggi, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/116/2af61de9-aa0d-4430-8d2e-157b0575fb34.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Stonemason in the outdoor garden
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   There is no one person like Seok-in brought from each province such as Jinju-si, Gyeongnam-do, Jindo-gun, Jeonnam, and Jeju-do. Some have a serene look, while others have round eyes. It usually wears off over time and winds down, making it hard to see. What did the mason look like when he pricked stones and breathed freshly? Imagine a face hundreds of years ago. An open mouthed stoner speaks. “Don&#39;t frown like that. Don&#39;t be so happy. Then everything is washed away. ” It is comfort that only those who endure for hundreds of years can do. Those who have passed through these long and long years teach without change.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;16&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Tianjin Innocent Face - Gwangju, Gyeonggi, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/116/ac2ddeac-0a54-410f-b24d-9d5f75caaf35.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Tianjin Innocent Face
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   When you enter the face of the museum, you may be confused about what to look for. The viewing method is simple. Keep an eye out for the disordered objects, and then look at them when you see a catchy face. Soon silence will be broken. A museum with thousands of faces is full of quiet turmoil.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   There are many faces in Gwangju, Gyeonggi-do. Look carefully. To hear beyond what he does not say. So we dare to understand others. If &#39;expansion of awareness&#39; is called travel, Gwangju is a good destination.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;17&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Stoneman showing the passage of time - Gwangju, Gyeonggi, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/116/45ec404d-0cd6-4b94-84e0-0d4668bae84d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Stoneman showing the passage of time
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel info
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Japanese comfort women history museum
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Address: 85, Gaesaegol-gil, Tochonchon-myeon, Gwangju-si, Gyeonggi-do
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Inquiries: 031-768-0064
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Hours: 10: 00 ~ 17: 00
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Day off: Mondays and national holidays
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Admission Fee: Adult 5,000 won, Student 3000 won
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Museum face
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Address: 3-6, Bunwon-gil, Namjong-myeon, Gwangju-si, Gyeonggi-do
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Contact: 031-765-3522
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Hours: Wednesday-Sunday 10:00-18:00 (Closed at 17:30)
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Day off: Mon, Tue
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Admission Fee: Adults 4,000 won, Students 3,000 won
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.visagej.org/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.visagej.org/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Restaurants near
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Gang Village Squirrel: Acorn Mukbab, Acorn Mulguksu / 556, Taehejeong-ro, Namjong-myeon, Gwangju-si, Gyeonggi-do / 031-762-5574
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Soeumgi: Cheonggukjang Jeongsik / 580-3, Jeongyoung-ro, Toegchon-myeon, Gwangju-si, Gyeonggi-do / 031-767-9852
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Lato Mate: Odeok Pizza, Pasta / 941-9, Jeongyoung-ro, Tochonchon-myeon, Gwangju
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Rooms
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Jeongon Pension: 38, Galol-gil 11beon-gil, Toegchon-myeon, Gwangju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea / 031-768-3917
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://jo-pension.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://jo-pension.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Dreaming House Pension: 934, Tianjinam-ro, Toegchon-myeon, Gwangju-si, Gyeonggi-do / 031-769-1278
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.드리밍하우스.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.드리밍하우스.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    J.Aland: 15-6, Dokgogae-gil 302beon-gil, Docheok-myeon, Gwangju-si, Gyeonggi-do / 031-797-3330
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.jrland.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.jrland.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was updated in March 2019 and may change afterwards, so please check before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ The information such as text, photos and videos used in this article is copyrighted by Korea Tourism Organization, so unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Travel Card] Weaving factory women&#39;s home, transformed into a culture and art village where stars rise! Gwangju Balsan Creative Culture Village - Seo-gu, Gwangju, South Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/travel-card-weaving-factory-womens-home-transformed-into-a-culture-and-art-village-where-stars-rise-gwangju-balsan-creative-culture-village-102/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 21:39:01 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/travel-card-weaving-factory-womens-home-transformed-into-a-culture-and-art-village-where-stars-rise-gwangju-balsan-creative-culture-village-102/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Seo-gu, Gwangju, South Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;travel-card-weaving-factory-womens-home-transformed-into-a-culture-and-art-village-where-stars-rise-gwangju-balsan-creative-culture-village--102&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34; - Seo-gu, Gwangju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/102/9513e8a4-cdcb-4caf-8c91-321c60b36fd8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   [Travel Card] Weaving factory women&#39;s home, transformed into a culture and art village where stars rise! Gwangju Balsan Creative Culture Village
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Seo-gu, Gwangju, South Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34; - Seo-gu, Gwangju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/102/820c0cc9-bf95-40a1-b7e5-0916b813d676.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34; - Seo-gu, Gwangju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/102/d807172b-1151-4c51-95fb-4a2810ca1820.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34; - Seo-gu, Gwangju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/102/58c26ccb-42fb-47f4-8dca-072ad83f6bb6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34; - Seo-gu, Gwangju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/102/86f399cf-1579-47bc-a7a0-d28d890085fd.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34; - Seo-gu, Gwangju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/102/ab14895e-c5d6-4fdc-b5b5-383fb16d615d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;14&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34; - Seo-gu, Gwangju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/102/bb600fe9-13fb-4407-9450-b4da6997f674.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;17&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34; - Seo-gu, Gwangju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/102/f061f3aa-e41a-4e2b-9f8a-1c5dd645a0bc.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;19&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34; - Seo-gu, Gwangju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/102/c1331fe6-0140-4e0b-b159-49c0a3ecead9.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;20&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34; - Seo-gu, Gwangju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/102/8cdbaf5a-a0ab-4fa2-9545-5c354b27ddd2.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;
    &lt;span style=&#34;font-weight: bold;&#34;&gt;
     Gwangju Balsan Creative Culture Village
    &lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://balsanvillage.com/kr/index.php&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://balsanvillage.com/kr/index.php
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;div style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was updated in January 2019 and may change afterwards. Please check before traveling.
    &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;
     ※ The information such as text, photos and videos used in this article is copyrighted by Korea Tourism Organization, so unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, South Korea - Honam Line KTX to Naduya, Gwangju Mining Area</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/honam-line-ktx-to-naduya-gwangju-mining-area-42/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 20:44:16 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/honam-line-ktx-to-naduya-gwangju-mining-area-42/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-title=&#34;honam-line-ktx-to-naduya-gwangju-mining-area--42&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Gwangju Songjeong Station - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/acf39ebe-6300-4c75-b577-2546cf4ee2a3.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Gwangju Songjeong Station
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Honam Line KTX to Naduya, Gwangju Mining Area
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, South Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The Honam Line KTX Express section has been extended to Gwangju Songjeong Station in Gwangju. KTX, which departed from Yongsan Station, arrived at Gwangju Songjeong Station in 1 hour 33 minutes, and it was possible to go out to Gwangju by taking a day trip in the metropolitan area. In the vicinity of Gwangju Songjeong Station, there are attractions such as Yonga Birthplace, Wolbong Seowon, Wolgye-dong Janggobun, Songjeong Park, and Sinchang-dong ruins.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Convenient for traveling by subway or city in front of Gwangju Songjeong Station
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Before the West Coast Highway was completed in 2001, it was convenient for tourists in the metropolitan area to use the Honam Highway Mine Tollgate to travel to Honam provinces such as Mokpo, Yeongam, and Naju. Since then, the emergence of the Gochang-Damyang Expressway followed the emergence of the West Coast Expressway, making the name “mining” faint in tourists&#39; heads. Then, with the recent opening of the Honam Line KTX, the mining district with Gwangju Songjeong Station was revived as a hot topic. Local residents expect that the number of visitors to Gwangju Songjeong Station will increase from 4,000 on average to 12,000.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;KTX at Gwangju Songjeong Station - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/a8d01ab7-1597-41ac-9729-c41f541ee3be.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     KTX at Gwangju Songjeong Station
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The name &#39;Gwangsan-gu&#39; was born in 1988 when Songjeong and Mining County were incorporated into Gwangju. Of the five districts that make up Gwangju, the area occupies 222.9㎢ (44.05%), the largest. There is a subway station with the same name right in front of the new station of Gwangju Songjeong Station. The subway in Gwangju runs between Okdong Station, Gwangju Songjeong Station, Gwangju Airport, Kimdaejung Convention Center, Geumnam-ro, Culture Hall, Hakdong and Jeungsimsa Entrance, and Yongsan Vehicle Station. Foreign travelers can take the Honam Line KTX and get off at Gwangju Songjeong Station and transfer to the subway for easy transportation around Gwangju.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Mugunghwa Lake stops at Gwangju Songjeong Station - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/8e923e82-af6f-4390-b796-dc64894bc9dc.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Mugunghwa Lake stops at Gwangju Songjeong Station
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Yong-A Park Enjoys Literary Journey at Birthplace
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   One of the most popular tourist attractions near Gwangju Songjeong Station in Gwangsan-gu is Yonga birthplace. &#39;Yong-ah&#39; is a child of Park Yong-cheol (1904 ~ 1938) who worked as a poet during the Japanese occupation. Born in Gwangsan-gu, he worked with Young-Rang Kim and Jung Ji-yong to publish Literary Literature. The poet published his leading works, Leaving Boats and Sending You in the Night Train, in The First of Poetry Literature. Here&#39;s a look at his poem Leaving Ship. The specialty is engraved on the granite fertilization of the flower bed of the dragon child.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     I&#39;m gonna go / my young age /
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     Are you going to send tears?
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Are these cozy harborers going to be easy?
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     Even the watery eyes like the fog
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Ripe beak shape on each foot of the valley /
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     Wrinkles also ripe eyes! Loved ones //
     &lt;br/&gt;
     I can&#39;t forget the one who throws it away /
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     What&#39;s different about being chased?
     &lt;br/&gt;
     The clouds look back, the wind is white /
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     Will there be hill climbers in front of us //
     &lt;br/&gt;
     I&#39;m so pretty / my young age /
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     Will you let go with tears?
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Fertilization set in the dragon birthplace - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/ddb73935-d6cc-4c49-864e-add053f35644.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Fertilization set in the dragon birthplace
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It is probably because of the song of singer Kim Soo-chul that this poem comes close to us. Kim Soo-cheol quotes a part of the poet Park Yong-chul&#39;s poems in the song &amp;lt;Go To Me Too&amp;gt;. The desire to leave younger ages with tears and to find a dream was the independence of the country for the poet Park Yong-chul, and for the singer Kim Soo-chul. Even though the direction is different according to the times, the value is still so many people love their words and lyrics.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Portrait of poets guarding the yard - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/75ab670b-5ac5-47c2-993a-f500d165eb45.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Portrait of poets guarding the yard
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Unspoken conversations with poets
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Let&#39;s follow Yonga Park&#39;s literary life a little longer. He also published Literary Monthly and Literature, and translated and introduced foreign poems and plays. He also worked as a literary critic, but unfortunately he died in his mid-30s. The cause of death was tuberculosis. In addition to his birthplace, his fertilization, which engraves Leaving Boat, is also set up on the slope of Yangji, which leads to Songjeong Park.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   The poet&#39;s birthplace is surrounded by stone walls cleared with ocher. It is a thatched house with a wide yard, flower bed, and jangdokdae. Perhaps because of his literary activities with Jung Ji-yong and Kim Young-rang, looking at every corner of his birthplace naturally reminds him of poems such as &amp;lt;Perfume&amp;gt; and Kim Young-rang&#39;s &amp;lt;Sunshine on a Stone Wall&amp;gt;.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Another thing that catches your eye is the large paintbrush that painted the faces of six poets. It was used in the Yonga Literary Festival in 2014, and there is even a paint board in the yard, so it is less lively. Poetry poets such as Kim Yun-sik, Jung In-bo, Byun Young-ro, Jung Yong-yong, Park Yong-cheol, and Lee Ha-yun bloomed like flower wine. Their footprints can also be found in the Museum of Literature and Literature (opened in 2012) in Gangjin-eup, Gangjin-gun. Kang Jin is the birthplace of Kim Young Rang. Leaving Yong-Ah&#39;s birthplace, I recall Park Yong-chul&#39;s other representative film, Sending You to the Night Train.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Thatched house - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/17fcbc08-8b03-47ee-9313-e72b7ea6ccbf.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Thatched house
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     Now, in the distant winter, spring day
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     I&#39;ll look at it.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Laughing like a spring day, he rushes his train
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     I&#39;ll wait.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     “Forget” Meaners Laugh like this /
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     Let me learn
     &lt;br/&gt;
     While walking through the rough road,
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     Let&#39;s follow the example.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     At last he will be a follower.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Poet&#39;s face as seen from Songjeong Park fertilization - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/6793ad6d-7d7d-4a0d-a54c-f922b0bddfda.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Poet&#39;s face as seen from Songjeong Park fertilization
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Learned from Wolbongseowon, the high peak
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The footsteps of travelers who enjoyed literary journeys lead to exploration of their vows. Wolbongseowon, located in Gwangsan-gu, Gwangsan-gu, is quite old-fashioned from the way from the parking lot to the entrance of Seowon. This is because a low dirt wall, neatly tiled, passes through a village road. Wolbongseowon was founded in 1578, after the death of the teacher. It is now considered one of the eight scenes of Gwangju.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Gobong is famous as a scholar who exchanged the theory with Toegye Lee Hwang. The main auditorium of Seowon is called Bingwoldang. Chungjo bought Gobong&#39;s noble school virtues and gave the title of ‘Bingsim Snowwall’. The kindly reading of the jury with the Korean translation kindly adds to the enjoyment of the vow. The book begins with ‘Get a book and find a teacher and rise to a high hermit, &#39;and ends the middle section with‘ What will be lamented later divided into dragons and pigs? ’. &#39;Strive today&#39; contains lessons.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   “The foundation of the state is to make the people at ease. Only after the people are comfortable can enlightenment be made. It must be taught after the people have been strengthened first, and the people have been made rich. ”
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Wolbongseowon View - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/db196ed4-3eac-4115-b420-18d04fcf5c49.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Wolbongseowon View
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you have plenty of time, let&#39;s walk the path of philosophers. This is a walking course from Wolbong Seowon to Baekwoojeong, Kyujeonam Ruins, Gobong Mausoleum and Khufujae.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The amount of Bingwoldang, the main lecture hall of Wolbong Seowon - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/0ec9602f-f344-483a-acce-20a9d9212d73.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The amount of Bingwoldang, the main lecture hall of Wolbong Seowon
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Ruins in downtown, Sinchang-dong ruins and Wolgye-dong Janggobun
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   After exploring the poet&#39;s birthplace and vows, he visits cultural remains that are not well known to foreign tourists, even though they are in the city center. Sinchang-dong ruins and Janggobun of Wolgye-dong are located near the Honam Expressway Mine Interchange.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Sinchang-dong ruins (Historic No. 375) may be disappointed because it is a field with no streets and no museums. However, according to the description of the Gwangju National Museum, there are many relics such as earthenware, wood, keel, and lacquerware that give a glimpse of the agricultural culture of the first century BC. Imagine the days when there would be no driveways or apartment complexes, and you can imagine that people were a very good place to live in groups. In particular, Shin Chang-dong was nicknamed the &#39;Ancient Textile Factory&#39; in that the oldest silk and burlap relics in Korea, bodies, thread bobbins and bone needles needed to produce these fabrics were excavated. In the main hall on the first floor of the Gwangju National Museum, a special exhibition will be held until May 25, &#39;The Silk Country, Textile Culture of Sinchang-dong, Gwangju&#39;.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;5&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sinchang-dong Historic Site - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/4e0190e6-2f28-430d-a7a6-8cae29027cf7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sinchang-dong Historic Site
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Janggobun, Wolgye-dong (Gwangju Metropolitan City Local Monument No. 20) is named after the tomb shape. It was discovered during the construction of Gwangju Advanced Science Park in the 1990s and is believed to have been built in the 5 ~ 6th centuries. A shopping mall and an apartment complex are built around the tomb and it is a cultural heritage that is loved as a place for citizens to stroll.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;5&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Wolgye-dong Janggobun - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/4839be3a-141d-484f-89f6-6cea258f06a3.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Wolgye-dong Janggobun
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Finish your trip with Tteokgalbi, Naksamtang, and Sundae Gukbap
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Go back to Gwangju Songjeong Station to taste the specialties of the mine. Tteokgalbi street was formed around Gwangsan-gu Office a long time ago, attracting travelers&#39; tastes. If the smell of baking tteokgalbi fills the alley, no matter how greedy, you can&#39;t help but relax. Nowadays, Japanese and Chinese tourists also come to hear the rumors. Songjeongri Tteokgalbi tastes slightly different from house to house, so you don&#39;t have to recommend a house.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;6&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Songjeong-ri Tteokgalbi - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/12f8958a-72eb-48ff-bf36-d845ebd7adb8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Songjeong-ri Tteokgalbi
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Naksamtang is also a delicacy in Gwangju. Boiled mung bean porridge with bone bone broth, put ginseng, chestnuts and jujube in it, and then add one to the octopus. Usamtang is a style of boiled boiled egg instead of octopus.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;6&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Naksamtang - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/8d5fd99c-b6c5-4184-a7f7-6eb398302745.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Naksamtang
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   There are five or six sundae soup restaurants at the beginning of the mine, opposite the entrance to the Songjeong station.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;6&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Songjeong station street market - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/e219acf6-393b-4493-8246-41ff3b59c163.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Songjeong station street market
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In addition to Sundae Gukbap, head soup, Naejang Gukbap, Seonji Gukbap, and Ampoon Sundae make the stomachs of lighter travelers lighter.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;6&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sundae Gukbap - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/58f2aec1-160e-4487-a499-f37b4c1ad57e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sundae Gukbap
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;7&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;15&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Wasabi on the market - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/f1b982b8-478e-4d38-9086-64a8c830ecf5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Wasabi on the market
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel info
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Dragon Baby
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Address: 24 Sochon-ro 46beon-gil, Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Inquiries: Mine Culture Office, Sports Division 062-960-8251
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Wolbong Seowon
      &lt;br/&gt;
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     Address: 133 Gwanggok-gil, Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Contact: 062-432-1318
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.wolbong.org/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
      http://www.wolbong.org/
     &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Nearby restaurants
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Jangan Octopus: Naksamtang / 5, Gwangsan-ro 30beon-gil / Gwangsan-gu / 062-942-4545
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Songjeong Tteokgalbi (1st Branch): Tteokgalbi / 1, Gwangsan-ro 29beon-gil, Gwangsan-gu / 062-944-1439
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Jangsu Gukbap: Sundae Gukbap / 1-1, Mine-ro, Gwangsan-gu / 062-945-8533
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Accommodation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Santamo Tourist Hotel: 10-11, Saam-ro 216beon-gil, Gwangsan-gu / 062-956-5000
    &lt;br/&gt;
    e-Motel: 13-12, Mujin-daero 231beon-gil, Gwangsan-gu / 062-430-5707
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Luxury Motel: 13-20, Mujin-daero 212beon-gil, Gwangsan-gu / 062-714-2110
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was made in February 2015. It may change afterwards, so please check before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ The information such as text, photos and videos used in this article is copyrighted by Korea Tourism Organization, so unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>