<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mokpo-si on Every Corner of Korea</title>
    <link>https://codecorea.github.io/tags/mokpo-si/</link>
    <description>Every Corner of Korea (Mokpo-si)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 00:56:11 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="https://codecorea.github.io/tags/mokpo-si/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A gourmet trip to find the taste of Mokpo, taste the 5 tastes of Mokpo - Mokpo-si, Jeollanam-do, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/a-gourmet-trip-to-find-the-taste-of-mokpo-taste-the-5-tastes-of-mokpo-332/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 00:56:11 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/a-gourmet-trip-to-find-the-taste-of-mokpo-taste-the-5-tastes-of-mokpo-332/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Mokpo-si, Jeollanam-do, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;a-gourmet-trip-to-find-the-taste-of-mokpo-taste-the-5-tastes-of-mokpo--332&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Indongju Village&#39;s Blue Crab Dressing Ceremony - Mokpo-si, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/332/f439a94d-7e27-4846-9bf0-585ee148fab7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Indongju Village&#39;s Blue Crab Dressing Ceremony
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   A gourmet trip to find the taste of Mokpo, taste the 5 tastes of Mokpo
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Mokpo-si, Jeollanam-do, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Mokpo is a historic port city and sea city that is more than 110 years old. As it is the home of the sea, it is also a place overflowing with various seafood from the Dadohae and Chajin tidal flats on the southwest coast. Three feet octopus, red tart samhap, blue crab seasoning and blue crab seasoning, miner sashimi and braised scallion are the &#39;5 beauty&#39; proud of Mokpo. How about enjoying a gourmet trip with Mokpo 5mi?
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Hongeo Samhap and Soy Sauce Crab and Indongju Enjoyed in Indongju Village
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    It is the redfish that Jeollado should never miss. It is a precious food that must be served to the guests, as there is a saying that if there is no redfish on the feast, there is a saying that you will kick back and return. Redfish are caught during all seasons except June, which is a taboo season, but I still hit redfish the best from winter to early spring when the spawning season takes place.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Speaking of a typical dish made in Hongeo, there is no doubt that it is Hongeo Samhap. It is a dish of sliced cutlet, boiled pork, and old paper in proper size. There are many people who are reluctant to eat three things together because of the strong scent produced by the fermentation of redfish, but the fresh scent of redfish, the lightness of pork, and the freshness of old paper harmoniously blend in the mouth. If makgeolli goes well, it becomes red tart samhap.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Indongju Village, located in Okam-dong, is a place where you can taste crab crabs along with redfish samhap. There are many signboards at the entrance to the restaurant, such as Jeonnam Sinjisikin, Namdo Food Street, and Mokpo Food Master&#39;s House. Indongju Village is a place to make food and make alcohol using Indongcho. Indongcho is a name given to endure cold and long winter with green leaves. Also called gold silver coin or honeysuckle. The tannins in the leaves make the stomach strong, effective against colds, and the leaves and stems are said to be effective in removing inflammation and poison.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Redfish Samhap - Mokpo-si, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/332/fa330ad5-76c3-42d7-880a-1dff219d8357.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Redfish Samhap
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In the crab crab, indongcho flowers are added to remove the fishy taste of the crab and to improve the taste. Ginger, radish, garlic, etc. are used without water to control the salty taste of the soy sauce. Indong Chomakgeolli and Pyeonghwaju are both long-lasting and fragrant. If you order blue crab baekban (for 4 people), you will get a generous prize with a combination of blue crab and scallions. In the spring, the redfish patriotic comes up as a delicacy, so if you want to taste the redfish properly, you should stop by before the spring.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Blue crab made with Indongcho - Mokpo-si, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/332/8a1d6370-6990-4253-9bac-58a1b3e0fe4b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Blue crab made with Indongcho
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you stopped by Indongju Village, there is something you cannot miss. That&#39;s Indongju. Indongju Village uses Indongcho to make Indongcho Makgeolli and Indongcho Peace. It is made by fermenting with yeast and non-glutinous rice for about 10 days, and then adding indongcho flowers and stems fermented for more than a year to mature for another 5 days. If you take Hongeo Samhap and Indong Chomak, literally, the true Hongtak Samhap is completed.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   * Indongju Village: 5, Boksan-gil 12beon-gil, Mokpo-si 061-284-4068
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Friendship team is stirring indong chomakgeolli - Mokpo-si, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/332/a02c7ac0-a78a-42d7-8c46-2860ea18b2a6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Friendship team is stirring indong chomakgeolli
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Rare fish, a rare fish that has nothing to throw away
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Miner is a fish from June to September. It is said to be synonymous with summer nourishment, not to be replaced with an island of rice. It was a fish that the people enjoyed since ancient times as it was listed as “miner” in “Sejong Sillok Geography” and “Sung Jeung Dongguk Yeojiram”. But now, it is not only expensive for the people to taste, but it is also a precious fish that can be tasted only when you go to the mountains. Previously, it could be seen in most parts of the west coast, but now it is mostly caught near the southwest coast of Gwangju, south of Yeongnam.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Fish is a fish that has nothing to throw away. Meat is eaten in the circuit, and bones and hair are good ingredients for Maeuntang. The part that can&#39;t be overlooked even in the language is the beret. If there is a child in the skate, there is a bure in the language. It is said that when fishermen begin to make noise, it is so noisy that beach fishermen can&#39;t sleep.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The auction of the freshwater fish I met at Yeongseongpo, Yeonggwang - Mokpo-si, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/332/0ea45637-8e0d-4d94-8ba9-33762f470154.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The auction of the freshwater fish I met at Yeongseongpo, Yeonggwang
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Hersado, located in Okam-dong, is the place where you can enjoy a set meal and a set meal. You can enjoy not only the fishermen&#39;s association and fishermen&#39;s exhibition, but also fishermen&#39;s bream.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Hersado&#39;s minced fish - Mokpo-si, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/332/74daa6d7-e208-4a83-8001-8850d84d03c1.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Hersado&#39;s minced fish
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It&#39;s not in season, so I can&#39;t easily taste it now. The day I tasted the freshwater fish was a precious freshwater fish that had been airlifted to the map of Yeongmyeon-myeon. It is not a chewy texture like flounder or gruel, but the bitterness and umami that come out as you chew is the best. The broiler broth seems to be a bit chewy, but the bitterness that spreads in the mouth after chewing for a long time can be said to be the white rice of the broiler.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Your precious rare fish society - Mokpo-si, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/332/e6c4c663-db4e-47ab-a075-8df173a3340e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Your precious rare fish society
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It is not in season now, but in the coming June, when the fishermen who have spawned start to cry out in the sea, they will head to Mokpo to taste the fishermen.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   * Hersado: 112, Pyeonghwa-ro, Mokpo-si 061-285-4888
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Freshwater fish - Mokpo-si, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/332/e6089677-b58c-4be8-af94-eb64800cfee0.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Freshwater fish
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Yeonpotang and brown stew, which decorate the beauty of Mokpo 5
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Tidal flats on the southwest coast of Jeollanam-do are chajin tidal flats where many living creatures lean. Octopus, which contains a lot of taurine and is called ‘Ginseng in the tidal flat’, also grows in this cold tidal flat. The three-footed octopus, which is named because its feet are thin like a new leg, is found in Mokpo and Muan.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    There is nothing to follow nutrition or taste like octopus. In particular, the autumn octopus bends the chopsticks, and the cow lying down makes it happen. There are more than 10 kinds of octopus dishes, including Yeonpotang, Galnaktang, Stir-fried octopus, Octopus horn, and octopus vinegar. Among them, Yeonpo-tang is the white rice of octopus.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The appearance of putting the octopus in the Yeonpotang - Mokpo-si, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/332/36bb6fe8-d10c-4070-8d9a-60cc57230171.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The appearance of putting the octopus in the Yeonpotang
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The Indian Ocean, located in Ongeum-dong, is well known for its excellent Yeonpotang. Octopus dishes can be easily eaten anywhere in the country, but octopus tasted in mountain regions has excellent freshness. This is because it is brought directly from the top of Mokpo Suhyup. It is said that octopus dishes have a lot of seasoning, and the taste of octopus unique to it is reduced. So there is no special secret. After boiling boiled Chinese medicine, such as jujube, ginkgo, and hwanggi, put the medium-sized live abalone and simmered red octopus. To enjoy Yeonpo-tang properly, you need to properly boil the octopus in the broth. This is because if you cook it too much, it will become tough and the taste of octopus will fall.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;strong&gt;
    * Indian Ocean:
   &lt;/strong&gt;
   47, Haean-ro, Mokpo-si, 061-243-0777
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A little cooked octopus - Mokpo-si, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/332/613f8e72-9a40-4a4c-800d-d6922c92822b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A little cooked octopus
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Mokpo&#39;s Galchi cuisine uses Mokpo lotus root seafood. Heuksan and Chuja are also mainly caught in the vicinity. Galchi is often divided into Eungalchi and Mulgalchi, and is called Jeju Eungalchi and Mokpo. However, the difference between silverfish and blackfish is the difference between fishing or netting. It is said to be silverfish when caught by fishing, or eaten when caught by the net. So, the difference in taste of brownfish will be quite different. Let&#39;s leave the subtle differences in taste to gourmets. It is said that these days, galchi is more expensive than &#39;gold galchi&#39;, so it is called &#39;diagalchi&#39;. That&#39;s because the catch has been reduced a lot. When it is expensive, it is said that it costs 80,000 won for one large blackfish, so it seems that the blackfish is also in the ranks of precious fish.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Grassland restaurant - Mokpo-si, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/332/33faac8a-155b-4836-960b-5a9d6d5ed533.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Grassland restaurant
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The famous place for braised pork is the grassland restaurant. It is well known for the reputation of a 25-year-old grassland restaurant, as middlemen who buy brownfish often come and eat. The braised stew of the meadow restaurant is cooked by adding sweet potato, kimchi and radish. It is a bit salty, but the spicy aftertaste that comes strongly is attractive.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    * Meadow restaurant: 37-6, Bunhwa-ro, Mokpo-si, 061-243-2234
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Braised stew with soft flesh - Mokpo-si, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/332/38bd8d5e-7354-41ef-94ed-3004e7259ae6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Braised stew with soft flesh
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1.Nearby Restaurants
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Sinan Shun Nakji: Yeonpotang / 16 Cheongho-ro, Mokpo-si / 061-243-8181
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://blog.naver.com/dbdb8181&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://blog.naver.com/dbdb8181
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Dokcheon Restaurant: Yeonpo-tang / 3-1 Honam-ro 64beon-gil, Mokpo-si / 061-242-6528
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Gold Medal Restaurant: Hongeo Samhap / 8, Hugwang-daero 143beon-gil, Mokpo-si / 061-272-2697
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Youngran Sashimi: Mineohoe / 47, Beonhwa-ro, Mokpo-si / 061-243-7311
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2.Accommodation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Royal Motel: 12 Tongil-daero, Mokpo-si / 061-282-6659
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Windsor Motel: 16 Tongil-daero, Mokpo-si / 061-282-9349
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was updated in May 2015, and may be changed later, so please check before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>