<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hwaseong-si on Every Corner of Korea</title>
    <link>https://codecorea.github.io/tags/hwaseong-si/</link>
    <description>Every Corner of Korea (Hwaseong-si)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2020 20:32:06 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="https://codecorea.github.io/tags/hwaseong-si/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Fantastic drive course created by Sihwaho - Hwaseong-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/fantastic-drive-course-created-by-sihwaho-326/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2020 20:32:06 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/fantastic-drive-course-created-by-sihwaho-326/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Hwaseong-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;fantastic-drive-course-created-by-sihwaho--326&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Dongjeongri Dinosaur Egg Fossil - Hwaseong-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/326/981f5a7a-d1be-4bd7-a494-913862e269a4.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Dongjeongri Dinosaur Egg Fossil
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Fantastic drive course created by Sihwaho
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Hwaseong-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The wind passes over a vast reed field and migratory birds fly and rest. There is a drive course where you can enjoy your own time while looking at the scenery spread out from the window. There is also a long spectacle of walking through the reeds in search of dinosaur traces. Let&#39;s feel the happiness of a half-day outing with the fantastic drive course created by Sihwaho. It is a course where you can buy abundant seafood at the Sagang Market and taste the godfather and clam noodles.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The road to Dinosaur Egg Fossil in Hwaseong-si, Gyeonggi-do, was a place where the seawater shook. Wetland plants, such as reeds and turkeys, began to grow on the reclaimed land created by the creation of the Sihwa Seawall. As the ground hardened, it became possible to walk to the islands called upper salt, heavy salt, and lower salt, and found about 30 eggs and over 200 dinosaur eggs. It was in 1999. These dinosaur egg fossils are considered to be the world&#39;s three largest dinosaur egg fossils and were designated as a natural monument No. 414 in 2000.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sihwa Lake Reclaimed Road - Hwaseong-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/326/9982b62d-ae14-4c5b-8c7e-2e65d4df9c49.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sihwa Lake Reclaimed Road
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   A trail leading through a wide reed field leads to a wooden deck. Its length is 1.53km, so if you walk slowly between the reed fields, it is a wonderful way to forget even the thoughts of dinosaur eggs. It seems to be walking in an unrealistic landscape where there is only sunlight and wind. There is a small observation deck and log bench in the middle, so you can take a break. This is where the vast reed field washes your eyes and the wind blows your heart.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox type2 clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Trail to Dinosaur Egg Traces - Hwaseong-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/326/1d72e2b0-a62b-44d3-9d4a-3cddd58232d7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Trail to Dinosaur Egg Traces
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Heavy Han Dinosaur Egg Fossil - Hwaseong-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/326/100586b0-2764-404b-bdef-fd6ab826e545.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Heavy Han Dinosaur Egg Fossil
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The wooden deck leads to the four rocky mountains that were once islands. The rocky mountain composed of red conglomerate and sandstone reveals the traces of the sea water. Among them, dinosaur fossils found in heavy salt have been released to the public. In addition to heavy salt, dinosaur egg fossils have been found on chicken islands and ant islands in the northeast, and many dinosaur egg fossils are expected to be hidden on the bottom of tidal flats. This is because this area was a colony of dinosaurs.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Family looking at the reed field - Hwaseong-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/326/721bff59-9b6c-4798-bbcf-56a571704b5c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Family looking at the reed field
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The Cretaceous Period of the Mesozoic Era 100 million years ago, when many dinosaurs stayed here and laid eggs, is a long time ago. However, I think the dinosaur traces may still be hidden under the vast reed field, so it seems that the dinosaur will walk out with a ‘kung-kung’ footsteps somewhere.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   Dinosaur egg fossil learning version of heavy salt is a dinosaur egg fossil that is gathered in the middle of the earth. It is not possible to determine what dinosaur the mother was, but the small size suggests that it was a herbivorous dinosaur.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox type2 clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Dinosaur egg fossil learning version of heavy salt - Hwaseong-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/326/8e7b5730-b4c6-4f62-abfb-82bc228ff262.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Dinosaur egg fossil learning version of heavy salt
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Dinosaur eggs fossil - Hwaseong-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/326/5dd1d4de-d900-472c-99ff-5fb817adeb99.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Dinosaur eggs fossil
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    If you walk the long reed trail again and go to the visitor center, you can find a description of dinosaur egg fossils and various materials about dinosaurs. The fossils of the Korea Ceratops Hwaseong Nsys found in the nearby Jeokok Port breakwater are also displayed. It is a new genus and species of horned dinosaur that was first discovered in Korea, meaning `` Korean ceratopsian dinosaur found in Mars. &#39;&#39; It is also unusual to see the process of processing dinosaur eggs fossils. On the second floor, the movie hall screens images of the dinosaur age environment every 20 minutes.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox type2 clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Dinosaur Egg Fossil Mountain Visitor Center - Hwaseong-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/326/c825be88-d3eb-4d68-82e3-cba4c76bd7d7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Dinosaur Egg Fossil Mountain Visitor Center
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Dinosaur Egg Fossil Mountain Visitor Center - Hwaseong-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/326/8ca424e5-da49-44ee-bf60-d413f39a36d3.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Dinosaur Egg Fossil Mountain Visitor Center
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Let&#39;s get out of the Dinosaur Egg Fossil of Jeongjeong-ri and go to the Sihwa Lake Observatory, operated by the Korea Water Resources Corporation. Sihwa Embankment, Daebu Island, and Sihwa Lake reclamation area are all at a glance. It is still unpaved, so you have to run for a while on a bumpy, unpaved road, but it is a place where word of mouth is also known as a photo club&#39;s outlook because of the beautiful sunset over the reclamation area.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;14&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The sunset seen from the Sihwa Lake Observatory - Hwaseong-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/326/c51df847-412b-46a0-bb24-ededdc56724c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The sunset seen from the Sihwa Lake Observatory
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   When you come back and head for Masan-ri, the full-scale drive course begins. Masan-ri, formerly a seaside port town, is a famous producer of Songsan grapes. The vineyards in the low hills are spectacular, especially when you pass Masan-ri on a summer day when the grapes are ripening, the sweet grape scent vibrates. You can also buy freshly picked grapes from a roadside retailer.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;16&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Fish Island from the Reclaimed Road - Hwaseong-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/326/7907fc04-cf64-4560-acec-9d01d901a74f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Fish Island from the Reclaimed Road
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The reclamation road starts at the end of Masan-ri. After passing a short unpaved section with the island on the left side, famous for the light aircraft boarding experience, you will see an asphalt pavement that stretches out. It is a way to run slowly while being escorted by shiny reeds under the sunshine. This reed field is large enough to resemble the great plains of foreign countries, and has become a regular filming location for TV dramas and movies.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   When the Sihwa Seawall floodgate opens, water enters here, creating an environment like a tidal flat, transforming it into a habitat for various animals. Shiwha Lake once smelled rotten, causing many people&#39;s worries and sighs. However, nature proved to have the ability to purify and regenerate itself, and it brought new life. Elk and bunting run, egrets and mallards fly for food.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;18&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The reed field is becoming a regular location - Hwaseong-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/326/32f65ae5-b5d5-4d20-a930-33165d87d694.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The reed field is becoming a regular location
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   This road should slow down as fast as possible and pass slowly. Birds floating on water in search of food may be amazed. Birdwatchers, who watch cars from the side of the road with a telescope, can be bored.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   “You have to be careful when crossing this road. The birds are surprised by the noise of the vehicle. We&#39;re hiding here in the car and watching the birds. Sometimes, because of the people driving in a hurry, when the birds are surprised and go away, they go to another place again. The grandmother in the white car down there watches the birds all the way back and forth all day, and I really like birds. ”
   &lt;br/&gt;
   This is a story of a low-pitched voice by a searcher on the road to take a picture.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   The bird&#39;s mind floats in peace, making the viewer&#39;s mind peaceful. A willow tree that grows with roots in its roots makes a reclaimed land like a picture.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   The mountain overlooking the willow is an island called Hyeongdo. At one time, fishing boats went in and out, but now they have been incorporated into reclamation lands and have become islands rather than islands.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;20&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sihwa Lake is becoming a shelter for birds - Hwaseong-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/326/d3100a83-cac8-4d87-b462-046ffe82ff1a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sihwa Lake is becoming a shelter for birds
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   With Hyeongdo Island on the right, the road bends sharply and continues along the transmission tower of the Sihwa Seawall Tidal Power Plant. In the distance, the building forest of Songdo New Town also follows. There are long towers of pylons towering over the sea, and you can often see them filming music videos against a unique scenery.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;22&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The bird-watching bird is on the camera - Hwaseong-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/326/7d5df554-51fb-4a9a-b4cf-1e1a039411ec.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The bird-watching bird is on the camera
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The road now passes through Mokseom Island to Daebudo Island. It is a moment that has just crossed the border between Hwaseong and Ansan. On the road to the giant wind turbine, you can turn the car&#39;s audio volume up a bit. Open the car window and feel the romance of the traveler while feeling the cool breeze. Even if there are no special attractions or events, the true taste of a drive trip is to enjoy the fact that you have left your daily life.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;24&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Hyeongdo, an island that has become a land as a reclamation site of Sihwa Lake - Hwaseong-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/326/39d227e3-a226-4539-afef-9d71eb187466.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Hyeongdo, an island that has become a land as a reclamation site of Sihwa Lake
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    In front of the wind turbine, the road is divided into two branches. If you go to the right, Sihwa Seawall is on the left, and Daebu Island, famous for grilled clams and clams, is the street of clams. Fill the hungry stomach with a bowl of Kalguksu with a long drive.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox type2 clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;26&#34; id3=&#34;15&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Road along the transmission tower of Sihwaho tidal power plant - Hwaseong-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/326/263caca6-1f6a-420d-bdd9-49be00a8c4fa.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Road along the transmission tower of Sihwaho tidal power plant
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;26&#34; id3=&#34;16&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Daebudo Island where the clams and noodles collection is gathered - Hwaseong-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/326/a1a27194-af95-4943-adcb-fd79bcd7b07d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Daebudo Island where the clams and noodles collection is gathered
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   You can run the road from Daebu-do to Seonjae-do to Yeongheung-do, and you can go back and enjoy a leisurely drive once again. On the way back, stop by Sagang Market. Sagang Market is a port fishing market that boasted a large scale until the time of the Sihwa Dynasty. Even now, clams, clams, jukkumi, and octopus are abundant, and you can also taste the seafood that has been prepared on the spot in the restaurant inside.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   It&#39;s a great drive trip where you can enjoy the joy of daily escape without much preparation.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox type2 clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;28&#34; id3=&#34;17&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sagang market scenery - Hwaseong-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/326/9e01879e-6b98-4b89-b66b-5f17d45b85d3.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sagang market scenery
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;28&#34; id3=&#34;18&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Seafood from Sagang Market - Hwaseong-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/326/b75dc2a8-25bb-4e6e-a9c9-37a92cead5d2.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Seafood from Sagang Market
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    * Hwaseong City Hall Tourism Promotion Section 031-369-6018
    &lt;br/&gt;
    * Jungjeong-ri Dinosaur Egg Fossil Visitor Center 031-357-3951
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    1.Access
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    * Jungjeong-ri Dinosaur Egg Fossil
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    West Coast Highway Bibong IC → Turn right toward Hwaseong City Hall and Jebudo (National Highway No. 313) → Turn right towards Sagang Intersection, Gojeongri (National Highway No. 305) → Move along Dinosaur Egg Fossil Road → Visitor Center for Dinosaur Egg Fossil Mountain
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    * Godfather
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Dinosaur Egg Fossil → Go to Sagang Intersection → Masanri → Eomseom → Go along Lakeside Road → Daebu Island
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    2. Delicious
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    National Treasure 966 Old Tofu: Tofu Mushroom Hotpot / 407, Madobuk-ro, Madodo-myeon, Hwaseong-si, Gyeonggi-do / 031-355-7966
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Cheongmi Restaurant: Live fish society, Maeuntang / 177, Sagang-ro, Songsan-myeon, Hwaseong-si, Gyeonggi-do / 031-357-7822
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Woori Wheat Kalguksu: Bajirak Kalguksu / 1361, Daebu Hwanggeum-ro, Danwon-gu, Ansan-si, Gyeonggi-do / 032-884-9083
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Yunsook Inesone Kalguksu: Bajirak Kalguksu / 1425 Daebu Hwanggeum-ro, Danwon-gu, Ansan-si, Gyeonggi-do / 032-882-1947
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    3.Accommodation
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Haneul Sarangchae Pension: 16-4, Eomseom-gil 259beon-gil, Songsan-myeon, Hwaseong-si, Gyeonggi-do / 031-357-1711
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    White House Pension: 327-22, Eomseom-gil, Songsan-myeon, Hwaseong-si, Gyeonggi-do / 010-9533-8288
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Daebudo Pension Village: 25, Chamsal 4-gil, Danwon-gu, Ansan-si, Gyeonggi-do / 1566-3315 /
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.daebudovil.com&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     www.daebudovil.com
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Sun Rich Leisure Town: 203 Gubong-gil, Danwon-gu, Ansan-si, Gyeonggi-do / 032-884-6622
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;span style=&#34;color: rgb(213, 0, 0);&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was updated in February 2019, and may be changed later, so please check before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/span&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>