<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Yeongwol-gun on Every Corner of Korea</title>
    <link>https://codecorea.github.io/tags/yeongwol-gun/</link>
    <description>Every Corner of Korea (Yeongwol-gun)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 07:43:01 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="https://codecorea.github.io/tags/yeongwol-gun/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A masterpiece created by nature for many years, Yeongwol Yoseonam Rock - Yeongwol-gun, Gangwon-do, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/a-masterpiece-created-by-nature-for-many-years-yeongwol-yoseonam-rock-223/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 07:43:01 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/a-masterpiece-created-by-nature-for-many-years-yeongwol-yoseonam-rock-223/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Yeongwol-gun, Gangwon-do, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;a-masterpiece-created-by-nature-for-many-years-yeongwol-yoseonam-rock--223&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox type2 clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Sciatica - Yeongwol-gun, Gangwon-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/223/32764a7d-692c-460e-835a-9fc74a4ca343.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Sciatica
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Sciatica - Yeongwol-gun, Gangwon-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/223/54a734d3-ae7f-40e7-a362-895eef99f8aa.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Sciatica
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   A masterpiece created by nature for many years, Yeongwol Yoseonam Rock
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Yeongwol-gun, Gangwon-do, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    If you go to the museum, you will encounter a masterpiece that has been filled with many years in nature, as you can see the old artifacts created by the time of history. One of the masterpieces is the Yeongseonam rock formation hole in Yeongwol Mureung-ri, designated as Natural Monument No. 543 in April. In times of frightening nature, nature is the most natural virtue created by a master writer. Let&#39;s visit the natural exhibition of the master artist from the upper stream of the Jucheon River.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   A masterpiece created by the ages of billionaires
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   copper
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The Yoseonam Rock Grotto in Mureung-ri, Suju-myeon was designated as a natural monument in April. The cleft hole is well-known as a &#39;pot hole&#39;, and is also called a hemoptysis. It is caused by vortices that flow as the water swirls in the concave area of the rock. As the sand or gravel swirls along with the water, the topography that develops due to the wear of the rock is the pit.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox type2 clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Concave - Yeongwol-gun, Gangwon-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/223/7334a3c8-0ccd-4b65-a30d-394a0ba9233f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Concave
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Streams flowing through wide rocks - Yeongwol-gun, Gangwon-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/223/4cba29fe-34ec-487e-83c0-f9e5e8850326.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Streams flowing through wide rocks
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Mureung-ri Yoseonam rock opening is located at the point where the streams of Jucheon River originating from Taegisan, which forms the boundary between Pyeongchang, Hoengseong, and Hongcheon, and Beopheung Valley originating from Mt. There is a large rock called Yoseonam, which is a large granite rock by the river. Along with Anpyeong-daegun, Kim-gu, and Han-ho, Bongrae Yangseon, who was called as the 4th calligrapher of the Joseon Dynasty, stayed with Pyeongchang-gun, contrary to the scenery here, meaning the word &#39;yoseonam (암)&#39;, meaning &#39;where the new ship was flying&#39; I lost, and the name came from there.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox type2 clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Travelers looking around the sciatica hole - Yeongwol-gun, Gangwon-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/223/6c07bc9b-3784-48c7-aa08-e4825925f4d7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Travelers looking around the sciatica hole
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Travelers looking around the sciatica hole - Yeongwol-gun, Gangwon-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/223/fd674dcd-c3df-4a9f-9c74-4e7f18aad3b9.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Travelers looking around the sciatica hole
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    You can easily find the stone hole if you find Yoseonjeong or Mt. In the past, you could drive to Maitreyaam, but now you have to park your car at the entrance to Maitreyaam and walk. After walking about 200m along a low mountain with Yoseonjeong, you can see Mireukam. Standing on a small stone staircase descending from Mireukam to the river, a rock with a stone hole quickly reveals its appearance. Looking at Yoseonam from Gilmok, the graceful curves of the rock created by the water and the time come into sight. The closer you get to the rock, the more pronounced the curve of the rock.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox type2 clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Smooth curves - Yeongwol-gun, Gangwon-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/223/89c09fdc-2459-49a7-b9fa-323bb90cce6f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Smooth curves
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Smooth curves - Yeongwol-gun, Gangwon-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/223/1a8e54f2-d299-4b6e-851f-42ce76e0ccdc.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Smooth curves
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    No matter how hard a person struggles, it is difficult to live for 100 years. In order to make a hole, a person&#39;s life span needs to be multiplied by hundreds or even thousands of times, even if the human life span is 100 years. Since many times and streams of water have been made by touching and trimming natural granite plates, they are once surprised by the time of frighteningness, and once again endured by the appearance of the stone hole that is now in its shape. It&#39;s been a long time since it was raining, but it&#39;s somewhat dry and rough, but it&#39;s hard to keep an eye out for the smooth curves of the rock. It draws a curve as if it were a wave, and a thick cylindrical shape as if a giant weapon passed. Ms. Pongrae Yang Saeon&#39;s life would have had this opening. Naturally, freshness seemed to be in his eyes.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox type2 clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sciatica - Yeongwol-gun, Gangwon-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/223/7450d161-5ad9-4d5f-8364-8a964f95fdfb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sciatica
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Travelers looking around the sciatica hole - Yeongwol-gun, Gangwon-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/223/43b8660a-c40c-4cfc-8dfc-06319df75347.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Travelers looking around the sciatica hole
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Meet the beautiful scenery of the Jucheon River, Yo Seonjeong
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    After looking around Yoseonam, be sure to visit Yoseonjeong. Yoseonjeong is at the top of a low mountain behind Mireukam. It takes less than 5 minutes to climb along a pretty trail with a sprawling pine tree lined up. In a fairly spacious space, Yo Seon-jeong, Maae-bul, and a small stone pagoda that lost my shape are guarded.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    It is said that this place was originally a small hermitage attached to Beopheungsa Temple. Yo Seonjeong is a small pavilion with 2 spaces on the front and 2 spaces on the side. In 1915, during the Japanese colonial rule, the Yoseon-gyewons were founded in the center to seal Sukjong&#39;s yesterday. Sukjong&#39;s yesterday&#39;s poem was originally hung in Cheongheru, Jucheon, and was destroyed by fire. Later, after King Sukjong, Yeongjo, who was immediately found out, wrote and rewrote Sukjong&#39;s yesterday&#39;s poems, and then gave the sum. It is said that Jeongjo, who succeeded Yeongjo, also lowered the amount of money yesterday and walked to Cheongheru. During the Japanese colonial rule, when Cheong Heo-ru fell and the lumps in the hand fell into the hands of the Japanese, the stocks of Jucheon&#39;s retainers repurchased the lumps and enshrined them in the yard. In Yeonseonjeong, Yeongjo wrote yesterday&#39;s King Sukjong and King Jeongjo&#39;s yesterday.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Yo Seon-jung and Mureung-ri Maaerae Statue - Yeongwol-gun, Gangwon-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/223/913090b6-0fb3-4a9f-8427-43a9b85c41df.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Yo Seon-jung and Mureung-ri Maaerae Statue
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   On the large rock shaped like a drop of water in front of Yoseonjeong, Maebul is carved. It is the statue of Maaeraerae in Mureung-ri, Yeongwol, designated as tangible cultural property No. 74 in Gangwon-do. It appears to be dull by engraving on the rock, but it is as if it has just popped out of water droplets.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Yesterday, King Sukjong the Great inside Yosunjeong - Yeongwol-gun, Gangwon-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/223/a6cf2d29-877a-481b-a40e-47f3f877938b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Yesterday, King Sukjong the Great inside Yosunjeong
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Yoseonjeong is rumored to have a beautiful scenery. When you return to the back of Maaebul, you can see the streams of Jucheon River and Beopheung Valley below the sheer cliffs, and blue mountain ridges all over. At the edge of the cliff, a handsome pine tree makes the scenery of the Jucheon River even more relaxing.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Pines and Jucheon River at the back of the statue of Maaerae in Mureung-ri - Yeongwol-gun, Gangwon-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/223/315ef8f3-c93e-4682-8e99-42819a9eda9f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Pines and Jucheon River at the back of the statue of Maaerae in Mureung-ri
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Jeokjeungbokgung and the nameplate of Gusan Seonmun, Mt.
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you go up the Bheungheung Valley, you will meet the historic temple of Bongheungsa Temple under Mt. Beopheungsa Temple is one of the top temples of the Lion Mountain Gate among the Gusan Seonmun and one of the top five extinction palaces in Korea that enshrines the Buddha&#39;s truth. Gusan Seonmun and Jeokjeombogung have common features that are typical mountain temples located in the middle of rare mountains. This is because the temples of the unified Shilla Dynasty and the Sunjong, which emphasized self-discipline, were largely built, and temples were built in the mountains far away from the world. Beopheungsa Temple was built in the middle of the mountain, which is blocked by the mountain of Saja and is no longer connected. Nevertheless, the Buddhist temple pilgrimage continues, creating a strange contrast.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Beopheungsa remains the only cultural property designated as a treasure in Yeongwol. That is Yeongwol Heungnyeongsaji Jinghyo Ambassador Monument (Treasure No. 612). This is a monument engraved on the hall from Ambassador Jing Hyo-nyeong&#39;s birth to enrollment. Isu, the headstone, and the head of a dragon-shaped abdomen and inscription remain intact. On the lower hill, there is also the Jing Hyo-guksabu, which is dedicated to Ambassador Jing Hyo&#39;s saree.
   &lt;br/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Beopheungsa Temple - Yeongwol-gun, Gangwon-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/223/a5e2ed75-3a5f-43af-ba69-d6eba040a2ee.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Beopheungsa Temple
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The path to the Eruption Bogung is breathtakingly breathtaking, but a huge cluster of red pine leaves the eyes to the fullest. Declining your neck with a mineral water and climbing around the mother&#39;s labyrinth, you quickly reach the extinction palace. Since he had a Jinsinsari, there is a low hill with no Buddha statues, and low hills and mountainous hills surrounding him. It is said that Jinsinsari was brought somewhere in the mountain. Only the tomb-shaped crypt and broken stone that Jajangyulsa has devoted the capital replace the old story.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox type2 clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The red pine colony on the way to the Ruin - Yeongwol-gun, Gangwon-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/223/55b90703-e3ec-46d9-9e77-07ee77257df3.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The red pine colony on the way to the Ruin
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;15&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Jeokbokgung Palace - Yeongwol-gun, Gangwon-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/223/5ac19686-7fc7-4c1c-8394-71e09973fd7a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Jeokbokgung Palace
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    These days, it is getting hot and steaming, and I miss the cool and relaxing prices. Don&#39;t be satisfied just by looking around Beopheungsa and enjoy the Tak people in the surrounding valley. The streams starting from the foot of Mt. Gubong and Mt. Baekdeok on the left and right of Mt. The small valley that flows next to Beopheungsa Temple is perfect for enjoying the Tak people. Beopheung Valley from Yoseonjeong to Beopheungsa Temple is not only great for playing in the water, but it also has a camping site, so it&#39;s easy to relax.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;16&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Family enjoying the Tak in the valley next to Beopheungsa Temple - Yeongwol-gun, Gangwon-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/223/eda71d48-7d79-4d1c-982b-58b6bd402715.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Family enjoying the Tak in the valley next to Beopheungsa Temple
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    [Yo Seon Jeong]
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Address: 13-39, Dowon Unhak-ro, Suju-myeon, Yeongwol-gun, Gangwon-do
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Inquiries: Yeongwol Tourist Information 1577-0545
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    1.Access
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    * Self-driving
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Junglim Expressway, Sillim IC → Turn right at the prefectural road No. 88 toward Jucheon → Go straight past Jucheon-myeon → Go straight to Juju-myeon → Turn left after going to Mureung 2-gyo → Turn left after Hoyajiri Museum → Turn left toward Unhak → Yoseonjeong
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    2. Restaurants around
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Sinil Restaurant: Colduguksu / 1225-7, Jucheon-ri, Jucheon-myeon, Yeongwol-gun / 033-372-7743
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Jucheonmuk House: Buckwheat Mukbab / 742-8 Solchi-ro, Jucheon-myeon, Yeongwol-gun / 033-372-3800
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Dahanu Head Office: Hanwoogui / 83, Jucheon-ro, Jucheon-myeon, Yeongwol-gun / 033-372-2227 /
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.dahanoo.com&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창에서 열림&#34;&gt;
     http://www.dahanoo.com
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    3.Accommodation
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Jocheondang, Jucheon Old House: 27, Gogaok-gil, Jucheon-myeon, Yeongwol-gun / 033-372-7229 /
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.jogyundang.com&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     www.jogyundang.com
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Yesol Nuri Pension: 1069, Dowon Unhak-ro, Suju-myeon, Yeongwol-gun / 033-374-7084 /
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.yesolnuri.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;예솔누리펜션으로이동&#34;&gt;
     http://www.yesolnuri.com/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Bobo Scott Pension: 50-24, Midari-gil, Jucheon-myeon, Yeongwol-gun / 033-375-1011 /
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://boboscot.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;보보스갓 관광농원으로 이동&#34;&gt;
     http://boboscot.com/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    ※ The above information was created in June 2013, and may be changed later, so be sure to check it before you travel.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>