<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Changnyeong-gun on Korea Tour</title>
    <link>https://codecorea.github.io/tags/changnyeong-gun/</link>
    <description>Korea Tour (Changnyeong-gun)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 10:36:20 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="https://codecorea.github.io/tags/changnyeong-gun/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Changnyeong-gun, Gyeongnam, Korea - Exploring the Beautiful Cultural Heritage of Changnyeong</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/exploring-the-beautiful-cultural-heritage-of-changnyeong-61/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 10:36:20 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/exploring-the-beautiful-cultural-heritage-of-changnyeong-61/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Changnyeong-gun, Gyeongnam, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;exploring-the-beautiful-cultural-heritage-of-changnyeong--61&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Gyodong Tombs - Changnyeong-gun, Gyeongnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/61/0ca73a2f-0e2d-4547-9d88-be08865d7bc9.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Gyodong Tombs
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Exploring the Beautiful Cultural Heritage of Changnyeong
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Changnyeong-gun, Gyeongnam, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Changnyeong reminds me of Upo Swamp first. However, if the only thing that comes to mind is Upo Wetland, we will underestimate Changnyeong. Changnyeong is the place where Bihwagaya, one of the Gaya nations, gained power. It was also the hometown where King Jin-ra, the King of Silla, declared the land of Shilla after subjugating Gaya. There are vast historical remains from the Gaya era to the Joseon dynasty, and you can find precious cultural heritages, including two national treasures and four treasures.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Non-professional with the history of Gaya
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you go out to Changnyeong IC on Buinland Expressway, Mt. Hwangwang stands out from the wide open Changnyeong-eup. In the Three Kingdoms era, it was called non-military army and Hwawang-gun. Changnyeong, based on the Visage Army of the Three Kingdoms Period, is called Bisabeul, meaning “red field.”
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;National Treasure No. 34 - Changnyeong-gun, Gyeongnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/61/79cb4382-f10c-4794-9763-640d59edefcc.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     National Treasure No. 34
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Bisabul is a place where Bhagagaya, a small country of Gaya, gained power. Gyodong Tombs and Songhyeon-dong Tombs, considered to be the traces of Bihwagaya, including the Jinheung Royal Guards, established by the King of Silla Jinheung and established in the land, the Sulwha-dong East-West Three-stone Pagoda, Yinyangsa-joseongbi, Songhyeon-dong The Changnyeong Seokbingo and Changnyeong Hyanggyo are scattered around the town.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Treasure No. 520 Liquor Tower - Changnyeong-gun, Gyeongnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/61/30de64be-7c6b-454a-be90-dbf2bbb5b837.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Treasure No. 520 Liquor Tower
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It is good to meet cultural heritage one by one, but it is also recommended to walk the &#39;Jungheung Wanghaengcha-gil&#39; and &#39;Songhyuni-gil&#39;, which are built around the cultural heritage of Changnyeong-eup. The Jinheung Wanghaeng-gil road is centered on the Jinheung Wangcheok Guard and the distance of travel is about 7km. Songhyeon Yi-gil is a way to get into the story of a Gaya girl 1,500 years ago, the owner of Sunjang Ingol, excavated at Songhyeon-dong Tombs. It was discovered in Song Hyun-ri, so the girl was given the name &#39;Song Hyun-i&#39;, and Gil followed the name. Songhyeon Lee&#39;s moving distance is about 4 km. Although the two roads overlap each other, it is perfect for enjoying cultural heritage exploration while walking in the small town of Changnyeong.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Treasure No. 310 Changnyeong Seokbingo - Changnyeong-gun, Gyeongnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/61/ae134335-223c-4149-8dd0-a06d6cf77a51.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Treasure No. 310 Changnyeong Seokbingo
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The Jinheung Wanghaeng-gil departs from Changnyeong Museum to Manokjeong Park with the Jinheung Royal Scenic Guard, Changnyeong Seokbingo, and Suljeong-ri High Pass, Suljeong-ri East and West Three-story Stone Pagoda, Orthogonal Dangji Branch, Seongsa-sa Temple Monument, Sajik, Mandeokji, and Changnyeong Hyanggyo. Songhyeon Yi-gil is a course that takes you back to Gyodong Tombs and Changnyeong Museums from Changnyeong Museum through Gyodong, Songhyeon-dong Mounds, Songhyeon-dong, Maae Yeosang Statue, Jinheung Wangcheok Guard, Changnyeong Seokbingo, and Changnyeong Hyanggyo.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Treasure No. 227 Salvation History - Changnyeong-gun, Gyeongnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/61/5907ed32-ef5b-465b-bcbf-68d79418ac0a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Treasure No. 227 Salvation History
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Meet beautiful cultural heritage that shines Changnyeong
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The first to meet on the way from Changnyeong IC to Changnyeongeup is Seojeongli Seoseom Pagoda. It is good to look around compared with each other in the Suljeolli East Three-storied Pagoda, which is less than 1km away.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Remains of the old temple around the Three-story Stone Pagoda - Changnyeong-gun, Gyeongnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/61/35e0cdb0-a82f-4624-9e98-30b3435eccd6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Remains of the old temple around the Three-story Stone Pagoda
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The two three-storied pagoda is divided into the east and the west of the Sulgori. Both are stone pagodas of the Unified Silla period, but they differ in many ways. The East Three-storied Pagoda is designated National Treasure No. 34, and the West Three-storied Pagoda is Treasure No. 520. The Dongsam Three-storied pagoda is a bit large, and the form and appearance of the pagoda are generally similar. The Dongsam Three-storied Pagoda has a sense of stability, sharp lines, and refined feeling. In comparison, the West Three-storied pagoda is a bit slender, and the lines are blunt and soft. West Three Storey Stone Pagoda can be met by following a narrow road to Namjung Park, while the East Three Storey Stone Pagoda is easy to find Changnyeong Public Market.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Seojeongseom Seoryon Stone Tower - Changnyeong-gun, Gyeongnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/61/2b786468-934e-450c-a4be-6fe7fbb7fc7b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Seojeongseom Seoryon Stone Tower
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   When you exit Changnyeong Permanent Market and turn right along Myeongdeok-ro, you will meet Changnyeong Seok Bingo, a masterpiece of Joseon Dynasty. Seokbingo is an ice warehouse that was built during the Joseon Dynasty. The movie &#39;Gone with the Wind,&#39; starring Cha Tae-hyun, which was released in 2012, was based on Servingo, a stone ice bin of Hanyang in the Joseon Dynasty. Seokbingo is also located in Gyeongju, Andong, Qingdao, and Dalseong. There are two Seokbingo in Changnyeong-eup and Yeongsan-myeon. Changnyeong Seokbingo was designated Treasure No. 310.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A monument engraved with records about Changnyeong Seokbingo - Changnyeong-gun, Gyeongnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/61/6aefb634-f5e1-4917-9d3d-24838a25a5b6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A monument engraved with records about Changnyeong Seokbingo
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Yinyangsajoseongbi (Treasure No. 227) near Samjin Apartment near the entrance to Changnyeong-gun Office, and Songhyeon-dong Mae Ehagae statue (Treasure No. 75) near Changhwa Temple at the entrance of Songhyeon-dong Tomb are also to be seen in Changnyeong-eup. It is a valuable cultural heritage.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Monk&#39;s face carved into salvage - Changnyeong-gun, Gyeongnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/61/37133ad6-eb5a-439a-a2a6-de14dd5b43d7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Monk&#39;s face carved into salvage
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Trace of the secretary and the sun-drenched girl
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   National highway No. 20, which runs through the town of Changnyeong, crosses the Qingdao to the north and the Nakdong River to the south, leading to the Rural Land. Gyodong Tombs are located near the national road from Cheongdo to Cheongdo and Songhyeondong Tombs are near Changhwasa at the entrance of Hwawangsan County Park. Two burial mounds were grouped together and designated Historic Site No. 514. Gyodong and Songhyeon-dong burial mounds were formed in the 5th and 6th centuries, and are traces of the non-gagaya who developed their forces around the non-professionals. According to Samguk-yusa, built by the Goryeo Dynasty, non-gagaya was included in the 5-gaya along with the Gwan-gwan-gaya, the elderly, the Aragaya, and the Seongsan-gaya.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Gyodong and Songhyeon-dong burial mounds formed over 150 mounds before the Japanese colonial rule. Excavations were made in 1918, during the Japanese colonial rule, when a huge relic was excavated. However, most of the artifacts were taken to Japan, and tombs were thoroughly destroyed.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Travelers walking in Gyodong Tombs - Changnyeong-gun, Gyeongnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/61/b04b8a5e-5624-4bdc-89c2-f1ee9d652a11.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Travelers walking in Gyodong Tombs
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In Songhyeon-dong burial mounds, there were traces of sunjang 1,500 years ago. In the burial mound, only traces of grave robbers remained, and when they were removed, four bones were found along with various ornaments and earthenware. The first one, which remains intact, has been restored by a team of experts in archeology, forensics, anatomy, and formative arts. The name given to this Sunjang girl is ‘송현 이’.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Tomb Creation Diorama of Changnyeong Museum - Changnyeong-gun, Gyeongnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/61/dbcf68ec-75eb-4a77-9472-8131041a8c76.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Tomb Creation Diorama of Changnyeong Museum
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The traces of Bihwagaya remain intact at the Changnyeong Museum. Various relics excavated from Gyo-dong and Songhyeon-dong tombs, as well as restoration materials of Sunjang Ingol are also displayed. Outside the museum, there is an exhibition hall that relocates and restores Gyeseong burial mounds discovered near Gwanryongsa.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Changnyeong Museum Exhibition Space - Changnyeong-gun, Gyeongnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/61/9832dd0c-5ad1-43c7-ab3c-3fc7f43510c9.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Changnyeong Museum Exhibition Space
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Gyodong Tombs and Songhyeon-dong Tombs are quite good trails. As you walk along the towering tombs, the surrounding scenery changes every moment. The scenery is as beautiful as the Jisan-dong Tomb of the elderly in Gyeongbuk.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Jinheung Royal Guards Monument in Manokjeong Park - Changnyeong-gun, Gyeongnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/61/9116292f-d4b4-4d0f-b2f4-3cd0a85ac1a8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Jinheung Royal Guards Monument in Manokjeong Park
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Jinheung King is the king who expanded the territory of the Silla era the most. As he pioneered the territory, the pure rains that he set up in each region remain in Mt. Bukhan, Maun-ryeong, Hwangcho-ryeong, and in Changnyeong, there is a guard for Jinheung Wangcheok. Chuck Kyung-bi refers to the rain that was made in commemoration of public sentiment by patrolling the land after King Jinheung pioneered the territory. Another pure rain built in the Jinheung Wangdae has a title of &#39;Pure Water Pavilion (巡狩 管 境)&#39;. It is a monument that was built after the king patrolled by the king, and the list of the servants who performed the king is engraved. Whether it is a steal guard or a pure expense, it is clear that this is evidence of the expansion of King Chin&#39;s territory.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Jinheung Royal Spine Guard - Changnyeong-gun, Gyeongnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/61/890bd985-6f48-4ca5-9a94-6b9b1fd6fe2c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Jinheung Royal Spine Guard
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you go to Manokjeong Park, about 400 meters from Changnyeong Seokbingo, you can meet Jinheung Royal Guard. A student who had a picnic near Mt. Masan fortress at the foot of Mt. Hwangwang during the Japanese colonial rule discovered it and found it to be a stone monument of Silla and moved to its present location in 1924. In Manokjeong Park, there is also a selection fee for Chosonhwabi, which was built during Heungseondaewon-gun, and the three-storied pagoda of Tokcheon-ri, Changnyeongsa, and officials of Joseon dynasty who passed through Changnyeong.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Chuckhwa Monument, built during Heungseondaewon - Changnyeong-gun, Gyeongnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/61/80e0b0b1-f389-468b-8ca4-815df026b735.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Chuckhwa Monument, built during Heungseondaewon
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel info
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Changnyeong Museum
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Address: 34, Changmil-ro, Changnyeong-eup, Changnyeong-gun, Gyeongnam
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Contact: 055-530-1500
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Changnyeong-gun tour guide
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Contact: 055-530-1000
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Nearby restaurants
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Yangban Cheongguk: Cheonggukjang / 64 Hwawangsan-ro, Changnyeong-eup, Changnyeong-gun / 055-533-0066
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Zelkova House: Natural Song Dakguk / 17 Daman-gil, Changnyeong-eup, Changnyeong-gun / 055-521-3678
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Siraegi Rice Award: Siraegi Rice Award / 63 Oncheon-ro, Yeongsan-myeon, Changnyeong-gun / 055-536-4555
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Accommodation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Hwawangsan Natural Recreation Forest: 128-126, Cheongan-gil, Goam-myeon, Changnyeong-gun / 055-533-2332
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.hwawang.or.kr/main/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.hwawang.or.kr/main/
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    S Motel: 1221 Upo 2-ro, Changnyeong-eup, Changnyeong-gun / 055-532-6542
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was updated in May 2017 and may change afterwards, so please check before traveling.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ The information such as text, photos and videos used in this article is copyrighted by Korea Tourism Organization, so unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>