<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jeollanam-do on Every Corner of Korea</title>
    <link>https://codecorea.github.io/tags/jeollanam-do/</link>
    <description>Every Corner of Korea (Jeollanam-do)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 16:04:24 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="https://codecorea.github.io/tags/jeollanam-do/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Damyang Art Warehouse, a colorful transformation of Yanggok Warehouse - Damyang-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/damyang-art-warehouse-a-colorful-transformation-of-yanggok-warehouse-156/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 16:04:24 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/damyang-art-warehouse-a-colorful-transformation-of-yanggok-warehouse-156/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Damyang-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;damyang-art-warehouse-a-colorful-transformation-of-yanggok-warehouse--156&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Namsong Warehouse has been transformed into a light art warehouse. - Damyang-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/156/9a136495-e2b3-4aaf-a0c5-7a81363e774a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Namsong Warehouse has been transformed into a light art warehouse.
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Damyang Art Warehouse, a colorful transformation of Yanggok Warehouse
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Damyang-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Is the transformation of the warehouse innocent? Namsong warehouse and bamboo product processing plant, which had been left for many years next to Gwanbangjerim in Damyang, were reborn as a space of culture and art in 2015. In the name of &#39;Dambit Art Warehouse&#39;. It is located in the middle of Metasequoia Garosu-gil and Gwanbangjerim, making it a must-see destination for visitors to Damyang. In addition to the regularity of bamboo and metasequoia, let&#39;s take part in the fragrance of art.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   A different transformation of an old warehouse
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Before hearing the story of the birth of the Dambit Art Warehouse, let&#39;s look at a case where a grain storage warehouse in a rural area that lost its vitality has become a tourist attraction. First of all, Samrye Culture &amp;amp; Arts Village in Wanju-gun, Jeollabuk-do is considered as a representative runner. Until 2010, there were several dongs in the Yanggok warehouse and houses built during the Japanese colonial period. As the rapid urbanization caused Samrye-eup to lose vitality day by day, the villagers sought to become a giant. The slogan that united their will into one is ‘Geun Ja-yeol Sang-rae (近 者 悅 遠 者 來)’. This means that people who live nearby should have fun, and people who are far away also come. Yes. If I don&#39;t like it, I can&#39;t help others. They have turned warehouses that no one is eyeing into places of culture and art.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A nameplate on a red brick - Damyang-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/156/b4f1912e-6d4a-4172-ad43-58ea4ec60604.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A nameplate on a red brick
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   From 2011 to 2014, the residents of Samrye carried out the project of creating a Samrye Culture and Art Village with the motto of “Art is tourism”. Finally, large warehouses have been transformed into visual media art museum, book studio north art center, design museum, Kim Sang-lim woodwork, book museum, and cultural cafe. Samrye Culture &amp;amp; Arts Village is widely known not only in Jeonbuk but also in Seoul and the metropolitan area, where visitors line up.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Residents of Andeok-myeon, Seogwipo-si, Jeju Island have converted old citrus warehouses into cafes. The interior of the cafe boasts a surprisingly sensuous interior for urban people. Citrus sweets, tangerine crunchino, and daengja aide made by aging with a secret method will attract travelers&#39; taste.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sculpture placed in the courtyard of Samrye Culture and Arts - Damyang-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/156/d3bfdcc3-dba0-4105-aaca-725dc0152de7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sculpture placed in the courtyard of Samrye Culture and Arts
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   The red warehouse building is a gallery and a literary cafe.
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Let&#39;s go back to the Dambit Art Warehouse and take a look at every corner. In the past, if you were traveling to Damyang, you would have visited Juknokwon or Metasequoia Road first, but this trip is different. Since there was an art yard in Damyang, visiting there is a top priority.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Book Museum at Samrye Culture and Art Village - Damyang-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/156/7449366f-b010-416c-955a-da8d8d12312d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Book Museum at Samrye Culture and Art Village
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   When viewed from the front, the art warehouse is painted with red brick walls in white, and the Chinese characters written in black are first noticed. &#39;Namsong Warehouse&#39;. This is a typeface with a long age ring. Building 2 meets at a right angle
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A literary cafe where you can listen to bamboo pipe organ performances - Damyang-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/156/f54cf777-5fa6-482f-aa7d-7b51eec164fe.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A literary cafe where you can listen to bamboo pipe organ performances
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Murals are painted on the wall of the house on the right side of the lawn in front of the warehouse. When you go to the back of the warehouse building, several works like the sculpture park take place and talk to the visitors.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Literary cafes have a lot of books on the bookshelves, making a book cafe atmosphere. - Damyang-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/156/50e68b95-6c40-4bea-bf2e-e22f0e24c999.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Literary cafes have a lot of books on the bookshelves, making a book cafe atmosphere.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Healing while watching works of art from various genres
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The artists who participated in the exhibition of the Dambit Art Warehouse were 12 people including Lee Nam Lee, Byeongchan Lee, Daewon Jo, Sungyeon Joo, and Jung Unhak. Jinwol-ji of the Damyang-gun Cultural Foundation said, “I am a military unit without going to a large city such as Gwangju Metropolitan City.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Step inside the exhibition room and slowly fall in love with the appreciation of the work. Although the Dambit Art Warehouse is less than the size of the Yangpyeong County Museum of Art, compared to the military unit art museum, it has the confidence that its life will last, as it has its own garden, such as literary cafes, sculpture parks, and giant trees of Gwanbangjerim.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Enjoy bamboo pipe organ performance while drinking tea leaves
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The impressions received while appreciating the works of the complex are continued in the literary cafe. The bamboo pipe organ performance was in progress. Pipe organs are very expensive and large, so they are often installed in cathedrals and churches. The performance starts every week on Tuesday / Thursday at 2 o&#39;clock and on the weekend / holiday at 3 o&#39;clock, each lasting 30 minutes. The taste of having a cup of tea leaves and watching a bamboo pipe organ while reading a book is a happiness that cannot be enjoyed without a trip to Damyang. The spacious space has a high ceiling, so the organ sound is magnificent. As much as the playing time, even the chatter of adults and the shuffling of children are cut off.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Bamboo pipe organ in literary cafe - Damyang-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/156/0c78a15f-9d3b-4637-aa9f-fbea9089f56f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Bamboo pipe organ in literary cafe
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Watching the bamboo pipe organ performance felt only briefly, and curiously laughed from corner to corner, I found a blackboard hidden under a staircase going up to the second floor. When I look at the chart drawn under the heading of &#39;Government Grain Storage Status&#39;, I realize that this was the Yanggok warehouse. How many people have actually seen a thermometer, moisture meter, etc. in the list of management equipment written on the board? The cafe sells Americano, Green Tea Latte, Juice, Smoothie, Aid, Sandwich, Cookie, Cake, etc. in addition to the tea leaves and tea leaves.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Blackboard with &#39;Government Grain Storage Status&#39; - Damyang-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/156/cd08359b-185f-4951-82b0-4746c2ef366a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Blackboard with &#39;Government Grain Storage Status&#39;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Sculpture-lined garden, Gwanbangjerim, Metasequoia Trail
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Sculpture garden and Gwanbangjerim are spread behind the literary cafe. It has a large through-glass window, so it has an excellent open feeling. If you leave the book you read in place and go out as a sponsor, a scary-looking tiger statue greets you. I put a long tail on my back, but the tip of the tail is a pine shape, so I have to look into the description of the work. It is a story called ‘The Story of the Tiger and the Turtle’. “It was based on the story that a tiger can settle for a thousand years by holding its tail. As I read the passage, “I express the feeling of the pine tree in the tail part,” the question raises my head asking, “Is Damyang the part of the tiger&#39;s tail?”
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;5&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Pond behind Dambit Art Warehouse - Damyang-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/156/f01e8afb-a8a6-4fe7-91e7-51e6f07d8965.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Pond behind Dambit Art Warehouse
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Around the tiger, funny things such as “Tale of the Dog and Chicken of Damyang”
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;5&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Tiger statue - Damyang-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/156/d8f23a4d-3635-4b72-8485-9c63301f7191.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Tiger statue
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   After that, the Chuseong Stadium and the Gwanbangjerim embankment continue. If you walk along the causeway leading along the Yeongsan River, you will see the entrance to Juknokwon and Damyang Guksu Street, which is packed with noodles. Also, just a little east along Jukhyang-daero, Metasequoia Garosu-gil begins.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   On the roadside, Honam Climate Change Experience Hall or a singer who died out Kim Jung-ho (1952 ~ 198
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Myeongokheon and Sikyeongjeong tour and finish with bamboo shoots
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Damyang is the hometown of sperm culture, so the last trip is to visit a couple of sperm such as Myeongokheon in Goseo-myeon and Sikyeongjeong in Nam-myeon.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;6&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Myeongokheon Garden Pond - Damyang-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/156/7a92c0d4-bd7a-4063-8e4d-c092e1cf11c2.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Myeongokheon Garden Pond
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In Sikyeongjeong, I smelled the tree. The smell of summer. There were many trees covered in tall in front of the pavilion, making it difficult to see Mudeungsan Mountain. For the panoramic view, shouldn&#39;t the trees in front of Sikyeongjeong be turned into short trees? The stone stairs that go up and down are also scary on rainy days. I want to ask Damyang-gun to make a handle for the elderly.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;6&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Jeongyoung Jeong - Damyang-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/156/2d2773a3-bd59-4fad-88d5-aa1c3ab5151d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Jeongyoung Jeong
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   One of the ‘Damyang 10 beauty’ must be tasted before the tour of Damyang is over. Tteokgalbi, Changpyeonggukbap, Daetongbap, Hanjeongsik, bamboo shoots, Korean and rice syrup, charcoal pork ribs, Korean beef, Damyang noodles, catfish steamed and Tang, bamboo shoots were selected from 10 dishes.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;6&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Bamboo tour - Damyang-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/156/1690a6a2-347b-450c-a619-b10d56c33470.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Bamboo tour
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   People living in Damyang, the home of bamboo, cook and eat bamboo shoots in a variety of ways, including marinated, steamed, sweet and sour pork, and boiled fish.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;6&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Boiled bamboo shoots - Damyang-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/156/54fe25ae-e8d2-4686-a179-1f14b2424104.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Boiled bamboo shoots
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Dambit Art Warehouse
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Address: 75, Gaeksa 7-gil, Damyang-eup, Damyang-gun, Jeonnam
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Contact: 061-383-8240
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1.Nearby Restaurants
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Hansang Modern Traditional Rice House: Daetongbab / 113, Damjang-ro, Wolsan-myeon, Damyang-gun / 061-382-1999
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Traditional restaurant: Hanjeongsik / 38-4, Goeuphyeon-gil, Goseo-myeon, Damyang-gun / 061-382-3111
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Jukyanggol Restaurant: Juksun Fish Steak / 1341 Chuseong-ro, Damyang-eup, Damyang-gun / 061-382-1278
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2.Accommodation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Damyang Resort Tourist Hotel: 202, Geumseongsanseong-gil, Geumseong-myeon, Damyang-gun / 061-380-5000
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.damyangresort.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.damyangresort.com/
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Vice Hotel: 26 Mujeong-ro, Damyang-eup, Damyang-gun / 061-381-
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://boo-hotel.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://boo-hotel.com/
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    From the old house of Hanok: 88-9, Doldam-gil, Changpyeong-myeon, Damyang-gun / 061-382-3832
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was updated in July 2019, and may be changed later, so please check before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two Buddhist culture experiences, Boseong Daewonsa Temple and Tibet Museum - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/two-buddhist-culture-experiences-boseong-daewonsa-temple-and-tibet-museum-152/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 09:00:51 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/two-buddhist-culture-experiences-boseong-daewonsa-temple-and-tibet-museum-152/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;two-buddhist-culture-experiences-boseong-daewonsa-temple-and-tibet-museum--152&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Summit Gwangmyeong Pagoda, the Tibetan Pagoda, and Daewonsa Tibet Museum - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/152/aa58f1d1-3797-45b2-93d5-64eafc6ce64f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Summit Gwangmyeong Pagoda, the Tibetan Pagoda, and Daewonsa Tibet Museum
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Two Buddhist culture experiences, Boseong Daewonsa Temple and Tibet Museum
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div style=&#34;text-align: justify;&#34;&gt;
    In April, full of spring scent, the way to visit Daewonsa Temple, a temple in Boseong, Jeollanam-do, is a snowy road. This is because cherry blossoms are in full bloom at the 5.5km driveway. If you walk as if you are drunk with the scattered rain, you will arrive at the entrance of the temple. However, unlike any temple where Iljumun welcomes, an exotic pagoda stands out. It is a Tibetan stupa called &#39;Chorten&#39;. The 15m high white sumi light tower combined with the blue sky and the colorful flags fluttering in the wind are colorful. On the opposite side, the Daewon Sa Tibet Museum, built in the Tibetan temple style, stood tall. It seems unfamiliar and unreal to face the scenery you saw in an overseas documentary program.
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;In April, cherry blossoms form a tunnel along the entrance to Daewonsa Temple. &amp;lt;Photo Credit: Boseong County Office&amp;gt; - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/152/ec86515e-e118-46bc-8bca-9e352dcb2868.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     In April, cherry blossoms form a tunnel along the entrance to Daewonsa Temple. &amp;lt;Photo Credit: Boseong County Office&amp;gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div style=&#34;text-align: justify;&#34;&gt;
    Daewonsa Tibet Museum and Sumi Gwangmyeong Pagoda were founded by the chief field monk of Daewonsa. It was found that he met the Dalai Lama, a Tibetan Buddhist leader while traveling in India. Tibetan Buddhist culture is regarded as one of the spiritual civilizations achieved by mankind. The museum was opened in 2001 to introduce this spirit culture and art world of Tibet and to promote exchange with Korean Buddhism. In addition, the Dalai Lama&#39;s message celebrating the opening of the museum, the Sumi Gwangmyeong Pagoda was created to welcome the Buddha Sari from Tibet and Nepal.
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox type2 clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Inside the Sumi Gwangmyeong Pagoda, murals and mandalas painted by Tibetan royal painters were enshrined. - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/152/eb99bd8e-1f9b-4fe3-9f11-09b45e76aa0d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Inside the Sumi Gwangmyeong Pagoda, murals and mandalas painted by Tibetan royal painters were enshrined.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Tarcho, a multicolored flag with scriptures - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/152/63243d32-2ece-4ff3-beaa-29187286be72.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Tarcho, a multicolored flag with scriptures
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div style=&#34;text-align: justify;&#34;&gt;
    Inside the pagoda, murals and mandalas painted by Tibetan royal painters were enshrined, and 108 Manibo wheels made in Nepal were collected outside. It is a good idea to experience the wishes come true when you turn the pagoda one time while turning the Manibo wheel, which contains Buddhist scriptures. At this time, reciting the ‘Ommani Bapthumum’ of Tibetan Buddhism. It means that the mercy of the Buddha spreads all over the world. The multicolored flag blowing in the wind is &#39;tarcho&#39;. The blue, yellow, red, white, and green flags that symbolize the five elements of the universe (sky, earth, fire, clouds, and sea) were written with strings of scripture scriptures. It was hoped that the Buddha&#39;s teachings would spread all over the world.
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox type2 clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;At the Daewon Satibet Museum, a special exhibition, &amp;lt;Traveling with God&amp;gt; is held. - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/152/668f1a14-552a-4c1b-b51b-bb488cacff45.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     At the Daewon Satibet Museum, a special exhibition, &amp;lt;Traveling with God&amp;gt; is held.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Death experience room to take a picture of Yeongjeong and write a will - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/152/1f67ca28-d716-4bd5-a363-eed6f6e764fb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Death experience room to take a picture of Yeongjeong and write a will
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div style=&#34;text-align: justify;&#34;&gt;
    In the museum, you can see the Dalai Lamasil, the Tibetan Buddhist painting Tangka, the Tibetan daily necessities, the teapot, the Buddha statue created by the Sakyamite artisans directly descended from Sakyamuni, and the Mandala, one of the Tibetan Buddhist essences. The special exhibition 〈Traveling with Gods〉 is also exciting. Compare and display the seven hells in the movie &amp;lt;With God--Sin and Punishment&amp;gt; and the ten hells of Buddhism, which dramatizes the afterlife of Buddhism. The death experience room, which takes pictures of Yeongjeong, writes a will, and enters the coffin after experiencing the Tibetan funeral culture that feeds the dead from the body of an eagle, provides a thrilling and reflexive opportunity. The scene of the ceiling (promotion) where people who leave and think that &#39;the body from which the soul has left is only a rotten piece of meat&#39; is put out finely with flesh and bones so that birds can eat without any conflict is somewhat shocking.
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;You can see the paradise in front of Yeonjimun, which has a large wooden table hitting it with its head. - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/152/cad62902-989c-47a1-b96b-5a9ee2d3c029.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     You can see the paradise in front of Yeonjimun, which has a large wooden table hitting it with its head.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div style=&#34;text-align: justify;&#34;&gt;
    After Tibetan Buddhism, it is time to meet Korean Buddhism. The Daewonsa Temple, founded in Baekje, is burned down by fire and continues to be built again. Jubuljeon is a paradise (Jeollanam-do Tangible Cultural Heritage No. 87), symbolizing the western paradise of the ideal of Buddhism. After passing through Iljumun and Sacheonwangru and crossing the Guumgyo Bridge, climbing the stairs reveals a paradise show beyond Yeonjimun. There was a large wooden table hitting the head at Yeonjimun. Hold the wooden table with both hands and hit it three times with your forehead and say, &#34;Gone bad memories, brighten my wisdom, and my enemies will be good.&#34; The pond under the old school bridge is considered the most beautiful place in Daewonsa. There are seven ponds on the grounds of Daewonsa Temple, and in summer, it resembles an ecological park with blooming lotus flowers and various aquatic plants.
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;13&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Mural of Gwaneum Bodhisattva on the western wall of Daewonsa Temple - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/152/5e137acf-5be5-4fc4-9434-a6f3b1fef767.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Mural of Gwaneum Bodhisattva on the western wall of Daewonsa Temple
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div style=&#34;text-align: justify;&#34;&gt;
    It is recommended that you watch the inside of the paradise. Pay particular attention to the murals that decorate the left and right walls. On the western wall, he painted murals of the Gwaneum Bodhisattva with white and Gwaneum Bodhisattva, and on the east wall, the murals of the Dharma Ambassador and the Dharma Ambassadors and the Hyagadanbi. Boseong Daewonsa Temple Geuknakjeon Gwaneum Bodhisattva Mural Painting (Treasure No. 1861), presumably from 1766 ~ 1767 during the reign of King Yeongjo
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox type2 clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;15&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Dongja statue and Taean Jizo Bodhisattva statue to comfort the floating young soul - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/152/d831abbe-28b7-48e8-b2c6-20897634ebbc.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Dongja statue and Taean Jizo Bodhisattva statue to comfort the floating young soul
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;15&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Plum blossoms on the grounds of Daewonsa Temple - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/152/4cad8a60-dcfa-4421-bf23-20341c67b1e9.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Plum blossoms on the grounds of Daewonsa Temple
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div style=&#34;text-align: justify;&#34;&gt;
    Daewonsa Temple is a hieroglyphic prayer to comfort a young spirit (fetal spirit) who has not seen the light of the world, and there are many bronze statues wearing red hats everywhere. Next to Kukrakjeon, there is the Taean Jijang Bodhisattva statue which was enshrined to deliver young souls, and a hundred days prayer is held for heaven. Other major events include Kim Ji-Jang, Hwang Hee-Jung, Seung-Young-Gak, Ado-Young-Gak, Death Experience Hall (Su-Gwan-Jung), and a preservation for the temple stay. This year, Daewon Temple plans to arrange a variety of programs, including experiences in the world of Tibetan music and art with locals in Tibet. Please refer to the website for detailed schedule and participation method.
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;17&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Boseong County Baekmin Museum located at the entrance of Daewonsa Temple - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/152/be02f26c-68da-48ea-ae8f-93c58a1c61ca.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Boseong County Baekmin Museum located at the entrance of Daewonsa Temple
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div style=&#34;text-align: justify;&#34;&gt;
    Before and after visiting Daewonsa Temple, you can visit the Boseong County Paikmin Museum or Seojaepil Memorial Park. Boseong County Pavilion Museum is the first military art museum in Korea to open in 1993. Baekmin, a native of Boseong, and Kyu-il Cho, a Korean elder and middle-aged artist, and foreign artists are exhibited. Seojaepil Memorial Park is a place to honor Seo Jae-pil, a teacher who devoted himself to the liberation of his country by organizing an independent association and publishing &amp;lt;Independent Newspaper&amp;gt;. However, the Seojaepil Memorial Hall, which exhibits artifacts and various materials, can be viewed after April when the internal construction is over.
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;19&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;On the second floor of the Taebaeksanmaek Literature Museum, there is a manuscript of the novel `` Taebaeksanmaek &#39;&#39; by the son and daughter-in-law of Jo Jung-rae. - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/152/3be6a81f-33b8-49a3-b94a-dd9a40c79e6a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     On the second floor of the Taebaeksanmaek Literature Museum, there is a manuscript of the novel `` Taebaeksanmaek &#39;&#39; by the son and daughter-in-law of Jo Jung-rae.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div style=&#34;text-align: justify;&#34;&gt;
    Beolgyo, the stage of the novel The Taebaek Mountain Range, is an essential part of the trip to Boseong. Leading to the literary world of Jo Jeong-rae, and the Taebaeksan Mountain Literature Museum, the House of the digestive, Hyunbuja&#39;s House, Kim Bum-woo&#39;s House, the Beolgyo Hongkyo, the former Beolgyo Financial Association, the old Boseong Inn, and the Jungdobangjuk. The path to Taebaeksan Mountain Literature that follows the famous spots in the novel is popular.
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;21&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The largest and most beautiful bulkyo hongkyo among the remaining hongkyo in Korea - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/152/b9a8fe1c-2e63-4715-bb28-90084e278d2c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The largest and most beautiful bulkyo hongkyo among the remaining hongkyo in Korea
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div style=&#34;text-align: justify;&#34;&gt;
    Among the bridges crossing the port of Beolgyo, the oldest Beolgyo Honggyo is the largest and most beautiful of the remaining Honggyo in Korea, and has been designated as Treasure No. 304. The former Vulgyo Financial Association (Registered Cultural Property No. 226) is a modern building that reflects Japanese architectural style and is currently used as an exhibition space for Korean currency companies. The old Boseong Inn (Registered Cultural Properties No. 132), which emerges from the novel as Namdo Inn, was restored and was born into a complex space with cafes, archives, exhibition hall, small theater, and accommodation. A night in a modern building will be a special experience.
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &amp;lt;Day trip course&amp;gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    Daewon Sa Tibet Museum and Sumi Gwangmyeong Tower → Daewonsa Temple → Boseong County Paikmin Museum → Seojaepil Memorial Park
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &amp;lt;2 days and 1 night trip course&amp;gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    Day 1 / Daewon Sa Tibet Museum and Sumi Gwangmyeong Tower → Daewonsa Temple → Boseong County Baekmin Museum → Seojaepil Memorial Park
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    Day 2 / Taebaek Mountain Range Memorial Hall → Taebaek Mountain Range Literature Tour
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    ○ Related website address
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    -Boseong Culture Tour
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://tour.boseong.go.kr&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;[새창열림]‘보성문화관광’ 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
     http://tour.boseong.go.kr
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    -Daewonsa Temple
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.daewonsa.or.kr&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;[새창열림]‘대원사’ 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
     http://www.daewonsa.or.kr
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    -Daewon Sa Tibet Museum
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.tibetan-museum.org&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;[새창열림]‘대원사티벳박물관’ 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
     http://www.tibetan-museum.org
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    -Taebaeksan Mountain Literature Museum
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://tour.boseong.go.kr/tbsm&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;[새창열림]‘태백산맥문학관’ 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
     http://tour.boseong.go.kr/tbsm
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    -Old Boseong Inn
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.boseonginn.org&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;[새창열림]‘구 보성여관’ 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
     http://www.boseonginn.org
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    ○ Inquiry phone
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    -Boseong County Office Cultural Tourism Division 061) 850-5214
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    -Daewonsa Temple 061) 852-1755
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    -Daewon Sa Tibet Museum 061) 852-3038
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    -Taebaeksan Mountain Literature Museum 061) 850-8653
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    -Old Boseong Inn 061) 858-7528
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    ○ Public transportation information
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    [Bus] Operates every 5 to 30 minutes (05:30 to 02:00 the next day) from Seoul-Gwangju and Central City Terminals, takes about 3 hours and 20 minutes. It takes about 2 hours and 30 minutes from the Gwangcheon Terminal Bus Stop at No. 217 Rural Fishing Village Bus and Sipyeong Terminal Bus Stop at Boseong-Beolgyo Rural Fishing Village Bus.
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    * Inquiry: Central City Terminal 02) 6282-0114 Express Bus Integrated Ticket
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.kobus.co.kr&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;[새창열림]‘고속버스통합예매’ 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
     http://www.kobus.co.kr
    &lt;/a&gt;
    Gwangju Youth Square 062) 360-8114,
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.usquare.co.kr&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;[새창열림]‘광주유스퀘어’ 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
     http://www.usquare.co.kr
    &lt;/a&gt;
    Hwasun Transportation 062) 373-5666
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    ○ Self-driving information
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    Honam Expressway → Gwangju 2nd Ring Road toward Hwasun → From Hwasun IC toward Beolgyo and Dongbok → From Guam Intersection toward Mofusan, Beolgyo and Boseong → From Daewonsa Intersection toward Daewonsa and Boseong County Baekmin Museum → Daewonsa
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    ○ Accommodation information
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    -Former Boseong Inn: Taebaeksanmac-gil, Beolgyo-eup, 061) 858-7528,
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.boseonginn.org&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;[새창열림]‘구 보성여관’ 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
     http://www.boseonginn.org
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    -Beolgyo Small Tourist Hotel: Beolgyo-eup Sinjeong-gil, 061) 858-9800,
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.벌교펜션호텔.kr&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;[새창열림]‘벌교소형관광호텔’ 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
     http://www.벌교펜션호텔.kr
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    -Hotel Dahyang: Joseong-myeon Joseong 3-gil, 061) 804-1004,
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.bosungcc.co.kr/html/facility/facility06.asp&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;[새창열림]‘호텔다향’ 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
     http://www.bosungcc.co.kr/html/facility/facility06.asp
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    ○ Restaurant information
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    -Boseong Nokcha Tteokgalbi Aid: Hanwoo Tteokgalbi, Boseong-eup, Heungseong-ro, 061) 853-0300,
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://보성떡갈비원조.crw.kr&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;[새창열림]‘보성녹차떡갈비원조’ 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
     http://보성떡갈비원조.crw.kr
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    -Subok Restaurant: Hanjeongsik, Boseong-eup Jungang-ro, 061) 853-3032,
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.수복식당.kr&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;[새창열림]‘수복식당’ 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
     http://www.수복식당.kr
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    -Kookil Restaurant: Komakjeongsik, Taebaeksanmac-gil, Beolgyo-eup, 061) 857-0588
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    ○ Festival and event information
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    -Boseong Cherry Blossom Festival: April 6, 2019, around the entrance of Daewonsa Temple, 061) 850-8281 ~ 4 (Mundeok-myeon Office)
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    ○ Things to see
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    Juam Lake, Yulpo Seawater Green Tea Center, Deokryang Station Memories Street, Korea Tea Museum
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p align=&#34;justify&#34;&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was created in March 2019, and may change later, so be sure to check it before you travel.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p align=&#34;justify&#34;&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;img src=&#34;https://support.visitkorea.or.kr/img/call?cmd=VIEW&amp;amp;id=66913896-8285-4e87-aec5-b969ff107303&amp;amp;mode=raw&#34; style=&#34;width:100%;&#34;/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>