<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jeollanam-do on Every Corner of Korea</title>
    <link>https://codecorea.github.io/tags/jeollanam-do/</link>
    <description>Every Corner of Korea (Jeollanam-do)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2020 03:16:32 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="https://codecorea.github.io/tags/jeollanam-do/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The breath of Alpine Sunsundo is scattered by the blue rain, Haenam Nokwoodang - Haenam-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/the-breath-of-alpine-sunsundo-is-scattered-by-the-blue-rain-haenam-nokwoodang-295/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2020 03:16:32 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/the-breath-of-alpine-sunsundo-is-scattered-by-the-blue-rain-haenam-nokwoodang-295/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Haenam-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;the-breath-of-alpine-sunsundo-is-scattered-by-the-blue-rain-haenam-nokwoodang--295&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Opened in 2010, the panoramic view of Gosan Yunseondo artifact exhibition hall - Haenam-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/295/377d26d2-bed3-419b-bcac-0069122b5f2f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Opened in 2010, the panoramic view of Gosan Yunseondo artifact exhibition hall
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   The breath of Alpine Sunsundo is scattered by the blue rain, Haenam Nokwoodang
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Haenam-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Everyone experiences the end in life. There are various ends, such as a scheduled one and a sudden one, but it is difficult to get used to it. It would be a similar context if we wanted to go to the &#39;end of the earth&#39; at least once. Because I have the expectation that I can start again after seeing the end of the earth and walking again. Following the expectation, people gather from Seoul to Cheonni-gil, so the land was once abandoned.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Namdo Exploration Station, Haenam, at the southern end of the Korean Peninsula
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    As the name suggests, the end of the Korean peninsula and the starting point of the land, as the name suggests, are located in the southernmost part of Haenam, the southernmost point of the peninsula. Thanks to this, people follow the symbolism of end and beginning to visit the end of Haenam. When departing from the metropolitan area, a full day is a distance you need to run. This is the reason why it is too much to look at the end of the earth after coming to Haenam. Let&#39;s take a look at every corner of Haenam. Haenam tour overflowing with highlights and food, starting from now on.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    When you open the map of Haenam, you can see the ruins of the high mountain Yunseon-do, Daeheungsa, Mihwangsa, and Gocheonam migratory birds that stretched out from side to side. A minimum of 2 nights and 3 days is required to properly explore all of this (based on self-driving from the metropolitan area). You can decide the route by adding or subtracting according to your preference and schedule. Remembering the end of the land where you can see both sunrises and sunsets, Mihwangsa, Gocheonam migratory birds, and flower gardens, which are considered as sunset points, can help you in choosing lodging and travel.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    If you enter Haenam Land after passing Haenam IC or Pyeongdong IC, there are nearby Gosan Yunseondo Historic Site and Daeheungsa Temple (Duryunsan Provincial Park). First, I visited the ruins of the Yunsan Island in Gosan and visited Daeheungsa Temple. After watching the sunset at Mihwangsa Temple, I decided to move to the end of the earth and stay for 1 night. The next day, it is a good time to see the sunrise of Memseom and look around the end of the earth. If the arrival time is in the afternoon, it is okay to first look at the end of the ground, watch the sunset and sunrise here, and then move in the opposite direction.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Haenam Yoon, a prestigious family member of the Joseon Dynasty, is full of artifacts
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The journey of Haenam starts from the ruins of Yunseon-do, Gosan. Haenam is full of attractions, but it is regrettable except for the high mountains. Let&#39;s take a look at the relics exhibition at Yunseon Island in Gosan and head to the Nokwoodang area (History No. 1, historical site No. 167). Dongseon also continues naturally.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Opened in 2010, Gosan Yunseondo Relics Exhibition shows the situation of the times through the works of Gosan and Haenam Yoon&#39;s servants. You can also naturally learn about Haenam Yoon&#39;s family, which was a prestigious father-in-law. Heirlooms from Gosan, as well as his great-grandson Yun Doo-seo&#39;s tribute portraits (National Treasure No. 240), are handed down from generation to generation. It&#39;s amazing that there are so many treasures in a house. Each of the relics that filled the exhibition hall is conveyed by the descendants of the descendants who have kept nothing but light. It seems that he is facing a distant alpine entity that he met only in textbooks through &amp;lt;The Fisherman History&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;Ouga&amp;gt;.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Artifact Exhibition Hall - Haenam-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/295/8aa86934-a617-445d-80b3-c46197e38914.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Artifact Exhibition Hall
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Let&#39;s take a look at Alpine. Gosan Yunseon (1587 ~ 1671). In 1628 (Injo 6), he started a manor at the beginning of the Byeolsimundae and became the master of Bongrimdaegun (Hyojong). Jung-soo, Noron&#39;s Yeong-su, Woo-am and Song Si-yeol. It would have been the best time of his political life filled with Guiyang and hermit. Nokwoodang is a house where the Bongrim Daegun descended to the throne and was given to the teacher, Gosan. The house in Suwon was moved to Gohaean as Hasan descended.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Artifact Exhibition Hall - Haenam-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/295/1eae8a0a-ff23-4683-8379-26abb6af6fb6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Artifact Exhibition Hall
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Alpine house in Visa Tree Forest, and Nokwoodang
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Haenam Yoon&#39;s Jongtaek, which embraces Anchae, Sarangchae, Gosan shrine, Eochoeun shrine, and Chuwondang, is also referred to as Nokwoodang (Historical Site No. 167). Dang Ho, &#39;Nokwoo&#39;, was written by Ikdong Iseo (1662 ~ 1723), the first author of Donggukjin.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Nokwoodang from the top - Haenam-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/295/531cbd2b-12ac-4a09-b8c6-59eb5aa7f71f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Nokwoodang from the top
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Nokwoodang&#39;s plate is also his work. He was close with Yoon Doo-seo, a great-grandson of high mountains. It is a &#39;green rain&#39; if you unravel the &#39;green&#39;. Rain, which falls when the grass and trees are green, means fresh water of life. In addition, it is often interpreted as the sound of ginkgo leaves in front of Nokdangdang and the wind that sweeps through the forest behind Ndungdang.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Yoon-Hik Yoon, the 14th descendant of Kosan, who protects Nokdang - Haenam-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/295/07fd6011-fe1d-4b40-acd5-006a0d32401a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Yoon-Hik Yoon, the 14th descendant of Kosan, who protects Nokdang
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Is it because it is so famous as an alpine site? Eure Nokdang is regarded as the birthplace of an alpine mountain. In fact it is not. Looking at the relics&#39; bilateral preliminary drafting document (Treasure No. 482-5), it can be seen that Alpine was adopted as a big house when he was 8 years old.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Naengwoodang, Sarangchae, where Haenam Yoon&#39;s Jongson stayed - Haenam-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/295/5cb4d4f5-0e4d-49eb-b9ee-e5693ec6833d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Naengwoodang, Sarangchae, where Haenam Yoon&#39;s Jongson stayed
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   When he first stepped on Haenam, he turned 25. Until then, he lived in Seoul. The longest stay in Seoul, except the 20 years spent in the exile in the life of Gosan in 1985, was Seoul. It is said that he stayed here in Haenam Nokwoodang for 6 years and Geumgye-dong for 9 years. I spent almost as much time in his hiding place in Bogildo, so if you want to feel more of the alpine trail, you should stop by Bogildo. At the end of the land, a passenger ship departs for Bogil Island (Ohwado Island).
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Naengwoodang, Sarangchae, where Haenam Yoon&#39;s Jongson stayed - Haenam-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/295/957904b0-bc01-4caa-b4cd-9857ffbf364e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Naengwoodang, Sarangchae, where Haenam Yoon&#39;s Jongson stayed
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It takes a lot of time to properly examine the remains of the Gosan Yunseondo Art Museum.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&amp;lt;Sanjungsingok&amp;gt; where you can see the alpine handwriting - Haenam-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/295/389eaeca-3905-44e7-953f-54b2d3e6d0e0.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     &amp;lt;Sanjungsingok&amp;gt; where you can see the alpine handwriting
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Nobi documents of the Goryeo Dynasty (Treasure No. 483), including books such as &amp;lt;Gold Chain Motive (Treasure No. 482-2)&amp;gt; &amp;lt;Sanjungsingok (Treasure No. 482-3)&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;The Fisherman&#39;s History&amp;gt; This is because there are plenty of things to see, such as the bilateral preliminary drafting document (Treasure No. 482-5).
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Manor level presentation right - Haenam-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/295/98d53f41-e9d9-4dcb-9a14-96ba163a6540.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Manor level presentation right
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The works of the great-grandson Gong-jae are also difficult. Self-portraits of the public offerings introduced earlier, including Doo-seo Yun (National Treasure No. 240), Gongjaehwahwa (Treasure No. 481), Baekmado (Treasure No. 481), Dongguk Yeoji Map (Treasure No. 481-3), still life paintings, and Jinkyungsan hydration The back is waiting.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;14&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Self-portrait of Yoon Doo-seo, a great-grandson of high mountains - Haenam-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/295/62266079-c205-48c1-b730-9d46c4c1e9c6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Self-portrait of Yoon Doo-seo, a great-grandson of high mountains
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Let&#39;s go to Nokwoodang after looking at the relics. The gently curved walls continue to shine. Interestingly, the towering gate is on the side.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;16&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The beauty figure that Yun Yong, the grandson of Gongjae, drew - Haenam-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/295/efb8c0a1-8b36-46ef-8e94-bb94d859d16c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The beauty figure that Yun Yong, the grandson of Gongjae, drew
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Haenam-gun Office&#39;s cultural commentator Park Mi-rye explained that it means &#34;I will live quietly without revealing myself to the world.&#34;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;18&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The rising gate of the alpine house facing sideways without facing Sarangchae - Haenam-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/295/645d59e5-5c43-4b0c-87a2-af1244ee3629.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The rising gate of the alpine house facing sideways without facing Sarangchae
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Nokwoodang is currently living in Gosan, the 14th descendant of Gosan. In the double eaves for heat preservation that was not used at the time by the Sadaebu, we can see the tradition of pursuing real-world poetry.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;20&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Stone wall path of a luxurious alpine house - Haenam-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/295/b3651f35-96d4-4fea-9c97-1446d27f275f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Stone wall path of a luxurious alpine house
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you go to Nokdangdan, walk along the stone wall to the Visa Tree Forest. After passing the alpine shrine, Haenam&#39;s ancestral ancestral fishery, Echo Hyo-jeong (1476 ~ 1543), passes through the shrine, and the Visa Tree Forest Road is designated as a natural monument. Eochoeun, Hyojeong Yoon, took the ground at Nokwoodang and laid the foundation for Haenam Yoon to flourish. It was said that the descendants planted the Visa tree in response to his instruction, &#34;If you see a rock on the back mountain, the village will be poor.&#34; This is also the reason why Haenam&#39;s delicacy was created. When they visited Mr. Haenam Yoon&#39;s Jongtaek, who said that farts would change, they were treated to Visa-made Korean tea and tea.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;22&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Alpine shrine - Haenam-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/295/e8c3285d-e2c1-42da-bd3d-0ff7b63617b8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Alpine shrine
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Even now, I haven&#39;t even been able to see Visa Gangjeong, but even in the middle of winter, I still soothe the rain in the midst of the rain. Did Alpine heard this rain here?
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;24&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Eochoeun Shrine - Haenam-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/295/f5abcc1c-0b1d-433d-8204-ee2e53654109.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Eochoeun Shrine
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   TIP Gosan Yunseondo Historic Site
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    To enter the ruins of the Alpine Yunseon-do, you have to pay an admission fee. 2,000 won for adults, 1,500 won for youth and military guards, and 1,000 won for children. You can also hear explanations from cultural commentators residing at the relics exhibition hall. Closed on Mondays, from 9am to 6pm. After inspecting the relics exhibition, it takes a generous 2 hours to go all the way to Nokwoodang&#39;s Bijarim walk.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     ▶ Contact
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Gosan Yunseondo Historic Site: 061-530-5548, 135 Nokwoodang-gil, Haenam-eup, Haenam-gun, Jeollanam-do
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Haenam-gun Office Cultural Tourism 061-530-5918
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Nearby restaurants
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    There are quite a few restaurants where you can taste Korean food and sashimi in towns and tourist areas near the county office. Chicken specialty shops, known as another delicacy in Haenam, are also gathered in Dongyeon-ri. There are many restaurants and lodging facilities at the end of the earth.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Cheonil Restaurant
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Hanjeongsik / Haenam-eup, Eupnaeri / 061-536-4001
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Seongjeong Han
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Han Jeong-sik / Gugyo-ri, Haenam-eup / 061-536-1060
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Honam Restaurant
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Hanjeongsik (Mushroom Course) / Samsan-myeon Gurim-ri / 061-534-5400
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Wired pipe
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Han Jeong-sik / Samrim-myeon Gurim-ri / 061-534-2959
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Longevity Chicken
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Chicken cuisine / Haenam-eup Dongdong-ri / 061-535-1003
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Hosanjeong
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Chicken cuisine / Haenam-eup Dongdong-ri / 061-534-8844
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Land End Garden Hall
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Songji Song Hori / 061-532-3004
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     End of the sea
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Songji Songhori / 061-534-6422
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Do it
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Songji Song Hori / 061-532-0005
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2.Accommodation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Land End Motel
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Songji Songhori / 061-535-5001
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Haenam Land End Hotel
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Namdong-gil, Haenam-eup / 061-530-8000
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Blue motel
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Songji Song Hori / 061-534-6677
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Wired pipe
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Daeheungsa-gil, Samsan-myeon / 061-534-2959
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.yuseongwan.com/html/main.php&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.yuseongwan.com/html/main.php
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was created in May 2016, and may be changed later, so be sure to check it before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The season of the hut is here. - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/the-season-of-the-hut-is-here-293/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2020 03:16:30 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/the-season-of-the-hut-is-here-293/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;the-season-of-the-hut-is-here--293&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;The charm of the rich tidal flats of Namdo - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/293/86007a6c-8bae-4824-80fa-8464c50359fd.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    The charm of the rich tidal flats of Namdo
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   The season of the hut is here.
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Cock. Before I called his name, he was just one of many fish and shellfish. However, when he calls his name, which starts from the name, “Kokmak”, born and raised in the volcanic Namdo tidal flat, turns on. Regardless of where you come from, it&#39;s just nice to be a kid, but there is no way to hide your excitement because the best companion “Beolgyo” is added. &#39;Bolgyo Komak&#39;, called the highest peak of Komak. How can we turn away from having a small festival there? In the autumn wind, a real cold energy is added, so we go to Bolgyo in season.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Namdo&#39;s tidal flats are rich in taste. When the cold breeze blows, I started to go to Boseong beolgyo to taste the chewy cock.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Beolgyo Cockle Festival celebrated 13 times this year - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/293/e935e9d7-1c75-4990-97b6-f249d4258eb3.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Beolgyo Cockle Festival celebrated 13 times this year
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The “Beolgyo Kok Festival”, which has already opened the gates of Kokcheol Cheol, which has already reached the 13th, has been held for three days since October 31st. The festival has passed briefly, but it is not necessary to be disappointed as the start is from now on.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;It has been going on for three days since October 31st. - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/293/b69bbc7d-e203-4bfd-9613-5c5748101dba.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     It has been going on for three days since October 31st.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Let&#39;s go for a taste of the chilly wind that gets more chewy!
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   For those who are still curious, let&#39;s take a moment to take a look at the Kkot Festival. The annual Beolgyo Coal Festival held from the end of October to the beginning of November is the main festival along the Beolgyo Stream.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Daepo Village where various experience events were held - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/293/681c24a0-fb2c-4685-895c-925a76f77ea9.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Daepo Village where various experience events were held
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Hands-on fishing, running in the tidal flats are held in Daepo-ri, a small fishing village. If you really want to collect the cockle, you have to go to the farther sea, but on the day of the festival, sprinkle the cockle in the mudflat for an experiential event.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Daepo Village where various experience events were held - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/293/d5b81564-6290-446f-8a56-e196a916c169.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Daepo Village where various experience events were held
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   All experience events are free to participate, and even the smallest ones can be tasted in full.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Beolgyocheon Stream held the opening ceremony of the Beolgyo Kok Festival on November 1st. - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/293/e0b75dba-cfca-4691-b537-1ec785c4a6f9.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Beolgyocheon Stream held the opening ceremony of the Beolgyo Kok Festival on November 1st.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Exciting experiences are overflowing. If you aren&#39;t afraid that your whole body will be mud-filled, you can challenge &#39;Kokkakki&#39; if you can only allow the amount of salty water on your hands. Also, don&#39;t miss the “Let&#39;s boil the tasting”, which is the most expected of everyone who participates in the Kolk Festival.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;On the day of the Kokmak Festival, an experience event was held around Bolgyocheon. - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/293/6cf3c838-b774-442e-8ea5-39af17957ddf.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     On the day of the Kokmak Festival, an experience event was held around Bolgyocheon.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Various experience streets are waiting for you to enjoy the rugged tidal flats of Namdo Island, such as a boat ride experience and running a tidal flat.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;On the day of the Kokmak Festival, an experience event was held around Bolgyocheon. - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/293/c8d952e1-64d2-4ada-9dee-7d212a17b0f3.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     On the day of the Kokmak Festival, an experience event was held around Bolgyocheon.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Let&#39;s just eat it as a cock festival. Events that awaken the five senses, such as the K-pop festival, the novel &amp;lt;Taebaek Mountain Range&amp;gt;, a literary tour, and a small song show, add to the depth of the festival.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Poomba Performance - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/293/be103866-e447-4726-aefe-777ed9a8b4a5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Poomba Performance
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Now that we have looked at the past festivals, let&#39;s go on a full-scale trip. No matter how ‘Beolgyo’ is ‘Kokmak’, ‘Kokmak’ is ‘Beolgyo’, but where can I taste it? In addition to Kokmak, Yangdae Mountain Mountain and Daeha Fiction &amp;lt;Taebaek Mountain Mountain&amp;gt;, which represent Beolgyo, cannot be overlooked. Between Suncheon and Boseong, the beolgyo, which embraces the warm tidal flats of the women&#39;s and Suncheon bays, is the actual stage of Jung Tae-rae&#39;s novel &amp;lt;Taebaeksanmaek&amp;gt;, which deals with the tragedy of cognitive conflict caused by ideological confrontation. It has been loved as a literary destination since. The Kokmak Festival was also held under the theme of ‘Takbaek Mountain Range Literary Tour according to the taste of Kokmak at Beolgyo’.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;14&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Korean Traditional Music Event - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/293/b22c7567-76c7-4a3f-ab17-3346cb80f926.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Korean Traditional Music Event
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   The actual stage of the novel &amp;lt;Taebaek Mountain Range&amp;gt;
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   right. &amp;lt;Taebaek Mountain Range&amp;gt; comes first if you enter the &#39;Bulgyo&#39; land. In the novel, &#39;Kok-mak&#39;, which the bee-gyo bears, appears to stimulate the imaginative imagination. Let&#39;s take a look at &amp;lt;Taebaek Mountain Range&amp;gt; for a moment. The background of the novel was the year of the Yeosun incident in 1948, when the punishment of the left wing occupied the military again and was confused. It starts with a scene where left-wing secret party member Jung Ha-seop enters the punishment.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Beolgyo, the first literary tour that can travel on both feet - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/293/46c07eff-419c-434c-95ba-7aae206f8dd0.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Beolgyo, the first literary tour that can travel on both feet
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The house of fire hydrant and Hyunbu Pines, where Jung Ha-seop was hiding, also keep their place. If you know &amp;lt;Taebaek Mountain Range&amp;gt;, you must be glad. The scene where the background in the novel and the movie unfolds in front of the eyes adds &#39;uniqueness&#39; to the trip to beolgyo. It has a meaning of multiplicity, adding to history and culture, rather than just a travel destination. The bridges over Beolgyocheon that penetrate the town of Beolgyo greet travelers. Even looking at these ‘legs’ can make a great beolgyo trip. An iron bridge where Yeom Sang-gu competes with a double sword to take control of the fist world of punishment. The bridges I saw in the novel, such as the Buyonggyo, where many people died due to conflict between the North and the South, are hanging on the beolgyocheon.
   &lt;br/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Beolgyo, the first literary tour that can travel on both feet - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/293/1222f926-2641-4bb3-b2af-83ff9a5585e2.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Beolgyo, the first literary tour that can travel on both feet
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Buyonggyo, also known as the ‘Sohwa Bridge’, is not just a bridge. A number of people died here during the Yeosun incident and when the rebels were suppressed. Now, a new bridge that allows vehicles to pass is added. When you go upstream of the digestive bridge, you will see Honggyo (Treasure No. 304), which Yeom Sang-jin stacked up to distribute to the tenants the rice they stole. It is said that this place has a bridge made of rafts, and the place has been named “Bulgyo”. Honggyo, located on the foot of a raft bridge, was built as a stone bridge in 1729 by a draft missionary. It became the Rainbow Bridge since the bridge was repaired in 1737 (Yeongjo 13).
   &lt;br/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Beolgyo Market where you can see various marine products - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/293/4cd40e5c-c9de-402c-ab91-5b71e7c95172.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Beolgyo Market where you can see various marine products
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In addition, there are also middle school rooms, night school clubs, Namdo inn, and Kim Bum-woo&#39;s home, which were used as lodging units for the Tobal University. It is a space that embraces the modern and contemporary history of Korea, where the ideology in conflict with the sorrow lost to the country aimed at the sword.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Beolgyo Market where you can see various marine products - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/293/603c6909-2c24-4377-a2fe-1ccd91e2167d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Beolgyo Market where you can see various marine products
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Hand is going, hand is going, on the chewy little cock!
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Now, following the &amp;lt;Taebaek Mountain Range&amp;gt;, we took a tour of the history of Bolkyo, so it&#39;s time to taste it. In the novel &amp;lt;Taebaek Mountain Range&amp;gt;, a small cock also appears. This is a scene where the firefighter who met Jeong Ha-seop is preparing for breakfast and regrets that there is no kid, and Yeom Sang-gu compares the outsider&#39;s house to &#39;it looks like a winter kid&#39;. In particular, after digesting Jeong Ha-seop, after one night, preparing for breakfast, he regrets that there is no skewer.
   &lt;br/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Bokkocheon boasts a chewy taste and grows best in the tidal flats around the Gaet River where fresh water flows from the sea. Is that so? With the tidal flats that only contain women, the people of beolgyo are called ‘Cham 뻘’. Here I am a cockerel. The wrinkles are deep and the skin is hard. It&#39;s chewy, chewy, and even smells of the sea. It is delicious just to eat and delicious as a side dish.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The left side of the picture is a true black - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/293/85719bc1-31c3-43c2-bfe3-728a36bc96ec.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The left side of the picture is a true black
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It&#39;s not just that there&#39;s a true little. There is also a new style of cock called a cock of a cocky name. The wrinkles of the shell are relatively shallow compared to the true corn. Some people say that the taste is slightly deteriorated. Looking at the true and new cock, you can clearly distinguish them only by their appearance. Chamkomak is the most delicious from Chuseok to New Year&#39;s Day, but it is hard to taste chewy and firm komak until early March in spring.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;15&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The left side of the picture is a true black - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/293/4ab5f5f5-0ba5-45fd-8a1b-055dcf468128.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The left side of the picture is a true black
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   There are many specialty shops around the festival grounds located around Beolgyocheon. You can taste Kokmak as a side dish at a restaurant in the town of Beolgyo, but it is still unfortunate to pass a Kokmak restaurant. The komak set meal is about 15,000 won per person. Various kinds of small dishes such as boiled buckwheat and fresh buckwheat, simmered skewer, and simmered skewer come out.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;16&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Kokjeong set Korean food at Bolgyo - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/293/e258aaf8-b821-4858-b63c-63592bd93288.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Kokjeong set Korean food at Bolgyo
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Don&#39;t let your feet fall off with a delicious cock. I am sorry to find out the price. Even during the festival, it is a small cock boasting of a reasonable ransom price. Chamkomak is 15,000 ~ 7000 won per 1kg, and the new komak is cheaper than that.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;17&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Spicy seasoning with spicy and sour sauce - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/293/4546c254-cf1f-4d92-a663-46613924ab17.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Spicy seasoning with spicy and sour sauce
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Remember that you can buy a small price at the beejangjang on the 4th and 9th, and at the morning stand in front of the beolgyo station every morning.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;18&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Fried chicken with vegetables and eggs - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/293/c62b4804-8042-4b4b-985f-e83caab2b361.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Fried chicken with vegetables and eggs
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1.Nearby Restaurants
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Dick Cock Restaurant: Chaedongseon-ro, Beolgyo-eup / 061-858-2255
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The original small house: Jeongjorae-gil, Beolgyo-eup, Boseong-gun / 061-857-9919
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.bgkomak.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.bgkomak.com/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Jangdo Well-being Komak Set: Boseong 1-gil Market 1-gil / 061-858-9300
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2.Accommodation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Boseong Inn: Taebaeksanmac-gil, Beolgyo-eup, Boseong-gun / 061-858-7528
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.boseonginn.org/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.boseonginn.org/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Grand Motel: Boseong-gun, Boseong-gun / 061-858-5050
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Daedojang: Boseong-gun, Boseong-gun / 061-858-0039
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Boseong Da Beach Condo: Chungui-ro, Hoecheon-myeon, Boseong-gun / 061-850-1114
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.dabeach.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.dabeach.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was updated in December 2015, and may be changed later, so please check before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gourmet Tour of National Road No. 2 ④Boseong ~ Jangheung, Boseong Green Tea, Beolgyo Komak, Jangheung Hanwoo Samhap - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/gourmet-tour-of-national-road-no-2-boseong-jangheung-boseong-green-tea-beolgyo-komak-jangheung-hanwoo-samhap-285/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 22:54:34 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/gourmet-tour-of-national-road-no-2-boseong-jangheung-boseong-green-tea-beolgyo-komak-jangheung-hanwoo-samhap-285/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;gourmet-tour-of-national-road-no-2-boseong-jangheung-boseong-green-tea-beolgyo-komak-jangheung-hanwoo-samhap--285&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;The main characters of Jangheung Hanwoo Samhap are Korean beef, clams and mushrooms. - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/285/b627c1fe-efe8-43b4-a5c8-fcef8d3a6e5b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    The main characters of Jangheung Hanwoo Samhap are Korean beef, clams and mushrooms.
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Gourmet Tour of National Road No. 2 ④Boseong ~ Jangheung, Boseong Green Tea, Beolgyo Komak, Jangheung Hanwoo Samhap
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Passing through the Seomjin River and entering the Honam region, a feast of authentic taste unfolds. After passing Hadong, he entered Jeolla-do Land, which is commonly known as &#39;Namdo&#39; through Gwangyang. From Gwangyang, where you have finished your last taste tour, you will go directly to Boseong along National Highway 2. It&#39;s time to enjoy the taste of Boseong (Beolgyo) and Jangheung. The sky rises and the horses begin to eat in this season, the foodies of Namdo.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Gwangyang&#39;s bulgogi also tastes good, but maybe it&#39;s probably from now on that you feel the food of Namdo. Anyone who has visited Namdo will have a memory that was fascinated by a side dish with a land, sea, and sea ball that would fill up a statue even if only one hundred and a half were ordered. Even if you don&#39;t have to look for delicacies, what is the taste of naro from this land that is delicious enough? The saliva goes beyond just imagining how generous it will be.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Boseong first. If there is Hadong in Yeongnam, there is Boseong in Honam. All are famous for cars. Boseong, famous for its green tea fields, has been successful in commercializing green tea not only as a “landscape” but also as a “flavor”. When asked, &#34;What is the best thing in the Boseong green tea field?&#34; The sensation of touching the tongue is more clearly remembered than seen with the eyes. The soft ice cream with a rich green tea flavor kept me looking for green tea ice cream while I was in Boseong. Not only that. Pork raised with Boseong green tea. Boseong green money is also indispensable.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    At the same time, pigs raised by feeding green tea are added with green tea powder, so they feel less and the greenness of green tea is added. (Even though it&#39;s hard to understand) Even those who don&#39;t eat pork well have a difference when they see chopsticks if they are Bosung green beans. It is not difficult to see around Dawon in every corner of Boseong.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Boseong Daehan Dawon - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/285/abb186ca-ddc3-4e95-8c69-32498f4c221c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Boseong Daehan Dawon
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Once you taste it, you can&#39;t forget it
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    And there is another place, Boseong, which Boseong embraces. The first thing that comes to mind before saying &#39;Don&#39;t be proud in punishment&#39; is a short story. It is a beolgyo that has been recessed inland even in South Island. Thanks to this, only a woman, such as a woman, had a generous tidal flat, and here it is a stiff cock.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    People here are proud of the scampi, saying, “Three months in the cold, the taste of the scampi doesn&#39;t change even if it tastes like a predisposition.” Thanks to its exceptionally chewy and deep flavor, it has also been awarded to the King Surasang, the small school of beolgyo. The season starts in late October when the cold breeze begins to blow. In the market located in Beolgyo, there is a lot of enthusiasm, and the people who try to taste it are also continuing. Of course, the world is now better. You can taste anything at any time, regardless of season, but still, the taste of the cockle taste in season is different from that of frozen.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Boseong Bridge, the delicacy of Boseong Sea - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/285/b29679c6-58c6-4b51-9b6f-5d35e4316b3f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Boseong Bridge, the delicacy of Boseong Sea
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In the past, it was overflowing in November, and it was said that “after the water seal, the generous one was the cock seal”, and now it has become so famous that it has become a precious body weighing more than 10,000 won per kg. Remember that this also depends on how much you get each year.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Difference between true cock and new cock - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/285/a8151589-d3a6-4f58-9c0a-f2503b403ed1.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Difference between true cock and new cock
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It is divided into three types: the natural kommak, the new kommak, and the pikomak. The persimmon comes from the name, but it beats the true name. Some people say that the new cock is better. It is said that a new cock with few goals and only stripes is a shit cock. Boil and serve as a side dish. When you go to the restaurant, the side dish that you serve is the new side. Relatively large blood cork is added to the seasoning and eaten in circuit. The crispy texture is delicious.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Difference between true cock and new cock - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/285/afee48f0-cd64-4634-8a7a-a832de7d1259.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Difference between true cock and new cock
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   No matter how you eat it, how will the people here taste it? Marketers say, &#34;Just eat boiled skewer, eat grilled skewer, eat it even if you boil it.&#34;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Cinnamon - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/285/2df62bd4-97b2-4660-b6b1-9f467acc3b44.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Cinnamon
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   You can taste boiled and simmered skewer if you order a skewer set meal of 12,000 won per serving.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A small battle - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/285/d6b61a52-c865-4212-ac94-f0334ff21155.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A small battle
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Hanwoo met the key shell and mushroom, Jangheung Hanwoo Samhap
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   “Feast of Taste” is probably a word for him. Jangheung Hanwoo Samhap, who adds high quality Korean beef to fresh clams and mushrooms, is a longing for tasting sometime for those who know his existence. The reason why such hot food was born can be seen by looking at Jangheung for a while.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Jangheung Hanwoo Samhap Hansang - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/285/baa2cf2c-d7ff-42e6-97f6-6a61793253a6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Jangheung Hanwoo Samhap Hansang
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Jangheung is considered to be the nation&#39;s largest producer of Korean beef that produces and consumes 56,000 Korean beef a year. In the sea he harbors, another key shellfish, which is considered as another delicacy in Jangheung, appears. As the representative delicacies of the land and the sea have met, the expectation will definitely increase. Add some mushrooms that are good for your body! What can you say before you taste it?
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Jangheung Hanwoo - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/285/61fe4022-90b5-47b8-8442-5026d3efe933.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Jangheung Hanwoo
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    If you want to taste Korean beef in Jangheung, Jeonnam, you can visit Jeongnamjin Saturday Market, where Korean beef streets are created. It is said that Janghung has more Korean beef than Jangheung Gunmin, so Jangheung is the hometown of Korean beef. When looking for a Saturday market, “Korean native cattle”, which was only heard in words, comes into contact with the skin. Samwoo Restaurant as well as Korean beef wholesalers are located all over the place, making it easy to buy and taste only ingredients.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Key shells and mushrooms of Janheung Korean beef - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/285/ef70e505-6a7e-42f4-80cf-217e4493c3f9.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Key shells and mushrooms of Janheung Korean beef
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The main ingredients of Hanwoo Samhap are Korean beef, clams and mushrooms. If you buy ingredients and enter the restaurant, you can enjoy Samhap at a small price. If there are not a lot of people, it is wise to go directly to the &#39;meat shop&#39; that serves as a restaurant. Select the desired amount of Korean beef from the desired site. Key clams and mushrooms are tied together, so you can prepare them according to the amount of meat.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;How to enjoy Jangheung Hanwoo Samhap - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/285/7314f9b1-2fa8-48ae-bc4b-b4097befbad8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     How to enjoy Jangheung Hanwoo Samhap
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    There is nothing enviable in the world at that moment if you put a key shell, Korean beef, and mushrooms on a heated plate. Although it varies slightly depending on the site, even if you choose the finest flower sirloin, you can enjoy Samhap as much as any glutton if it costs 30,000 to 40,000 won per person. Tall clams and mushrooms cost 15,000 won per pack.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;How to enjoy Jangheung Hanwoo Samhap - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/285/eb5402a1-24fd-402a-96e6-3f563ebf00d5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     How to enjoy Jangheung Hanwoo Samhap
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Key clams and mushrooms catch the taste that can be felt with Korean beef alone. It is difficult to cook too closely to preserve the taste of each ingredient. The song comes out at one point in Samhap. Namdo&#39;s customs are not in vain.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;How to enjoy Jangheung Hanwoo Samhap - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/285/35fd4114-1b2e-4255-9aee-ec6e113fdec6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     How to enjoy Jangheung Hanwoo Samhap
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1.Nearby Restaurants
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;strong&gt;
   &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ▶ Bosung
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Chamok Arboretum
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    : Nokdon / Hoecheon-myeon / 061-853-5558
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Special Hall
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    : Nokdon / Boseong-eup / 061-852-4545
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.specialhouse.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.specialhouse.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     The original small restaurant
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    : Komak / Beolgyo-eup / 061-857-9919
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Cock small restaurant
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    : Komak / Beolgyo-eup / 061-858-2255
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Beolgyo Small Restaurant
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    : Komak / Beolgyo-eup / 061-857-7675
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     ▶ Jangheung
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Sinnokwon Hall
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    : Traditional Korean meal / 10-33 Donggyo-ro, Jangheung-eup / 061-863-6622
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Sea House
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    : Kijogaemuchim / 139 Sumun Yonggok-ro, Anyang-myeon, Jangheung-gun / 061-862-1021
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Village Restaurant
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    : Grilled beef sirloin / 36 Mullebanganggan-gil, Jangheung-eup, Jangheung-gun / 061-863-2584
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2.Accommodation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;strong&gt;
   &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ▶ Bosung
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Boseong Da Beach Condo
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    : Hoecheon-myeon / 061-850-1114
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Dahyang Motel
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    : Hoecheon-myeon / 010-5347-8733
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.greenteamotel.com/www/index.html&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.greenteamotel.com/www/index.html
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     ▶ Jangheung
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Jinsong Tourist Hotel
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    : 1, Donggyo 2-gil, Jangheung-eup / 061-864-7775
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.jinsonghotel.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.jinsonghotel.com/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Cypress Forest Woodland
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    : 180 Woodland-gil, Jangheung-eup / 061-864-0063
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Spa Resort Andante
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    : 270, Sumunyonggok-ro, Anyang-myeon, Jangheung-gun / 061-862-2100
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was created in September 2013, and may change later, so be sure to check it before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A beautiful island called Soheoksando, Sinan Uido - Sinan-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/a-beautiful-island-called-soheoksando-sinan-uido-226/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 07:43:04 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/a-beautiful-island-called-soheoksando-sinan-uido-226/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Sinan-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;a-beautiful-island-called-soheoksando-sinan-uido--226&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Sonam Jeongjeong Village from the exile site - Sinan-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/226/6c56a0de-cd9f-4ed7-b069-623cb97c789b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Sonam Jeongjeong Village from the exile site
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   A beautiful island called Soheoksando, Sinan Uido
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Sinan-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Uido, named after the ears of a cow, is an island about three and a half hours away from Mokpo by boat and is well known for its sand dunes. It is a beautiful island not only with clear and clean beaches such as Donmok, Seongchon, and the beach beyond the band, but also the scenery of the tea ceremony on the top of Sangsanbong. It is also the exile site of the Sonam Jeongyakjeon and remains a dock in the Joseon Dynasty that retains the old image. Let&#39;s take a look at the history of Uido along with the unexplored Uido.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Fragrance of Jeongyakjeon in Truth Village, 《Pyohae Shimsal》 and Uido Dock
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    A ferry to Uido departing from Mokpo Coastal Passenger Terminal arrives in Uido in three and a half hours via Tochodo. Kaido, which serves as the gate of Uido, greets the passenger ship first, and the ship arrives at Uido Port, where the truth village (Ui 1 District) is located. On the other side of Uido Port, where the truth village is located, you can see East and West Souido and Songdo. Uido is the name given to Dori and Mokseom, which protrude to the west of the island, resembling the shape of a cow&#39;s ears. Other names are called Sogu Island and Ugaedo Island. Uido is mostly dependent on fishing because it has very few farmland due to the development of mountainous areas around Sangsanbong, the highest elevation on the island, 359m above sea level.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In Uido, there are quite a few historical and cultural heritages. In 1801, the brothers Son Jeong-jak and Dasan Jeong Yak-yong went on their way to Guiyang after spending the last night at Yuljeongjeom intersection at Geumseongsan Mountain in Naju. The exile site of Jeongyakjeon was Uido, which was called Soheksando Island. Heuksando is well-known as the place of exile in Jeongyakjeon, but Jeongyakjeon seems to have loved Uido more. He first settled in Uido, and only in 1807 went into Heuksan-do, 40 km from Uido. There is also a record that the Jeong Yak-jeon was caught secretly at night to go to Ui-do near the land.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   During the exile in Daeheksan-do, Jeong Yak-jeon, who left behind 《Assassin ’, left a book titled‘ Pyohae-shim ’during his exile in Soeuksan-do. The story of Pyohae Shim-moon tells the story of Moon Soon-deuk, who lived as a spearfisher on Soheksan Island. Moon Soon-deuk, who learned of Jeong Yak-jeon during his exile, went to buy a redfish on a nearby Taesado Island and drifted to meet Pung Rang. He survived fortunately, and returned to his hometown in three years and two months through Okinawa, the Philippines, Macau, Nanjing and Beijing. In the 9th year article of the Joseon Dynasty, there was a record in the article of the 9th year of King Sunjo, saying, &#34;I order you to repatriate the drifter of the country of transit.&#34; He unveiled the full story that he experienced while traveling around the world different from that of Joseon to Jeong Yak-jeon, and the book he wrote based on his dictation is the poetry. In Uido, there remains the birthplace of Hong Soo Jangsu, Sun Soon-deuk, along with the exile of Son Am Jeong-jeon.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sonam Jeongjajeon Exile - Sinan-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/226/d2e1a81c-ea5f-41ae-a4a5-c198c4fe8022.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sonam Jeongjajeon Exile
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    At the entrance to the Truth Village, there are traces of Uido&#39;s strategic importance in the Joseon Dynasty. This is the Uido dock. Uido was also used as a naval base during the Joseon Dynasty, and it is said that there was a gwan-a and a hill at the foot of the truth village. The Uido Dock was created in 1745 during the Joseon Dynasty. He was responsible for the function of the muzzle to anchor the ship, the breakwater to prevent waves, and the shipyard to build and repair the ship. In fact, it is said that the boat was cut from a nearby mountain in the mountains. The Uido dock is made by stacking stones at a height of 3m. In the center of the dock, there is also a relay line that binds the boat. The Uido Dock is the oldest and most intact dock in Korea, and was designated as Monument No. 243 in Jeollanam-do.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Uido dock built in the Joseon Dynasty - Sinan-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/226/b7dd3a57-9439-4475-8db9-3f2d7d25027d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Uido dock built in the Joseon Dynasty
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Meeting the Unexplored Uido Islands
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Where to stay in Uido is Truth Village in the east of Uido, Donmok in the west, and Seongchon Village. If you want to look around Uido, you have to bear the inconvenience of moving on foot. The mountain and sea can be enjoyed at the same time, making it a very attractive place for travelers who have plenty of time or want to enjoy nature.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The beach beyond the band, located about 1 km away from the truth village, is not well known due to the popularity of Donmok and Seongchon Beach, but it is the most beautiful beach in Uido. Beyond the band, the beach is a place that has many belts used instead of rice straw when connecting thatch roofs. The belt reaches the beach only when it crosses a hill that forms a colony like a field.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox type2 clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Way to the beach beyond the band - Sinan-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/226/42e4ad3b-3e4f-4181-995e-bc8c9428410c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Way to the beach beyond the band
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The band that came from the beach beyond the field - Sinan-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/226/21c6a1b4-10f2-43c6-8ad1-2366d83da757.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The band that came from the beach beyond the field
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    If you climb the uphill road about 500m from the crossroads over the band, the beach spreads out over the band down the hill. On the hills, there are piles of rainrooms (stone walls) built to prevent wind. When you descend the hill, the beach beyond the band, about 1km long, reveals itself. The foot of the mountain, which descended from Sangsanbong, fell to the beach, separating the beach beyond the band and the Seongchon beach beyond. It is a fault that the waves are strong, but it is perfect for swimming in the sea because it has a fine and hard white sand.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox type3 clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Beach Beyond a Beautiful Band - Sinan-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/226/8adb4518-1ca8-4a97-a27e-0487318b70f0.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Beach Beyond a Beautiful Band
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Beach Beyond a Beautiful Band - Sinan-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/226/11d515c7-485e-4f0d-a285-5751b8d3c5de.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Beach Beyond a Beautiful Band
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The sand dune that meets at the edge of the beach beyond the band - Sinan-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/226/28ec644c-312b-4de8-91a9-1157e48a88b7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The sand dune that meets at the edge of the beach beyond the band
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    When you come out of the crossroads over the beach and go up the road to Donmok and Seongchon villages, you reach the truth hill near the water supply source of Uido people. The truth hill is a way to climb to the highest peak in Uido, Sangsan Peak. The road is not rough, so you can climb without hesitation. After about 10 minutes, the mountain peaks around Sangsan Peak slowly appear. Uido&#39;s appearance is clear along the border between the island and the sea. As you climb the Sangsan Peak, the breathtaking view of the tea ceremony unfolds so that your heart can pierce. To the east, the truth village is not visible due to the peak in front of Sangsan Peak, but there are more and more islands off the coast of Sinan, including Uido Port and Gado, Songdo, East and West Souido, as well as Bigeumdo, Tochodo, Hauido, and Sangha and Hataedo. . To the west, it overlooks Donmok Village, Seongchon Village, and the Donmok Beach filling the gap. In the mountains, traces of villages are also found. It is the first town in Uido, but it is now the ruins of Daechori Village.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox type3 clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Donmok Village, Seongchon Village, and Donmok Beach from Sangsanbong - Sinan-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/226/953fc3c6-51e8-4150-a71d-9ef38df58a6a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Donmok Village, Seongchon Village, and Donmok Beach from Sangsanbong
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The scenery seen from the way up the mountain - Sinan-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/226/27ab2069-abce-41a2-b544-d0bd5c1ca793.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The scenery seen from the way up the mountain
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;From the top of Sangsanbong, toward the truth village - Sinan-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/226/1ad806f5-b163-44b2-99a7-7c969c83aaa5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     From the top of Sangsanbong, toward the truth village
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Uido&#39;s real exhaust, sand dunes and Donmok beach
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    camp
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   After passing Daechori Village, you will reach Donmok Beach. The left side of Donmok Beach is Donmok Village and the right side is Seongchon Village. The sand dunes on Donmok Beach are Uido&#39;s representative spots. It is also the place where the protagonist, Democrat Kim Ji-soo, was found in the film &amp;lt;Autumn&amp;gt; for a documentary filming. The sand dunes are 100m above sea level and 20m wide, and are known as the largest Pungseong sand dunes in the East. Between Seongchon Beach and Donmok Beach, the beach and sand dunes go well together. Right now, it is forbidden to enter the park to protect the sand dunes, but it&#39;s a painful effort to get back to the old look. At the moment, you can&#39;t go in and out to protect the sand dunes, but the scenery of the sand dunes looking over the Donmok Beach changes from time to time.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox type2 clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Daechori Village - Sinan-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/226/64967c20-1c43-4785-9890-b6c1c8cd8589.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Daechori Village
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The restored Daechori well - Sinan-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/226/8eda2b48-8bea-4e7d-ab9c-4c6a0710f159.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The restored Daechori well
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Located between Donmok Village and Seongchon Village, Donmok Beach has a long beach about 1.5km long. This sandy and hard beach is the most popular beach in Uido. In particular, this year, it was selected as one of the cleanest beaches in the water quality test of 187 beaches. Dalmulge is full of people&#39;s feet on the beach of Donmok. It is said to be the largest dwelling colony in Korea. When it feels popular, the crab quickly runs away with cute side steps.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Uido Sand Dunes and Seongchon Village seen from Donmok Beach - Sinan-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/226/dac6e4dc-5350-4006-b2a6-8c5869674bb9.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Uido Sand Dunes and Seongchon Village seen from Donmok Beach
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The ferry to Uido departs once a day from Mokpo. The trip is a bit unique, so if you take advantage of it, your trip to Uido will be easier. When you depart from Mokpo at 11:40 am, you will first arrive at the truth village of Ui 1-gu via Tochodo, and then arrive clockwise through East and West Soido, Yeri, Donmok, and Seongchon. The ship departs at Tocho-do for one day and departs at 6 am. After passing through the opposite directions of Seongchon, Donmok, Yeri, Dong-seoso-ido, and Truth, we go to Mokpo through Tocho-do.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox type2 clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Uido Sand Dunes seen from Donmok Beach - Sinan-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/226/557f913d-cef1-4fd7-844d-9462cfdd1972.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Uido Sand Dunes seen from Donmok Beach
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;15&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Dalrang crab I met at Donmok Beach - Sinan-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/226/833dc49c-0783-4196-b77d-4074ecb0e465.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Dalrang crab I met at Donmok Beach
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    1.Access
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    * Self-driving
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Seohaean Expressway Mokpo IC → Turn left at Yeonsan-dong Intersection → Go straight about 4.3km → Mokpo Coastal Passenger Terminal
    &lt;br/&gt;
    ※ Passenger ships to Uido depart from Mokpo Coastal Passenger Terminal at 11:40 am (approximately 3 hours 30 minutes via Tochodo)
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    2. Restaurants around
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Seolhee Neminbak: Home-style Baekban / 34-7 Uijin-ri-gil, Tocho-myeon, Sinan-gun / 061-262-7056
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    3.Accommodation
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Seolhee Neminbak: 34-7, Uijin-ri-gil, Docho-myeon, Sinan-gun / 061-262-7056
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Damoamine Park: 33-1 Donmok-gil, Tocho-myeon, Sinan-gun / 061-261-4455
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Seongchon B &amp;amp; B: 33 Seongchon-gil, Docho-myeon, Sinan-gun / 061-261-5187
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    ※ The above information was created in July 2013, and may change later, so be sure to check it before you travel.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Invitation for “Time Travel” from Naju-eupseong - Naju-si, Jeollanam-do, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/invitation-for-time-travel-from-najueupseong-201/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 08:08:44 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/invitation-for-time-travel-from-najueupseong-201/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Naju-si, Jeollanam-do, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;invitation-for-time-travel-from-najueupseong--201&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Wansacheon - Naju-si, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/201/73d9bd31-9338-4e44-9c29-9a8b0735fda2.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Wansacheon
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Invitation for “Time Travel” from Naju-eupseong
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Naju-si, Jeollanam-do, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Naju is a large flat area with a mountain facing the river. It is good to live in the beautiful Gangsan, so it is natural for people to gather. So many stories are piled up in Naju. The main story is about Naju-eupseong.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   &#39;Wansacheon&#39;, a kind of water with willow leaves
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    I have a place to stop before entering Naju-eupseong. Headed to &#39;Wansacheon&#39; where Wang Geon met a woman who fell in love at first sight. Before Wang Geon built Goryeo, he came to Naju as a general of the royal court to fight the dog. At a spring, a woman washing clothes asked for a bowl of water, and a willow leaf floated in the water that the woman passed. If you drink it in a hurry, you may pretend that it will float. This woman is the wife of Queen Oh. The background of this story is Wansacheon. It is also a historical point from the Three Kingdoms period to the Goryeo Dynasty and from ancient society to medieval society.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Goryeo&#39;s and Naju&#39;s deep relationship are conveyed in the sculptures of horseback Wang Geon and Queen Janghwa. &#39;Jeonrado&#39; is a very important place since Naju, from the point of view that Goryeo Hyeonjong was named after the first ruler of Jeonju and Naju and the place where Hyeonjong escaped due to the invasion of Georan was Naju.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Wang Geon and Queen Rain Boots - Naju-si, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/201/c09e856f-c0b4-4293-ad3e-3daeafd6296c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Wang Geon and Queen Rain Boots
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   &#39;Najumok Cultural Center&#39; at a glance telling the story of Najumok in 1000
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The words that often appear when talking about Naju are &#39;najumok&#39;, &#39;pastor&#39; and &#39;moksagol&#39;. You can check the importance of Naju at that time in the common &#39;Thu&#39;. Mok is an administrative unit of Goryeo and Joseon Dynasty, similar to poetry and military of these days. In Jeonnam, Naju was designated as the only tree and served as the center of the economy, culture and military. Najumok, a story from 983 to 1895, is displayed in the Najumok Cultural Center for easy understanding.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox type2 clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Najumok Cultural Center outside - Naju-si, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/201/61dc2ea7-665e-4099-8c90-afc38ae75a2a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Najumok Cultural Center outside
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Najumok Cultural Center - Naju-si, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/201/eef5cfc4-a15a-41b6-8a38-c4ebca2e9f32.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Najumok Cultural Center
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    On one side of the cultural hall, a model of Naju-eupseong from the Joseon Dynasty is precisely made. In the Joseon Dynasty, there were many townspeople. According to Dongguk Yeojiram, there are 179 villages with towns and villages. Naju-eupseong began to be renovated and expanded in earnest as the Japanese invasion became frequent. By the time the construction was completed, it is estimated that the circumference of Naju-eupseong was about 3.5 km. If you look at the model of Naju-eupseong and draw a tour line around it, you can feel a greater impression while traveling. Don&#39;t forget to take a map at the tourist information center in front of the Cultural Center.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Naju-eupseong model - Naju-si, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/201/a1cdde53-3e33-4136-8b1f-e665238c3c56.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Naju-eupseong model
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   &#39;Geumseonggwan&#39;, the center of Naju-eupseong
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    At the center of the model is Naju Guest. It is also the next destination. The guest house in the Goryeo Dynasty was a facility where high-ranking people and foreign reaper could stay, but as the Joseon Dynasty passed, the local courthouse &#39;Chungcheong&#39; was added to the guest house. A royal battle symbolizing the king was placed at the government office, and a recital was made to swear allegiance to the king. In addition, the king&#39;s notice was published in front of the government office, and when the king died, the people gathered in front of the government office and wept.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Next to the bus stop at Geumseonggwan, Manghwaru - Naju-si, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/201/64e57539-03c5-484a-be32-8bbbda49f3d6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Next to the bus stop at Geumseonggwan, Manghwaru
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The guest went outside after passing through &#39;Manghwaru&#39; in Oesammun. Naesammun without a fence guards the middle of a clean space The awkwardness of the unfinished space wraps. After passing through Naesammun, the building seen from the guest is placed in front of it, and it looks a bit stable.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Scenery between Oesammun and Naesammun - Naju-si, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/201/9edd6697-cb8c-46ea-a373-d05dc0a17e3c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Scenery between Oesammun and Naesammun
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Three buildings are lined up. In the middle, the building is composed of Chungcheong-in &#39;Geumseonggwan&#39;, Seoikheon in the west, and Dongikheon in the east. It is said that the Naju guest in the Joseon Dynasty was the largest in the country, and its size and splendor are outstanding.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox type2 clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;From left, Seoikheon, Geumseonggwan, and Dongikheon - Naju-si, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/201/f07f5ce6-bd3d-476e-ae57-6838f993ea66.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     From left, Seoikheon, Geumseonggwan, and Dongikheon
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The roof of the government office symbolizing the king - Naju-si, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/201/d75be80e-5189-4d23-975e-b470ba4b865e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The roof of the government office symbolizing the king
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   &#39;A Pastor&#39;s House&#39; with a spacious kitchen
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Let&#39;s go to the pastor&#39;s house, &#39;My Pastor&#39;. Get out of Manghwaru and pass &#39;Jungsuru&#39;, the gateway to Najumok Gwana on your right. There is a large drum on the second floor of the water tower. It is said that Hakbong Kim Sung-il, a pastor of Naju, walked the drum, saying, &#34;Whoever wants to complain about a normal job, play this drum?&#34;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Water purification - Naju-si, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/201/5fb72dc6-0fc2-4e5d-92fc-877193f1a0be.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Water purification
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    After passing the water tower, I went into the pastor Naea, about 40m away. Near the gate, Munganchae, &#39;U&#39; shaped anchae, and the courtyard were in harmony with the simple feeling. Because of the large number of hospitality, the kitchen was wide. Currently, it is designated as a cultural property, so it is possible to experience accommodation, and there is a room named after Pastor Seong-il Kim, who learned from the story of Jeongsu-ru&#39;s drum.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The drum of Jeongsuru, where Pastor Seong-il Kim said - Naju-si, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/201/0ec42784-a280-4325-b056-780c89ffc566.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The drum of Jeongsuru, where Pastor Seong-il Kim said
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    From Geumseonggwan, which symbolized the king, I went to Najuhyanggyo through the house where Pastor Naju stayed. As you move further away from the center of Eupseong, traces of ancestors with low status appear. In the town of Eupseong during the Joseon Dynasty, officials, people working in Gwana, and wealthy farmers could live. For the commoners, the castle was also a wall of identity that cannot be crossed. After Seoseongmun, I arrived at Najuhyanggyo outside the town.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Pastor - Naju-si, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/201/17f46175-c28f-446e-9eb2-e81c0c699f56.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Pastor
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   &#39;Najuhyanggyo Confucian School&#39;
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    In the 11th year of Seongjong, Joseon, 10 students from Han Hyanggyo simultaneously suppressed the past. They were disciples of Na Joo Hyang-kyo&#39;s chilly Park Seong-geon. In addition, in the Goryeo and Joseon Dynasty, it was called the &#39;People&#39;s Treasure&#39;, where Naju&#39;s figures rise a lot in the office.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;5&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Najuhyanggyo Confucian Temple - Naju-si, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/201/16a74630-154a-4e66-9784-1b6cee7ba651.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Najuhyanggyo Confucian Temple
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The Najuhyanggyo Confucian School was said to have been established in the late Goryeo Dynasty, during the period of the 12th anniversary of the nation. Among the Hyanggyo, it shows the arrangement of Jeonmyo Huk (the space of the sacrifice and the space of the learning in the future). Among them, the Najuhyanggyo Daeseongjeon Hall attracts attention, and it is said that the walls were made of soil from Confucius&#39; hometown, and it was said that this building was used as a specimen when rebuilding Sungkyunkwan, which was lost due to the Imjin War. Dong-jae and Seo-jae, who were studying while sleeping, are enormous. At that time, I can guess that there were many larvae studying at Najuhyanggyo.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;5&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The glow permeated under the shadow of the roof. - Naju-si, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/201/24c35867-b19d-49f4-b459-c87f6c78a87d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The glow permeated under the shadow of the roof.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    After the tour of Naju&#39;s major cultural properties is over, I recommend that you walk around without a hitch. While walking to the point where I can&#39;t hold my breath, I can see the remains of Naju-eupseong left over everywhere. Suddenly, Naju colored the heart with a wonderful hometown of the old days that was more friendly than the dignity of Geumseonggwan and the reputation of Najumok.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;5&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Long corridor in the larvae&#39;s dormitory &#39;Dongjae&#39; - Naju-si, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/201/551d9da8-9206-4a04-862f-54cb4d1957bf.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Long corridor in the larvae&#39;s dormitory &#39;Dongjae&#39;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    1.Access
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    * Self-driving
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Muan Gwangju Expressway Naju IC → Yangcheon Intersection (toward Naju) Labok Intersection → Mahanro Yeongsanpo (to Naju City Hall) → Wansacheon → Najuro, in front of Korea Telecom (turn right to Naju Tax Office) → Naju Guest (turn left) → Najumok Cultural Center, Tourist Information Center
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    2. Delicious
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Naju Gomtang Presbyopia Collection: Geumgye-dong, Naju-si, 061-333-2053
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Mihyang Gomtang: Seongbuk-dong, Naju-si, 061-334-2550
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Yeongsan Hongga: Yeongsan-dong, Naju-si, 061-334-0585
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Youngsan Podae Park Hong-eo: Lee Chang-dong, Naju-si, 061-335-5544
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Great Eel: Daji-myeon, Naju-si, 061-336-1265
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Emerging Eel: Daji-myeon, Naju-si, 061-335-9109
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    3.Accommodation
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Pastor Naju: Geumgye-dong, Naju-si, 061-332-6565
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Dorae Village Old House: 06-336-3675, Dado-myeon, Naju-si
    &lt;br/&gt;
    The Ritz-Carlton Motel: Daeho-dong, Naju-si, 061-334-9777
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Jungheung Gold Spa &amp;amp; Resort; Nampyeong-eup, Naju-si, 1688-5200
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    ※ The above information was created in January 2013, and may change later, so be sure to check it before you travel.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A place where Tam&#39;s reaper and horses rested, Gangjin Maryang Port and Route 23 trip - Gangjin-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/a-place-where-tams-reaper-and-horses-rested-gangjin-maryang-port-and-route-23-trip-184/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 13:25:26 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/a-place-where-tams-reaper-and-horses-rested-gangjin-maryang-port-and-route-23-trip-184/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Gangjin-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;a-place-where-tams-reaper-and-horses-rested-gangjin-maryang-port-and-route-23-trip--184&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Beautiful evening scenery in Maryang Port - Gangjin-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/184/0f3f2742-1138-42a7-976f-96636a3dc377.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Beautiful evening scenery in Maryang Port
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   A place where Tam&#39;s reaper and horses rested, Gangjin Maryang Port and Route 23 trip
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Gangjin-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Maryang Port, known as the US Port, is located at the southern end of Gangjin Bay in Jeollanam-do. Maryang Port is a place full of beauty and vitality of the port along with a vibrant hydrophilic space. Route 23, which runs from Gangeup town to Maryang Port along Gangjin Bay, has beautiful scenery and lots of fun. Soak up the charm of Maryang Port along Route 23.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   The gateway to Goryeo celadon and Jeju villages
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Maryang&#39;s history has a long history dating back to the Three Kingdoms period. Tamjin is Gangjin&#39;s old name. It was called Chonjinhyeon and changed to Gangjinhyeon during the Joseon Dynasty. Tamjin is the name given to the ship when it was built by the lion of Tamla, the island of Jeju, where the ship stayed at the oral cannon near Maryang Port. In short, Maryang was the gateway to maritime transportation to Tamla.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Jeju Dolharbang built in Maryang Port - Gangjin-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/184/fc8dbc00-02c2-4c38-bb17-2a8e84b6a91a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Jeju Dolharbang built in Maryang Port
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In addition, during the Goryeo Dynasty, it was the starting point of the 500 km boatway that carried Goryeo celadon made in Gangjin Bay, such as Chilyang-myeon, to Kaesong. It was named Maryang because it was the place where the horses from Tamla along the boatway first landed and ate prey. In my heart
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Horse shelter I met at Shinma Village - Gangjin-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/184/220e184d-99b7-4635-9302-80b25be2d4b6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Horse shelter I met at Shinma Village
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Maryang Port was selected as the &#39;Fishing Area Complex Project for Fishing Villages&#39; for the first time in the country in 2006. This project is to create a fishing port or a fishing port with a potential for tourism as a complex space. It deviates from the existing secluded port concept and seeks a multi-functional fishing port that harmonizes the fishing village&#39;s life, recreation, and tourism concepts. Maryang Port has a wide range of activities, including three breakwaters in East, China and China, a water threat market, and a marine product sales center. Also, there are about 20 sushi restaurants along the road, so it is perfect for tasting fresh fish.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Crooked sashimi from Maryang Port - Gangjin-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/184/43465278-dffc-4e60-b182-56d47e62f2c8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Crooked sashimi from Maryang Port
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The breakwater at Maryang Port was created as a lively hydrophilic space. With the theme of dynamic feeling, east, middle and lower breakwaters are divided into spaces of life, motion, and persimmon, respectively.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Maryang Port from Kogeum Bridge - Gangjin-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/184/0f785422-25ce-4c51-9cb9-72d5e89423fd.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Maryang Port from Kogeum Bridge
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The mid-breakwater created as a living space on the right side of Maryang Port has a variety of themed spaces, including a pine garden, a cigar square, a small square, and a blue dragon column, as well as a rest area such as a wave bench and a fish bench, and a black island. Equipped with an overlooking view facility. At the end of the breakwater reaching 320m, a white lighthouse stands.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sunset seen from Maryang Port hydrophilic space - Gangjin-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/184/970ddc40-c90a-48e3-ad58-55983aca8ad7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sunset seen from Maryang Port hydrophilic space
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The lower breakwater in the middle is a copper space, and a stage with a 36m diameter circular pier at the end of the breakwater was created. Saturday concerts are held every week from March to October.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;13&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Maryang Port - Gangjin-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/184/037773ac-64fe-4532-a989-1628f3814150.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Maryang Port
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The East Breakwater, overlooking the Golden Gate Bridge, is a space of persimmons, where you can enjoy fishing and walking in beautiful natural scenery.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;15&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Way to Maryang Port Lighthouse - Gangjin-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/184/cc40680b-deea-4d17-8f5d-472913b7a784.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Way to Maryang Port Lighthouse
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   A life and nature inevitably in love
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Maryang Port, with its natural environment, is a rich port full of seasonal seafood. Kamak Island at the entrance of Maryang Port serves as a fisherman that provides an environment where fish can inhabit.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Marine products auction at Maryang Port Fisheries Commission - Gangjin-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/184/08f99521-7fd0-44d4-9e97-4d047e7030bb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Marine products auction at Maryang Port Fisheries Commission
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   To see the true value of Maryang Port, a treasure house of seafood, you should go to Maryang Port Suhyupjangjang. A seafood auction held every morning at Maryang Port Water Nesting Market offers a variety of fun and attractions. It is full of energy from the early dawn. When the fishing boat comes back through the dawn, freshly caught fresh seafood enters the top of the box and packed in boxes.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Marine products auction at Maryang Port Fisheries Commission - Gangjin-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/184/445541dc-4733-478c-8f8c-c1b220c88f5c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Marine products auction at Maryang Port Fisheries Commission
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   There are people who go to and from fishing boats, boats, and boards. At the top of the market, not only fish such as black sea bream, sea bass, roe rook, and trout, but also blue crabs, abalone, clams, and hearing occupy one place and wait for an auction. The auction begins when auctioneers in blue vests and brokers in red vests gather. The auction here, held every morning at 8:00, is a hand signal
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The use of a calculator for auction is unique. - Gangjin-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/184/4d75de7a-c961-4807-8ced-de1ec59740d1.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The use of a calculator for auction is unique.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Maryang Port, located at the end of Gangjin-gun, is a tourist port that attracts tourists. There is a breakwater where you can enjoy fishing and walking, and the North Mountain Park behind Maryang Port serves as the best observatory for viewing the beautiful Maryang Port and surrounding islands.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sunrise from Kogeum Bridge - Gangjin-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/184/a27325b1-1de9-417b-994a-e7c8a53a48a2.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sunrise from Kogeum Bridge
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   You can also enjoy a trip to the island of Kogeumdo and Yaksando across the Kogeumdaegyo Bridge leading to Kogeumdo.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sunset seen from Maryang Port - Gangjin-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/184/5f6d7408-ce73-4cdb-b200-d93d212c5810.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sunset seen from Maryang Port
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Route 23 scenery leading to Maryang Port
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   When the stream of Tamjin River enters the sea, only Gangjin is filled with tidal flats. National Route 23, which follows the rich Gangjin Bay, leads to Maryang Port, a beautiful port that dreams of Naples in Korea.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sunset of Gangjin Bay seen from Jeongja - Gangjin-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/184/038db084-01c2-42fe-b746-d83769e3a4cc.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sunset of Gangjin Bay seen from Jeongja
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   To meet the sea of Gangjin Bay in the town of Gangjin, you must pass Chilyang-myeon, famous for Onggi. National highway No. 23 passes through Maejiri Park, and a heel rises largely. From this point, the tidal flats and sea of Gangjin Bay unfold without filtration. The scenery of Gangjin Bay overlooking from the small pavilion on the right side of the ridge is quite quiet. Especially at sunset, the tidal flats turn golden and create a spectacular view.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Gangjin Bay tidal flats dyed golden - Gangjin-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/184/b72486de-47ab-4c28-a708-50b1531221b4.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Gangjin Bay tidal flats dyed golden
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    After passing through the pavilion, the rice cake in the middle of Gangjin Bay is immediately visible. Gaudo is named after the island&#39;s shape resembles a yoke of a cow. Of the eight islands in Gangjin, Gaudo is the only Yuin Island. A few years ago, a bridge was laid to stop the tourists on their way to Maryang. The 430 meter-long so-called &#39;Gaudo Chulleongdari&#39; is a footbridge that cars cannot go through. After crossing this bridge and passing through the forest, you will find Gaudo Village, where 13 families gather. It is quite exciting to say that there is another rocking bridge from Gaudo to Mankho village across the sea.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;15&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Gaudo and Rocket Bridge as seen from Hajeo Fishing Village - Gangjin-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/184/f6090dd6-e035-4557-9c7f-6afcdc7234c7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Gaudo and Rocket Bridge as seen from Hajeo Fishing Village
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   After passing the road, you can experience Hajeo, Baeksa, and Seojung Fishing Village where you can experience the rich tidal flats of Gangjin Bay. If the tide is right, it is also a good idea to enjoy the shellfish experience. After passing the Hajeo village in Gaudo, there is a good view called Kobao Evergreen Park. Seomyeon River
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;16&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Kamak Island from the Kamak Island Observatory - Gangjin-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/184/656c2128-55ef-4b93-ac01-d1adab6f3a17.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Kamak Island from the Kamak Island Observatory
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   At the entrance of Maryang Port, the site of Madōjin was installed in the Joseon Dynasty, and a castle site called Manhoseong runs along the foot of Busan, the back mountain of Maryang Port. During the Imjin War, General Admiral Yi Sun-sin&#39;s Chosun navy stayed at Gogeumdo Island overlooking Maryang Port. It is well-known as a place where the Turtle Ship anchored at all times, as it procured manpower and military beauty through the port of Maryang.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;17&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Castle wall - Gangjin-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/184/7e14c25d-d807-4d43-8d44-0dc908582555.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Castle wall
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Across from Manhoseong, there is an observation deck where you can see Kamak Island, designated as Natural Monument No. 172, with thick trees and various evergreen forests.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;13&#34; id3=&#34;18&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Kamak Island Evergreen Forest, designated as a Natural Monument - Gangjin-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/184/a9fd8a67-6250-4ead-b579-c1bf04900b2c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Kamak Island Evergreen Forest, designated as a Natural Monument
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1.Nearby Restaurants
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Chungjeongwon Sashimi Restaurant: Live fish society / 179, Mihang-ro, Maryang-myeon, Gangjin-gun / 061-434-3253
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Suin-gwan: Pork Bulgogi Baeban / 107-10 Byeongyeongseong-ro, Byeongyeong-myeon, Gangjin-gun / 061-432-1027
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Cheongja Goljonggajip: Han Jeong-sik / 106-11, Gunjang-myeon Sports Complex, Gangjin-gun / 061-433-1100
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Haitai Restaurant: Hanjeongsik / 6, Seoseongan-gil, Gangjin-eup, Gangjin-gun / 061-434-2486
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2.Accommodation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Prince Happy Hotel: 113-1, Boeun-ro, Gangjin-eup, Gangjin-gun / 061-433-7300
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.princemt.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.princemt.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Dahyang Shrine: 7-5, Dasanchodang 1-gil, Doam-myeon, Gangjin-gun / 061-432-0360
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://다향소축.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://다향소축.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Dasan Village Myeongga: 68, Dasanchodang-gil, Doam-myeon, Gangjin-gun / 061-434-5252
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    ※ The above information was updated in April 2014, and may be changed later, so please check before you travel.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Damyang Art Warehouse, a colorful transformation of Yanggok Warehouse - Damyang-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/damyang-art-warehouse-a-colorful-transformation-of-yanggok-warehouse-156/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 16:04:24 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/damyang-art-warehouse-a-colorful-transformation-of-yanggok-warehouse-156/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Damyang-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;damyang-art-warehouse-a-colorful-transformation-of-yanggok-warehouse--156&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Namsong Warehouse has been transformed into a light art warehouse. - Damyang-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/156/9a136495-e2b3-4aaf-a0c5-7a81363e774a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Namsong Warehouse has been transformed into a light art warehouse.
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Damyang Art Warehouse, a colorful transformation of Yanggok Warehouse
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Damyang-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Is the transformation of the warehouse innocent? Namsong warehouse and bamboo product processing plant, which had been left for many years next to Gwanbangjerim in Damyang, were reborn as a space of culture and art in 2015. In the name of &#39;Dambit Art Warehouse&#39;. It is located in the middle of Metasequoia Garosu-gil and Gwanbangjerim, making it a must-see destination for visitors to Damyang. In addition to the regularity of bamboo and metasequoia, let&#39;s take part in the fragrance of art.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   A different transformation of an old warehouse
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Before hearing the story of the birth of the Dambit Art Warehouse, let&#39;s look at a case where a grain storage warehouse in a rural area that lost its vitality has become a tourist attraction. First of all, Samrye Culture &amp;amp; Arts Village in Wanju-gun, Jeollabuk-do is considered as a representative runner. Until 2010, there were several dongs in the Yanggok warehouse and houses built during the Japanese colonial period. As the rapid urbanization caused Samrye-eup to lose vitality day by day, the villagers sought to become a giant. The slogan that united their will into one is ‘Geun Ja-yeol Sang-rae (近 者 悅 遠 者 來)’. This means that people who live nearby should have fun, and people who are far away also come. Yes. If I don&#39;t like it, I can&#39;t help others. They have turned warehouses that no one is eyeing into places of culture and art.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A nameplate on a red brick - Damyang-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/156/b4f1912e-6d4a-4172-ad43-58ea4ec60604.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A nameplate on a red brick
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   From 2011 to 2014, the residents of Samrye carried out the project of creating a Samrye Culture and Art Village with the motto of “Art is tourism”. Finally, large warehouses have been transformed into visual media art museum, book studio north art center, design museum, Kim Sang-lim woodwork, book museum, and cultural cafe. Samrye Culture &amp;amp; Arts Village is widely known not only in Jeonbuk but also in Seoul and the metropolitan area, where visitors line up.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Residents of Andeok-myeon, Seogwipo-si, Jeju Island have converted old citrus warehouses into cafes. The interior of the cafe boasts a surprisingly sensuous interior for urban people. Citrus sweets, tangerine crunchino, and daengja aide made by aging with a secret method will attract travelers&#39; taste.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sculpture placed in the courtyard of Samrye Culture and Arts - Damyang-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/156/d3bfdcc3-dba0-4105-aaca-725dc0152de7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sculpture placed in the courtyard of Samrye Culture and Arts
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   The red warehouse building is a gallery and a literary cafe.
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Let&#39;s go back to the Dambit Art Warehouse and take a look at every corner. In the past, if you were traveling to Damyang, you would have visited Juknokwon or Metasequoia Road first, but this trip is different. Since there was an art yard in Damyang, visiting there is a top priority.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Book Museum at Samrye Culture and Art Village - Damyang-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/156/7449366f-b010-416c-955a-da8d8d12312d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Book Museum at Samrye Culture and Art Village
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   When viewed from the front, the art warehouse is painted with red brick walls in white, and the Chinese characters written in black are first noticed. &#39;Namsong Warehouse&#39;. This is a typeface with a long age ring. Building 2 meets at a right angle
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A literary cafe where you can listen to bamboo pipe organ performances - Damyang-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/156/f54cf777-5fa6-482f-aa7d-7b51eec164fe.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A literary cafe where you can listen to bamboo pipe organ performances
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Murals are painted on the wall of the house on the right side of the lawn in front of the warehouse. When you go to the back of the warehouse building, several works like the sculpture park take place and talk to the visitors.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Literary cafes have a lot of books on the bookshelves, making a book cafe atmosphere. - Damyang-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/156/50e68b95-6c40-4bea-bf2e-e22f0e24c999.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Literary cafes have a lot of books on the bookshelves, making a book cafe atmosphere.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Healing while watching works of art from various genres
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The artists who participated in the exhibition of the Dambit Art Warehouse were 12 people including Lee Nam Lee, Byeongchan Lee, Daewon Jo, Sungyeon Joo, and Jung Unhak. Jinwol-ji of the Damyang-gun Cultural Foundation said, “I am a military unit without going to a large city such as Gwangju Metropolitan City.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Step inside the exhibition room and slowly fall in love with the appreciation of the work. Although the Dambit Art Warehouse is less than the size of the Yangpyeong County Museum of Art, compared to the military unit art museum, it has the confidence that its life will last, as it has its own garden, such as literary cafes, sculpture parks, and giant trees of Gwanbangjerim.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Enjoy bamboo pipe organ performance while drinking tea leaves
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The impressions received while appreciating the works of the complex are continued in the literary cafe. The bamboo pipe organ performance was in progress. Pipe organs are very expensive and large, so they are often installed in cathedrals and churches. The performance starts every week on Tuesday / Thursday at 2 o&#39;clock and on the weekend / holiday at 3 o&#39;clock, each lasting 30 minutes. The taste of having a cup of tea leaves and watching a bamboo pipe organ while reading a book is a happiness that cannot be enjoyed without a trip to Damyang. The spacious space has a high ceiling, so the organ sound is magnificent. As much as the playing time, even the chatter of adults and the shuffling of children are cut off.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Bamboo pipe organ in literary cafe - Damyang-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/156/0c78a15f-9d3b-4637-aa9f-fbea9089f56f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Bamboo pipe organ in literary cafe
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Watching the bamboo pipe organ performance felt only briefly, and curiously laughed from corner to corner, I found a blackboard hidden under a staircase going up to the second floor. When I look at the chart drawn under the heading of &#39;Government Grain Storage Status&#39;, I realize that this was the Yanggok warehouse. How many people have actually seen a thermometer, moisture meter, etc. in the list of management equipment written on the board? The cafe sells Americano, Green Tea Latte, Juice, Smoothie, Aid, Sandwich, Cookie, Cake, etc. in addition to the tea leaves and tea leaves.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Blackboard with &#39;Government Grain Storage Status&#39; - Damyang-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/156/cd08359b-185f-4951-82b0-4746c2ef366a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Blackboard with &#39;Government Grain Storage Status&#39;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Sculpture-lined garden, Gwanbangjerim, Metasequoia Trail
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Sculpture garden and Gwanbangjerim are spread behind the literary cafe. It has a large through-glass window, so it has an excellent open feeling. If you leave the book you read in place and go out as a sponsor, a scary-looking tiger statue greets you. I put a long tail on my back, but the tip of the tail is a pine shape, so I have to look into the description of the work. It is a story called ‘The Story of the Tiger and the Turtle’. “It was based on the story that a tiger can settle for a thousand years by holding its tail. As I read the passage, “I express the feeling of the pine tree in the tail part,” the question raises my head asking, “Is Damyang the part of the tiger&#39;s tail?”
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;5&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Pond behind Dambit Art Warehouse - Damyang-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/156/f01e8afb-a8a6-4fe7-91e7-51e6f07d8965.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Pond behind Dambit Art Warehouse
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Around the tiger, funny things such as “Tale of the Dog and Chicken of Damyang”
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;5&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Tiger statue - Damyang-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/156/d8f23a4d-3635-4b72-8485-9c63301f7191.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Tiger statue
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   After that, the Chuseong Stadium and the Gwanbangjerim embankment continue. If you walk along the causeway leading along the Yeongsan River, you will see the entrance to Juknokwon and Damyang Guksu Street, which is packed with noodles. Also, just a little east along Jukhyang-daero, Metasequoia Garosu-gil begins.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   On the roadside, Honam Climate Change Experience Hall or a singer who died out Kim Jung-ho (1952 ~ 198
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Myeongokheon and Sikyeongjeong tour and finish with bamboo shoots
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Damyang is the hometown of sperm culture, so the last trip is to visit a couple of sperm such as Myeongokheon in Goseo-myeon and Sikyeongjeong in Nam-myeon.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;6&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Myeongokheon Garden Pond - Damyang-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/156/7a92c0d4-bd7a-4063-8e4d-c092e1cf11c2.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Myeongokheon Garden Pond
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In Sikyeongjeong, I smelled the tree. The smell of summer. There were many trees covered in tall in front of the pavilion, making it difficult to see Mudeungsan Mountain. For the panoramic view, shouldn&#39;t the trees in front of Sikyeongjeong be turned into short trees? The stone stairs that go up and down are also scary on rainy days. I want to ask Damyang-gun to make a handle for the elderly.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;6&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Jeongyoung Jeong - Damyang-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/156/2d2773a3-bd59-4fad-88d5-aa1c3ab5151d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Jeongyoung Jeong
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   One of the ‘Damyang 10 beauty’ must be tasted before the tour of Damyang is over. Tteokgalbi, Changpyeonggukbap, Daetongbap, Hanjeongsik, bamboo shoots, Korean and rice syrup, charcoal pork ribs, Korean beef, Damyang noodles, catfish steamed and Tang, bamboo shoots were selected from 10 dishes.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;6&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Bamboo tour - Damyang-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/156/1690a6a2-347b-450c-a619-b10d56c33470.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Bamboo tour
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   People living in Damyang, the home of bamboo, cook and eat bamboo shoots in a variety of ways, including marinated, steamed, sweet and sour pork, and boiled fish.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;6&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Boiled bamboo shoots - Damyang-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/156/54fe25ae-e8d2-4686-a179-1f14b2424104.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Boiled bamboo shoots
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Dambit Art Warehouse
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Address: 75, Gaeksa 7-gil, Damyang-eup, Damyang-gun, Jeonnam
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Contact: 061-383-8240
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1.Nearby Restaurants
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Hansang Modern Traditional Rice House: Daetongbab / 113, Damjang-ro, Wolsan-myeon, Damyang-gun / 061-382-1999
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Traditional restaurant: Hanjeongsik / 38-4, Goeuphyeon-gil, Goseo-myeon, Damyang-gun / 061-382-3111
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Jukyanggol Restaurant: Juksun Fish Steak / 1341 Chuseong-ro, Damyang-eup, Damyang-gun / 061-382-1278
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2.Accommodation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Damyang Resort Tourist Hotel: 202, Geumseongsanseong-gil, Geumseong-myeon, Damyang-gun / 061-380-5000
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.damyangresort.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.damyangresort.com/
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Vice Hotel: 26 Mujeong-ro, Damyang-eup, Damyang-gun / 061-381-
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://boo-hotel.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://boo-hotel.com/
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    From the old house of Hanok: 88-9, Doldam-gil, Changpyeong-myeon, Damyang-gun / 061-382-3832
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was updated in July 2019, and may be changed later, so please check before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two Buddhist culture experiences, Boseong Daewonsa Temple and Tibet Museum - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/two-buddhist-culture-experiences-boseong-daewonsa-temple-and-tibet-museum-152/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 09:00:51 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/two-buddhist-culture-experiences-boseong-daewonsa-temple-and-tibet-museum-152/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;two-buddhist-culture-experiences-boseong-daewonsa-temple-and-tibet-museum--152&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Summit Gwangmyeong Pagoda, the Tibetan Pagoda, and Daewonsa Tibet Museum - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/152/aa58f1d1-3797-45b2-93d5-64eafc6ce64f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Summit Gwangmyeong Pagoda, the Tibetan Pagoda, and Daewonsa Tibet Museum
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Two Buddhist culture experiences, Boseong Daewonsa Temple and Tibet Museum
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div style=&#34;text-align: justify;&#34;&gt;
    In April, full of spring scent, the way to visit Daewonsa Temple, a temple in Boseong, Jeollanam-do, is a snowy road. This is because cherry blossoms are in full bloom at the 5.5km driveway. If you walk as if you are drunk with the scattered rain, you will arrive at the entrance of the temple. However, unlike any temple where Iljumun welcomes, an exotic pagoda stands out. It is a Tibetan stupa called &#39;Chorten&#39;. The 15m high white sumi light tower combined with the blue sky and the colorful flags fluttering in the wind are colorful. On the opposite side, the Daewon Sa Tibet Museum, built in the Tibetan temple style, stood tall. It seems unfamiliar and unreal to face the scenery you saw in an overseas documentary program.
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;In April, cherry blossoms form a tunnel along the entrance to Daewonsa Temple. &amp;lt;Photo Credit: Boseong County Office&amp;gt; - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/152/ec86515e-e118-46bc-8bca-9e352dcb2868.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     In April, cherry blossoms form a tunnel along the entrance to Daewonsa Temple. &amp;lt;Photo Credit: Boseong County Office&amp;gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div style=&#34;text-align: justify;&#34;&gt;
    Daewonsa Tibet Museum and Sumi Gwangmyeong Pagoda were founded by the chief field monk of Daewonsa. It was found that he met the Dalai Lama, a Tibetan Buddhist leader while traveling in India. Tibetan Buddhist culture is regarded as one of the spiritual civilizations achieved by mankind. The museum was opened in 2001 to introduce this spirit culture and art world of Tibet and to promote exchange with Korean Buddhism. In addition, the Dalai Lama&#39;s message celebrating the opening of the museum, the Sumi Gwangmyeong Pagoda was created to welcome the Buddha Sari from Tibet and Nepal.
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox type2 clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Inside the Sumi Gwangmyeong Pagoda, murals and mandalas painted by Tibetan royal painters were enshrined. - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/152/eb99bd8e-1f9b-4fe3-9f11-09b45e76aa0d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Inside the Sumi Gwangmyeong Pagoda, murals and mandalas painted by Tibetan royal painters were enshrined.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Tarcho, a multicolored flag with scriptures - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/152/63243d32-2ece-4ff3-beaa-29187286be72.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Tarcho, a multicolored flag with scriptures
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div style=&#34;text-align: justify;&#34;&gt;
    Inside the pagoda, murals and mandalas painted by Tibetan royal painters were enshrined, and 108 Manibo wheels made in Nepal were collected outside. It is a good idea to experience the wishes come true when you turn the pagoda one time while turning the Manibo wheel, which contains Buddhist scriptures. At this time, reciting the ‘Ommani Bapthumum’ of Tibetan Buddhism. It means that the mercy of the Buddha spreads all over the world. The multicolored flag blowing in the wind is &#39;tarcho&#39;. The blue, yellow, red, white, and green flags that symbolize the five elements of the universe (sky, earth, fire, clouds, and sea) were written with strings of scripture scriptures. It was hoped that the Buddha&#39;s teachings would spread all over the world.
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox type2 clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;At the Daewon Satibet Museum, a special exhibition, &amp;lt;Traveling with God&amp;gt; is held. - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/152/668f1a14-552a-4c1b-b51b-bb488cacff45.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     At the Daewon Satibet Museum, a special exhibition, &amp;lt;Traveling with God&amp;gt; is held.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Death experience room to take a picture of Yeongjeong and write a will - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/152/1f67ca28-d716-4bd5-a363-eed6f6e764fb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Death experience room to take a picture of Yeongjeong and write a will
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div style=&#34;text-align: justify;&#34;&gt;
    In the museum, you can see the Dalai Lamasil, the Tibetan Buddhist painting Tangka, the Tibetan daily necessities, the teapot, the Buddha statue created by the Sakyamite artisans directly descended from Sakyamuni, and the Mandala, one of the Tibetan Buddhist essences. The special exhibition 〈Traveling with Gods〉 is also exciting. Compare and display the seven hells in the movie &amp;lt;With God--Sin and Punishment&amp;gt; and the ten hells of Buddhism, which dramatizes the afterlife of Buddhism. The death experience room, which takes pictures of Yeongjeong, writes a will, and enters the coffin after experiencing the Tibetan funeral culture that feeds the dead from the body of an eagle, provides a thrilling and reflexive opportunity. The scene of the ceiling (promotion) where people who leave and think that &#39;the body from which the soul has left is only a rotten piece of meat&#39; is put out finely with flesh and bones so that birds can eat without any conflict is somewhat shocking.
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;You can see the paradise in front of Yeonjimun, which has a large wooden table hitting it with its head. - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/152/cad62902-989c-47a1-b96b-5a9ee2d3c029.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     You can see the paradise in front of Yeonjimun, which has a large wooden table hitting it with its head.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div style=&#34;text-align: justify;&#34;&gt;
    After Tibetan Buddhism, it is time to meet Korean Buddhism. The Daewonsa Temple, founded in Baekje, is burned down by fire and continues to be built again. Jubuljeon is a paradise (Jeollanam-do Tangible Cultural Heritage No. 87), symbolizing the western paradise of the ideal of Buddhism. After passing through Iljumun and Sacheonwangru and crossing the Guumgyo Bridge, climbing the stairs reveals a paradise show beyond Yeonjimun. There was a large wooden table hitting the head at Yeonjimun. Hold the wooden table with both hands and hit it three times with your forehead and say, &#34;Gone bad memories, brighten my wisdom, and my enemies will be good.&#34; The pond under the old school bridge is considered the most beautiful place in Daewonsa. There are seven ponds on the grounds of Daewonsa Temple, and in summer, it resembles an ecological park with blooming lotus flowers and various aquatic plants.
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;13&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Mural of Gwaneum Bodhisattva on the western wall of Daewonsa Temple - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/152/5e137acf-5be5-4fc4-9434-a6f3b1fef767.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Mural of Gwaneum Bodhisattva on the western wall of Daewonsa Temple
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div style=&#34;text-align: justify;&#34;&gt;
    It is recommended that you watch the inside of the paradise. Pay particular attention to the murals that decorate the left and right walls. On the western wall, he painted murals of the Gwaneum Bodhisattva with white and Gwaneum Bodhisattva, and on the east wall, the murals of the Dharma Ambassador and the Dharma Ambassadors and the Hyagadanbi. Boseong Daewonsa Temple Geuknakjeon Gwaneum Bodhisattva Mural Painting (Treasure No. 1861), presumably from 1766 ~ 1767 during the reign of King Yeongjo
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox type2 clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;15&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Dongja statue and Taean Jizo Bodhisattva statue to comfort the floating young soul - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/152/d831abbe-28b7-48e8-b2c6-20897634ebbc.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Dongja statue and Taean Jizo Bodhisattva statue to comfort the floating young soul
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;15&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Plum blossoms on the grounds of Daewonsa Temple - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/152/4cad8a60-dcfa-4421-bf23-20341c67b1e9.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Plum blossoms on the grounds of Daewonsa Temple
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div style=&#34;text-align: justify;&#34;&gt;
    Daewonsa Temple is a hieroglyphic prayer to comfort a young spirit (fetal spirit) who has not seen the light of the world, and there are many bronze statues wearing red hats everywhere. Next to Kukrakjeon, there is the Taean Jijang Bodhisattva statue which was enshrined to deliver young souls, and a hundred days prayer is held for heaven. Other major events include Kim Ji-Jang, Hwang Hee-Jung, Seung-Young-Gak, Ado-Young-Gak, Death Experience Hall (Su-Gwan-Jung), and a preservation for the temple stay. This year, Daewon Temple plans to arrange a variety of programs, including experiences in the world of Tibetan music and art with locals in Tibet. Please refer to the website for detailed schedule and participation method.
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;17&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Boseong County Baekmin Museum located at the entrance of Daewonsa Temple - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/152/be02f26c-68da-48ea-ae8f-93c58a1c61ca.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Boseong County Baekmin Museum located at the entrance of Daewonsa Temple
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div style=&#34;text-align: justify;&#34;&gt;
    Before and after visiting Daewonsa Temple, you can visit the Boseong County Paikmin Museum or Seojaepil Memorial Park. Boseong County Pavilion Museum is the first military art museum in Korea to open in 1993. Baekmin, a native of Boseong, and Kyu-il Cho, a Korean elder and middle-aged artist, and foreign artists are exhibited. Seojaepil Memorial Park is a place to honor Seo Jae-pil, a teacher who devoted himself to the liberation of his country by organizing an independent association and publishing &amp;lt;Independent Newspaper&amp;gt;. However, the Seojaepil Memorial Hall, which exhibits artifacts and various materials, can be viewed after April when the internal construction is over.
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;19&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;On the second floor of the Taebaeksanmaek Literature Museum, there is a manuscript of the novel `` Taebaeksanmaek &#39;&#39; by the son and daughter-in-law of Jo Jung-rae. - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/152/3be6a81f-33b8-49a3-b94a-dd9a40c79e6a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     On the second floor of the Taebaeksanmaek Literature Museum, there is a manuscript of the novel `` Taebaeksanmaek &#39;&#39; by the son and daughter-in-law of Jo Jung-rae.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div style=&#34;text-align: justify;&#34;&gt;
    Beolgyo, the stage of the novel The Taebaek Mountain Range, is an essential part of the trip to Boseong. Leading to the literary world of Jo Jeong-rae, and the Taebaeksan Mountain Literature Museum, the House of the digestive, Hyunbuja&#39;s House, Kim Bum-woo&#39;s House, the Beolgyo Hongkyo, the former Beolgyo Financial Association, the old Boseong Inn, and the Jungdobangjuk. The path to Taebaeksan Mountain Literature that follows the famous spots in the novel is popular.
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;21&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The largest and most beautiful bulkyo hongkyo among the remaining hongkyo in Korea - Boseong-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/152/b9a8fe1c-2e63-4715-bb28-90084e278d2c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The largest and most beautiful bulkyo hongkyo among the remaining hongkyo in Korea
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div style=&#34;text-align: justify;&#34;&gt;
    Among the bridges crossing the port of Beolgyo, the oldest Beolgyo Honggyo is the largest and most beautiful of the remaining Honggyo in Korea, and has been designated as Treasure No. 304. The former Vulgyo Financial Association (Registered Cultural Property No. 226) is a modern building that reflects Japanese architectural style and is currently used as an exhibition space for Korean currency companies. The old Boseong Inn (Registered Cultural Properties No. 132), which emerges from the novel as Namdo Inn, was restored and was born into a complex space with cafes, archives, exhibition hall, small theater, and accommodation. A night in a modern building will be a special experience.
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &amp;lt;Day trip course&amp;gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    Daewon Sa Tibet Museum and Sumi Gwangmyeong Tower → Daewonsa Temple → Boseong County Paikmin Museum → Seojaepil Memorial Park
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &amp;lt;2 days and 1 night trip course&amp;gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    Day 1 / Daewon Sa Tibet Museum and Sumi Gwangmyeong Tower → Daewonsa Temple → Boseong County Baekmin Museum → Seojaepil Memorial Park
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    Day 2 / Taebaek Mountain Range Memorial Hall → Taebaek Mountain Range Literature Tour
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    ○ Related website address
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    -Boseong Culture Tour
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://tour.boseong.go.kr&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;[새창열림]‘보성문화관광’ 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
     http://tour.boseong.go.kr
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    -Daewonsa Temple
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.daewonsa.or.kr&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;[새창열림]‘대원사’ 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
     http://www.daewonsa.or.kr
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    -Daewon Sa Tibet Museum
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.tibetan-museum.org&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;[새창열림]‘대원사티벳박물관’ 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
     http://www.tibetan-museum.org
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    -Taebaeksan Mountain Literature Museum
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://tour.boseong.go.kr/tbsm&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;[새창열림]‘태백산맥문학관’ 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
     http://tour.boseong.go.kr/tbsm
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    -Old Boseong Inn
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.boseonginn.org&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;[새창열림]‘구 보성여관’ 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
     http://www.boseonginn.org
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    ○ Inquiry phone
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    -Boseong County Office Cultural Tourism Division 061) 850-5214
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    -Daewonsa Temple 061) 852-1755
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    -Daewon Sa Tibet Museum 061) 852-3038
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    -Taebaeksan Mountain Literature Museum 061) 850-8653
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    -Old Boseong Inn 061) 858-7528
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    ○ Public transportation information
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    [Bus] Operates every 5 to 30 minutes (05:30 to 02:00 the next day) from Seoul-Gwangju and Central City Terminals, takes about 3 hours and 20 minutes. It takes about 2 hours and 30 minutes from the Gwangcheon Terminal Bus Stop at No. 217 Rural Fishing Village Bus and Sipyeong Terminal Bus Stop at Boseong-Beolgyo Rural Fishing Village Bus.
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    * Inquiry: Central City Terminal 02) 6282-0114 Express Bus Integrated Ticket
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.kobus.co.kr&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;[새창열림]‘고속버스통합예매’ 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
     http://www.kobus.co.kr
    &lt;/a&gt;
    Gwangju Youth Square 062) 360-8114,
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.usquare.co.kr&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;[새창열림]‘광주유스퀘어’ 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
     http://www.usquare.co.kr
    &lt;/a&gt;
    Hwasun Transportation 062) 373-5666
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    ○ Self-driving information
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    Honam Expressway → Gwangju 2nd Ring Road toward Hwasun → From Hwasun IC toward Beolgyo and Dongbok → From Guam Intersection toward Mofusan, Beolgyo and Boseong → From Daewonsa Intersection toward Daewonsa and Boseong County Baekmin Museum → Daewonsa
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    ○ Accommodation information
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    -Former Boseong Inn: Taebaeksanmac-gil, Beolgyo-eup, 061) 858-7528,
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.boseonginn.org&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;[새창열림]‘구 보성여관’ 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
     http://www.boseonginn.org
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    -Beolgyo Small Tourist Hotel: Beolgyo-eup Sinjeong-gil, 061) 858-9800,
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.벌교펜션호텔.kr&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;[새창열림]‘벌교소형관광호텔’ 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
     http://www.벌교펜션호텔.kr
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    -Hotel Dahyang: Joseong-myeon Joseong 3-gil, 061) 804-1004,
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.bosungcc.co.kr/html/facility/facility06.asp&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;[새창열림]‘호텔다향’ 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
     http://www.bosungcc.co.kr/html/facility/facility06.asp
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    ○ Restaurant information
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    -Boseong Nokcha Tteokgalbi Aid: Hanwoo Tteokgalbi, Boseong-eup, Heungseong-ro, 061) 853-0300,
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://보성떡갈비원조.crw.kr&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;[새창열림]‘보성녹차떡갈비원조’ 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
     http://보성떡갈비원조.crw.kr
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    -Subok Restaurant: Hanjeongsik, Boseong-eup Jungang-ro, 061) 853-3032,
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.수복식당.kr&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;[새창열림]‘수복식당’ 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
     http://www.수복식당.kr
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    -Kookil Restaurant: Komakjeongsik, Taebaeksanmac-gil, Beolgyo-eup, 061) 857-0588
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    ○ Festival and event information
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    -Boseong Cherry Blossom Festival: April 6, 2019, around the entrance of Daewonsa Temple, 061) 850-8281 ~ 4 (Mundeok-myeon Office)
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    ○ Things to see
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    Juam Lake, Yulpo Seawater Green Tea Center, Deokryang Station Memories Street, Korea Tea Museum
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p align=&#34;justify&#34;&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was created in March 2019, and may change later, so be sure to check it before you travel.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p align=&#34;justify&#34;&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;img src=&#34;https://support.visitkorea.or.kr/img/call?cmd=VIEW&amp;amp;id=66913896-8285-4e87-aec5-b969ff107303&amp;amp;mode=raw&#34; style=&#34;width:100%;&#34;/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>