<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dong-gu on Every Corner of Korea</title>
    <link>https://codecorea.github.io/tags/dong-gu/</link>
    <description>Every Corner of Korea (Dong-gu)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 00:56:10 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="https://codecorea.github.io/tags/dong-gu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The song of the sea will take us, trekking to Daewangam Park - Dong-gu, Ulsan, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/the-song-of-the-sea-will-take-us-trekking-to-daewangam-park-331/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 00:56:10 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/the-song-of-the-sea-will-take-us-trekking-to-daewangam-park-331/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Dong-gu, Ulsan, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;the-song-of-the-sea-will-take-us-trekking-to-daewangam-park--331&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Reddish Daewangam - Dong-gu, Ulsan, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/331/c225b515-2e21-4212-9708-6026a7b00733.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Reddish Daewangam
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   The song of the sea will take us, trekking to Daewangam Park
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Dong-gu, Ulsan, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you want to feel the lyricism of Ulsan, which you have never imagined, go to Daewangam Park. You will meet the new Ulsan as you walk along the fresh coastal path from Daewangam Park to Seoldo Jindo.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Along the trunk of the east coast, Ulsan reaches Pohang on the top and Busan on the bottom. Is it because there are many tourist cities that are up and down? Many people remember Ulsan, which is located between the two, as an “industrial city”. It is a distance from the &#39;tourist city&#39;. I think it&#39;s a similar expression to a blind dated entrant who says, “Your personality (only) looks good”. How to be patient to find ‘volumes’ that you must see and see and see the charm. The more blunt and uninteresting the opponent is, the more exciting it is to be a true country.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    So I prepared. A space where you can fully enjoy the nature of Ulsan, which has been stuck in the image of an industrial city for a long time. Introducing Daewangam Park, a glimpse of the unexpected charm of Ulsan. It is a space that Ulsan citizens regard as the best date course. We will walk along the coastal promenade around Daewangam Park to Deoljinjin Island.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   The story of the lighthouse at the end of Ulsan
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Daewangam Park was designated as the first park in Ulsan in 1962. It is called “Ulgi Lighthouse Park” after the name of Ulgi Lighthouse, which is located near Daewangam. It was renamed in 1984 because of “Japan&#39;s Remnants”. During the Russo-Japanese War of 1905, Japan, which made a wooden lantern to light the sea off the coast of Ulsan, built a 6-meter light tower the following year and gave it the name “Ulgi Lighthouse”. It means the lighthouse at the end of Ulsan. At this time, Japan also planted pine trees in order not to reveal the military base around the lighthouse to the outside.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Over time, when the pine trees grew taller than the lighthouse and became unable to serve as a lighthouse even with a 3m extension, a candlestick-shaped new light tower was erected in 1987. This is why the new and old towers of Ulgi Lighthouse are in good standing. The Uldung Lighthouse Gudeung Pagoda, which shows the architectural style 100 years ago, was recognized as a cultural asset and registered as a registered cultural asset No. 106.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Daewangam from different angles - Dong-gu, Ulsan, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/331/20eda851-8923-47c8-a557-01d89c0d2e18.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Daewangam from different angles
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Dong-gu, Ulsan, where Daewangam Park belongs, has three sides in the sea. The shape that protrudes south toward the sea seems to be perfect for coastal trekking. In 2012, Dong-gu, Ulsan Metropolitan City completed the &#39;Daewangam Solbaram-gil&#39; by constructing coastal roads from Mipo Coast to Daewangam Park and Seuldo to the former pier. Today&#39;s walk is part of Daewangam Solbaram-gil. Before going on a full-fledged trek, let&#39;s look at ‘Daewangam Solbaramgil’ first.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Mailbox of hope and love - Dong-gu, Ulsan, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/331/d09b3509-8939-4ad7-910e-d81d2a774fee.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Mailbox of hope and love
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The Daewangam Solbaram-gil leads to three sections: ① Mipo Coast ~ Ilsan Beach ② Daewangam Park ③ Island End Village ~ the former pier. It is still called by various names such as &#39;Daewangam Solbaram-gil&#39;, &#39;Daewangam Dulle-gil&#39; and &#39;Daewangam Park Trail&#39;. “In 2012, through the storytelling project, the coastal road in the vicinity of the Daewangam Solbaramgil was tentatively decided,” said Yoo Seongdeok, director of Dong-gu Office in Ulsan Metropolitan City. I said.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Ulgi Lighthouse Sin-gu Light Tower - Dong-gu, Ulsan, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/331/146cee76-c289-4cc7-8fd7-13c2683eadfa.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Ulgi Lighthouse Sin-gu Light Tower
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Whispers of mysterious strange rocks, Solwangramgil in Daewangam Park
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The section that we are introducing this time is from Daewangam Park to Seongdo Jindo. According to the Solbaram-gil section, ② Daewangam Park and ③ Island End Village ~ the former part of the pier belong. There is room for confusion, and this article tries to call it &#39;Suldo ~ Daewangam Park Trekking&#39; instead of &#39;Daewangam Solbaramgil&#39;.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   When you enter the entrance to Daewangam Park, take a brochure. When you enter the park from the entrance to the left, the coastal walkway spreads along the slim Gomsol. Outer Makgi ~ Anmakgi ~ Yonggul ~ Ulgi Lighthouse ~ Daewangam ~ Gwagaean ~ Godong Island Observatory ~ Noaegaean (Middle Point) ~ Suldo, in the middle of Daewangam Park, will take a big turn along the coast. Along the coast, there are attractions with various names. Instead of getting stressed out looking for it, I recommend you to enjoy the beautiful sea of Ulsan.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Daewangam Park Entrance - Dong-gu, Ulsan, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/331/27b16275-ae6c-4b4f-87c4-9682ee9b2f24.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Daewangam Park Entrance
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The ‘Yonggul’ bears the tale that a spoiled blue dragon is trapped, a pair of affectionate pine trees, and passes through Ulgi Lighthouse to reach Daewangam. When I see the huge ocher rocks that are located across the sea, I am reminded of the king of the moon, Silla, who fell asleep in the sea saying that he would be a god after he died and protect the country. Some people explain that Daewangam is also a place where Queen Munmu was asleep to defend the country by accepting the will of the king, but such a legend is beautiful enough to set aside. Until the Great Bridge was established, Daewangam went back and forth by boat. You can see the sunrise rising behind the great rock from the sunrise observatory located at the basement.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Seasong continues along the left coast - Dong-gu, Ulsan, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/331/390293e9-5fee-4be4-b9de-a088815a7c0c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Seasong continues along the left coast
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The farther away from Daewangam Park, the more shy the waters of Ulsan&#39;s sea become. I reach the overpass (Neven dogs) that the stones follow the path that I can walk forever. As the name of the wide coast, the soft coastline is warmly embraced. It was a coast that drove and captured whales until the 1960s. “There is a record that our ancestors, who were obliged to serve, returned the sea to the sea when a whale was pushed back,” said Park Ae-kyung, a cultural tourism commentator. I got a lot, ”he added.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Overdose, which means &#39;wide eye&#39; - Dong-gu, Ulsan, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/331/a7f9c303-35d6-491c-95f0-93fa044f799d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Overdose, which means &#39;wide eye&#39;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The road from Gugae-an to Suldo faces Godong Island. The transformation from ‘Suribau’ to ‘Sorabawi’ was converted to kanji and became ‘Godong Island’. There are two black rocks that do not resemble the beating. Let&#39;s remember that the moonlit night view is beautiful.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Coastal road scenery connecting Daewangam Park and the end of the island - Dong-gu, Ulsan, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/331/8d2d46cb-9569-40b4-b489-6c3b9d209946.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Coastal road scenery connecting Daewangam Park and the end of the island
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    How long did you walk? It hits the middle point. It stands in the middle of the boundary between Ilsan-dong and Defensive-dong. It is also called old-fashioned eye care. As you walk through this section, you often encounter a puddle. “This was a farm that raised Gunma in the Joseon Dynasty. Can you see the puddle here? It&#39;s the negative water that was feeding the horse. Even now, every house is used as agricultural water. ”
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A friendly brother-like island of Godong - Dong-gu, Ulsan, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/331/b9b426fb-6215-404b-b69a-78b68fb8fe58.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A friendly brother-like island of Godong
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Singing Rock Island, Seuldo
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;span&gt;
     It would not have been possible to feed the horse salty water. As I walked along this road, I used to think that it resembled Jeju Island, but I also raised my words. I see the good scenery and imagine the horse that I could have run to my heart&#39;s content, and reach the island village. The island end village, located between the island (Suldo) and 뭍, is also called the “Sung End Village”. In fact, there are traces of the &#39;castle&#39; that piles up stones along the coast of the village. It is also a village of haenyeo. There are a lot of sea divers from Jeju because it has a lot of seaweed and seafood because it touches the hole rock. You can still see the female divers who are material. As it became known as the location of the 2012 MBC drama &amp;lt;May Queen&amp;gt;, more and more people are looking for it. Alley murals decorated with colors greet tourists.
    &lt;/span&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;span&gt;
     If you cross the Seoldogyo Bridge at the end of the island, you reach Seoldo Island in Gombo Island. It became a gombo island by being surrounded by holey rocks left by stone clams. In addition, through this hole, the sound of sea water is expressively expressed, and Gombo Island became &#39;Suldo (瑟 島)&#39;. Although it is still uninhabited, it is not lonely anymore because the people who seek it under the influence of the drama continue to walk. The whale sculpture next to Seolgyo Bridge tells us that this is Ulsan, the home of whales. Still, the point is the lighthouse. The wooden chair under the lighthouse overlooks the sea. As I sat on a chair facing the sea, the Ulsan sea poured in coolly. What is the lighthouse waiting for, looking at the sea where whales might have someday played?
    &lt;/span&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox type3 clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Seuldo Lighthouse became famous as a location for drama - Dong-gu, Ulsan, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/331/a404ba6f-e38f-4122-9238-192f6d217853.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Seuldo Lighthouse became famous as a location for drama
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The appearance of the female divers - Dong-gu, Ulsan, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/331/245d6d6e-14e1-4a08-bd31-eb6fd1a8d3e7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The appearance of the female divers
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Seoldogyo Bridge connecting Island End Village and Uninhabited Island - Dong-gu, Ulsan, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/331/a3d581ad-e8bf-44c5-86e8-4f2e0554d425.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Seoldogyo Bridge connecting Island End Village and Uninhabited Island
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   tip. Daewangam Park
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Open year-round. The entrance time is not set, so you can always watch the sunrise at Daewangam. Ulgi Lighthouse, located in Daewangam Park, hosts a lighthouse experience program that combines lodging during elementary school vacations every year. In July and early December, go to the Ulsan Regional Maritime Affairs and Port website to apply. Up to 12 people can enter. Only families with elementary and junior high school students can apply. If more than 20 people visit Ulsan, contact the Ulsan Metropolitan City Office (052-229-3852, guide.ulsan.go.kr) to accompany the cultural tourism commentator.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Daewangam Park Inquiries: Dong-gu Office Culture and Sports Section 052-209-3470, Dong-gu Office Park Greenery Section 052-209-3754
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Ulgi Lighthouse Accommodation Inquiries: Ulgi Lighthouse 052-251-2125, Maritime Safety Facility Division 052-228-5610
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    1.Access
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    * Self-driving
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Gyeongbu Expressway Eonyang Junction → Ulsan Expressway → Sinbok Rotary → Nambu Ring Road → Turn right toward Ulsan MBC in front of Dongdeok Apartment → Turn left at Gyebyeon-ro → Gapsam 3-way direction toward Deokjinjin → Myeongchon Bridge → Goheon-ro → Turn right at Daewangam Park at Lighthouse Intersection → Daewangam Park
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    2. Delicious
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Eonyang Traditional Bulgogi: Eonyang-eup, Ulju-gun / Eonyang Bulgogi / 052-262-0940
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Whale Meat Aid Grandma Restaurant: Jangsaengpo Whale-ro, Nam-gu / Whale Meat / 052-261-7313
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Donghae Farm Restaurant: Yeonam-dong, Buk-gu / Boar Bulgogi / 052-288-4545
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Dodongsanbang: Sangbuk-myeon, Ulju-gun / Hanjeongsik / 052-254-7076
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Bean Love: Ilsan-dong, Dong-gu / Soybean Cuisine, Hwang-tae / 052-252-0023
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    3.Accommodation
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Kyungwon BIZ Motel: Noksu 7-gil, Dong-gu / 052-233-2000
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Hi Hotel: Dong-gu Badrae-gil / 052-944-1010
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Bioncheon Motel: Sangbuk-myeon, Ulju-gun / 052-254-1700
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Jakcheonjeong Pension Resort: Sangbuk-myeon, Ulju-gun / 052-264-4900
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Azela Resort Training Center: Sangbuk-myeon, Ulju-gun / 052-257-8040, 052-257-8041
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    ※ The above information was created in April 2013, and may be changed later, so be sure to check it before you travel.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>There is a sea in Daegu! Alive Aquarium Daegu - Dong-gu, Daegu, South Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/there-is-a-sea-in-daegu-alive-aquarium-daegu-114/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 09:54:39 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/there-is-a-sea-in-daegu-alive-aquarium-daegu-114/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Dong-gu, Daegu, South Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;there-is-a-sea-in-daegu-alive-aquarium-daegu--114&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Alive Aquarium Daegu&#39;s main tank - Dong-gu, Daegu, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/114/58719880-9373-41d2-9533-23d91c87b723.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Alive Aquarium Daegu&#39;s main tank
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   There is a sea in Daegu! Alive Aquarium Daegu
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Dong-gu, Daegu, South Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   A hot place like an oasis has appeared in Daegu surrounded by mountains such as Palgongsan and Bisleul Mountain. The main character is &#39;Alive Aquarium Daegu&#39;, which was ambitiously presented at Shinsegae Department Store Daegu. It&#39;s a sea in the inland city. Alive Aquarium Daegu, as its name suggests, contains lifelike sea life every tank. Visitors are immersed in the mysterious sights of the ocean.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Underwater trip from the top of the department store
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Alive Aquarium Daegu (hereafter Alive Aquarium) can be found on the 9th floor, the top floor of Shinsegae Department Store Daegu Main Building. It is an aquarium set in the highest position in Korea. The sea creatures on display are about 200 species, including manatees, California sea lions and zebra sharks. Viewing routes consisted of a one-way that allows you to look around all the exhibition spaces from the entrance to the exit in one direction. It is about 800m long and takes about 95 minutes.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Fantastic view of the jellyfish aquarium - Dong-gu, Daegu, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/114/3129e989-8738-4b15-b3c6-56b2bf07c29c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Fantastic view of the jellyfish aquarium
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The first thing you&#39;ll encounter past the entrance to the Alive Aquarium is the jellyfish aquarium, which embellishes the interior with a fluorescent sky. The moment you see it, it is a sight that makes you resilient. As the jellyfish floats across the cylindrical aquarium, spreading its caps, a small full moon, like its name (full moon jellyfish), floats. Elegant movements that cannot be imitated by any living creature add to the ever-changing lighting, giving you a slightly dreamy atmosphere. The jellyfish aquarium is mirrored on four sides, creating a magnificent view.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Jellyfish wide open - Dong-gu, Daegu, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/114/0463b46b-8648-4982-88b6-38c82dc96c77.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Jellyfish wide open
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   When you leave the jellyfish aquarium, three long rectangular tanks occupy space. The garden is a scary garden where the tail is buried in the sand, the Bangga Cardinal with its cute looks and slender fins, the unicorn with its horns on its head, and the parakeet that resembles a parrot&#39;s beak. Can be.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sea ecosystems in long tanks - Dong-gu, Daegu, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/114/61b20c5c-2f59-43e2-9dd7-a5b004a4db93.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sea ecosystems in long tanks
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Garden-il attracts the attention of visitors because of its rather silly appearance. The elongated body that oozes out over the sand is like a blade of grass swaying in the wind.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Garden work with a tail buried in the sand and swimming Bengalika Cardinal - Dong-gu, Daegu, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/114/b6956cdd-e468-4b8c-a909-7d938533ee80.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Garden work with a tail buried in the sand and swimming Bengalika Cardinal
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Cafés and kids zones greet visitors as they pass by the fish tank and photo tank where you can take commemorative photos. Kids Zone has a touch pool where children can touch eel and octopus, and a facility where children can play with various toys. There is a sketch aquarium on one wall. After coloring the paper on which the sea creatures are drawn, scan the finished picture on the device and the animal appears on the screen to swim. While energetic kids are engrossed in playing, adults can enjoy a bit of tea at a cafe.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Kids Zone for Children - Dong-gu, Daegu, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/114/2e542ff3-4d2b-4cbd-9bb8-a26f9545b0fc.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Kids Zone for Children
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   There is also a small zoo inside the Alive Aquarium. You&#39;ll find a cute hare, land turtle Sulgata, a crazy meerkat and a raccoon that rides through trees. Rabbits and turtles can be touched directly by the zookeeper. Children squirm behind the rabbits, imitating rabbits, and stroking their mothers and zookeepers and petting them.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;13&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Children petting a rabbit - Dong-gu, Daegu, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/114/a413bcd5-a246-4b0f-a88e-25b0aca8d7b2.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Children petting a rabbit
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The Seaso Manatee is the mascot of the Alive Aquarium. I am proud of a cute appearance not to match the size and get a lot of popularity. There are only a thousand rare species left in the world, so it is worth noting.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;15&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Manatee Enjoying Swimming &amp;lt;Photo courtesy of Alive Aquarium&amp;gt; - Dong-gu, Daegu, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/114/c5a7d995-1bb0-4414-9abd-2a4ebda4ce98.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Manatee Enjoying Swimming &amp;lt;Photo courtesy of Alive Aquarium&amp;gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The Manatee Aquarium reproduces the depth of Manatee&#39;s main habitat, a lagoon (a shallow lake separated from the sea by sedimentary obstacles such as sand). Manatee eats 20 kg of vegetables per day, including bok choy, cabbage, cabbage, and jerk. It&#39;s interesting to see how people use their hands to eat vegetables as if they were people. Excessive amounts of waste are excreted frequently, which feed on omnivorous fish in the same aquarium.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;17&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;State of Manatee Aquarium - Dong-gu, Daegu, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/114/844d540f-da1e-45a7-971b-96c7c0c3ff5b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     State of Manatee Aquarium
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you keep moving along the viewing route, you will have a spacious space. You can meet the treehouse where you can feed animals such as parrots and interact with them. The screen also allows you to observe the features of parrots and otters in detail.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;19&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Mother with Child Looking at California Sea Lion - Dong-gu, Daegu, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/114/e46da8da-ad2d-4c8c-912b-b630925951ef.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Mother with Child Looking at California Sea Lion
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   After watching the magic show and walking, the 360-degree sardine aquarium on the ceiling reveals itself. You can enjoy the lively group of sardines. The ecstasy of the sardines&#39; movement in groups. A little exaggeration is the feeling of seeing the Milky Way swirling in the night sky. The dark interior, herds of sardines revealing a silver belly, and the aquarium design reminiscent of human eyes create an artistic harmony. Seats are reserved for convenience.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;21&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Herd of Sardine Swarm - Dong-gu, Daegu, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/114/e629cd10-3dd2-452b-82a6-f48cf72999af.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Herd of Sardine Swarm
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   From the sardine aquarium, you can meet the clownfish, famous for Nemo, while passing through a tunnel reminiscent of a tunnel. Then, after leaving the corner, the main tank, the sea of Daegu, will appear. It has a small sea with zebra sharks, large stingrays and sea turtles.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;23&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;An aquarium was placed in the passage reminiscent of the tunnel. - Dong-gu, Daegu, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/114/501a99f9-8453-4044-949e-6f4c813ef6a8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     An aquarium was placed in the passage reminiscent of the tunnel.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It&#39;s amazing and fun just to look at it, but the specialty of the main tank is complete with a variety of programs. The Blue Mermaid is a beautiful feast of three mermaids among sea creatures. Every time the mermaid waved and smiles at the younger crowd, cheers burst out. &#39;Alive Girls&#39; is a delightful underwater ballet performance, and &#39;Igley and Friends&#39; is a program where the aquaticist closes the sea creatures with a camera in the tank.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;25&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A Blue Mermaid performance &amp;lt;Photo courtesy of Alive Aquarium&amp;gt; - Dong-gu, Daegu, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/114/8bf4ec33-bed2-4198-9ca9-ea86ecb3119a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A Blue Mermaid performance &amp;lt;Photo courtesy of Alive Aquarium&amp;gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The Shark Bridge is installed near the main tank. Literally, it&#39;s a bridge where you can walk on sharks. After the Shark Bridge experience, the tour ends with a giant grouper called `` Siktam Hemp King &#39;&#39;. The Giant Grouper was originally from the main tank and was thrown out of his current tank because he was eating a shark.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;27&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Visitors walking the Shark Bridge - Dong-gu, Daegu, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/114/3bf365a8-d8d8-4b96-876c-d36809af4486.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Visitors walking the Shark Bridge
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Move space from the sea to the jungle, &#39;Juraji&#39;, a rooftop theme park
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   After watching the Alive Aquarium, go out through the aisle and you will see the rooftop theme park &#39;Juraji&#39; with the concept of a jungle. The underwater journey ends and the jungle exploration begins. You are moving from space to a completely different environment.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Panoramic view of the rooftop theme park `` Juraji &#39;&#39; - Dong-gu, Daegu, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/114/9f522518-51f7-44c4-bcbf-d28ff6459078.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Panoramic view of the rooftop theme park `` Juraji &#39;&#39;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In the Juraji, various sculptures that fit the concept were placed. The elephant &#39;Choji&#39; lies down in front of the fountain, and the three ladybug trains carry the children and run between the legs of the giant spider &#39;Buibui&#39;. The wood crocodile Gumu is willing to slide his head out for the kids. On one side, bamboo baobabs stand majestic. In the meantime, various wild animals such as giraffe and rhinoceros hang out. Visitors can walk through a wooden deck that extends into the air, overlooking an African-like landscape.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;15&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;There is a wooden deck among the baobabs. - Dong-gu, Daegu, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/114/712fffd5-6099-40bb-b2e0-b8296238dee2.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     There is a wooden deck among the baobabs.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   At the end of the roof, you can step on a fluffy mound and have a view of downtown Daegu and Palgong Mountain. It is popular as a date place for lovers to see the night view at night. Dongdaegu Station, shown to the right, is the main stage of the movie &amp;lt;To Busan&amp;gt;. It is a scene where a train running toward Busan stops in the ruins of Dongdaegu, and people who are not infected with zombies, such as sharing, struggle with zombies that have increased exponentially.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;16&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Giraffe Sculpture - Dong-gu, Daegu, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/114/24fce7e6-335f-4fe8-b323-dd6bff3fb07b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Giraffe Sculpture
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Concentric Filled Aquarium, Alive Aquarium
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Throughout the Alive Aquarium, the children&#39;s laughter and groaning continued. Responding violently to every mysterious gesture of the sea creatures, he revealed the pleasures of raw foods. The feelings of the child were conveyed to the adults, and the adults looked into the aquarium with pure eyes as if returning to their childhood for a while. The aquarium of Alive Aquarium was filled with generational concentricity.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel info
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Alive Aquarium Daegu
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Address: 9th floor, Shinsegae Department Store Daegu, 149 Dongbu-ro, Dong-gu, Daegu Metropolitan City
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Contact: 053-247-8899
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.aliveaqua.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.aliveaqua.com/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Restaurants near
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    P.F Chang&#39;s: Mongolian Beef / Shinsegae Department Store Daegu 8F, Luang Street / 053-661-6873
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.pfchangs.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.pfchangs.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Gangsan Myeonok: Pyeongyang Naengmyeon / Shinsegae Department Store Daegu Branch 8F, Luang Street / 053-661-6862
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Tong House Night: Tempura Tung House / 12, Ayang-ro 7-gil, Dong-gu, Daegu, Korea
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Rooms
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Daegu Grand Hotel: 305, Dongdaegu-ro, Suseong-gu / 053-742-0001
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.daegugrand.co.kr/grand/main/index.php&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.daegugrand.co.kr/grand/main/index.php
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Benikea Hotel Suseong: 106-7, Yonghak-ro, Suseong-gu / 1899-1001
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.hotelsusung.co.kr&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.hotelsusung.co.kr
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Aega: 46-6, Seoseong-ro 16-gil, Jung-gu / 053-781-5215
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://aegahanok.modoo.at/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://aegahanok.modoo.at/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was updated in January 2019 and may change afterwards. Please check before traveling.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ The information such as text, photos and videos used in this article is copyrighted by Korea Tourism Organization, so unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>