<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Yeoncheon-gun on Every Corner of Korea</title>
    <link>https://codecorea.github.io/tags/yeoncheon-gun/</link>
    <description>Every Corner of Korea (Yeoncheon-gun)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 15:28:15 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="https://codecorea.github.io/tags/yeoncheon-gun/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Peace to settle on the Korean Peninsula with classical music, Yeoncheon DMZ International Music Festival - Yeoncheon-gun, Gyeonggi-do, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/peace-to-settle-on-the-korean-peninsula-with-classical-music-yeoncheon-dmz-international-music-festival-192/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 15:28:15 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/peace-to-settle-on-the-korean-peninsula-with-classical-music-yeoncheon-dmz-international-music-festival-192/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Yeoncheon-gun, Gyeonggi-do, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;peace-to-settle-on-the-korean-peninsula-with-classical-music-yeoncheon-dmz-international-music-festival--192&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;KBS Symphony Orchestra - Yeoncheon-gun, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/192/d6d9f646-c9a1-4429-b22d-d45c0fe17d43.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    KBS Symphony Orchestra
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Peace to settle on the Korean Peninsula with classical music, Yeoncheon DMZ International Music Festival
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Yeoncheon-gun, Gyeonggi-do, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   From July 25th to August 2nd, &#39;Yeoncheon DMZ International Music Festival&#39; will be held in Yeoncheon-gun, Gyeonggi-do for 9 days. The main stage of the festival is the Jeokgok-ri Seonje Historic Site, Hantan River Tourist Site, and Sureul Art Hall. This year, with the theme of “coexistence,” about 40 musicians, including Sook-ryun Park, will produce chords. Orchestra performances, concerts by artists from around the world, fringe concerts, visiting concerts, music academies, and classical lectures are held throughout the music festival. I believe that the feast of beautiful classics created by travelers from Yeoncheon-gun and artists from around the world will greatly contribute to the settlement of peace on the Korean Peninsula.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The tragedy of the Korean War, which broke out in 1950, ended on July 27, 1953, three years later. That day was the day the Armistice Agreement was signed. The formal name of the Armistice Agreement is the Agreement on the Military Armistice of the Republic of Korea, with the Commander-in-Chief of the United Nations as one side and the Supreme Commander of the Democratic People&#39;s Republic of Korea and the Commander of the People&#39;s Republic of China as the other. On this day, the UN, North Korean and Chinese forces signed the Armistice Agreement under Article 5, Section 63. Korea, a party to the Korean War, was excluded. This ended the war that lasted for three years and a month, but demilitarized zones (DMZs), literally banned areas of armament, formed on the Korean Peninsula.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   According to data from DMZ Museum, the demilitarized zone of the Korean Peninsula is 155 miles (about 248 km) from Gyodongdo Island on the western side of Yeseong River and Hangang River to Panmunjom in the southern part of Kaesong, through Cheorwon and Geumhwa in the central region to Goseong Myeongho (Unification Observatory) on the east coast. ), Which means 2 km between the north and the south, about 300 million pyeong (3,360 km) of the buffering zone, centered on the Military Demarcation Line (MDL). You can see the DMZ from the key observation deck north of Yeoncheon-gun. You must bring your ID to visit the Key Observation Deck.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It&#39;s a place of heartbreaking history, but you can&#39;t just stay in the past. Yeoncheon-gun has repeatedly transformed itself into the number one spot in security tourism for peace and reunification, and has been holding the Yeoncheon DMZ International Music Festival since 2011 as one of its new efforts. The DMZ is also the site of the division of the Fatherland, but the festival focuses on classical music every year in the hope of being reborn as a site of reunification, peace, and ecology.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Students participating in the music academy walking the iron fence next to the key observatory - Yeoncheon-gun, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/192/e169fa92-d7c8-4790-b071-6182c5f59e33.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Students participating in the music academy walking the iron fence next to the key observatory
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Starting on the opening concert of Yeoncheon Culture and Sports Center on Saturday, July 25, the music school &#39;Music Academy&#39; with the best classical artists at home and abroad, &#39;DMZ experience&#39; that allows you to know the reality of the divided country and experience the military border area directly &#39;,&#39; Mini Peace Concert &#39;that sings peace and hope,&#39; Nara Love Concert &#39;, which wishes for peace on the Korean Peninsula and around the world,&#39; Artist Concert Series&#39; where artists full of personality perform, and &#39;Specials&#39; held by top artists from around the world Following the guest concert, it will be finished with a &#39;closing concert&#39; where all participating artists participate.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Let&#39;s look at each program in more detail. The opening concert will be performed by Mostly Philharmonic Orchestra (Director Park Sang-hyun), Yeoncheon YES Orchestra (Director Seo Hong-jun), Pianist Manuel Obregon and Violinist Frederick Morrow. Here, the stages of singers Cho Yong-nam and Hyo-beom Shin are familiar. In addition, the music school &#39;Music Academy&#39;, which is held throughout the festival, will be held with private lessons, master classes, and celebrity lectures of piano, violin, cello, and viola parts from elementary to general.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Also, it is a pity to miss the “Artist Concert Series,” where you can fully appreciate the performances of pianist Ivan Yanakov, Seonghoon Kim, Eurk Demus, and cellist Dorel Bodoreanu. It is held at Herb Village Olive Hall. For those with various musical tastes, fringe concerts filled with various genre performances and performances, such as classical, pop, jazz, song, and percussion performances, add to the richness.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Yeoncheon DMZ International Music Festival 2015 &amp;lt;Photo Source: DMZ International Music Festival Secretariat&amp;gt; - Yeoncheon-gun, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/192/daa0c297-1f1a-45bc-86ea-6786013182c1.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Yeoncheon DMZ International Music Festival 2015 &amp;lt;Photo Source: DMZ International Music Festival Secretariat&amp;gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   On August 1st (Sat), 7 days before the closing day, the closing concert will be held at all Yeoncheonsu Leul Art Hall with all participating artists. Not only foreign performers who showed their appearance at the opening performance, but also domestic performers all appeared, and they gave the music of excitement and harmony.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Mostly Philharmonic Orchestra - Yeoncheon-gun, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/192/2b5be86a-ebce-4675-bc7e-76913b805db8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Mostly Philharmonic Orchestra
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   At the DMZ International Music Festival, Yeoncheon-gun recommends destinations called “The Five Spots of Security” and “The Seven Spots of Nature” for travelers who are impressed by the classics. The 5th security refers to the hurricane observatory, key observatory, promotion OP, 1st tunnel, and 1,21 armed defense invasion route. The seven natural scenery are the Imjin River Tourist Site, the Hantan River Tourist Site, the Baekhak Reservoir, the Dongmakgol Amusement Park, the Jain Waterfall, the Ancient Mountain, and the Twelve Creek.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Commemorative photo of students participating in Music Academy - Yeoncheon-gun, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/192/0f137e1a-d7d7-45d6-b0e6-a5e82b62c500.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Commemorative photo of students participating in Music Academy
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   On the other hand, if you&#39;re traveling with elementary school children, check out the Jeokgok Seonsa Museum, located in Jeokgok-ri, the home of the Paleolithic people 350,000 years ago. What is more eye-catching is the model of human ancestors reproduced in vivid form. Tumai, the ancestor of humanity about 7 to 6 million years ago, Australopithecus who lived in eastern and southern Africa 4 to 2 million years ago, Homo erectus that appeared about 1.8 million years ago, appeared in Africa about 200,000 years ago Homo sapiens and others welcome visitors.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   In the cave paintings section, it is interesting to reproduce murals found in Lasco Cave in France and Altamira Cave in Spain. If you go to the outdoor experience center, you will be waiting for the fist ax making experience.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;13&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Exhibits at the Jeokok Seonsa Museum &#39;The Great March of Human Evolution&#39; - Yeoncheon-gun, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/192/be3d6ba0-72ad-45a3-8b44-5cbad0bc18b7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Exhibits at the Jeokok Seonsa Museum &#39;The Great March of Human Evolution&#39;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Yeoncheon DMZ International Music Festival Secretariat
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     031-955-5982
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.dmzimf.com&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
      www.dmzimf.com
     &lt;/font&gt;
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Department of Culture, Sports and Tourism, Yeoncheon-gun Office
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     031-839-2061
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.iyc21.net&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
      www.iyc21.net
     &lt;/font&gt;
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Jeokok Seonsa Museum
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     031-830-5600
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.jgpm.or.kr&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
      www.jgpm.or.kr
     &lt;/font&gt;
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Yeoncheon Soul Art Hall
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     031-834-3770
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.sureul.com&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
      www.sureul.com
     &lt;/font&gt;
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1.Nearby Restaurants
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Maeeuntang beyond the hill: Freshwater Maeuntang / 43-21, Solnero-gil, Gunnam-myeon, Yeoncheon-gun / 031-833-0447
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Hanam Restaurant: Freshwater Maeuntang / 175, Jeonsu-ro, Jeongok-eup, Yeoncheon-gun / 031-832-0625
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Goryeo Garden: Mushroom Bulgogi / 381, Soonguijeon-ro, Misan-myeon, Yeoncheon-gun / 031-835-5464
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://cafe.daum.net/goryogarden&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://cafe.daum.net/goryogarden
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2.Accommodation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Royal Hanok Hotel in Chosun: 339-10, Hyeonmun-ro, Yeoncheon-eup, Yeoncheon-gun / 031-834-8383
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Chosung Motel: 97, Cheongsin-ro, Cheongsan-myeon, Yeoncheon-gun / 031-835-2610
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Hantan River Motel: 185-6, Jeonsu-ro, Jeongok-eup, Yeoncheon-gun / 031-832-7330
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was updated in July 2015, and may be changed later, so please check before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>