<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Yeonggwang-gun on Every Corner of Korea</title>
    <link>https://codecorea.github.io/tags/yeonggwang-gun/</link>
    <description>Every Corner of Korea (Yeonggwang-gun)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 14:43:46 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="https://codecorea.github.io/tags/yeonggwang-gun/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Deokja, barley gulbi, and rice thieves all gather! Glory Bob Thief Travel - Yeonggwang-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/deokja-barley-gulbi-and-rice-thieves-all-gather-glory-bob-thief-travel-363/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 14:43:46 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/deokja-barley-gulbi-and-rice-thieves-all-gather-glory-bob-thief-travel-363/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Yeonggwang-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;deokja-barley-gulbi-and-rice-thieves-all-gather-glory-bob-thief-travel--363&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;When you don&#39;t have any appetite, it&#39;s best if you don&#39;t put water in the rice - Yeonggwang-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/363/0399cde1-f629-4539-9454-994806232270.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    When you don&#39;t have any appetite, it&#39;s best if you don&#39;t put water in the rice
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Deokja, barley gulbi, and rice thieves all gather! Glory Bob Thief Travel
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Yeonggwang-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   When the long and long summer is over, the taste that left the house returns and sits at the head of the table. Even in the summer and in the fall, the best rice thief is Byeolgulpo in Beopseongpo. Roll it in cold water and put a piece of salty gulbi on it, and the rice sticks to your mouth. Dukja and Gejang do not fall into Gwangbi&#39;s rice thief. From midsummer to the most delicious, spicy and spicy duck soup and blue crab seasoned with spicy sauce, the rice thieves searched for a meal of glorious rice thieves.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   All of the early and Gulbi, the legality of Gulbi
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   On a hot summer day, he dreams of a simple meal that sits on a cool ridge. After scooping up a spoonful of rice on the barley tea, then tearing the dried oysters to the side and dipping it in red pepper paste to eat it. When Gulbi, Gwangju Beopseongpo comes to mind first. This is because the oyster stew dried in the sea wind of Beopseongpo, pickled in natural salt of Glory, whether it is a natural reference machine or a cultivated cultivated product, is the best. It was called ‘Jogi (해서)’ because it has the effect of boosting the body&#39;s energy. It is rich in protein and calcium, so it is also excellent for growth and rejuvenation.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   You can go to Beopseongpo to see the true taste of the non-formed reference machine. In Gwanggwang, you can select Beopseongpo Gulbijeong, Myeongga-echan, Darang-gaji, Munjeong Hanjeongsik, and Bicheteul Restaurant. If you go to the Beopseongpo Gulbi restaurant that dries Gulbi directly, you can taste all the foods made using Gulbi. The owner of the Beopseongpo Gulbi-sik set about December 20 to hang the gulbi and collect it when the wind is coldest for about two months. You shouldn&#39;t be hard on your liver, so you need to keep the dates accurate. This is because the taste of oysters varies depending on the process of seasoning with sea salt and drying in the sea breeze.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The old gulbi was kept dry like this - Yeonggwang-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/363/72780551-3f55-4f6e-a48e-91209f828b8e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The old gulbi was kept dry like this
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Gulbi Hanjeongsik, which comes with all the food that can be made with Gulbi, starts softly with early skin. In addition to the fish porridge, 8 menus are available from early to early, grilled oysters, barley oysters, gochujang oysters, early steamed, early geiritang, and early salted fish.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Beopseongpo Gulbi Set meal table full of rice thieves - Yeonggwang-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/363/323b5247-ffdf-4edb-968f-c1b5f66befec.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Beopseongpo Gulbi Set meal table full of rice thieves
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   No matter what anyone says, the main character of Gulbi Hansik is barley gulbi that is soaked in rice water to reduce salinity and spread on the steamer.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Beopseongpo Barley Gulbi has a savory taste - Yeonggwang-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/363/cdd141c2-f887-462d-905f-b3c5dffddddd.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Beopseongpo Barley Gulbi has a savory taste
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The oyster alone is good for umami, and the air of rice can be spoiled, but the crab crab soy sauce made with grinded fruit is also a steal of rice. Adding one bowl of rice to the oyster meal is not an option, but a must.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Crab soy sauce crab with fresh fruit and cool taste - Yeonggwang-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/363/d770a92f-fc0f-4b24-97b9-df06a144032b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Crab soy sauce crab with fresh fruit and cool taste
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The fresh early war and the early steaming of the Albaegi have good freshness, so the flesh is on the side and the texture is excellent. The barley gulbi is marinated in red pepper paste, and the red pepper paste barley gulbi is eaten with a spicy and salty taste. Fortunately, the side dishes at Beopseongpo Gulbi Restaurant are not very simple.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Barley Gulbi, Gochujang Gulbi, and Gulbi Roast are three brothers - Yeonggwang-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/363/9a5d4518-a6e5-4f31-a7b2-a99fbe520aa7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Barley Gulbi, Gochujang Gulbi, and Gulbi Roast are three brothers
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The early geography soup that boils cleanly is also cool. The 20 side dishes that fit the name of Hanjeongsik are also boring and light. Early steamed egg simmered in spicy seasoning and early salted fish with attractive and unique taste of salted fish are perfect as a side dish.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;13&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Boil the hot water only in the early days of operation within 3 days of winter - Yeonggwang-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/363/e9c77e5b-b6a9-4bb1-85f7-3181282fb423.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Boil the hot water only in the early days of operation within 3 days of winter
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Beopseongpo Gulbi Restaurant is located in Golbi Alley, Beopseongpo, with the Sea of Chilsan in between. It is not unusual that the 6-year-old old paper that was soaked in preparation for the opening of the restaurant is served with gulbi set&#39;s Hongeo Samhap. If you just tell the story of Gulbi in front of the owner or employee of your hometown, or at the table, you are a prominent liquidator. While applying barley gulbi and grilled oysters to eat, the history of Beopseongpo and the pride of gulbi are delicious.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;15&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Beopseongpogul non-formal appearance that goes well with the jar - Yeonggwang-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/363/f3ee69fd-9521-402f-a988-f186046d4b44.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Beopseongpogul non-formal appearance that goes well with the jar
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Steamed duck and crab crab seasoned with rice thieves, Haechon Restaurant
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Haechon Restaurant is 5 minutes away from Yeonggwang Terminal. This restaurant is famous for its lunch menu called dried gulbi green tea iced rice, which is eaten in green tea by drying the fat that is plump in the Haesung of Beopseongpo.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Haechon Restaurant is 5 minutes from the terminal - Yeonggwang-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/363/12950bbd-174e-43f1-b7a6-b108472913e3.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Haechon Restaurant is 5 minutes from the terminal
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Lunch specials, featuring a seasoned crab with fresh blue crab caught in the fresh taste of the pre-formed bouche with cool green tea water, are also available at a reasonable price, but the best menu in Haechon is Deokja Steamed. From May to June, bottled fish and jukeum, from July to September, Deokja and Gulbi, from September to November, and mullet are waiting in December, but until September, steamed duck is the best.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Haenchon Restaurant&#39;s lunch special menu, dried gulbi green tea iced rice - Yeonggwang-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/363/42e052ba-4099-4b8c-970c-dccd7554f224.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Haenchon Restaurant&#39;s lunch special menu, dried gulbi green tea iced rice
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Dukja is characterized by its large size, and its fins black. It is more delicious than octopus and has a softer taste. Deokja is rich in protein and unsaturated fatty acids, and rich in amino acids such as taurine and glutamic acid, making it excellent for rejuvenation and good for people with skin problems. As it is tasty and rich in nutritional value, it is priced as a cigar. The price varies from 50,000 to 70,000 won depending on the size of the fish that comes in every day, and when you make a reservation, it is cooked for 3 to 4 servings.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Steamed duck with seasoning of miso and red pepper paste - Yeonggwang-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/363/e9e38824-3ada-4146-9375-21536c3ae685.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Steamed duck with seasoning of miso and red pepper paste
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The first secret of Haechon Restaurant&#39;s food taste is to cook only the creatures without using frozen fish in any season. The second trick is to use generously red pepper powder purchased from Gwanggwang and season with the miso and red pepper paste to match the seasoning. The third trick is to season with fresh ingredients such as fresh garlic and scented ginger and sweet onions.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A piece of thick duck cake is delicious - Yeonggwang-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/363/8a72fb9e-ea93-4942-be80-c9c79ce7fc0f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A piece of thick duck cake is delicious
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you look at the cooking process of Deokja steamed, it is more like boiled than steamed. The fish is so thick that it starts stewing an hour before the reservation. Deokja-jjim, which is made by dipping Dukja in an airy seasoning sauce, boils down, and tastes delicious with plump and light flesh. Even if you eat fish meat and marinade with rice, the two tastes are sharp and cool. At Haechon Restaurant, two air per person is natural. When steamed with savory and spicy duck, a side dish of fresh seaweed is the basis for two rice.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Seasoned crab served with dried gulbi green tea iced rice - Yeonggwang-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/363/1ee59886-a6ab-44b9-906c-f032b95414cb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Seasoned crab served with dried gulbi green tea iced rice
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   You should eat dried gulbi green tea iced rice with one bowl of gulbi and another bowl with blue crab. Blue crab meat seasoned with spicy red pepper powder seasoning with only sweet crab meat is an attractive menu. Add a spoonful of crab marinade to hot rice and simmer it in a bite. If you eat it, it melts sweet and spicy in your mouth.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;13&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;It is delicious even if you mix the rice with crab sauce - Yeonggwang-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/363/e5e0bb43-55ad-41b1-89e5-95713ba0e063.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     It is delicious even if you mix the rice with crab sauce
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Beopseong Pogul Ratio Formula
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Address: 7 Beopseongpo-ro, Beopseong-myeon, Yeonggwang-gun, Jeonnam
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Contact: 061-356-7575
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Haechon
      &lt;br/&gt;
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     Address: 149 Sinnam-ro, Yeonggwang-eup, Yeonggwang-gun, Jeonnam
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Contact: 061-353-8897
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Nearby destinations
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Bulgapsa Temple: 450 Bulgapsa-ro, Bulgap-myeon, Yeonggwang-gun / 061-352-8097
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Kamami Beach: 355, Kamami-ro, Hongnong-eup, Yeonggwang-gun / 061-356-1020
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Baeksu Coastal Road: 957 Haean-ro, Baeksu-eup, Yeonggwang-gun / 061-350-5600
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2.Accommodation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Yeonggwang Country Club: 1362-70, Haean-ro, Baeksu-eup, Yeonggwang-gun / 061-350-2000
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Forester Pension: 77-22, Forester Road, Beopseong-myeon, Yeonggwang-gun / 010-2023-3387
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.happyvil.co.kr/default/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.happyvil.co.kr/default/
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Yeonggwang Glory Tourist Hotel: 74, Okdang-ro, Yeonggwang-eup, Yeonggwang-gun / 061-351-8700
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was written in August 2015, and may change later, so be sure to check it before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>