<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Goyang-si on Every Corner of Korea</title>
    <link>https://codecorea.github.io/tags/goyang-si/</link>
    <description>Every Corner of Korea (Goyang-si)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 00:56:12 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="https://codecorea.github.io/tags/goyang-si/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>On the white snowy field, the world of horses, &#39;Goyang Wondang Ranch&#39; - Goyang-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/on-the-white-snowy-field-the-world-of-horses-goyang-wondang-ranch-333/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 00:56:12 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/on-the-white-snowy-field-the-world-of-horses-goyang-wondang-ranch-333/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Goyang-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;on-the-white-snowy-field-the-world-of-horses-goyang-wondang-ranch--333&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Horses running on the snow field - Goyang-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/333/82c2f9bf-2f25-4fe5-a0d0-0bae197bf61a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Horses running on the snow field
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   On the white snowy field, the world of horses, &#39;Goyang Wondang Ranch&#39;
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Goyang-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The horses leap over the vast snow field. The kids roll in the snow on a wide ranch or stroking horses, and laughing. The Wondang Ranch in winter is elegant. The vast snowfields and horses that no one stepped on create an atmosphere like a scene in a movie. Nearby the ranch, there were places where you could feel the gentle smell of Seosamneung and Herb Farm, designated as World Heritage Sites.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The role of Wondang Ranch is changed from the stallion ranch to a horse race training center for training jockey and horse experts. An apartment village was formed in the vicinity of Samsong-ri, so the way to go is quite different, but the scenery of horses running on the ranch is still the same. Ranch area is only 360,000 m2. The large ranch hidden in Gyeonggi-do creates a peaceful scenery in which horses run in the middle of winter.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Eunsashi Tree Road and Seosamneung
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It is fascinating from the beginning to enter the ranch. The silver road leading to the entrance is covered with snow in winter, and its color and atmosphere add to the atmosphere. The pass is popular as a dating course for lovers, but it&#39;s better to walk quietly and quietly rather than just passing by car.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Ranch became popular as a location for dramas and movies even before it was known as an outing course. Dramas &amp;lt;City Hall&amp;gt;, &amp;lt;Coffee Prince No. 1&amp;gt;, and &amp;lt;Legend of Ambition&amp;gt; were filmed here. Eunsashi Tree Road also served as the backdrop for the dramas &amp;lt;Spring Day&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;Sand Clock&amp;gt;.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Eunsashi Tree Road, the backdrop of the drama - Goyang-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/333/eef8c11c-0a6b-4700-9b07-96f113cc672c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Eunsashi Tree Road, the backdrop of the drama
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The entrance to the ranch also borders Seosamneung, where the Joseon royalty is asleep. Seosamneung is one of the royal tombs designated as a World Heritage Site. It is called Samreung because there are Yeolneung of Joseon Chongjong and Queen Cheolin, Kim Yeongneung of King Jungjong, Heeungneung where Queen Jangkyung Yoon was buried. The snowy royal tomb is quiet and calm. Walking along the trail of the Royal Mausoleum where it is difficult to find people is also a unique feature.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;I like horses stroking their noses - Goyang-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/333/66057864-eacf-4982-b946-dca189c81fed.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     I like horses stroking their noses
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   After passing the Seosamneung, an open farm catches the eye. The little kids first meet the snow world before going on a horse tour. They roll down the snow field and have a snowball fight and shake off the long winter boredom. It is fortunate to encounter such a large playground in nature on a winter day.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Seosamneung, a World Heritage Site - Goyang-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/333/d2b37b23-b109-4119-a0a9-5e7c635bacc3.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Seosamneung, a World Heritage Site
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The ranch is neatly refurbished. There is an observation deck and space for horses, and there are convenient facilities such as walkways. There are benches on the promenade for a date and relaxation.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Horse racing jockeys training scene - Goyang-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/333/995608dd-6e8f-4aaa-bc03-da2152a1bdbc.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Horse racing jockeys training scene
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The Wondang Horse Farm has been open to the public since 1997. In the past, sleek and talented racehorses were born and domesticated here. Seedlings managed here were treasures of over a billion won. With the relocation of the Horse Racing Training Center in 2007, you can also watch the jockey trainees taming horses or galloping recently.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Snow scene of Wondang Ranch - Goyang-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/333/1be5607e-bd79-4821-8e41-193f61660963.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Snow scene of Wondang Ranch
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   On the way to the observatory, there are plenty of pictures of horses of various breeds. From pony, about 1m tall, such as Repizza and Parabella, to stunning racehorses, you can take a look at the friendly explanations with photos.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;13&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Horses that enjoy the weight - Goyang-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/333/027b30b0-fa12-42a9-9d31-86ac4ebacd2a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Horses that enjoy the weight
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Enjoy the herb farm after horse watching
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Below the observation deck is a world of horses. Horses grazing here escape the narrow massa and enjoy the winter sun. When people approach and stroke their noses, they lick their hands as friendly as pet dogs. Sometimes you bite or kick, so don&#39;t slow down.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Even if the horses seem to just run, there is a certain sequence in between. &#34;When a new horse enters the fence, the activity gets faster because of the quarrel. If you feed it, you will know. The first one to eat is the boss.&#34; As the steward explains, an unfamiliar horse arrives at a leisurely ranch, and the movement of eastern westerners becomes agile. It is like a racing horse.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    The taboo is that the horses are cute and you shouldn&#39;t throw sweets. Even if you touch your head instead of eating, the horses approach your friend with a pretty comfortable look.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;You can enjoy walking in the middle of the ranch - Goyang-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/333/74519b7f-75e5-4210-8d0b-995c78f115b4.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     You can enjoy walking in the middle of the ranch
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The body shriveled by walking on a winter ranch can be warmly melted in the herb farm on the way back. Herb Land is located at the entrance of Eunsashi Tree Road where the village bus stands. When entering the plantation, warm herbal teas and herbal compresses greet guests. Various herbs are growing from familiar herbs such as lavender, rosemary, and mint to healthy things such as lemon balm and thyme. Even if you visit each person, you can experience planting herbs and making herb plants for 5,000 won per person. You can also soothe the cold with herbal tea or buy herbal cosmetics and scented candles in a candle cafe filled with aromas. Herbland has a unique herbal hospital, but if the herbs it has grown at home get sick, treat them and return them.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Horse mascot of ranch walkway - Goyang-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/333/ba74f09b-7172-44dc-810a-8329cde23fe2.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Horse mascot of ranch walkway
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you want to immerse yourself in an exotic Latin culture, visit the Latin American Cultural Center nearby. Head towards Gupabal and turn towards Munsan and run for about 15 minutes. There are more than 3,000 artifacts from the Aztec, Inca, and Mayan civilizations on display. In addition to wood, stoneware, and earthenware, there are many novelties from Latin America. In addition, more than 200 masks with unique facial expressions and shapes make eye-catching outings more interesting.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   The trip to the Wondang Ranch is good because you can feel the winter mood evenly. It is also a great attraction to stroll through the ranch, royal tombs, and herb farms to enjoy a charming experience and scenery.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Wondang Herb Land Indoor Plantation - Goyang-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/333/0aff37aa-1bd3-499b-97d3-ae646304b15a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Wondang Herb Land Indoor Plantation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1.Access
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    * Self-driving
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Outer Ring Road Tongil-ro IC → Samsong direction → Nonghyup University, Seosamneung → Turn right at Hubland Samgeori
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    * public transport
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    From Samsong Station on Subway Line 3, village buses run every 20 to 30 minutes. After passing through Nonghyup University, get off at Herb Land.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    ※ Ranch opening time is from 9 am to 4:30 pm and admission is free. Closed on Mondays and Tuesdays. Parking facilities are insufficient, so it is better to use public transportation on weekends.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Restaurants around
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Daejagol Local Food: Deokyang-gu Daeja-dong / Chueo-tang / 031-962-8545
    &lt;br/&gt;
    So Bae-chan: Daehwa-dong, Seosan-gu, Ilsan / Hanwoo / 031-932-5533
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Canaan Duck Gumteo: Ilsandong-gu Pungdong / Duck roast / 031-901-3292
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     3.Accommodation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Avatar Hotel: Tanhyeon-dong, Seosan-gu, Ilsan / 031-919-6761
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.아바타호텔.kr&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     www.아바타호텔.kr
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Hotel Cleopatra: Baekseok-dong, Ilsan-dong / 031-908-0136
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Luxury Hotel: Daehwa-dong, Seosan-gu, Ilsan / 031-917-1717
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was created in February 2013, and may change later, so be sure to check it before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>