<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Uljin-gun on Every Corner of Korea</title>
    <link>https://codecorea.github.io/tags/uljin-gun/</link>
    <description>Every Corner of Korea (Uljin-gun)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 14:55:07 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="https://codecorea.github.io/tags/uljin-gun/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Heat reflection, 3 trekking in the backcountry valley, Wangpicheon in Uljin. - Uljin-gun, Gyeongbuk, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/heat-reflection-3-trekking-in-the-backcountry-valley-wangpicheon-in-uljin-148/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 14:55:07 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/heat-reflection-3-trekking-in-the-backcountry-valley-wangpicheon-in-uljin-148/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Uljin-gun, Gyeongbuk, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;heat-reflection-3-trekking-in-the-backcountry-valley-wangpicheon-in-uljin--148&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Gangwon Inje Morning Valley - Uljin-gun, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/148/7c12fbab-3ee8-49c3-9088-d515a6f2536c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Gangwon Inje Morning Valley
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Heat reflection, 3 trekking in the backcountry valley, Wangpicheon in Uljin.
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Uljin-gun, Gyeongbuk, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The weather is getting hot. Some Bangkok people say that it is enough to have watermelon in the air-conditioning wind, but there are those who want to leave the summer resort in nature. In this case, trekking in the valley along the cool stream is the best. Walk and paint water
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   #One. Uljin Wangpicheon, full of wild charm
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Wangpicheon is a 61km-long waterway that flows from Wangpi-ri and Gusan-ri to Uljin, originating from the nutritional defense of Gyeongbuk. Surrounded by mountains and cliffs, it was not easy to reach, so people were less likely to walk, and thanks to it, it was considered a clean area to recognize. The name &#39;Wangpiri&#39;, meaning &#39;town where the king has fled&#39;, also indicates that this area was remote. It is in the same context that Wangpicheon area was designated as an ecological and landscape conservation area in 2005. It is the largest in Korea. In 2013, four ecological trails were opened in the vicinity of Wangpicheon and designated as eco-tourism areas, where local residents operate the Wangpicheon Eco Tour Group.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Wolmi, Yongso of Uljin Wangpicheon, one of the best places in the world &amp;lt;Photo courtesy, Uljin County Office&amp;gt; - Uljin-gun, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/148/baac6183-8e18-4ccc-944c-646e8d418214.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Wolmi, Yongso of Uljin Wangpicheon, one of the best places in the world &amp;lt;Photo courtesy, Uljin County Office&amp;gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The starting point of this Wangpicheon trekking course was taken to Gulguji Village. Gulguji Village, which is considered to be an outback in Uljin, is a name that says that only nine bends should go around the mountain. The trekking route between Wangpicheon Soksa Village, upstream of Wangpicheon and Gulguji Village, downstream of Gusan-ri, is the most successful. Either way, you can start, but if you are a beginner or a child with little trekking experience, it is recommended that you start at Goolji Village and return to the camp. The valley is gentle and you can trek gently.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Uljin Wangpicheon Ecological Trail Information Center - Uljin-gun, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/148/512b95fe-46d6-49e9-a87e-ee9966d03686.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Uljin Wangpicheon Ecological Trail Information Center
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Wonderful scenery follows the quiet stream. Nevertheless, I am not careful that the water is shallow. Mossy stones are slippery. In addition, the Gulguji Village ~ Sangcheondong ~ Yongso ~ Turtle Rock Observation Course belongs to the 2nd course of the Wangpicheon Ecological Trail, so you can walk on the forest path, not the water path. If you are walking in the valley and become crowded, you can also climb the forest path. Still, trekking in the valley is recommended to properly see the skin of Wang Picheon. Walk about 4km from Gulguji Village and you will reach the best view of the Wangpicheon. The area where the dragon seems to be floundering must be violated due to the steep and rough cliffs. If individual valley trekking is a burden, you can use ecological exploration at the Wangpicheon Eco Tour Group.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Eco-tour inquiry, Uljin Wangpicheon Valley Eco Tour Project
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.wangpiecotour.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;[새창열림]‘울진왕피천계곡 에코투어사업단’ 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
     http://www.wangpiecotour.com/
    &lt;/a&gt;
    .
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Uljin Specialty Geumgangsong - Uljin-gun, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/148/4baba732-3f6c-4350-baf6-749db0b98678.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Uljin Specialty Geumgangsong
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   #2. Jade Valley, a hot-water fish, inje morning
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Before walking in the morning, let&#39;s look at the Prophet Jeonggamrok of the Joseon Dynasty. In &amp;lt;Junggamrok&amp;gt;, there are three disaster-free locations that do not have three disasters: water, fire, and wind.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;When you enter the morning valley from the vibrating valley, the wild forest road begins. - Uljin-gun, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/148/a5d0c91e-30d3-46b5-8a64-b12db6cee854.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     When you enter the morning valley from the vibrating valley, the wild forest road begins.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Inje morning valley where lush native forest and clean valley are combined. It means &#39;in the midst of a spooky mountain, where it is only about a year to plow the field in the morning&#39;. It is a valley that still has the feeling of outback, as its name suggests. Morning Garrigol originated from Guryong Deokbong, flows about 20km and meets Bangtaecheon of Dongdongri, especially the 5km downstream section. In addition, the slope is gentle, so it is easy to go up the valley. The water path is easier to walk than the forest path, which is hard to see.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Water play in the vibrating valley - Uljin-gun, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/148/493d1275-eea4-4228-9c9d-364846832b0c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Water play in the vibrating valley
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Trekking in the morning is going to start at the opposite side of the vibratory valley, Sanchon Cultural Recreation Center (or Vibratory Mountain House). As soon as you cross the vibrating valley, the forest path in the thick forest begins. As soon as you pass through the lush forest, you can go morning and reach the downstream. The origin return course that goes back and forth from the morning Gargol-Jogyeongdong bridge to Bangdong Yaksu is the most successful. If you want to see upstream in the morning, you need about 10 hours. If the distance is a burden, it is also a good idea to enjoy the water in the vibrating valley after watching the morning goal.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Valley trekking, aqua shoes or sandals - Uljin-gun, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/148/9221ad93-14f5-4692-a3b8-35ce98c1f278.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Valley trekking, aqua shoes or sandals
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   # 3. Deep mountain valley road, Jeongseon Deoksangi Valley
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Deoksangi Valley, one of Jeongseon&#39;s remote areas. It was a secret valley known only to people who knew it until it was introduced to TV programs. It was revealed to the world when it was chosen as a place for outdoor weddings by famous celebrities, but the still waters still remain.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   With a total length of 12km, there are Dosagok, Deoksangi, and Hebei-dong villages in the valley of Deoksangi, which is surrounded by Songdae. Dozens of households lived on the ground and left for flooding in 1979. Guest houses and pensions are located along the valley. In general, we find many courses from Deokuri to Budong-ri.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Deoksangi Valley, Jeongseon, one of the remote areas - Uljin-gun, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/148/a31e8b2d-c7d9-478a-b8ab-e67485eaad0d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Deoksangi Valley, Jeongseon, one of the remote areas
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Those staying in a pension or guest house in the Deoksangi Valley should park and walk in the Deoksan Bridge. The cement road continues for the villagers living in the valley of Deoksangi. A proud stand rising by the gentle stream greets you. To enjoy Deoksangi Valley trekking properly, it is better to go after rain.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Jeongseon Deoksangi Valley Trekking - Uljin-gun, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/148/83b02117-3f93-4060-a947-93d9f346375c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Jeongseon Deoksangi Valley Trekking
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   tip. Safety checks for exciting valley trekking
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Similar to regular trekking, but needs more &#39;valley&#39; preparation. There are some gentle paths, but there are also valleys that reach the knees, so it is better to prepare extra shoes, and sticks make it easier. Moss is quite slippery, so walking barefoot
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel info
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Restaurants near
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Mangyangjeong Sashimi Restaurant: 716-6 Sanpo 4-ri, Geunnam-myeon, Uljin-gun, Gyeongbuk / Sashimi / 054-783-0430
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Jindongsanchaega: 1073, Jochimyeong-ro, Girin-myeon, Inje-gun, Gangwon / Korean Food / 033-463-8484
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Dongbakgol: 1314 Jeongseon-ro, Jeongseon-eup, Jeongseon-gun, Gangwon-do / Gondrenamul Rice / 033-563-2211
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Sarigol: 231-2 Bongyang-ri, Jeongseon-eup, Jeongseon-gun, Gangwon-do / Gondrenamulbab / 033-562-4554
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.ssarigol.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.ssarigol.com/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Rooms
     &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    -Tonggosan Natural Recreation Forest, Uljin: 880, Buyeonggyeok-ro, Seomyeon, Uljin-gun, Gyeongbuk
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Gulguji Mountain Village Pension in Uljin: 634 Wangpicheon-ro, Geunnam-myeon, Uljin-gun, Gyeongbuk / 054-782-3737
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://gulgugi.co.kr/default/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://gulgugi.co.kr/default/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Inje Bangtaesan Natural Recreation Forest: 377 Bangtaesan-gil, Girin-myeon, Inje-gun, Gangwon / 033-463-8590
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Bangtae Emperor Bed and Breakfast: 24, Dundeok-dong-gil, Girin-myeon, Inje-gun, Gangwon-do / 033-463-3309
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Water clear homestay: 110 Deoksangi-gil, Jeongseon-eup, Jeongseon-gun, Gangwon-do / 033-562-0744
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was updated in June 2019, and may be changed later, so please check before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ The information such as text, photos and videos used in this article is copyrighted by Korea Tourism Organization, so unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>