<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Samcheok-si on Every Corner of Korea</title>
    <link>https://codecorea.github.io/tags/samcheok-si/</link>
    <description>Every Corner of Korea (Samcheok-si)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2020 10:34:25 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="https://codecorea.github.io/tags/samcheok-si/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Samcheok Gomchiguk, a winter delicacy that makes the nation&#39;s favorite - Samcheok-si, Gangwon-do, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/samcheok-gomchiguk-a-winter-delicacy-that-makes-the-nations-favorite-308/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2020 10:34:25 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/samcheok-gomchiguk-a-winter-delicacy-that-makes-the-nations-favorite-308/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Samcheok-si, Gangwon-do, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;samcheok-gomchiguk-a-winter-delicacy-that-makes-the-nations-favorite--308&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Samcheok Gomchi soup with old paper and boiled - Samcheok-si, Gangwon-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/308/beecfc57-1ba3-4b99-92da-940a1ef2b472.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Samcheok Gomchi soup with old paper and boiled
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Samcheok Gomchiguk, a winter delicacy that makes the nation&#39;s favorite
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Samcheok-si, Gangwon-do, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Sea fish called Gomchi in the East Sea, water catfish in the South Sea, and water fish in the West! The season of Gomchi caught across the coast of the Korean Peninsula has arrived. Another reason why lovers and gourmets from all over the country are waiting for the winter, heading to Samcheok, his hometown, to taste Gomchi soup, a taste of winter season.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The winter east coast is rich. This is thanks to a variety of foods that will satisfy our taste, unlike the look that looks lonely. For the same reason, gourmets and lovers from all over the country run to the east coast in winter. Start with Yangmi-ri and Guamegi in the northern part of Gangwon, and head down the east coast. Samcheok&#39;s gomchi soup with a sweet drink, gourmets&#39; taste, and the long legs snow crab of Uljin and Yeongdeok, and Gwamegi of Pohang, are all lined up with ‘delicious things’.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Among them, if Yangmi-ri and Guamegi, and snow crab and Guamegi are &#39;Anju Yong&#39;, &#39;Gomchiguk&#39; is &#39;Haejangyong&#39; to solve all of them in one shot. Of course, it&#39;s a great &#39;flavor&#39; for a single meal without dividing it into anjuyong and haejangyong, but if you visit the scene to taste them, so if you come across the winter sea breeze and face these foods, the idea of &#39;hanzan&#39; You will hear by itself. Why the winter sea is so bright (remembering alcohol)!
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Winter coastal hidden gourmet gomchi soup
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    I want to go to taste all the food on the east coast because I feel like it. If you have a drink in Yangmi-ri and snow crab and dissolve with Gomchi-guk, then go to Pohang and finish with Gwamegi and Water, what&#39;s the better winter coastal taste of East Coast? However, the main character of this tour is Gomchiguk, which is relatively less known than other winter coastal delicacies.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Fish fills the East Coast of winter - Samcheok-si, Gangwon-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/308/fcb65b22-ef83-49ec-85ae-cfd084d9ea23.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Fish fills the East Coast of winter
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Gomchi soup, as its name suggests, is a fish called Gomchi. The name of this guy caught across the coast of Korea is slightly different from coast to coast. It is called Gomchi or Water Bear in the East Sea, Water Mage or Water Catfish in the South Sea, and Jambang or Water Tumbang in the West Sea. It can be interpreted that it is as common and popular that the word for the same fish varies from coast to coast. The most familiar name for us right now is water catfish and water squirrel, among which ‘water squirrel’ is the name that fishermen who caught gomchi threw ‘tumbles’ back into the water after seeing the appearance. The appearance of Gomchi, which can never be observed, can be seen in his nickname.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Fish fills the East Coast of winter - Samcheok-si, Gangwon-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/308/5873b06e-2946-4d92-88b5-cd65cccf6dab.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Fish fills the East Coast of winter
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    However, in the Encyclopedia of Fish in the Joseon Dynasty &amp;lt;Jangsaebo&amp;gt;, Jeong Yak-jeon wrote Gomchi and said, &#34;The taste is mild and good for the sake bottle.&#34; It wasn&#39;t that the name of Multumbung was a joke from the bosses who caricatured his ugly appearance. Or maybe it was a trick by lovers who noticed the true value of Gomchi. A name that was called ‘water bear’ or ‘gomchi’ because of its dark appearance is like a bear is also a good hint of his appearance. Some of the divers are bitter because of their ferocious nature, they are far from the appearance and personality that can be loved.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Samcheok Port&#39;s Information Board &#39;Today. Gomchi soup sea urchin - Samcheok-si, Gangwon-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/308/10abb2d6-d0bd-46a7-ad18-b9f41abcb2b7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Samcheok Port&#39;s Information Board &#39;Today. Gomchi soup sea urchin
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Nevertheless, the only thing that Gomchi is loved is because of the &#39;flavor&#39;. Unlike the outrageous personality and ugly appearance, the soft flesh that melts at the tip of the tongue and the cool soup taste! The lyrics to the song “I want to see once and see twice and keep looking” are transferred to “I want to eat once and eat twice and keep eating”.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Scenery of Samcheok Port, known as the hometown of Gomchi - Samcheok-si, Gangwon-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/308/98e656ce-e5df-41b7-9804-f58dd11b4481.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Scenery of Samcheok Port, known as the hometown of Gomchi
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The texture of this fish coexists with soft flesh and slippery skin texture. The viscous part between the skin and the flesh may be unfamiliar to the newcomers, but if you are a lover, you will get used to it after you taste it twice. Those who like &#39;Agujjim (Aguijjim is the real name)&#39; come up with a similar texture. At first, the slippery viscous part is awkward because it is “like a runny nose,” but sometimes they argue that they will eat each other. In the case of Samcheok Gomchi soup, which is boiled with old paper, it is easy to pass by mouth. Ah, there are differences in how to cook Gomchi soup and how it comes out.
   &lt;br/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Scenery of Samcheok Port, known as the hometown of Gomchi - Samcheok-si, Gangwon-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/308/c6f5d68a-cecc-4f4d-8b1a-7a2f91c14903.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Scenery of Samcheok Port, known as the hometown of Gomchi
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Even though the names of the East, South and West Seas are different, the cool soup tastes great!
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Samcheok, known as the hometown of Gomchiguk, puts old paper and boils it sharply. Served in a large soup bowl one by one. In the South Sea and West Sea area, famous for ‘Mulgigitang’, it is seasoned with radish and green onion, and boiled clearly. It is usually sold in large, medium, and small. There are also places where gomchi soup is boiled in the east sea.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&amp;lt;Sea Sashimi House&amp;gt;, known as the original home - Samcheok-si, Gangwon-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/308/aad1d52e-511c-49be-9b33-305a5f832994.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     &amp;lt;Sea Sashimi House&amp;gt;, known as the original home
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   When you go to Samcheok Port, the hometown of Gomchiguk, you will see a notice board saying &#39;Become Gomchiguk&#39;. Does that mean that you have become your own body? The price of 15,000 won for a bowl (per serving) is not just as cheap. At one time, Gomchi was so common that in winter, it was a winter delicacy that residents of this town had eaten at every house. Gomchi soup, where should I taste it?
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Gomchi with soft skin - Samcheok-si, Gangwon-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/308/1457448b-1165-41bf-b09f-9b839c22d6ab.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Gomchi with soft skin
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    In Samcheok, Gomchi&#39;s hometown, there are restaurants where you can taste Gomchi soup, such as &amp;lt;Sea Sashimi&amp;gt;, which started selling Gomchi soup for the first time, and &amp;lt;Geumseong Restaurant&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;Donga Restaurant&amp;gt;. Each restaurant has a little difference in taste, so comparing the subtle taste difference adds to the fun of the taste of “Gomchiguk”.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;There are also places in pots that can be boiled - Samcheok-si, Gangwon-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/308/8e945a7a-c9d6-4b0b-bb50-a9eaca82b01d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     There are also places in pots that can be boiled
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you&#39;ve tasted a bowl of Gomchi soup that was boiled and boiled with old paper, let&#39;s take a look around Samcheok Port (Jungna Port), which still embraces the scenery of the fishing village. As you walk along the breakwater in front of Samcheok Isabu Square, you can see Samcheok&#39;s blue sea in the future, and along the hillside, you can see the charming houses.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Samcheok Isabu Square, located at the base of Samcheok Port - Samcheok-si, Gangwon-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/308/c5dcb1cd-3054-4692-8443-c173bbed43bf.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Samcheok Isabu Square, located at the base of Samcheok Port
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Home-style gomchi soup, which would have been boiled in every house in front of you, will become famous. Now, as many restaurants as homes are located along Samcheok Port (Jungra Port). The experience of unwinding in a sip of cool broth is the share of lovers who ran thick the day before. When you eat, you will feel relieved at the same time as you drink again, and you will be a true sweetheart and a sip of gomchi soup. This season, where you can enjoy the taste of Gomchi soup, is important. Gomchi, which melts well and can only be tasted locally, is in the winter season from December to February.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;It is good to take a bowl with Gomchi soup - Samcheok-si, Gangwon-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/308/8e98662a-079c-4ed2-80e3-6d027a735f59.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     It is good to take a bowl with Gomchi soup
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Nearby restaurants
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Sea sashimi: Gomchiguk / 88, Sacheonnyeon-ro, Jeongha-dong, Samcheok-si, Gangwon-do / 033-574-3543
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Ocean Village: Gomchiguk / 14 Galcheon-dong, Samcheok-si, Gangwon / 033-572-5559
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Dong-A Restaurant: Gomchi-guk / 125-1 Jeongha-dong, Samcheok-si, Gangwon / 033-574-5870
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Rooms
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Moon Motel: 174-49, Jungang-ro, Samcheok-si, Gangwon-do / 033-572-4436
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Pacific Motel: 39, Samcheok City Theme Town Road, Gangwon-do / 033-576-0162
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Rose Valley Pension: 525-9, Jangwonan-gil, Wondeok-eup, Samcheok-si, Gangwon / 033-573-3539
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.rosevalley.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.rosevalley.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    ※ The above information was updated in February 2017, and may change later, so be sure to check it before you travel.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>