<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ulsan on Every Corner of Korea</title>
    <link>https://codecorea.github.io/tags/ulsan/</link>
    <description>Every Corner of Korea (Ulsan)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 00:56:10 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="https://codecorea.github.io/tags/ulsan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The song of the sea will take us, trekking to Daewangam Park - Dong-gu, Ulsan, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/the-song-of-the-sea-will-take-us-trekking-to-daewangam-park-331/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 00:56:10 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/the-song-of-the-sea-will-take-us-trekking-to-daewangam-park-331/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Dong-gu, Ulsan, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;the-song-of-the-sea-will-take-us-trekking-to-daewangam-park--331&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Reddish Daewangam - Dong-gu, Ulsan, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/331/c225b515-2e21-4212-9708-6026a7b00733.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Reddish Daewangam
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   The song of the sea will take us, trekking to Daewangam Park
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Dong-gu, Ulsan, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you want to feel the lyricism of Ulsan, which you have never imagined, go to Daewangam Park. You will meet the new Ulsan as you walk along the fresh coastal path from Daewangam Park to Seoldo Jindo.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Along the trunk of the east coast, Ulsan reaches Pohang on the top and Busan on the bottom. Is it because there are many tourist cities that are up and down? Many people remember Ulsan, which is located between the two, as an “industrial city”. It is a distance from the &#39;tourist city&#39;. I think it&#39;s a similar expression to a blind dated entrant who says, “Your personality (only) looks good”. How to be patient to find ‘volumes’ that you must see and see and see the charm. The more blunt and uninteresting the opponent is, the more exciting it is to be a true country.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    So I prepared. A space where you can fully enjoy the nature of Ulsan, which has been stuck in the image of an industrial city for a long time. Introducing Daewangam Park, a glimpse of the unexpected charm of Ulsan. It is a space that Ulsan citizens regard as the best date course. We will walk along the coastal promenade around Daewangam Park to Deoljinjin Island.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   The story of the lighthouse at the end of Ulsan
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Daewangam Park was designated as the first park in Ulsan in 1962. It is called “Ulgi Lighthouse Park” after the name of Ulgi Lighthouse, which is located near Daewangam. It was renamed in 1984 because of “Japan&#39;s Remnants”. During the Russo-Japanese War of 1905, Japan, which made a wooden lantern to light the sea off the coast of Ulsan, built a 6-meter light tower the following year and gave it the name “Ulgi Lighthouse”. It means the lighthouse at the end of Ulsan. At this time, Japan also planted pine trees in order not to reveal the military base around the lighthouse to the outside.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Over time, when the pine trees grew taller than the lighthouse and became unable to serve as a lighthouse even with a 3m extension, a candlestick-shaped new light tower was erected in 1987. This is why the new and old towers of Ulgi Lighthouse are in good standing. The Uldung Lighthouse Gudeung Pagoda, which shows the architectural style 100 years ago, was recognized as a cultural asset and registered as a registered cultural asset No. 106.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Daewangam from different angles - Dong-gu, Ulsan, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/331/20eda851-8923-47c8-a557-01d89c0d2e18.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Daewangam from different angles
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Dong-gu, Ulsan, where Daewangam Park belongs, has three sides in the sea. The shape that protrudes south toward the sea seems to be perfect for coastal trekking. In 2012, Dong-gu, Ulsan Metropolitan City completed the &#39;Daewangam Solbaram-gil&#39; by constructing coastal roads from Mipo Coast to Daewangam Park and Seuldo to the former pier. Today&#39;s walk is part of Daewangam Solbaram-gil. Before going on a full-fledged trek, let&#39;s look at ‘Daewangam Solbaramgil’ first.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Mailbox of hope and love - Dong-gu, Ulsan, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/331/d09b3509-8939-4ad7-910e-d81d2a774fee.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Mailbox of hope and love
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The Daewangam Solbaram-gil leads to three sections: ① Mipo Coast ~ Ilsan Beach ② Daewangam Park ③ Island End Village ~ the former pier. It is still called by various names such as &#39;Daewangam Solbaram-gil&#39;, &#39;Daewangam Dulle-gil&#39; and &#39;Daewangam Park Trail&#39;. “In 2012, through the storytelling project, the coastal road in the vicinity of the Daewangam Solbaramgil was tentatively decided,” said Yoo Seongdeok, director of Dong-gu Office in Ulsan Metropolitan City. I said.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Ulgi Lighthouse Sin-gu Light Tower - Dong-gu, Ulsan, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/331/146cee76-c289-4cc7-8fd7-13c2683eadfa.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Ulgi Lighthouse Sin-gu Light Tower
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Whispers of mysterious strange rocks, Solwangramgil in Daewangam Park
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The section that we are introducing this time is from Daewangam Park to Seongdo Jindo. According to the Solbaram-gil section, ② Daewangam Park and ③ Island End Village ~ the former part of the pier belong. There is room for confusion, and this article tries to call it &#39;Suldo ~ Daewangam Park Trekking&#39; instead of &#39;Daewangam Solbaramgil&#39;.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   When you enter the entrance to Daewangam Park, take a brochure. When you enter the park from the entrance to the left, the coastal walkway spreads along the slim Gomsol. Outer Makgi ~ Anmakgi ~ Yonggul ~ Ulgi Lighthouse ~ Daewangam ~ Gwagaean ~ Godong Island Observatory ~ Noaegaean (Middle Point) ~ Suldo, in the middle of Daewangam Park, will take a big turn along the coast. Along the coast, there are attractions with various names. Instead of getting stressed out looking for it, I recommend you to enjoy the beautiful sea of Ulsan.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Daewangam Park Entrance - Dong-gu, Ulsan, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/331/27b16275-ae6c-4b4f-87c4-9682ee9b2f24.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Daewangam Park Entrance
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The ‘Yonggul’ bears the tale that a spoiled blue dragon is trapped, a pair of affectionate pine trees, and passes through Ulgi Lighthouse to reach Daewangam. When I see the huge ocher rocks that are located across the sea, I am reminded of the king of the moon, Silla, who fell asleep in the sea saying that he would be a god after he died and protect the country. Some people explain that Daewangam is also a place where Queen Munmu was asleep to defend the country by accepting the will of the king, but such a legend is beautiful enough to set aside. Until the Great Bridge was established, Daewangam went back and forth by boat. You can see the sunrise rising behind the great rock from the sunrise observatory located at the basement.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Seasong continues along the left coast - Dong-gu, Ulsan, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/331/390293e9-5fee-4be4-b9de-a088815a7c0c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Seasong continues along the left coast
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The farther away from Daewangam Park, the more shy the waters of Ulsan&#39;s sea become. I reach the overpass (Neven dogs) that the stones follow the path that I can walk forever. As the name of the wide coast, the soft coastline is warmly embraced. It was a coast that drove and captured whales until the 1960s. “There is a record that our ancestors, who were obliged to serve, returned the sea to the sea when a whale was pushed back,” said Park Ae-kyung, a cultural tourism commentator. I got a lot, ”he added.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Overdose, which means &#39;wide eye&#39; - Dong-gu, Ulsan, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/331/a7f9c303-35d6-491c-95f0-93fa044f799d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Overdose, which means &#39;wide eye&#39;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The road from Gugae-an to Suldo faces Godong Island. The transformation from ‘Suribau’ to ‘Sorabawi’ was converted to kanji and became ‘Godong Island’. There are two black rocks that do not resemble the beating. Let&#39;s remember that the moonlit night view is beautiful.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Coastal road scenery connecting Daewangam Park and the end of the island - Dong-gu, Ulsan, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/331/8d2d46cb-9569-40b4-b489-6c3b9d209946.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Coastal road scenery connecting Daewangam Park and the end of the island
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    How long did you walk? It hits the middle point. It stands in the middle of the boundary between Ilsan-dong and Defensive-dong. It is also called old-fashioned eye care. As you walk through this section, you often encounter a puddle. “This was a farm that raised Gunma in the Joseon Dynasty. Can you see the puddle here? It&#39;s the negative water that was feeding the horse. Even now, every house is used as agricultural water. ”
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A friendly brother-like island of Godong - Dong-gu, Ulsan, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/331/b9b426fb-6215-404b-b69a-78b68fb8fe58.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A friendly brother-like island of Godong
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Singing Rock Island, Seuldo
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;span&gt;
     It would not have been possible to feed the horse salty water. As I walked along this road, I used to think that it resembled Jeju Island, but I also raised my words. I see the good scenery and imagine the horse that I could have run to my heart&#39;s content, and reach the island village. The island end village, located between the island (Suldo) and 뭍, is also called the “Sung End Village”. In fact, there are traces of the &#39;castle&#39; that piles up stones along the coast of the village. It is also a village of haenyeo. There are a lot of sea divers from Jeju because it has a lot of seaweed and seafood because it touches the hole rock. You can still see the female divers who are material. As it became known as the location of the 2012 MBC drama &amp;lt;May Queen&amp;gt;, more and more people are looking for it. Alley murals decorated with colors greet tourists.
    &lt;/span&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;span&gt;
     If you cross the Seoldogyo Bridge at the end of the island, you reach Seoldo Island in Gombo Island. It became a gombo island by being surrounded by holey rocks left by stone clams. In addition, through this hole, the sound of sea water is expressively expressed, and Gombo Island became &#39;Suldo (瑟 島)&#39;. Although it is still uninhabited, it is not lonely anymore because the people who seek it under the influence of the drama continue to walk. The whale sculpture next to Seolgyo Bridge tells us that this is Ulsan, the home of whales. Still, the point is the lighthouse. The wooden chair under the lighthouse overlooks the sea. As I sat on a chair facing the sea, the Ulsan sea poured in coolly. What is the lighthouse waiting for, looking at the sea where whales might have someday played?
    &lt;/span&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox type3 clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Seuldo Lighthouse became famous as a location for drama - Dong-gu, Ulsan, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/331/a404ba6f-e38f-4122-9238-192f6d217853.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Seuldo Lighthouse became famous as a location for drama
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The appearance of the female divers - Dong-gu, Ulsan, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/331/245d6d6e-14e1-4a08-bd31-eb6fd1a8d3e7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The appearance of the female divers
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Seoldogyo Bridge connecting Island End Village and Uninhabited Island - Dong-gu, Ulsan, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/331/a3d581ad-e8bf-44c5-86e8-4f2e0554d425.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Seoldogyo Bridge connecting Island End Village and Uninhabited Island
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   tip. Daewangam Park
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Open year-round. The entrance time is not set, so you can always watch the sunrise at Daewangam. Ulgi Lighthouse, located in Daewangam Park, hosts a lighthouse experience program that combines lodging during elementary school vacations every year. In July and early December, go to the Ulsan Regional Maritime Affairs and Port website to apply. Up to 12 people can enter. Only families with elementary and junior high school students can apply. If more than 20 people visit Ulsan, contact the Ulsan Metropolitan City Office (052-229-3852, guide.ulsan.go.kr) to accompany the cultural tourism commentator.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Daewangam Park Inquiries: Dong-gu Office Culture and Sports Section 052-209-3470, Dong-gu Office Park Greenery Section 052-209-3754
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Ulgi Lighthouse Accommodation Inquiries: Ulgi Lighthouse 052-251-2125, Maritime Safety Facility Division 052-228-5610
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    1.Access
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    * Self-driving
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Gyeongbu Expressway Eonyang Junction → Ulsan Expressway → Sinbok Rotary → Nambu Ring Road → Turn right toward Ulsan MBC in front of Dongdeok Apartment → Turn left at Gyebyeon-ro → Gapsam 3-way direction toward Deokjinjin → Myeongchon Bridge → Goheon-ro → Turn right at Daewangam Park at Lighthouse Intersection → Daewangam Park
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    2. Delicious
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Eonyang Traditional Bulgogi: Eonyang-eup, Ulju-gun / Eonyang Bulgogi / 052-262-0940
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Whale Meat Aid Grandma Restaurant: Jangsaengpo Whale-ro, Nam-gu / Whale Meat / 052-261-7313
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Donghae Farm Restaurant: Yeonam-dong, Buk-gu / Boar Bulgogi / 052-288-4545
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Dodongsanbang: Sangbuk-myeon, Ulju-gun / Hanjeongsik / 052-254-7076
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Bean Love: Ilsan-dong, Dong-gu / Soybean Cuisine, Hwang-tae / 052-252-0023
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    3.Accommodation
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Kyungwon BIZ Motel: Noksu 7-gil, Dong-gu / 052-233-2000
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Hi Hotel: Dong-gu Badrae-gil / 052-944-1010
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Bioncheon Motel: Sangbuk-myeon, Ulju-gun / 052-254-1700
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Jakcheonjeong Pension Resort: Sangbuk-myeon, Ulju-gun / 052-264-4900
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Azela Resort Training Center: Sangbuk-myeon, Ulju-gun / 052-257-8040, 052-257-8041
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    ※ The above information was created in April 2013, and may be changed later, so be sure to check it before you travel.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>