<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Boryeong on Korea Tour</title>
    <link>https://codecorea.github.io/tags/boryeong/</link>
    <description>Korea Tour (Boryeong)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 05:47:42 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="https://codecorea.github.io/tags/boryeong/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Борён, Южная Корея - Boryeong Mud Festival ждал малыша!</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/boryeong-mud-festival-waited-for-baby-37-ru/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 05:47:42 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/boryeong-mud-festival-waited-for-baby-37-ru/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-title=&#34;boryeong-mud-festival-waited-for-baby--37&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Boryeong Mud Festival, Почетный национальный фестиваль Кореи - Борён, Южная Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/a00f05e1-b602-4338-a21c-24d6d9155761.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Boryeong Mud Festival, Почетный национальный фестиваль Кореи
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Boryeong Mud Festival ждал малыша!
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Борён, Южная Корея
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Один из первых захватывающих фестивалей летом! Фестиваль грязи Boryeong на пляже Boryeong Daecheon в Chungnam, Южная Корея, будет проходить с 15-го по 24-е. Пойдем на молодой и энергичный фестиваль. Если вам нравится фестиваль, грязевые пакеты, которые естественно падают на ваше тело, являются бонусом.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Boryeong Mud Festival больше не нуждается в объяснениях. Молодые люди, а также семейные единицы с маленькими детьми, и в этом году, даже пожилые люди и пожилые люди, которые пришли, чтобы услышать слухи, расширились. Давайте посмотрим на пляж Daecheon Beach, где проводится фестиваль грязи вокруг популярного Mud Experience Center (платная зона).
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Отправляйся в Тэчхон, где проливается грязь!
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Давайте сначала посмотрим на транспорт. Boryeong Mud Festival не сложно найти на общественном транспорте. Если вы не умеете водить, или если вы любитель, у вас нет машины. Если вы начинающий водитель и хотите поехать на фестиваль по выходным, вы должны оставить свой автомобиль далеко или воспользоваться общественным транспортом.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Цветная грязевая окраска это весело! - Борён, Южная Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/52d1912c-ad11-4218-b360-ff468127e8d6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Цветная грязевая окраска это весело!
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Станция Daecheon и автобусный терминал Boryeong находятся напротив вас, и всего в 10 минутах от пляжа Daecheon проводится фестиваль грязи Boryeong. Это означает, что вы можете достичь фестиваля столько, сколько захотите. Одной ночи и двух дней достаточно, чтобы насладиться праздником грязи. (Это основано на человеке со средней физической подготовкой в возрасте до 30 лет.) Если вы ищете грязевой фестиваль для семейного летнего отдыха, вы можете позволить себе этот жаркий летний отпуск, но вы не можете работать как корова. Мы рекомендуем соленый однодневный двухдневный курс после работы.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Цветная грязевая окраска это весело! - Борён, Южная Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/1bbcd5ba-2297-4929-b770-a4ed9d3c74ec.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Цветная грязевая окраска это весело!
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Daecheon VS. Тихий ирис
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Однажды общежитие попалось в Учан. Во время фестиваля цены на размещение на пляже Течеон стремительно растут. От 2,5 до 3 раз в низкий сезон. Если вам надоело приходить и уходить, и у вас есть много места, чтобы заплатить, вы можете найти место, чтобы остаться перед фестивалем. Но если вы не хотите быть шумным и многолюдным (Чеджу любит всю ночь любить корейских туристов корейским сакэ), Muchangpo находится в 15 минутах езды от пляжа Daecheon. Проживание стабильное и намного тише. Кроме того, пляж Muchangpo прекрасен. Наслаждаться приливом и отливом не так уж и много, и если вы любите, это также хороший курс для свиданий. Если вы хотите прошептать что-нибудь сладкое, каждый рекомендует относительно тихий ритуал, а не страстный, юный Тэчхон.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Детская зона для семей с детьми - Борён, Южная Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/11fa5fc8-dad2-411f-a460-2326131293df.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Детская зона для семей с детьми
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Выпив по стакану моллюсков в Мухангпо, он старательно отправляется в Тэчхон на следующий день. Цветы, грязевые впечатления и специальная сцена фестиваля Boryeong Mud расположены на площади Грязи между площадью Пагоды для граждан и Fountain Plaza. Существуют различные программы, чтобы насладиться грязью по всему телу. Генерал 10 000 вон, молодежь 8 000 вон. Группы от 20 человек и более получат скидку в 1000 вон. Между ними есть разница, поэтому, пожалуйста, задавайте вопросы на сайте. Есть место для детей.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Детская зона для семей с детьми - Борён, Южная Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/988d15a6-c6d5-41d5-b118-659267c84311.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Детская зона для семей с детьми
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Грязевой Опыт как раз к открытию!
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Для того, чтобы немного насладиться комнатой для грязевого опыта, пожалуйста, используйте ее утром во время открытия центра грязевого опыта (10:00). После 11 часов число людей быстро растет, и линия должна начинаться. Если это трудно, вам может быть запрещено входить в сад.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Петушиные бои в грязи Опыт - Борён, Южная Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/0b603715-26ef-428c-9caa-4cede8a5f847.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Петушиные бои в грязи Опыт
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Mud Experience Center, который открыт с 10:00 до 18:00, открыт с 12:30 до 13:30.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Садись в тюрьму и получи массаж всего тела с грязью! - Борён, Южная Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/d27a2db0-1373-4c4f-8cb6-15bd3f542ab4.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Садись в тюрьму и получи массаж всего тела с грязью!
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Если вы вводите грязевой опыт как раз к открытию 9:30, это будет успех. «Подходящие» и «свисающие хвосты» - это весело в большой грязевой ванне! Я ждал больше часа и наслаждался только несколькими минутами, но как только я получил удовольствие от игры, ожидание прошло.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Садись в тюрьму и получи массаж всего тела с грязью! - Борён, Южная Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/e703ac75-786d-4bcf-895a-0a8812aa5902.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Садись в тюрьму и получи массаж всего тела с грязью!
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Однако, если вы двигаетесь немного усердно, вы можете наслаждаться различными грязевыми опытами, такими как Mud Superslide и Mud Prison.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Команда Джин запуталась в группах. - Борён, Южная Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/f36a819e-cc2d-49fe-ba1e-1bacc46d101e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Команда Джин запуталась в группах.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   О, так как Boryeong Mud Festival каждый год проводит фотоконкурс, вам нужен разум, чтобы покрыть лицо «цветной росписью тела». Это потому, что стекаются фотографы со всей страны. Лицо, которое не знает, где его взяли, можно использовать в качестве изображения для продвижения Фестиваля грязи в следующем году. Раскрыть свое тело и прикрыть лицо. Это увлекательный способ насладиться грязевым фестивалем.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Команда Джин запуталась в группах. - Борён, Южная Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/f3258df1-adf2-4cba-abc5-815e5796ed69.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Команда Джин запуталась в группах.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Следующая отделка грязевого пакета - морские купания
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Если все ваше тело полно грязи, и вы в полной мере наслаждались грязевым опытом, давайте побежим в Тэчхон. Пришло время наслаждаться плаванием. Вытирайте грязь ручьями на протяжении всего фестиваля, наслаждайтесь морскими купаниями и идите в душ. Не беспокойтесь, если у вас нет машины или жилья. В фестивале есть шкафчик и платный душ. Карты, мобильные телефоны и камеры перемещаются в водонепроницаемых упаковках. Даже если вы не подготовитесь заранее, вы можете легко получить его в магазине. Просто носите водонепроницаемый пакет. Тем не менее, следует проявлять осторожность с защитой от ультрафиолета. Солнцезащитные очки можно разбить при грязи, поэтому неплохо иметь шапку, подходящую к вашей голове. Грязь также блокирует ультрафиолетовые лучи, превращая ее в камень. Холод в середине лета вымывает вымытую грязью голову из холодного душа.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Если вы получили достаточно удовольствия от грязи, теперь вы можете делать то, что вам нравится. Вы также можете наслаждаться живописью и плаванием. Также есть стенд для приготовления грязевого мыла. Также проводятся игры на приливных квартирах, соревнования по короткому марафону и соревнования по пляжному мини-футболу. Если время подходит, наслаждайтесь чем угодно. Почему бы вам не заполнить его разнообразными фаршированными продуктами по всей территории фестиваля и не бежать, пока не вернетесь к реальности.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Примите ванну на пляже Daecheon, где проходит фестиваль грязи! - Борён, Южная Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/fbab0632-fdf2-407f-ac84-ed8f1c2f4d36.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Примите ванну на пляже Daecheon, где проходит фестиваль грязи!
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Наконец, один совет, чтобы насладиться фестивалем Boryeong Mud Возьми беруши. Потому что наша улитка драгоценна. Еще одна вещь, которую стоит добавить старушке, это носить купальный костюм. Какое пальто на нем носить? Обычное нижнее белье не может остановить грязь. Вам также понадобится водонепроницаемая упаковка, в которой будут храниться ключ от машины, карточка и сотовый телефон, упомянутые ранее.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     * вопрос
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Туристический информационный центр Борён 041-930-3882 / 041-930-3557
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Примите ванну на пляже Daecheon, где проходит фестиваль грязи! - Борён, Южная Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/a57fb2bd-701a-47b4-8337-9b1fe8e125a6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Примите ванну на пляже Daecheon, где проходит фестиваль грязи!
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   чаевые. Меры предосторожности при проведении фестиваля грязи Boryeong 2016
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Самое главное - соблюдать правила безопасности. Разминка обязательна перед тем, как играть в воду или грязь, а также после питья. Снег и нос по грязи опыт. Будьте осторожны, чтобы грязь не попала вам в рот или в уши. Полезно готовить затычки для ушей с водонепроницаемой упаковкой. Также остерегайтесь грязи, скользкой грязи внутри. Вы можете наслаждаться этим фестивалем грязи, если вы держите это так много. Ох, не обязательно нижнее белье, купальник!
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Информация о путешествии
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;topmr&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Близлежащие рестораны
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    Вдоль пляжа Тэчхон, где проходят фестивали, есть много отелей и ресторанов. Рестораны вдоль 4-километрового песчаного пляжа трудно подобрать. Когда вы обнимаете море, вас ждет множество вкусов, от сашими и калгуксу из морепродуктов до кафе и фаст-фуда. Если вы обычный кореец, вы можете насладиться им на пляже Тэчхон. Если вам нравится сашими или попробовать морепродукты по разумной цене, отправляйтесь на рыбный рынок в порту Тэчхон. Вы можете попробовать свежие сашими по относительно низкой цене.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Ресторан Yonggung:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Корейский, Maeuntang / Boryeong-si Beach 4-gil (Daecheon Beach) / 041-931-1444
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Морское рыболовство Тонгён:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Свежие морепродукты, морепродукты / Daecheonhang-ro, Boryeong-si (рынок морепродуктов в порту Тэчхон) / 041-934-8841
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Размещение
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    Daecheon Beach предлагает широкий выбор отелей, от роскошных отелей до отелей общего типа, мотелей и пансионатов. Цены растут во время фестиваля. Если вы бронируете номер заранее или переезжаете в Мучанпо, вы можете остановиться по обычной цене.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Отель Мудрин:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Boryeong-si Sinheuk-Dong / 041-934-1111
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     JFK Daecheon Water Park Hotel:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Boryeong-si Sinheuk-Dong / 041-930-2000
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://club-master.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://club-master.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Отель Datian Guangdao:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Boryeong-si Sinheuk-Dong / 041-932-0339
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Учан Фосе Палас:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Boryeong-si Uncheon-eup / 041-939-5602
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.beachepalace.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.beachepalace.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ Приведенная выше информация была обновлена в июне 2016 года. Впоследствии она может измениться, поэтому, пожалуйста, проверьте это перед поездкой.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Информация, такая как текст, фотографии и видео, используемые в этой статье, защищены авторским правом Корейской туристической организации, поэтому несанкционированное использование статьи запрещено.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boryeong, Corée du Sud - Le festival de boue de Boryeong attendait bébé!</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/boryeong-mud-festival-waited-for-baby-37-fr/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 01:11:20 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/boryeong-mud-festival-waited-for-baby-37-fr/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-title=&#34;boryeong-mud-festival-waited-for-baby--37&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Boryeong Mud Festival, un festival national honoraire de Corée - Boryeong, Corée du Sud (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/a00f05e1-b602-4338-a21c-24d6d9155761.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Boryeong Mud Festival, un festival national honoraire de Corée
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Le festival de boue de Boryeong attendait bébé!
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Boryeong, Corée du Sud
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   L&#39;un des premiers festivals passionnants de l&#39;été! Le festival de boue de Boryeong à la plage de Boryeong Daecheon à Chungnam, en Corée du Sud, se tiendra du 15 au 24. Allons à un festival jeune et énergique. Si vous aimez le festival, des packs de boue qui tombent naturellement sur votre corps sont un bonus.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Le festival de boue de Boryeong n&#39;a plus besoin d&#39;explication. Les jeunes ainsi que les unités familiales avec de jeunes enfants, et cette année, même les personnes âgées et les personnes âgées qui sont venues entendre les rumeurs ont augmenté. Jetons un coup d&#39;œil à la plage de Daecheon où se déroule le festival de la boue autour du célèbre centre d&#39;expérience de la boue (zone payante).
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Allez à Daecheon où la boue se déverse!
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Regardons d&#39;abord le transport. Le festival de boue de Boryeong n&#39;est pas difficile à trouver en transports en commun. Si vous n&#39;êtes pas bon au volant, ou si vous êtes un amoureux, ne possédez pas de voiture. Si vous êtes un conducteur débutant et que vous souhaitez vous rendre au festival le week-end, vous devez garer votre voiture loin ou utiliser les transports en commun.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;La peinture de boue de couleur est amusante! - Boryeong, Corée du Sud (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/52d1912c-ad11-4218-b360-ff468127e8d6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     La peinture de boue de couleur est amusante!
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    La gare de Daecheon et la gare routière de Boryeong sont situées en face de vous, et ce n&#39;est qu&#39;à 10 minutes de la plage de Daecheon où se tient le festival de boue de Boryeong. Cela signifie que vous pouvez atteindre le festival autant que vous le souhaitez. Une nuit et deux jours suffisent pour profiter de la fête de la boue. (Ceci est basé sur une personne ayant une forme physique moyenne du début à la mi-trentaine.) Si vous recherchez un festival de boue pour des vacances d&#39;été en famille, vous pouvez vous permettre ces chaudes vacances d&#39;été, mais vous ne pouvez pas travailler correctement comme un vache. Nous recommandons un cours salé d&#39;une nuit de deux jours après le travail.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;La peinture de boue de couleur est amusante! - Boryeong, Corée du Sud (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/1bbcd5ba-2297-4929-b770-a4ed9d3c74ec.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     La peinture de boue de couleur est amusante!
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Daecheon VS. Iris silencieux
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Une fois l&#39;auberge prise à Wuchang. Pendant le festival, le prix de l&#39;hébergement à Daecheon Beach monte en flèche. 2,5 à 3 fois la basse saison. Si vous avez la peine d&#39;aller et venir et que vous avez beaucoup de place pour payer, vous pouvez trouver un endroit pour rester devant le festival. Mais si vous ne voulez pas être bruyant et bondé (Jeju aime l&#39;amour des touristes coréens pour le saké coréen toute la nuit), Muchangpo est à 15 minutes en voiture de la plage de Daecheon. Le logement est stable et beaucoup plus calme. De plus, la plage de Muchangpo est magnifique. Ce n&#39;est pas trop pour profiter d&#39;une expérience de marée avec des enfants, et si vous êtes amoureux, c&#39;est aussi un bon cours de rendez-vous. Si vous voulez chuchoter quelque chose de sucré, tout le monde recommande un rituel relativement calme plutôt que Daecheon jeune et passionné.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Zone enfants pour les familles avec enfants - Boryeong, Corée du Sud (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/11fa5fc8-dad2-411f-a460-2326131293df.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Zone enfants pour les familles avec enfants
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Après avoir bu un verre de crustacés à Muchangpo, il se rend avec diligence à Daecheon le lendemain. Les fleurs, l&#39;expérience de la boue et la scène spéciale du festival de boue de Boryeong sont situées sur la place de la boue entre la place de la pagode des citoyens et la place de la Fontaine. Il existe différents programmes d&#39;expérience pour profiter de la boue sur tout votre corps. Général 10 000 wons, jeunes 8 000 wons. Les groupes de 20 personnes ou plus bénéficieront d&#39;une remise de 1 000 won. Il y a une différence entre eux, veuillez donc vous renseigner sur le site. Il y a un espace pour les enfants.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Zone enfants pour les familles avec enfants - Boryeong, Corée du Sud (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/988d15a6-c6d5-41d5-b118-659267c84311.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Zone enfants pour les familles avec enfants
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Mud Experience est à temps pour l&#39;ouverture!
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Afin de profiter un peu de la salle d&#39;expérience de la boue, veuillez l&#39;utiliser le matin à l&#39;heure d&#39;ouverture du centre d&#39;expérience de la boue (10h00). Après 11 heures, le nombre de personnes augmente rapidement et la ligne doit commencer. Si c&#39;est difficile, vous pouvez être empêché d&#39;entrer dans le jardin.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Cockfighting à Mud Experience - Boryeong, Corée du Sud (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/0b603715-26ef-428c-9caa-4cede8a5f847.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Cockfighting à Mud Experience
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Le Mud Experience Center, ouvert de 10 h à 18 h, est ouvert de 12 h 30 à 13 h 30.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Entrez en prison et obtenez un massage complet du corps avec de la boue! - Boryeong, Corée du Sud (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/d27a2db0-1373-4c4f-8cb6-15bd3f542ab4.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Entrez en prison et obtenez un massage complet du corps avec de la boue!
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Si vous entrez dans l&#39;expérience de la boue à temps pour l&#39;ouverture de 9h30, c&#39;est un succès. «Assortir» et «suspendre les queues» sont amusants dans un grand bain de boue! J&#39;ai attendu plus d&#39;une heure et n&#39;ai profité que de quelques minutes, mais une fois que j&#39;ai apprécié le jeu, l&#39;attente a disparu.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Entrez en prison et obtenez un massage complet du corps avec de la boue! - Boryeong, Corée du Sud (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/e703ac75-786d-4bcf-895a-0a8812aa5902.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Entrez en prison et obtenez un massage complet du corps avec de la boue!
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Cependant, si vous vous déplacez un peu avec diligence, vous pouvez profiter de diverses expériences de boue telles que Mud Superslide et Mud Prison.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;L&#39;équipe Jin est confuse en groupes. - Boryeong, Corée du Sud (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/f36a819e-cc2d-49fe-ba1e-1bacc46d101e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     L&#39;équipe Jin est confuse en groupes.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Oh, puisque le Boryeong Mud Festival organise chaque année un concours de photos, vous avez besoin d&#39;un sens pour vous couvrir le visage de «peinture corporelle colorée». C&#39;est parce que les photographes de partout dans le pays affluent. Un visage qui ne sait pas où il a été pris pourrait être utilisé comme image pour promouvoir le Festival de la boue l&#39;année prochaine. Exposez votre corps et couvrez votre visage. C&#39;est une façon amusante de profiter du festival de la boue.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;L&#39;équipe Jin est confuse en groupes. - Boryeong, Corée du Sud (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/f3258df1-adf2-4cba-abc5-815e5796ed69.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     L&#39;équipe Jin est confuse en groupes.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   La prochaine finition du pack de boue est le bain de mer
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Si tout votre corps est plein de boue et que vous avez pleinement profité de l&#39;expérience de la boue, courons à Daecheon. Il est temps de profiter de la natation. Essuyez la boue avec les ruisseaux tout au long du festival, profitez des bains de mer et allez sous la douche. Ne vous inquiétez pas si vous n&#39;avez pas de voiture ou d&#39;hébergement. Il y a un casier et une douche payante dans le festival. Les cartes, les téléphones portables et les appareils photo se déplacent dans des emballages étanches. Même si vous ne vous préparez pas à l&#39;avance, vous pouvez facilement l&#39;obtenir au dépanneur. Portez simplement un sac étanche. Cependant, des précautions doivent être prises avec la protection UV. Les lunettes de soleil peuvent être brisées lors de l&#39;expérience de la boue, c&#39;est donc une bonne idée d&#39;avoir une casquette qui s&#39;adapte à votre tête. La boue bloque également les rayons UV, ce qui en fait une pierre. Un froid au milieu de l&#39;été lavera la tête lavée de boue de la douche froide.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Si vous avez assez apprécié l&#39;expérience de la boue, vous pouvez maintenant faire ce que vous aimez. Vous pouvez également profiter de la peinture et de la natation. Il y a aussi un stand pour faire du savon de boue. Des jeux sur les marées, des compétitions de marathon court et des compétitions de futsal sur la plage sont également organisés. Si le moment est venu, profitez de tout. Pourquoi ne pas le remplir avec une variété d&#39;aliments farcis partout sur le terrain du festival et courir jusqu&#39;à ce que vous reveniez à la réalité.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Prenez un bain sur la plage de Daecheon où se déroule le festival de la boue! - Boryeong, Corée du Sud (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/fbab0632-fdf2-407f-ac84-ed8f1c2f4d36.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Prenez un bain sur la plage de Daecheon où se déroule le festival de la boue!
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Enfin, une astuce pour profiter du Boryeong Mud Festival. Obtenez des bouchons d&#39;oreille. Parce que notre cochlée est précieuse. Une dernière chose à ajouter à la vieille dame est de porter un maillot de bain. C&#39;est gratuit de porter quel genre de manteau dessus! Les sous-vêtements réguliers ne peuvent pas arrêter la boue. Vous aurez également besoin d&#39;un sac étanche qui contiendra la clé de voiture, la carte et le téléphone portable mentionnés précédemment.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     * question
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Centre d&#39;information touristique de Boryeong 041-930-3882 / 041-930-3557
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Prenez un bain sur la plage de Daecheon où se déroule le festival de la boue! - Boryeong, Corée du Sud (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/a57fb2bd-701a-47b4-8337-9b1fe8e125a6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Prenez un bain sur la plage de Daecheon où se déroule le festival de la boue!
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   pointe. Précautions pour profiter du festival de la boue de Boryeong 2016
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    La chose la plus fondamentale est de suivre les règles de sécurité. Les échauffements sont indispensables avant de jouer à l&#39;eau ou à la boue et après avoir bu. Neige et nez à l&#39;expérience de la boue. Faites attention de ne pas laisser de boue pénétrer dans votre bouche ou vos oreilles. Il est utile de préparer des bouchons d&#39;oreille avec un emballage étanche. Faites également attention à la boue glissante à l&#39;intérieur. Vous pouvez profiter de ce festival de boue si vous en gardez autant. Oh, pas forcément des sous-vêtements, un maillot de bain!
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Info voyage
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;topmr&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Restaurants à proximité
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    Le long de la plage de Daecheon, où les festivals ont lieu, il y a de nombreux hébergements et restaurants. Les restaurants le long de la plage de sable de 4 km de long sont difficiles à trouver. En embrassant la mer, de nombreuses saveurs vous attendent, du sashimi au kalguksu aux fruits de mer en passant par les cafés et les fast-foods. Si vous êtes un Coréen régulier, vous pouvez en profiter sur la plage de Daecheon. Si vous aimez le sashimi ou essayez les fruits de mer à un prix raisonnable, rendez-vous au marché aux poissons de Daecheon Port. Vous pouvez déguster du sashimi frais à un prix relativement bas.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Restaurant Yonggung:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Coréen, Maeuntang / Boryeong-si Beach 4-gil (Daecheon Beach) / 041-931-1444
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Pêche en mer de Tongyeong:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Fruits de mer frais, fruits de mer / Daecheonhang-ro, Boryeong-si (Daecheon Port Seafood Market) / 041-934-8841
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Hébergement
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    Daecheon Beach a une variété d&#39;hébergements, des hôtels de luxe aux hôtels généraux, motels et pensions. Les prix augmentent pendant le festival. Si vous faites une réservation à l&#39;avance ou déménagez à Muchangpo, vous pouvez rester à un prix régulier.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Hôtel Mudrin:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Boryeong-si Sinheuk-dong / 041-934-1111
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Hôtel JFK Daecheon Water Park:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Boryeong-si Sinheuk-dong / 041-930-2000
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://club-master.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://club-master.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Datian Guangdao Hotel:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Boryeong-si Sinheuk-dong / 041-932-0339
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Palais de Wuchang Phoece:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Boryeong-si Uncheon-eup / 041-939-5602
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.beachepalace.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.beachepalace.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ Les informations ci-dessus ont été mises à jour en juin 2016. Elles peuvent changer par la suite, veuillez donc vérifier avant de voyager.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Les informations telles que le texte, les photos et les vidéos utilisées dans cet article sont protégées par les droits d&#39;auteur de l&#39;Organisation coréenne du tourisme, de sorte que l&#39;utilisation non autorisée de l&#39;article est interdite.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boryeong, Corea del Sur - Boryeong Mud Festival esperaba bebé!</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/boryeong-mud-festival-waited-for-baby-37-es/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 01:08:34 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/boryeong-mud-festival-waited-for-baby-37-es/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-title=&#34;boryeong-mud-festival-waited-for-baby--37&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Boryeong Mud Festival, un festival nacional honorario de Corea - Boryeong, Corea del Sur (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/a00f05e1-b602-4338-a21c-24d6d9155761.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Boryeong Mud Festival, un festival nacional honorario de Corea
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Boryeong Mud Festival esperaba bebé!
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Boryeong, Corea del Sur
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   ¡Uno de los primeros festivales emocionantes en verano! Boryeong Mud Festival en Boryeong Daecheon Beach en Chungnam, Corea del Sur se llevará a cabo del 15 al 24. Vamos a un festival joven y enérgico. Si disfrutas del festival, los paquetes de lodo que naturalmente caen sobre tu cuerpo son una ventaja.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Boryeong Mud Festival ya no necesita explicación. Las personas más jóvenes, así como las unidades familiares con niños pequeños, y este año, incluso los ancianos y las personas mayores que vinieron a escuchar los rumores se han expandido. Echemos un vistazo a Daecheon Beach, donde se celebra el Mud Festival en torno al popular Mud Experience Center (zona de pago).
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   ¡Ve a Daecheon donde el barro se derrama!
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Veamos primero el transporte. El Festival de barro de Boryeong no es difícil de encontrar en transporte público. Si no es bueno para conducir, o si es un amante, no tenga un automóvil. Si eres un conductor novato y quieres ir al festival los fines de semana, debes estacionar tu auto lejos o usar el transporte público.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;¡La pintura de barro en color es divertida! - Boryeong, Corea del Sur (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/52d1912c-ad11-4218-b360-ff468127e8d6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     ¡La pintura de barro en color es divertida!
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    La estación de Daecheon y la terminal de autobuses de Boryeong se encuentran frente a usted, y está a solo 10 minutos de la playa de Daecheon, donde se celebra el Festival de lodo de Boryeong. Significa que puedes llegar al festival tanto como quieras. Una noche y dos días son suficientes para disfrutar del festival de barro. (Esto se basa en una persona con una condición física promedio de entre 30 y 30 años). Si está buscando un festival de lodo para unas vacaciones de verano en familia, puede permitirse estas vacaciones de verano, pero no puede trabajar adecuadamente como un vaca. Recomendamos un curso salado de una noche y dos días después del trabajo.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;¡La pintura de barro en color es divertida! - Boryeong, Corea del Sur (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/1bbcd5ba-2297-4929-b770-a4ed9d3c74ec.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     ¡La pintura de barro en color es divertida!
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Daecheon VS. Iris silencioso
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Una vez que el albergue está atrapado en Wuchang. Durante el festival, el precio del alojamiento en Daecheon Beach se dispara. 2.5 a 3 veces la temporada baja. Si te molesta ir y venir, y tienes mucho espacio para pagar, puedes encontrar un lugar para quedarte frente al festival. Pero si no quieres ser ruidoso y lleno de gente (Jeju ama el amor de los turistas coreanos por el sake coreano toda la noche), Muchangpo está a 15 minutos en coche de la playa de Daecheon. El alojamiento es estable y mucho más tranquilo. Además, la playa de Muchangpo es hermosa. No es demasiado para disfrutar de una experiencia de marea plana con niños, y si son amantes, también es un buen curso para citas. Si quieres susurrar algo dulce, todos recomiendan un ritual relativamente tranquilo en lugar de un Daecheon apasionado y juvenil.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Zona infantil para familias con niños - Boryeong, Corea del Sur (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/11fa5fc8-dad2-411f-a460-2326131293df.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Zona infantil para familias con niños
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Después de beber un vaso de mariscos en Muchangpo, va diligentemente a Daecheon al día siguiente. Las flores, la experiencia de barro y el escenario especial del Festival de barro de Boryeong se encuentran en la Plaza de barro, entre la Plaza de la Pagoda de los Ciudadanos y la Plaza de la Fuente. Existen varios programas de experiencia para disfrutar del barro en todo el cuerpo. General 10,000 wones, jóvenes 8,000 wones. Grupos de 20 personas o más recibirán un descuento de 1,000 wones. Hay una diferencia entre ellos, así que por favor pregunte en el sitio. Hay un espacio para niños.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Zona infantil para familias con niños - Boryeong, Corea del Sur (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/988d15a6-c6d5-41d5-b118-659267c84311.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Zona infantil para familias con niños
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   ¡Mud Experience está a tiempo de abrir!
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Para disfrutar un poco de la sala de experiencia de barro, úsela por la mañana a la hora de apertura del centro de experiencia de barro (10:00). Después de las 11 en punto, el número de personas crece rápidamente y la línea debe comenzar. Si es difícil, se le puede restringir el acceso al jardín.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Peleas de gallos en Mud Experience - Boryeong, Corea del Sur (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/0b603715-26ef-428c-9caa-4cede8a5f847.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Peleas de gallos en Mud Experience
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   El Mud Experience Center, que está abierto de 10 a.m. a 6 p.m., está abierto de 12:30 p.m. a 1:30 p.m.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;¡Entra en la cárcel y recibe un masaje de cuerpo completo con barro! - Boryeong, Corea del Sur (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/d27a2db0-1373-4c4f-8cb6-15bd3f542ab4.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     ¡Entra en la cárcel y recibe un masaje de cuerpo completo con barro!
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Si ingresas a la experiencia de barro a tiempo para la apertura de las 9:30, es un éxito. ¡&#39;Coincidencia&#39; y &#39;colas colgantes&#39; son divertidas en un gran baño de barro! Esperé más de una hora y solo disfruté unos minutos, pero una vez que disfruté del juego, la espera se fue.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;¡Entra en la cárcel y recibe un masaje de cuerpo completo con barro! - Boryeong, Corea del Sur (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/e703ac75-786d-4bcf-895a-0a8812aa5902.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     ¡Entra en la cárcel y recibe un masaje de cuerpo completo con barro!
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Sin embargo, si te mueves un poco diligentemente, puedes disfrutar de varias experiencias de barro, como Mud Superslide y Mud Prison.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;El equipo Jin está confundido en grupos. - Boryeong, Corea del Sur (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/f36a819e-cc2d-49fe-ba1e-1bacc46d101e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     El equipo Jin está confundido en grupos.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Oh, dado que el Festival de lodo de Boryeong celebra un concurso de fotografía cada año, necesitas un sentido para cubrirte la cara con &#39;pintura corporal coloreada&#39;. Esto se debe a que los fotógrafos de todo el país acuden en masa. Una cara que no sabe a dónde fue tomada podría usarse como una imagen para promover el Festival de Barro el próximo año. Expone tu cuerpo y cúbrete la cara. Esta es una forma divertida de disfrutar el festival de barro.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;El equipo Jin está confundido en grupos. - Boryeong, Corea del Sur (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/f3258df1-adf2-4cba-abc5-815e5796ed69.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     El equipo Jin está confundido en grupos.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   El siguiente final del paquete de lodo es el baño de mar.
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Si todo tu cuerpo está lleno de lodo, y has disfrutado al máximo de la experiencia del lodo, corramos a Daecheon. Es hora de disfrutar de la natación. Limpia el barro con los arroyos durante todo el festival, disfruta del baño en el mar y ve a la ducha. No se preocupe si no tiene un automóvil o alojamiento. Hay un casillero y una ducha paga en el festival. Las tarjetas, los teléfonos móviles y las cámaras se mueven en paquetes impermeables. Incluso si no se prepara con anticipación, puede obtenerlo fácilmente en la tienda de conveniencia. Solo use un paquete impermeable. Sin embargo, se debe tener cuidado con la protección UV. Las gafas de sol se pueden romper en la experiencia de barro, por lo que es una buena idea tener una gorra que se ajuste a su cabeza. El lodo también bloquea los rayos UV, convirtiéndolo en una piedra. Un frío en pleno verano lavará la cabeza lavada con barro de la ducha fría.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Si disfrutaste la experiencia de barro lo suficiente, ahora puedes hacer lo que quieras. También puedes disfrutar pintando y nadando. También hay una cabina para hacer jabón de barro. También se celebran juegos en los planos de mareas, competiciones cortas de maratón y competiciones de fútbol sala. Si es el momento adecuado, disfruta cualquier cosa. ¿Por qué no lo llenas con una variedad de alimentos rellenos en todo el recinto del festival y corres hasta que vuelves a la realidad?
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;¡Báñate en la playa de Daecheon, donde se celebra el Mud Festival! - Boryeong, Corea del Sur (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/fbab0632-fdf2-407f-ac84-ed8f1c2f4d36.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     ¡Báñate en la playa de Daecheon, donde se celebra el Mud Festival!
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Finalmente, un consejo para disfrutar del Boryeong Mud Festival. Consigue unos tapones para los oídos. Porque nuestra cóclea es preciosa. Una cosa más para agregar a la anciana es usar un traje de baño. ¡Es gratis usar qué tipo de abrigo! La ropa interior normal no puede detener el barro. También necesitará un paquete impermeable que contenga la llave del automóvil, la tarjeta y el teléfono celular mencionados anteriormente.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     * pregunta
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Centro de información turística de Boryeong 041-930-3882 / 041-930-3557
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;¡Báñate en la playa de Daecheon, donde se celebra el Mud Festival! - Boryeong, Corea del Sur (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/a57fb2bd-701a-47b4-8337-9b1fe8e125a6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     ¡Báñate en la playa de Daecheon, donde se celebra el Mud Festival!
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   propina. Precauciones para disfrutar del festival de barro de Boryeong 2016
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Lo más básico es seguir las reglas de seguridad. Los calentamientos son imprescindibles antes de jugar con agua o barro, y después de beber. Nieve y nariz en la experiencia de barro. Tenga cuidado de no dejar que el barro entre en su boca u oídos. Es útil preparar tapones para los oídos con un paquete impermeable. Además, tenga cuidado con el lodo resbaladizo del lodo en el interior. Puedes disfrutar de este festival de barro si guardas tanto. ¡Oh, no necesariamente ropa interior, traje de baño!
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Información de viaje
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;topmr&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Restaurantes cercanos
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    A lo largo de la playa Daecheon, donde se celebran festivales, hay muchos alojamientos y restaurantes. Los restaurantes a lo largo de la playa de arena de 4 km de largo son difíciles de encontrar. Mientras abraza el mar, le esperan muchos sabores, desde sashimi y kalguksu de mariscos hasta cafés y comida rápida. Si eres coreano habitual, puedes disfrutarlo en Daecheon Beach. Si te gusta el sashimi o probar mariscos a un precio razonable, ve al mercado de pescado de Daecheon Port. Puedes probar sashimi fresco a un precio relativamente bajo.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Restaurante Yonggung:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Coreano, Maeuntang / Boryeong-si Beach 4-gil (Daecheon Beach) / 041-931-1444(남성)
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Pesca en el mar de Tongyeong:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Mariscos frescos, Mariscos / Daecheonhang-ro, Boryeong-si (Mercado de Mariscos del Puerto de Daecheon) / 041-934-8841
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Alojamiento
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    Daecheon Beach tiene una variedad de alojamientos, desde hoteles de lujo hasta hoteles en general, moteles y pensiones. Los precios suben durante el festival. Si hace una reserva con anticipación o se muda a Muchangpo, puede quedarse a un precio regular.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Hotel Mudrin:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Boryeong-si Sinheuk-dong / 041-934-1111
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Hotel JFK Daecheon Water Park:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Boryeong-si Sinheuk-dong / 041-930-2000
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://club-master.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://club-master.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Hotel Datian Guangdao:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Boryeong-si Sinheuk-dong / 041-932-0339
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Palacio de Wuchang Phoece:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Boryeong-si Uncheon-eup / 041-939-5602
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.beachepalace.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.beachepalace.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ La información anterior se actualizó en junio de 2016. Puede cambiar después, así que verifique antes de viajar.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ La información como texto, fotos y videos utilizados en este artículo tiene copyright de la Organización de Turismo de Corea, por lo que está prohibido el uso no autorizado del artículo.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boryeong, Südkorea - Das Boryeong Mud Festival wartete auf Baby!</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/boryeong-mud-festival-waited-for-baby-37-de/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 01:05:37 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/boryeong-mud-festival-waited-for-baby-37-de/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-title=&#34;boryeong-mud-festival-waited-for-baby--37&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Boryeong Mud Festival, ein Ehrenfestival Koreas - Boryeong, Südkorea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/a00f05e1-b602-4338-a21c-24d6d9155761.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Boryeong Mud Festival, ein Ehrenfestival Koreas
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Das Boryeong Mud Festival wartete auf Baby!
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Boryeong, Südkorea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Eines der ersten aufregenden Festivals im Sommer! Das Boryeong Mud Festival am Boryeong Daecheon Beach in Chungnam, Südkorea, findet vom 15. bis 24. statt. Gehen wir zu einem jungen und energiegeladenen Festival. Wenn Sie das Festival genießen, sind Schlammpackungen, die natürlich auf Ihren Körper fallen, ein Bonus.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Das Boryeong Mud Festival braucht keine Erklärung mehr. Jüngere Menschen sowie Familieneinheiten mit kleinen Kindern und in diesem Jahr sogar ältere Menschen und Senioren, die die Gerüchte hörten, haben zugenommen. Werfen wir einen Blick auf Daecheon Beach, wo das Mud Festival rund um das beliebte Mud Experience Center (bezahlte Zone) stattfindet.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Geh nach Daecheon, wo Schlamm fließt!
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Schauen wir uns zuerst den Transport an. Das Boryeong Mud Festival ist mit öffentlichen Verkehrsmitteln nicht schwer zu finden. Wenn Sie nicht gut fahren können oder wenn Sie ein Liebhaber sind, haben Sie kein Auto. Wenn Sie ein Fahranfänger sind und am Wochenende zum Festival gehen möchten, sollten Sie Ihr Auto weit weg parken oder öffentliche Verkehrsmittel nutzen.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Farbschlammmalerei macht Spaß! - Boryeong, Südkorea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/52d1912c-ad11-4218-b360-ff468127e8d6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Farbschlammmalerei macht Spaß!
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Die Daecheon Station und der Boryeong Bus Terminal befinden sich vor Ihnen und sind nur 10 Minuten vom Daecheon Beach entfernt, wo das Boryeong Mud Festival stattfindet. Sie können das Festival also so oft erreichen, wie Sie möchten. Eine Nacht und zwei Tage reichen aus, um das Schlammfest zu genießen. (Dies basiert auf einer Person mit durchschnittlicher Fitness in den frühen bis mittleren 30ern.) Wenn Sie nach einem Schlammfest für einen Familiensommerurlaub suchen, können Sie sich diesen heißen Sommerurlaub leisten, aber Sie können nicht richtig arbeiten wie ein Kuh. Wir empfehlen einen salzigen zweitägigen Kurs für eine Nacht nach der Arbeit.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Farbschlammmalerei macht Spaß! - Boryeong, Südkorea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/1bbcd5ba-2297-4929-b770-a4ed9d3c74ec.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Farbschlammmalerei macht Spaß!
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Daecheon VS. Stille Iris
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Sobald das Hostel in Wuchang gefangen ist. Während des Festivals steigen die Preise für Unterkünfte in Daecheon Beach. 2,5 bis 3 mal die Nebensaison. Wenn Sie sich die Mühe machen zu kommen und zu gehen und viel Platz zum Bezahlen haben, können Sie vor dem Festival eine Unterkunft finden. Aber wenn Sie nicht laut und überfüllt sein möchten (Jeju liebt die ganze Nacht die Liebe koreanischer Touristen zu koreanischem Sake), ist Muchangpo eine 15-minütige Fahrt vom Daecheon Beach entfernt. Die Unterkunft ist stabil und viel ruhiger. Darüber hinaus ist Muchangpo Beach wunderschön. Es ist nicht zu viel, um ein Gezeitenerlebnis mit Kindern zu genießen, und wenn Sie Liebhaber sind, ist es auch ein guter Date-Kurs. Wenn Sie etwas Süßes flüstern möchten, empfiehlt jeder ein relativ ruhiges Ritual anstelle eines leidenschaftlichen, jugendlichen Daecheon.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Kinderzone für Familien mit Kindern - Boryeong, Südkorea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/11fa5fc8-dad2-411f-a460-2326131293df.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Kinderzone für Familien mit Kindern
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Nachdem er in Muchangpo ein Glas Schalentiere getrunken hat, geht er am nächsten Tag fleißig nach Daecheon. Die Blumen, das Schlammerlebnis und die Sonderprüfung des Boryeong Mud Festivals befinden sich auf dem Schlammplatz zwischen dem Bürgerpagodenplatz und dem Fountain Plaza. Es gibt verschiedene Erlebnisprogramme, um Schlamm am ganzen Körper zu genießen. Allgemein 10.000 Won, Jugend 8.000 Won. Gruppen ab 20 Personen erhalten einen Rabatt von 1.000 Won. Es gibt einen Unterschied zwischen ihnen, bitte erkundigen Sie sich vor Ort. Es gibt einen Platz für Kinder.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Kinderzone für Familien mit Kindern - Boryeong, Südkorea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/988d15a6-c6d5-41d5-b118-659267c84311.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Kinderzone für Familien mit Kindern
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Mud Experience ist pünktlich zur Eröffnung!
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Um den Schlamm-Erlebnisraum ein wenig zu genießen, nutzen Sie ihn bitte morgens zur Öffnungszeit des Schlamm-Erlebniszentrums (10:00 Uhr). Nach 11 Uhr wächst die Anzahl der Personen schnell und die Leitung muss beginnen. Wenn es schwierig ist, können Sie den Garten möglicherweise nicht betreten.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Hahnenkampf bei Mud Experience - Boryeong, Südkorea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/0b603715-26ef-428c-9caa-4cede8a5f847.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Hahnenkampf bei Mud Experience
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Das Mud Experience Center, das von 10 bis 18 Uhr geöffnet ist, ist von 12:30 bis 13:30 Uhr geöffnet.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Komm ins Gefängnis und hol dir eine Ganzkörpermassage mit Schlamm! - Boryeong, Südkorea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/d27a2db0-1373-4c4f-8cb6-15bd3f542ab4.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Komm ins Gefängnis und hol dir eine Ganzkörpermassage mit Schlamm!
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Wenn Sie rechtzeitig vor 9:30 Uhr in das Schlamm-Erlebnis eintreten, ist dies ein Erfolg. &#34;Matching&#34; und &#34;Hanging Tails&#34; machen Spaß in einem großen Schlammbad! Ich habe mehr als eine Stunde gewartet und nur ein paar Minuten genossen, aber sobald ich das Spiel genossen habe, ist das Warten vorbei.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Komm ins Gefängnis und hol dir eine Ganzkörpermassage mit Schlamm! - Boryeong, Südkorea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/e703ac75-786d-4bcf-895a-0a8812aa5902.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Komm ins Gefängnis und hol dir eine Ganzkörpermassage mit Schlamm!
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Wenn Sie sich jedoch etwas fleißig bewegen, können Sie verschiedene Schlammerlebnisse wie Mud Superslide und Mud Prison genießen.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Das Jin-Team ist in Gruppen durcheinander. - Boryeong, Südkorea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/f36a819e-cc2d-49fe-ba1e-1bacc46d101e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Das Jin-Team ist in Gruppen durcheinander.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Oh, da das Boryeong Mud Festival jedes Jahr einen Fotowettbewerb veranstaltet, brauchen Sie ein Gespür dafür, Ihr Gesicht mit &#39;farbiger Körperbemalung&#39; zu bedecken. Dies liegt daran, dass Fotografen aus dem ganzen Land strömen. Ein Gesicht, das nicht weiß, wo es aufgenommen wurde, könnte als Bild für das Mud Festival im nächsten Jahr verwendet werden. Legen Sie Ihren Körper frei und bedecken Sie Ihr Gesicht. Dies ist eine unterhaltsame Art, das Schlammfestival zu genießen.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Das Jin-Team ist in Gruppen durcheinander. - Boryeong, Südkorea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/f3258df1-adf2-4cba-abc5-815e5796ed69.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Das Jin-Team ist in Gruppen durcheinander.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Das nächste Ziel der Schlammpackung ist das Baden im Meer
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Wenn Ihr ganzer Körper voller Schlamm ist und Sie die Schlammerfahrung in vollen Zügen genossen haben, laufen wir zu Daecheon. Es ist Zeit zu schwimmen. Wischen Sie den Schlamm während des Festivals mit den Bächen ab, genießen Sie das Baden im Meer und gehen Sie unter die Dusche. Machen Sie sich keine Sorgen, wenn Sie kein Auto oder keine Unterkunft haben. Es gibt ein Schließfach und eine kostenpflichtige Dusche im Festival. Karten, Mobiltelefone und Kameras bewegen sich in wasserdichten Verpackungen. Auch wenn Sie sich nicht im Voraus vorbereiten, können Sie es problemlos im Supermarkt kaufen. Tragen Sie einfach eine wasserdichte Packung. Beim UV-Schutz ist jedoch Vorsicht geboten. Sonnenbrillen können beim Schlamm-Erlebnis kaputt gehen, daher ist es eine gute Idee, eine Kappe zu haben, die zu Ihrem Kopf passt. Der Schlamm blockiert auch UV-Strahlen und macht ihn zu einem Stein. Ein Schauer im Hochsommer wäscht den schlammgewaschenen Kopf aus der kalten Dusche.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Wenn Sie das Schlamm-Erlebnis genug genossen haben, können Sie jetzt tun, was Sie wollen. Sie können auch malen und schwimmen. Es gibt auch einen Stand für die Herstellung von Schlammseife. Es finden auch Spiele in den Wattflächen, Kurzmarathon-Wettbewerbe und Strand-Futsal-Wettbewerbe statt. Wenn die Zeit reif ist, genießen Sie alles. Warum füllst du es nicht mit einer Vielzahl von gefüllten Lebensmitteln auf dem gesamten Festivalgelände und rennst, bis du wieder in der Realität bist?
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Nehmen Sie ein Bad am Daecheon Beach, wo das Mud Festival stattfindet! - Boryeong, Südkorea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/fbab0632-fdf2-407f-ac84-ed8f1c2f4d36.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Nehmen Sie ein Bad am Daecheon Beach, wo das Mud Festival stattfindet!
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Zum Schluss noch ein Tipp, um das Boryeong Mud Festival zu genießen. Hol ein paar Ohrstöpsel. Weil unsere Cochlea kostbar ist. Eine weitere Sache, die Sie der alten Dame hinzufügen sollten, ist das Tragen eines Badeanzugs. Es ist kostenlos, welche Art von Mantel darauf zu tragen! Normale Unterwäsche kann den Schlamm nicht aufhalten. Sie benötigen außerdem eine wasserdichte Packung, in der der zuvor erwähnte Autoschlüssel, die Karte und das Mobiltelefon aufbewahrt werden.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     * Frage
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Touristeninformationszentrum Boryeong 041-930-3882 / 041-930-3557
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Nehmen Sie ein Bad am Daecheon Beach, wo das Mud Festival stattfindet! - Boryeong, Südkorea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/a57fb2bd-701a-47b4-8337-9b1fe8e125a6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Nehmen Sie ein Bad am Daecheon Beach, wo das Mud Festival stattfindet!
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Trinkgeld. Vorsichtsmaßnahmen für das Boryeong Mud Festival 2016
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Am grundlegendsten ist es, die Sicherheitsregeln zu befolgen. Aufwärmen ist ein Muss vor dem Spielen von Wasser oder Schlamm und nach dem Trinken. Schnee und Nase beim Schlammerlebnis. Achten Sie darauf, dass kein Schlamm in Ihren Mund oder Ihre Ohren gelangt. Es ist nützlich, Ohrstöpsel mit einer wasserdichten Packung vorzubereiten. Achten Sie auch auf schlammigen Schlamm im Inneren. Sie können dieses Schlammfest genießen, wenn Sie so viel behalten. Oh, nicht unbedingt Unterwäsche, Badeanzug!
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Reiseinformationen
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;topmr&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Restaurants in der Nähe
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    Entlang des Daecheon Beach, wo Festivals stattfinden, gibt es viele Unterkünfte und Restaurants. Die Restaurants am 4 km langen Sandstrand sind schwer zu finden. Wenn Sie das Meer umarmen, erwarten Sie viele Geschmacksrichtungen, von Sashimi und Kalguksu mit Meeresfrüchten bis hin zu Cafés und Fast Food. Wenn Sie ein normaler Koreaner sind, können Sie es am Daecheon Beach genießen. Wenn Sie Sashimi mögen oder Meeresfrüchte zu einem vernünftigen Preis probieren, besuchen Sie den Daecheon Port Fish Market. Sie können frischen Sashimi zu einem relativ niedrigen Preis probieren.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Yonggung Restaurant:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Koreanisch, Maeuntang / Boryeong-si Beach 4-Gil (Daecheon Beach) / 041-931-1444
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Tongyeong Seefischerei:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Frische Meeresfrüchte, Meeresfrüchte / Daecheonhang-ro, Boryeong-si (Daecheon Port Seafood Market) / 041-934-8841
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Unterkunft
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    Daecheon Beach bietet eine Vielzahl von Unterkünften, von Luxushotels bis hin zu allgemeinen Hotels, Motels und Pensionen. Die Preise steigen während des Festivals. Wenn Sie im Voraus reservieren oder nach Muchangpo ausziehen, können Sie zu einem regulären Preis übernachten.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Hotel Mudrin:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Boryeong-si Sinheuk-dong / 041-934-1111
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     JFK Daecheon Water Park Hotel:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Boryeong-si Sinheuk-dong / 041-930-2000
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://club-master.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://club-master.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Datian Guangdao Hotel:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Boryeong-si Sinheuk-dong / 041-932-0339
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Wuchang Phoece Palast:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Boryeong-si Uncheon-eup / 041-939-5602
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.beachepalace.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.beachepalace.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ Die oben genannten Informationen wurden im Juni 2016 aktualisiert. Sie können sich später ändern. Bitte überprüfen Sie dies, bevor Sie reisen.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Informationen wie Text, Fotos und Videos, die in diesem Artikel verwendet werden, sind von der Korea Tourism Organization urheberrechtlich geschützt. Daher ist die unbefugte Verwendung des Artikels verboten.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>韩国保宁 - 保宁泥浆节等着宝贝！</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/boryeong-mud-festival-waited-for-baby-37-zh-cn/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 01:02:36 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/boryeong-mud-festival-waited-for-baby-37-zh-cn/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-title=&#34;boryeong-mud-festival-waited-for-baby--37&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;韩国荣誉国庆节保宁泥节 - 韩国保宁 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/a00f05e1-b602-4338-a21c-24d6d9155761.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    韩国荣誉国庆节保宁泥节
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   保宁泥浆节等着宝贝！
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    韩国保宁
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   夏天最激动人心的节日之一！ 15日至24日，在韩国忠南市的保宁大川海滩举行的保宁泥节。 让我们去一个年轻而充满活力的节日。 如果您喜欢这个节日，自然会掉落在您身上的泥包是一种奖励。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   保宁泥浆节不再需要解释。 年轻人以及有年幼子女的家庭，今年甚至连听到谣言的老人和老人都在增加。 让我们看一下在著名的泥浆体验中心（收费区）周围举行泥浆节的大川海滩。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   去倒泥的大川！
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    让我们先看看运输。 乘坐公共交通工具不难找到保宁泥浆节。 如果您不擅长驾驶，或者您是情人，请不要开车。 如果您是新手，并且想在周末去参加音乐节，则应将车停在远处或使用公共交通工具。
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;彩色泥画很有趣！ - 韩国保宁 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/52d1912c-ad11-4218-b360-ff468127e8d6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     彩色泥画很有趣！
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    大川站和保宁汽车总站就在您的面前，距离举行保宁泥浆节的大川海滩仅10分钟路程。 这意味着您可以随心所欲地参加音乐节。 一晚零两天就足以享受泥巴节。 （这是根据30年代初至30年代中期身体状况一般的人而定。）如果您正在为家庭暑假寻找泥巴节，您可以负担得起这个炎热的暑假，但您不能像孩子一样正常工作 牛。 我们建议下班后进行一夜咸味的为期两天的课程。
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;彩色泥画很有趣！ - 韩国保宁 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/1bbcd5ba-2297-4929-b770-a4ed9d3c74ec.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     彩色泥画很有趣！
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   大川VS 虹膜无声
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    一旦宿舍被发现在武昌。 节日期间，大川海滩的住宿价格飞涨。 淡季的2.5至3倍。 如果您不愿意来来去去，而且还有很多钱可以支付，那么您可以在节日前找到一个住所。 但是，如果您不想吵闹和拥挤（济州岛整夜都喜欢韩国游客对韩国清酒的热爱），那么牟昌坡距离大川海滩有15分钟车程。 住宿稳定，安静得多。 此外，木场坡海滩很美。 与孩子一起享受潮汐体验并不过分，如果您是情侣，那也是一个不错的约会课程。 如果您想窃窃私语，每个人都建议您使用一种相对安静的仪式，而不是热情洋溢的年轻大川。
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;带孩子的家庭的儿童专区 - 韩国保宁 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/11fa5fc8-dad2-411f-a460-2326131293df.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     带孩子的家庭的儿童专区
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   在木厂坡喝了一杯贝类之后，他第二天勤奋地去了大川。 保宁泥浆节的鲜花，泥浆体验和特殊舞台位于市民宝塔广场和喷泉广场之间的泥浆广场上。 有各种体验计划可让您全身享受泥泞。 一般10,000韩元，青年8,000韩元。 20人或以上的团体可获得1,000韩元的折扣。 它们之间是有区别的，因此请在网站上咨询。 有一个供儿童使用的空间。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;带孩子的家庭的儿童专区 - 韩国保宁 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/988d15a6-c6d5-41d5-b118-659267c84311.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     带孩子的家庭的儿童专区
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   泥经验开放的时间！
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   为了稍微享受一下泥浆体验室，请在早上在泥浆体验中心（10:00）的开放时间使用它。 11点以后，人数迅速增加，生产线必须开始。 如果很难，可能会限制您进入花园。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;泥浆体验中的斗鸡 - 韩国保宁 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/0b603715-26ef-428c-9caa-4cede8a5f847.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     泥浆体验中的斗鸡
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Mud体验中心的开放时间为上午10点至下午6点，开放时间为12:30 pm至1:30。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;走进监狱，用泥浆进行全身按摩！ - 韩国保宁 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/d27a2db0-1373-4c4f-8cb6-15bd3f542ab4.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     走进监狱，用泥浆进行全身按摩！
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   如果您在9:30开幕之前及时输入了泥泞经验，那就成功了。 在大型泥浴中，“匹配”和“垂尾”很有趣！ 我等了一个多小时，只享受了几分钟，但是一旦享受了游戏，等待就消失了。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;走进监狱，用泥浆进行全身按摩！ - 韩国保宁 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/e703ac75-786d-4bcf-895a-0a8812aa5902.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     走进监狱，用泥浆进行全身按摩！
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   但是，如果您稍微移动一点，就可以享受各种泥泞体验，例如Mud Superslide和Mud Prison。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;晋队混在一起。 - 韩国保宁 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/f36a819e-cc2d-49fe-ba1e-1bacc46d101e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     晋队混在一起。
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   哦，因为每年的保宁泥节都会举办摄影比赛，所以您需要一种用“彩色人体彩绘”遮住脸的感觉。 这是因为来自全国各地的摄影师蜂拥而至。 一张不知道在哪里拍摄的面孔可以用作明年宣传泥节的形象。 露出身体，遮住脸。 这是享受泥节的一种有趣方式。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;晋队混在一起。 - 韩国保宁 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/f3258df1-adf2-4cba-abc5-815e5796ed69.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     晋队混在一起。
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   泥包的下一个终点是海水浴
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    如果您的全身都充满泥泞，并且您已充分享受了泥泞的经验，那就去大川吧。 是时候享受游泳了。 在整个节日期间，用溪流擦去泥浆，享受海水浴，然后去淋浴。 如果您没有车或住宿，请不要担心。 节日里有一个储物柜和收费淋浴。 卡片，移动电话和相机以防水包装袋移动。 即使您不事先准备，也可以在便利店轻松获得。 只需佩戴防水包。 但是，应注意防紫外线。 太阳镜可能会因泥泞而破损，因此最好戴上适合您的头部的帽子。 泥浆还阻挡了紫外线，使其成为石头。 盛夏的寒冷会把洗了头的泥洗掉。
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    如果您足够喜欢泥浆体验，那么现在您可以做自己喜欢的事情。 您还可以享受绘画和游泳的乐趣。 还有一个用来做肥皂的摊位。 还举行了滩涂比赛，短程马拉松比赛和沙滩五人制比赛。 如果时间合适，请尽情享受。 您为什么不在节日现场到处都塞满各种各样的填充食品，然后奔跑直到回到现实。
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;在发生泥节的大川海滩洗个澡！ - 韩国保宁 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/fbab0632-fdf2-407f-ac84-ed8f1c2f4d36.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     在发生泥节的大川海滩洗个澡！
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    最后，享受保宁泥节的小贴士。 拿些耳塞。 因为我们的耳蜗很珍贵。 给老太太增加的另一件事是穿泳衣。 穿什么外套是免费的！ 普通的内衣无法阻止泥泞。 您还将需要一个防水袋，该防水袋可容纳前面提到的车钥匙，卡和手机。
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     * 题
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     保宁旅游问询处041-930-3882 / 041-930-3557
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;在发生泥节的大川海滩洗个澡！ - 韩国保宁 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/a57fb2bd-701a-47b4-8337-9b1fe8e125a6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     在发生泥节的大川海滩洗个澡！
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   小费。 享受2016年保宁泥浆节的注意事项
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    最基本的是遵守安全规则。 在打水或打泥之前以及在喝酒之后，必须进行热身运动。 雪和鼻子在泥泞的体验。 注意不要让泥土进入您的嘴或耳朵。 准备带有防水包的耳塞很有用。 另外，请注意里面的泥滑泥。 如果坚持那么多，就可以享受这个泥巴节。 哦，不一定是内衣，泳衣！
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   旅游信息
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;topmr&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1.附近的餐馆
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    在举行节日的大川海滩沿岸，有许多住宿和餐馆。 沿4公里长的沙滩的餐厅很难挑选。 当您拥抱大海时，从生鱼片和海鲜kalguksu到咖啡馆和快餐店都有许多风味等待着您。 如果您是普通韩国人，则可以在大川海滩（Daecheon Beach）享用它。如果您喜欢生鱼片或以合理的价格品尝海鲜，请前往大川港口鱼市场。 您可以以相对较低的价格品尝新鲜的生鱼片。
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     龙宫餐厅：
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    韩国人，前云堂/保宁市海滩4吉（大川海滩）/ 041-931-1444
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     统营市海洋渔业：
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    新鲜海鲜，海鲜/保宁市大川行路（大川港海鲜市场）/ 041-934-8841
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2.住宿
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    大川海滩有多种住宿选择，从豪华酒店到一般酒店，汽车旅馆和养老金。 节日期间价格上涨。 如果您提前预订或搬到木厂坡，您可以按原价住宿。
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     穆德林酒店：
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    保宁市新平洞/ 041-934-1111
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     肯尼迪国际机场大川水上乐园酒店：
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    保宁市新平洞/ 041-930-2000
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://club-master.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://club-master.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     大田广岛饭店：
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    保宁市新平洞/ 041-932-0339
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     武昌菲斯宫：
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    保宁市云川邑/ 041-939-5602
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.beachepalace.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.beachepalace.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※以上信息于2016年6月更新。此后可能会发生变化，因此请在旅行前检查一下。
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※本文中使用的文字，照片和视频等信息均受韩国旅游组织版权保护，因此禁止未经授权使用本文。
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boryeong, South Korea - Boryeong Mud Festival waited for baby!</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/boryeong-mud-festival-waited-for-baby-37/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 00:59:44 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/boryeong-mud-festival-waited-for-baby-37/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-title=&#34;boryeong-mud-festival-waited-for-baby--37&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Boryeong Mud Festival, a Honorary National Festival of Korea - Boryeong, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/a00f05e1-b602-4338-a21c-24d6d9155761.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Boryeong Mud Festival, a Honorary National Festival of Korea
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Boryeong Mud Festival waited for baby!
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Boryeong, South Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   One of the first exciting festivals in summer! Boryeong Mud Festival at Boryeong Daecheon Beach in Chungnam, South Korea will be held from the 15th to the 24th. Let&#39;s go to a young and energetic festival. If you enjoy the festival, mud packs that naturally fall on your body is a bonus.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Boryeong Mud Festival no longer needs explanation. Younger people as well as family units with young children, and this year, even the elderly and seniors who came to hear the rumors have expanded. Let&#39;s take a look at Daecheon Beach where the Mud Festival is held around the popular Mud Experience Center (paid zone).
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Go to Daecheon where mud pours!
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Let&#39;s look at the transportation first. Boryeong Mud Festival is not difficult to find by public transport. If you&#39;re not good at driving, or if you&#39;re a lover, don&#39;t have a car. If you are a novice driver and want to go to the festival on weekends, you should park your car far away or use public transportation.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Color mud painting is fun! - Boryeong, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/52d1912c-ad11-4218-b360-ff468127e8d6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Color mud painting is fun!
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Daecheon Station and Boryeong Bus Terminal are located in front of you, and it is only 10 minutes from Daecheon Beach where Boryeong Mud Festival is held. It means you can reach the festival as much as you like. One night and two days is enough to enjoy the mud festival. (This is based on a person with average fitness in their early to mid 30&#39;s.) If you&#39;re looking for a mud festival for a family summer vacation, you can afford this hot summer vacation, but you can&#39;t work properly like a cow. We recommend a salty one-night two-day course after work.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Color mud painting is fun! - Boryeong, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/1bbcd5ba-2297-4929-b770-a4ed9d3c74ec.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Color mud painting is fun!
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Daecheon VS. Silent iris
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Once the hostel is caught in Wuchang. During the festival, the price of accommodation in Daecheon Beach is soaring. 2.5 to 3 times the low season. If you&#39;re bothered to come and go, and you have a lot of room to pay, you can find a place to stay in front of the festival. But if you don&#39;t want to be noisy and crowded (Jeju loves Korean tourists&#39; love of Korean sake all night long), Muchangpo is a 15-minute drive from Daecheon Beach. Accommodation is stable and much quieter. In addition, Muchangpo Beach is beautiful. It is not too much to enjoy tidal-flat experience with children, and if you are lovers, it is also a good date course. If you want to whisper something sweet, everyone recommends a relatively quiet ritual rather than passionate, youthful Daecheon.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Kids Zone for Families with Children - Boryeong, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/11fa5fc8-dad2-411f-a460-2326131293df.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Kids Zone for Families with Children
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   After drinking a glass of shellfish at Muchangpo, he diligently goes to Daecheon the next day. The flowers, mud experience and special stage of the Boryeong Mud Festival are located at the Mud Square between Citizens&#39; Pagoda Square and Fountain Plaza. There are various experience programs to enjoy mud all over your body. General 10,000 won, youth 8,000 won. Groups of 20 people or more will receive a discount of 1,000 won. There is a difference between them, so please inquire at the site. There is a space for children.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Kids Zone for Families with Children - Boryeong, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/988d15a6-c6d5-41d5-b118-659267c84311.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Kids Zone for Families with Children
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Mud Experience is in time for opening!
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In order to enjoy the mud experience room a little, please use it in the morning at the opening time of the mud experience center (10:00). After 11 o&#39;clock, the number of people grows rapidly and the line must start. If it is hard, you may be restricted from entering the garden.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Cockfighting at Mud Experience - Boryeong, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/0b603715-26ef-428c-9caa-4cede8a5f847.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Cockfighting at Mud Experience
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The Mud Experience Center, which is open from 10 am to 6 pm, is open from 12:30 pm to 1:30 pm.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Get into jail and get a full body massage with mud! - Boryeong, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/d27a2db0-1373-4c4f-8cb6-15bd3f542ab4.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Get into jail and get a full body massage with mud!
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you enter the mud experience in time for the opening of 9:30, it is a success. &#39;Matching&#39; and &#39;hanging tails&#39; are fun in a large mud bath! I waited for more than an hour and only enjoyed a few minutes, but once I enjoyed the game, the wait is gone.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Get into jail and get a full body massage with mud! - Boryeong, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/e703ac75-786d-4bcf-895a-0a8812aa5902.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Get into jail and get a full body massage with mud!
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   However, if you move a little diligently, you can enjoy various mud experiences such as Mud Superslide and Mud Prison.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The Jin Team are muddled in groups. - Boryeong, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/f36a819e-cc2d-49fe-ba1e-1bacc46d101e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The Jin Team are muddled in groups.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Oh, since the Boryeong Mud Festival holds a photo contest every year, you need a sense to cover your face with &#39;colored body painting&#39;. This is because photographers from all over the country flock. A face that doesn&#39;t know where it was taken could be used as an image to promote the Mud Festival next year. Expose your body and cover your face. This is a fun way to enjoy the mud festival.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The Jin Team are muddled in groups. - Boryeong, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/f3258df1-adf2-4cba-abc5-815e5796ed69.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The Jin Team are muddled in groups.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   The next finish of the mud pack is the sea bathing
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    If your whole body is full of mud, and you have enjoyed the mud experience to the fullest, let&#39;s run to Daecheon. It&#39;s time to enjoy swimming. Wipe the mud with the streams throughout the festival, enjoy the sea bathing, and go to the shower. Don&#39;t worry if you don&#39;t have a car or accommodation. There is a locker and a paid shower in the festival. Cards, mobile phones and cameras move in waterproof packs. Even if you do not prepare in advance, you can easily get it at the convenience store. Just wear a waterproof pack. However, care should be taken with UV protection. Sunglasses can be broken at the mud experience, so it&#39;s a good idea to have a cap that fits your head. The mud also blocks UV rays, making it a stone. A chill in midsummer will wash the mud-washed head out of the cold shower.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    If you enjoyed the mud experience enough, now you can do what you like. You can also enjoy painting and swimming. There is also a booth for making mud soap. Games on the tidal flats, short marathon competitions and beach futsal competitions are also held. If the time is right, enjoy anything. Why don&#39;t you fill it up with a variety of stuffed foods all over the festival grounds and run until you get back to reality.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Take a bath at Daecheon Beach where the Mud Festival takes place! - Boryeong, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/fbab0632-fdf2-407f-ac84-ed8f1c2f4d36.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Take a bath at Daecheon Beach where the Mud Festival takes place!
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Finally, one tip to enjoy the Boryeong Mud Festival. Get some earplugs. Because our cochlea is precious. One more thing to add to the old lady is to wear a bathing suit. It&#39;s free to wear what kind of coat on it! Regular underwear can&#39;t stop the mud. You will also need a waterproof pack that will hold the car key, card, and cell phone mentioned earlier.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     * question
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Boryeong Tourist Information Center 041-930-3882 / 041-930-3557
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Take a bath at Daecheon Beach where the Mud Festival takes place! - Boryeong, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/37/a57fb2bd-701a-47b4-8337-9b1fe8e125a6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Take a bath at Daecheon Beach where the Mud Festival takes place!
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   tip. Precautions for Enjoying the 2016 Boryeong Mud Festival
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The most basic thing is to follow the safety rules. Warm-ups are a must before playing water or mud, and after drinking. Snow and nose at the mud experience. Be careful not to let mud get into your mouth or ears. It is useful to prepare earplugs with a waterproof pack. Also, be careful of mud slippery mud inside. You can enjoy this mud festival if you keep this much. Oh, not necessarily underwear, swimsuit!
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel info
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;topmr&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Nearby restaurants
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    Along the Daecheon Beach, where festivals take place, there are many accommodations and restaurants. The restaurants along the 4km-long sandy beach are hard to pick up. As you embrace the sea, there are many flavors awaiting you, from sashimi and seafood kalguksu to cafes and fast food. If you are a regular Korean, you can enjoy it at Daecheon Beach If you like sashimi or try seafood at a reasonable price, go to Daecheon Port Fish Market. You can taste fresh sashimi at a relatively low price.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Yonggung Restaurant:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Korean, Maeuntang / Boryeong-si Beach 4-gil (Daecheon Beach) / 041-931-1444
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Tongyeong Sea Fisheries:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Fresh seafood, Seafood / Daecheonhang-ro, Boryeong-si (Daecheon Port Seafood Market) / 041-934-8841
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Accommodation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    Daecheon Beach has a variety of accommodations, from luxury hotels to general hotels, motels and pensions. Prices rise during the festival. If you make a reservation in advance or move out to Muchangpo, you can stay at a regular price.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Hotel Mudrin:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Boryeong-si Sinheuk-dong / 041-934-1111
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     JFK Daecheon Water Park Hotel:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Boryeong-si Sinheuk-dong / 041-930-2000
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://club-master.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://club-master.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Datian Guangdao Hotel:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Boryeong-si Sinheuk-dong / 041-932-0339
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Wuchang Phoece Palace:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Boryeong-si Uncheon-eup / 041-939-5602
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.beachepalace.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.beachepalace.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was updated in June 2016. It may change afterwards, so please check before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Information such as text, photos, and videos used in this article is copyrighted by Korea Tourism Organization, so unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>