<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ganghwa-gun on Every Corner of Korea</title>
    <link>https://codecorea.github.io/tags/ganghwa-gun/</link>
    <description>Every Corner of Korea (Ganghwa-gun)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 06:50:18 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="https://codecorea.github.io/tags/ganghwa-gun/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet the history of Ganghwado in one place, Ganghwado Ganghwa History Museum - Ganghwa-gun, Incheon, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/meet-the-history-of-ganghwado-in-one-place-ganghwado-ganghwa-history-museum-197/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 06:50:18 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/meet-the-history-of-ganghwado-in-one-place-ganghwado-ganghwa-history-museum-197/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Ganghwa-gun, Incheon, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;meet-the-history-of-ganghwado-in-one-place-ganghwado-ganghwa-history-museum--197&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Ganghwa History Museum - Ganghwa-gun, Incheon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/197/da867ee1-23fa-43e2-88d9-7cd9978be2d2.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Ganghwa History Museum
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Meet the history of Ganghwado in one place, Ganghwado Ganghwa History Museum
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Ganghwa-gun, Incheon, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Ganghwa Island, the fourth largest island in Korea. Although it is an island, it is not only a place in the metropolitan area, but also an easy way to cross Ganghwa Bridge or Choji Bridge. Ganghwado is a town with a variety of history from prehistoric times to modern times. The Ganghwa History Museum, where you can get a glimpse of Ganghwa Island&#39;s breathtaking history, is a place to visit before you go on a trip to Ganghwa Island, and is a space to enrich your trip to Ganghwa Island.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   From prehistoric times to old sayings, where Ganghwa has a history
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Ganghwa-do is a perfect place for exploring cultural heritage. It is not an exaggeration to say that the island itself is the birthplace of history. A variety of history is piled up from prehistoric times to Goryeo and Joseon periods. The ruins of the dolmen in Ganghwa-do were listed as UNESCO World Heritage Sites along with Hwasun in Jeollanam-do and Gochang in Jeollabuk-do. Ganghwa History Museum, located inside Ganghwa Dolmen Park, is a place where you can take a quick look at the history of Ganghwa Island, so it is the first place to visit before going on a trip to Ganghwa Island.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The old Ganghwa History Museum was located in Gapgot Dondae, where you meet as soon as you cross Ganghwa Bridge. After looking around the history building, it was a textbook course on a tour of excursions that toured the scenes of the western powers of the western powers in the late Joseon Dynasty, such as Gwangseongbo, Deokjinjin, and Chojijin. However, it is true that the size of the history hall is small, so it is not only impossible to see all the history of Ganghwa Island at a glance, but it has also been an exploration tour that is biased toward modern history.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;2nd floor permanent exhibition room - Ganghwa-gun, Incheon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/197/4c190dc0-f726-4362-ab3f-84974fe5f3cb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     2nd floor permanent exhibition room
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Ganghwa History Museum was expanded and moved to Dolmen Park in 2010. The Ganghwa History Museum, which consists of two floors, goes directly up to the second floor from the ticket counter on the first floor, first looks around the prehistoric period, then descends to the first floor and meets Goryeo and Joseon periods in turn.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Ganghwa History Museum - Ganghwa-gun, Incheon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/197/bc2cbc45-8d9a-4055-92e2-5aeaa5dedfd0.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Ganghwa History Museum
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The second floor of the museum displays prehistoric artifacts from the Old Stone Age to the Bronze Age. This is a great place for children to experience and learn the history of Ganghwa, including exploring the exciting Bronze Age and talking about the open sea of Ganghwa. In the exciting Bronze Age exploration, you can solve quizzes and puzzles on the screen, and there is also a photo zone where you can take a commemorative photo with the fairy of the Chamseongdan. Ganghwa&#39;s open sea story tells a shadow play. It contains the story of a Ganghwa young man who needs to send Goryeo celadon to the Philippines through the sea route. In addition, various stories that have been handed down to Ganghwa, such as Orunji Mountain of Goryeo Mountain, Jeondeungsa Temple, Nannasang, Sondol, and Bomunsa Seoksil Nahansang, are briefly composed and fun to read.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;‘Explore the exciting Bronze Age’ experience space - Ganghwa-gun, Incheon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/197/c88155a9-417f-46fb-8c7a-ae35076fb02f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     ‘Explore the exciting Bronze Age’ experience space
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Ganghwa-do meets the history of suffering
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   On the first floor of the Ganghwa History Museum, you can meet various relics and historical events from the Goryeo Dynasty to the Joseon Dynasty. At the end of the Joseon Dynasty, the frequent invasion of the western powers caused the Ganghwa Island to be thoroughly devastated.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Diorama reproducing Byeongin Yangyo - Ganghwa-gun, Incheon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/197/b30a142d-d4b7-41d5-9bfb-5420f877e1cc.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Diorama reproducing Byeongin Yangyo
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Byung In Yang Yoo was a case of French invasion of the persecution of Catholicism, and Shin Mi Yang Yoo was a case of the US invasion of the burning General Sherman in the Daedong River. Although the country and the reason for the invasion are different, Byeongin Yang and Shin Mi Yang are similar in many ways. In addition to the commonality of the imperial aggression of the Western powers, the process of looting and retrieval is exactly alike. France retreated and plundered the Uigwejangs and old books of the Joseon Dynasty, and the United States took General Suh Jae-gi, the longevity of General Jae-yeon Eo, as a loot. The Uigyu Janggak Uigui of the Joseon Dynasty stepped on the land of the homeland in 145 years in 2011, and Sujagi returned to the homeland of 2007 in 136 years. Needless to say, it is a joy that has been returned, but the sad history of the sad and dismal Joseon of Joseon is hidden behind the hidden side.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Diorama recreating new beauty - Ganghwa-gun, Incheon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/197/7b7f8529-676d-4921-a474-daa0018213a2.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Diorama recreating new beauty
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   A diorama that reproduces the scene of the French army invading Ganghwa during Byeonginyangyo and the battle between the U.S. military and Joseon troops in Gwangseongbo during Shinmiyangyo can give a glimpse of the situation at that time. In particular, life-size hand-crafts are hung on the diorama that reproduces the new beauty, and regret and cross meet.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Along with the new beauty diorama, it is hanging - Ganghwa-gun, Incheon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/197/79848557-6679-400e-8796-371eab773ba8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Along with the new beauty diorama, it is hanging
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Along the coastline of Ganghwa Island, there are military facilities in the Joseon Dynasty called Jin, Bo, and Dondae. Hyojong, the Joseon Dynasty, who carved the disgrace of Byeongja Horan on his chest, began to install it as one of the North Korean punishment plans. Among them, Chojijin, Deokjinjin, and Gwangseong were the places where fierce battles took place in 1871 (8th year of King Gojong). The power of the cannon shooting from the ship was so great that it could not be matched by the ship&#39;s canvas. The next day after giving out the earthquake, Deokjinjin and Gwangseongbo fell. Around 1000 Korean troops under General Eo Jae-yeon were killed, except for a few who could not have been misled. Sujagi, which was placed on the camp of the Joseon army, was replaced with stars and stripes. If you look at the miserable photos of Shin Mi Yang Yoo, you will become a performer. Even today, the remains of the shells remained on the walls and pine trees of Chojijin.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Super earthquake wall with traces of shells - Ganghwa-gun, Incheon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/197/34137b14-a1f5-4222-a94c-726b45dbeebb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Super earthquake wall with traces of shells
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Chojijin is an indispensable course on the excursion to Deokjinjin and Gwangseongbo along with the history of Ganghwa Island. It is also a good idea to walk on the 2nd course of Ganghwa Nadeulgil from Gapgot Dondae to Chojijin (17km).
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Gwangseongbo, where the hand-to-hand battle took place at the time of Shin Mi Yangyo - Ganghwa-gun, Incheon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/197/ce52d6a0-ac4e-4b54-ad64-0b4ddfa36a95.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Gwangseongbo, where the hand-to-hand battle took place at the time of Shin Mi Yangyo
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Meet the most beautiful dolmen in Korea
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The outside of Ganghwa History Museum is Dolmen Park. Dolmen is a representative tomb of the Bronze Age and is a cultural heritage representing the megalithic culture of the world. The dolmen named ‘Standing Stone’ is often referred to as Jiseokmyo. There are more than 30,000 dolmens in Korea alone, and if you add up to 30,000 dolmens in North Korea, it is a dolmen kingdom. It is no wonder that the dolmen ruins of Ganghwa Island, along with Gochang in Jeonbuk and Hwasun in Jeonnam, were registered as UNESCO World Heritage Sites in 2000.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    In Ganghwa Island, more than 100 dolmens are scattered mainly at the foot of Goryeo Mountain. It&#39;s not much compared to the dolmens in Gochang or Hwasun, but it comes to mind first when it comes to the image of dolmens. It is called dolmen in the vicinity. This dolmen is a typical drum-style dolmen that is covered with two stones. It looks like a table and is called a table-type dolmen, but it is a grand dolmen with a height of 2.5m and a cover stone of 50 tons.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    The dolmen is largely divided into a table type, a checkerboard type, and an open seat type. Among them, the table-style dolmen is a dolmen where the grave room is exposed on the ground. As a result, table-style dolmens are prone to robbery and damage over the years. Nowadays, the dolmen in the vicinity is composed of 2 goimdols and 1 shroud, but it is thought that it was originally a tomb room made of 4 goimdols and covered with a shroud. It is a dolmen that has been robbed and damaged over the years, leaving only empty shells. Whatever the reason, the dolmens in the vicinity of the neighborhood are majestic like a general full of dignity, which is impeccable even when looking around. The nearby dolmens are designated as historical sites No. 137 in the name of Jiseokmyo in the vicinity of Ganghwa.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Dolmen near Ganghwa - Ganghwa-gun, Incheon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/197/0833e28c-3089-4315-831e-8192a95d578a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Dolmen near Ganghwa
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Ganghwa History Museum
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Address: 994-19, Ganghwa-daero, Hajeom-myeon, Ganghwa-gun, Incheon
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Inquiries: 032-934-7887
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.ganghwa.go.kr/open_content/museum/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.ganghwa.go.kr/open_content/museum/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Restaurants near
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Chungnamseosanjip: Flower crab / 1210, Jungang-ro, Nagan-myeon, Ganghwa-gun / 032-933-1667
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Toga: Sundubu Shrimp Stew / 1912 Haeannam-ro, Hwado-myeon, Ganghwa-gun
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Wooriok: Korean food class / 12, Namsan-gil, Ganghwa-eup, Ganghwa-gun / 032-934-2427
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Rooms
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Largoville: 27, Haeamnam-ro 2845beon-gil, Hwado-myeon, Ganghwa-gun / 032-555-8868
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.largoville.com/pages/index.php&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.largoville.com/pages/index.php
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Toad Mud House: 2443 Haeannam-ro, Hwado-myeon, Ganghwa-gun / 010-3129-5009
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://dookkubie.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://dookkubie.com/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -109 House: 540 Haeanseo-ro, Yangdo-myeon, Ganghwa-gun / 032-937-8109
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.109house.com&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     www.109house.com
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was created in May 2013, and may change later, so be sure to check it before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>