<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jecheon-si on Every Corner of Korea</title>
    <link>https://codecorea.github.io/tags/jecheon-si/</link>
    <description>Every Corner of Korea (Jecheon-si)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 03:21:03 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="https://codecorea.github.io/tags/jecheon-si/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Filming locations in Jecheon, from the movie &#39;Parkha Candy&#39; to the drama &#39;Shark&#39; - Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/filming-locations-in-jecheon-from-the-movie-parkha-candy-to-the-drama-shark-243/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 03:21:03 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/filming-locations-in-jecheon-from-the-movie-parkha-candy-to-the-drama-shark-243/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;filming-locations-in-jecheon-from-the-movie-parkha-candy-to-the-drama-shark--243&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;The sunset of Cheongpung Lake makes the inland sea feel real - Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/243/5e967bae-bca0-4a72-9905-60e7f5ee1779.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    The sunset of Cheongpung Lake makes the inland sea feel real
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Filming locations in Jecheon, from the movie &#39;Parkha Candy&#39; to the drama &#39;Shark&#39;
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Located in the central inland, Jecheon is a small town. It is perfect for quiet walking around. Recently, it has emerged as a city of movies and dramas. The police station set of the Visual Media Center, Cheongpungho and Uirimji area bring together the beauty and scenery of Jecheon and the memories of the movie.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Take the train to the movie location
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   “I want to go back!”
   &lt;br/&gt;
   The end of the film &amp;lt;Parkha Candy&amp;gt; was a scene that would remain in the movie history. It is not an exaggeration to say that the scene that made today&#39;s movie star Seol Kyung-goo. It is near Jinso village in Baekwoon-myeon, Jecheon-si. It is located above the elevated railroad in Chungbuk Line between Gongjeon Station and Samtan Station. There are two forked bridges, which are in front of the tunnel through the middle of the cliff. At the time of shooting, it was remote. After the movie was successful, the road opened and the number of vehicles increased. Pensions have also entered quite a few. The movie changed the village. Since it was a 1999 work, it was 14 years ago.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &amp;lt;Parkha Candy&amp;gt; was a flare. Since then, many movies and dramas have visited Jecheon. Local small towns&#39; unique feelings and moods sometimes exist as a set of movies. Several factors have also been added. The first is a train. Jecheon is the starting point of the Central Inland Circulation Train (O-Train). The central inland circulation train is a circular train that connects the three provinces of central inland. Departing from Jecheon, Chungbuk, passes Yeongju, Gyeongbuk, and Taebaek, Gangwon-do. You can feel the beauty of Baekdu-daegan. It&#39;s a movie-like train journey.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;New exhibition on the first floor of Jecheon Media Center - Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/243/4e9552b2-8081-4b9f-9335-a896f1bb03d6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     New exhibition on the first floor of Jecheon Media Center
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The second is the movie itself. It&#39;s not just a movie, it&#39;s a music movie. It is composed of music or music. Jecheon hosts international film festivals representing Korea, along with Busan, Bucheon, and Jeonju. Jecheon International Music Film Festival. This year, it opened on August 14th (Wed) and held six days until Monday (19th). Movie fans who simply visited to enjoy the music festival are immersed in the city&#39;s fascination around the end of the festival. So, I visit Jecheon once again. This is to meet Jecheon again as a travel destination, not a movie city of Jecheon. In that case, I recommend taking a trip to a filming or drama location filmed in Jecheon. Most of Jecheon&#39;s main filming locations are Jecheon&#39;s famous travel destinations.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Jecheon Film Media Center, a renovated old city council building - Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/243/45bbd879-ca44-4712-b736-5192402cce98.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Jecheon Film Media Center, a renovated old city council building
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Gathering of movie information, spring of Jecheon Media Center
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The first step in traveling to the Jecheon Filming Site is to start from the Jecheon Film Media Center in spring. It is a place that holds various information of the movie city Jecheon. The old Jecheon City Council building was remodeled and opened in 2008. In particular, the office of the Cheongpung Film Commission, which discovers and introduces the location of Jecheon, is located. It is often difficult to find the exact location of the filming location, but you can also get help such as the location and transportation of filming locations, movies, and dramas that are being released recently.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Traces of filming also exist within the center. This is the police station set inside. Many of the recent movies, such as &amp;lt;Howling&amp;gt;, &amp;lt;Broken Arrow&amp;gt;, and &amp;lt;Kan Ki Nam&amp;gt;, are set by the Jecheon Video Media Center. It is also released to the general public, but the detailed settings are not usually made, so you can only feel the atmosphere. At the entrance on the first floor, movies and drama posters taken in Jecheon have filled the inner walls. &amp;lt;Wagon&amp;gt;, &amp;lt;Gone with the Wind&amp;gt;, &amp;lt;Chosunyeong Detective&amp;gt;. In front of the stairs going up to the second floor, there is a new prop, the main prop of the movie &amp;lt;Shinkijeon&amp;gt;. &amp;lt;Shin Ki-jeon&amp;gt; by Jung Jae-young is a 2008 work. It dealt with the production process of Shinkijeon, a rocket propulsion arrow made during the Joseon Dynasty. A set was built in the mountains of Geumseong-myeon and photographed. At the time of filming, Dr. Chae Seok-yeon, a researcher at the Korea Aerospace Research Institute, restored a new mechanism and gathered attention. The new mechanism in the center was donated by the production company to Jecheon City. The production plan written in &amp;lt;Army Prayer&amp;gt; in &amp;lt;&amp;lt; National Ordinance of the Ordinance&amp;gt; is attached like a manual.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Muam Reservoir that Han Yi-soo and Cho Hae-woo met in &#39;Shark&#39; (Photo: Cheongpung video court) - Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/243/f51b51d2-4b97-425f-9ed3-c465892f5dad.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Muam Reservoir that Han Yi-soo and Cho Hae-woo met in &#39;Shark&#39; (Photo: Cheongpung video court)
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The Jecheon Media Center is useful when it comes to film festivals or location information rather than travel. You can also relax in the cafeteria on the first floor.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Muam Reservoir filming &#39;Gone with the Wind&#39; - Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/243/a15d0cf1-3670-4bcd-b4ac-126d85552659.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Muam Reservoir filming &#39;Gone with the Wind&#39;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   The Secret Lake of the Drama &amp;lt;Shark&amp;gt;
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Cheongpungho is the best place to travel in Jecheon. Cheongpung Lake is an artificial lake created by the construction of Chungju Dam. The same lake is called Chungjuho in Chungju and Cheongpungho in Jecheon. It is called the inland sea because it has the largest size after Soyang Lake. Bibongsan Mountain, Geumsusan Mountain, Insan Mountain, etc. are combined with the spectacular waterways of Namhan River to form a superb view.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;High price of Cheongpung Cultural Heritage Complex - Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/243/1d9f32e8-a4fe-47ad-a3d2-f9585775931a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     High price of Cheongpung Cultural Heritage Complex
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Cheongpung Lake is about a 30-minute drive from downtown Jecheon. It is only a lakeside when you get out of downtown and enter Geumseong-myeon. It is also suitable as a drive course. The Cheongpung Lake is carried whenever the recording path is curved. The first pass is the lakeside KBS shooting set. Filmed major historical dramas of KBS such as &amp;lt;Taejo Wang Geon&amp;gt;. Now closed. Cheongpungho was once a mecca for Korean historical dramas, but after rumors as a destination, its momentum diminished. Rather, the shooting of modern theater has increased than that of historical drama. Rather than building a new set, it captures the beautiful nature of Cheongpungho. The drama &amp;lt;Shark&amp;gt; starring Son Ye-jin and Kim Nam-gil is typical.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Geumnamru, used as a gate for Cheongpung Elementary School - Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/243/8c978a2d-ace8-4c84-9d68-6696d482b8eb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Geumnamru, used as a gate for Cheongpung Elementary School
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   After passing KBS filming location, it is the way to Muamsa Temple on the left. In the past, there was a &amp;lt;Shingijeon&amp;gt; set near Muamsa Temple. This also has lost functionality now. Before the Muam Valley and Muamsa Temple, they passed through the Muam Reservoir (Muam No. 1). As you move from the road toward the reservoir, you will find a small vacant lot on the waterside surrounded by mountains. There is a lonely tree towards the lake. The scenery of the tranquil lake catches the heart. In the drama &amp;lt;Shark&amp;gt;, this is the lakeside next to the villa where Han Yi-soo (Kim Nam-gil) and Jo Ha-woo (Sun Ye-jin) secretly encountered. It is a space suitable for expressing the secret feelings of love and hatred entangled between the two main characters.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Cheongpung Lake from the top of Cheongpung Cultural Foundation - Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/243/48afac3e-6cca-41e9-a1c6-8b945ac3f207.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Cheongpung Lake from the top of Cheongpung Cultural Foundation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   On the one side of the reservoir, the water path of the Muam Valley is also teeming. It is not a professional camping ground, but there are also a few people who enjoy camping with tents. Ahead of the release, starring Ha Ji-won&#39;s &amp;lt;Chosun Beauty Three Musketeers&amp;gt; and Cha Tae-hyun&#39;s &amp;lt;Gone with the Wind&amp;gt; were also filmed in Muamsa and Muam Reservoir. In terms of the scenery of the trip, Muamsa or Valley is better, but Muam Reservoir is a fascinating image of the movie.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;There are a lot of interesting trees, including annual trees. - Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/243/451683f8-1d2b-431a-9beb-09dfe9aa94d3.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     There are a lot of interesting trees, including annual trees.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Magnificent scenery of Cheongpung Lakeside
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   After exiting Muam Reservoir of &amp;lt;Shark&amp;gt;, go to Cheongpung Cultural Foundation and Cheongpung Monorail. It is a travel destination that retains the gorgeous scenery of Cheongpungho. On the way, there is also Cheongpung Land, and it is better to meet Cheongpung Cultural Foundation and Cheongpung Monorail at sunset.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   When you cross Cheongpung Bridge, Cheongpung Cultural Foundation emerges. The cultural assets of Cheongpung, which were in danger of sinking with the Chungju Dam, were collected and created. Climb the foot of the mountain while looking at the remains of the overpass, pavilion, and dolmen. From the top, the panoramic view of Cheongpungho is embraced as a 360-degree panorama. The red baekilhong on each way to climb makes the Cheongpung Cultural Foundation of this time stand out more. Interesting trees like the heart tree and the thinking tree are also interesting. The Cheongpung Cultural Foundation had a SBS historical drama set site just two years ago. I filmed &amp;lt;Awaiting&amp;gt;, &amp;lt;Iljimae&amp;gt;, and &amp;lt;Jang Gil-san&amp;gt;, but it was recently demolished. You can&#39;t look into the stage of an old historical drama directly, but the outstanding nature of Cheongpungho, which forms the background, is enough comfort.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Cheongpung Land where you can enjoy extreme sports - Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/243/430293be-0214-4d45-b06b-8749e2d584e5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Cheongpung Land where you can enjoy extreme sports
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Fortunately, a larger scale facility overlooking the Cheongpung Lake was created. It is Cheongpung Monorail that entered last year. Originally used for transporting paragliding equipment to the summit of Bibongsan, it was developed for tourism. It operates 7 cars and travels 3km away in 23 minutes one way. The monorail climbs to the top of Bibongsan Mountain at 531 meters above sea level. The view from the top is too undue to climb easily. Mt. Seollang, Seongbong, Guksabong, and Daedeoksan create a delightful landscape.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sunset of Cheongpung Land, filming &amp;lt;Radio Star&amp;gt; - Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/243/fb8d1679-71fe-46ae-a428-90d3cfc21c06.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sunset of Cheongpung Land, filming &amp;lt;Radio Star&amp;gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you have a leisurely time, Jardrock Road is also recommended. It is a path that walks through the mountainous village of Cheongpungho, and is made of 7 courses, including a small Dongsan-gil, Jeongbangsa-gil, and Ice Valley Ecological Road. There are many walks along the lake, creating a unique scenery. The short course takes 90 minutes and the long course takes 280 minutes. Then, visit Cheongpung Land at sunset.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Jardrock Road along the foothills of Cheongpung Lakeside - Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/243/134d31b1-9b68-4a31-8570-c32435983dfc.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Jardrock Road along the foothills of Cheongpung Lakeside
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   &amp;lt;Radio Star&amp;gt; at sunset
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   During sunset, go to Cheongpung Land (Resort) again. The parking lot filmed a scene from the movie Radio Star. Singer Choi Gon (Park Jung-hoon) and manager Park Min-soo (An Sung-ki) shared a cup of coffee and regained their righteousness. The lonely middle-aged life is exquisitely matched with the glow of the blue wind. The sunset in Cheongpung Land is the best. It is an unprecedented view from the inland sea. The shadows of the mountains formed by Bibongsan Mountain, Indeungsan Mountain, and Keimyung Mountain across the lake make you lose your words. It makes my heart beat like a romance in a movie. As you go down the lake, there are extreme leisure facilities next to the lakeside stage. The country&#39;s tallest 62m bungee jump, the country&#39;s first ejection seat, and the country&#39;s longest 1.4km cable coaster (zip line) bring exciting excitement.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;5&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Euirimji Promenade, one of the most beautiful night views - Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/243/a6e0ef3a-35f7-46b1-8549-bb369dfa6013.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Euirimji Promenade, one of the most beautiful night views
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   After watching the sunset in Cheongpung Land, head to Urimim not far from downtown Jecheon. Along with Cheongpungho, it is a must-see and travel destination in Jecheon. Uirimji is the oldest reservoir in Korea along with Gimje Byeokgolje and Miryang Fisheries. It is said to have been built for the first time during the King of Singa Jinheung. Currently, it is faithful to the role of an amusement park with parklands and trails. Around the pond, pine trees and weeping willows add luck. It is popular as a dating spot for lovers, like &amp;lt;The Secret Charm of Female Professors&amp;gt;. In the daytime, it is also worth visiting Solim Park in Uirimji, where you shot the scene of the gang&#39;s picnic. However, the late night reservoir walk is also indispensable. Uirimji is one of the most beautiful night views in Jecheon. It is not just a night view, but a night scenery that you can feel while walking slowly. Since it is held at the tiptoe, it captures Jecheon&#39;s travel to Sinab.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;5&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Night scenery of willow trees with willow trees - Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/243/241521d8-0894-43fe-8908-948bd2b63c4c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Night scenery of willow trees with willow trees
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Visual Media Center Spring
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    : 242, Uirim-daero, Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, 043-645-4995
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Cheongpung Land (Cheonpung Lakeside Stage)
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    : 26, Gyo-ri, Cheongpung-myeon, Jecheon-si, Chungbuk 043-648-4151
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Cheongpung Cultural Foundation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    : 6-20, Multae-ri, Cheongpung-myeon, Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, 043-641-5532
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Cheongpung Tourist Monorail
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    : 114, Dogok-ri, Cheongpung-myeon, Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, 043-642-3326
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Willim
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    : 241, Mosan-dong, Jecheon-si, Chungbuk 043-651-7101
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1.Nearby Restaurants
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Yechon: Gondrenamul Rice / 30 Cheongpung Myeongwol-ro, Cheongpung-myeon, Jecheon-si / 043-647-3707
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Ant Restaurant: Herbal Medicine Sundae / 114 Yongducheon-ro, Jecheon-si / 043-643-5093
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Taejeong: Herbal Bibimbap / 184 Jangrak-ro, Jecheon-si / 043-646-6565
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.태정.전문.kr&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;태정으로 이동&#34;&gt;
     http://www.태정.전문.kr
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2.Accommodation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Cheongpung Resort: 1763 Cheongpungho-ro, Cheongpung-myeon, Jecheon-si / 043-640-7000
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cheongpungresort.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;청풍리조트로 이동&#34;&gt;
     http://www.cheongpungresort.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Early morning lakeside pension: 53-15 Cheongpungho-ro 42-gil, Cheongpung-myeon, Jecheon-si / 070-8876-8677, 010-9049-8677
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.dreamlakepension.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;이른아침호숫가로 이동&#34;&gt;
     http://www.dreamlakepension.com/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Dream Lake Pension: 53-10 Cheongpungho-ro 42-gil, Cheongpung-myeon, Jecheon-si / 043-648-6380
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.dreamlake.co.kr&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     www.dreamlake.co.kr
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was created in September 2013, and may change later, so be sure to check it before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A pleasant meeting between the mountain and the lake - Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/a-pleasant-meeting-between-the-mountain-and-the-lake-218/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 03:28:52 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/a-pleasant-meeting-between-the-mountain-and-the-lake-218/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;a-pleasant-meeting-between-the-mountain-and-the-lake--218&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Scenery of Gogok Castle Wall seen from Brothers&#39; Peak in Samusan (Photo courtesy of Jecheon City Hall) - Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/218/20beb6a5-55ec-425c-83b8-0c289786dcc2.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Scenery of Gogok Castle Wall seen from Brothers&#39; Peak in Samusan (Photo courtesy of Jecheon City Hall)
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   A pleasant meeting between the mountain and the lake
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The phrase &#39;Cheongpungho Jadrakgil&#39; is very pretty. It&#39;s also soft to pronounce, and it feels like ‘Sabujakjidada’, meaning that it acts lightly and effortlessly. I feel that it will be a trekking course that is easy to walk for some reason. Jadrak-gil refers to ‘a narrow path in a hilly country at the foot of a mountain.’ The name Cheongpungho is in front of it because the road runs around the mountain village surrounding Cheongpungho. It is a hiking trail, but it is difficult to walk. Of the 100 ridges in Cheongpungho in Jecheon, it is difficult to find a walking trail with such a great view point, as you walk along the beautiful scenery around the lake.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Cheongpungho Walk while looking at Cheongpungho
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In Cheongpungho Jardrock Road, 7 courses were developed. Among them, the 9.9km ‘Gokgok Wall Road’, starting from Oksunbong Rest Area in front of Oksundaegyo Bridge and passing through Gogok-ri and Dabul-ri to Gogogol in Jigok-ri, is the best course in harmony with a wonderful view and diverse flora.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   What is called Gogok Castle Wall Road is the place where the wall was formed in the past. The walls are not made of stone. The slopes of the slopes are named because they act as natural walls.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    jade
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Oksun Bridge, where the Gogok Wall Street begins - Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/218/fe52ce12-4356-48b8-929e-d7a5ddbe4bb4.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Oksun Bridge, where the Gogok Wall Street begins
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The hilly path at the foot of the mountain continues, and occasionally there is a place to breathe. It is good to keep the surrounding branches and weeds neatly organized. Occasionally, there is a shelter where you can see the scenery of Cheongpungho closely. Under the blue skies in May, the mountain streams colored by fresh green and the ripples of the lake with azure are spectacular.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Goegok Seongbyeok Trail - Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/218/9aceb191-e040-4ee7-90ba-b16e004c2962.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Goegok Seongbyeok Trail
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   From the start, I keep walking uphill, but it is not difficult. It is because the slope is gentle and comfortable. I&#39;m definitely hiking, but my steps are light. The white spring primrose and yellow yangji flower are greeted with bright light all over the place.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Goegok Seongbyeok Trail - Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/218/898fe378-dc26-4fbc-9465-b9d723ab7f9d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Goegok Seongbyeok Trail
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   this
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Great spot to take pictures - Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/218/4b9ceada-99fd-4224-a3f9-eb33a15db900.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Great spot to take pictures
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Turn around the road you came to and go to Dabuli, called &#39;the first town under the sky. If you follow the downhill path, the forest of trees will be cleared and you will see an open ridge, where there is the Baekbong Juk. This is a shelter created by the opening of Jardrock Road. For a moment, you can feel the emotion of a quiet and quiet mountain village filling thirst and hunger with rice wine and pancakes.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Dabuli called the first town under the sky - Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/218/e1afc1e3-ca1f-43b5-8f2c-42114a28a50e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Dabuli called the first town under the sky
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   From Baekbong Jukmak to the top of Dabuljae, a small village passes through a simple village. The road is paved with asphalt. The summit of Dabuljae is the middle point of Goebbulseongbyeokgil. From here, go round the foot of Samsan Mountain (478m) and go down to Gosugol. However, if you want to descend quickly because you feel limited by your physical strength or time, you can go down to where you first started through Gogok-ri.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Milestones informing Cheongpungho - Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/218/4d903782-4cfa-41c4-98b6-4bc5c92dfe8b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Milestones informing Cheongpungho
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   There are several roads where vehicles can be moved, and you can follow Imdo.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;14&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Milestones informing Cheongpungho - Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/218/a3f153ed-e7df-43f5-9af5-b7edc4150d78.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Milestones informing Cheongpungho
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   When you walk on a mountain path from Dabulam toward Gosugol, you pass through a dune field and thorny vines that exceed the height of your waist. The open ridge path is repeated and can be said to be a highlight section of the Goegokseong Wall Path while walking with Cheongpung Lake under your feet. If you walk for about an hour, you reach 403 bags, and if you walk another 15 minutes, Limdo comes out. The feeling of walking on Imdo is not just walking on a mountain path, but large and small fields spread out on the left and right sides of the road, allowing you to feel the freshness of green.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;16&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Hiker smelling herbal scents while hiking - Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/218/a1b0b75a-c47e-40f9-956b-b4879fdcb88c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Hiker smelling herbal scents while hiking
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Short but intense Jeongbangsagil
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;span&gt;
    &lt;span&gt;
     The advantage of Cheongpungho Jadrak Road is that it has a variety of courses. Even travelers who do not enjoy hiking or lack time can choose the course that suits their situation and enjoy the wonderful view of the mountain and lake.
    &lt;/span&gt;
   &lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Jeongbangsagil, a two-course course, is a short course of 1.6 km, but the nature in harmony with the temple makes an impressive impression. The way to climb from the entrance to the Neunggang Valley is quite Gapal sweat. Still, the forest is lush and the valley runs along the side of the road, so you can walk in the cool breeze. It is a pity that the road is paved, so it is not easy to drop the mountain.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Jeongbangsa scenery with a mountain on the back and a lake - Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/218/7b81d622-3861-47fe-9f48-9f0c7325443f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Jeongbangsa scenery with a mountain on the back and a lake
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The regret is rewarded with a wonderful scenery the moment you arrive at Jeongbangsa Temple. When you enter Jeolmadang, there are huge rocks that support the integrity of the cylinder, and in front, the Cheongpung Lake and the wavy ridge spread like a panorama. Sit in the yard chair and watch the scenery unfold before your eyes. This is a spectacular sight. Seokgansu, which rises out of the cliffs after the preservation of the cylinder, is an indispensable taste in Jeongbangsagil.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Jiak Jijang Bodhisattva statue carved in the rock wall - Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/218/4cb545fa-ccb7-44bc-94ac-31a34420b9df.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Jiak Jijang Bodhisattva statue carved in the rock wall
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Icygol Ecological Road where ice freezes in the middle of summer
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;span&gt;
    &lt;span&gt;
     The entrance to Neunggang Valley, where Jeongbangsaenggil begins, is also the starting point of the Ice Course, Ice Course, 3 courses. It is a 5.4km section that passes through the stone tower road along the valley and climbs Mandangam and Cheokdae to the ice valley. It is a mysterious natural phenomenon in which ice freezes even in the middle of summer.
    &lt;/span&gt;
   &lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Neunggang Valley at the entrance of Ice Valley (Photo provided by Jecheon City Hall) - Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/218/2c659a82-3441-4062-9c9c-7405b026e81e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Neunggang Valley at the entrance of Ice Valley (Photo provided by Jecheon City Hall)
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   When summer approaches, there are many people who open the valley next to the road and enjoy the Tak. It is because the cool time in the valley is more attractive than hiking. If the ice valley feels far away, it is recommended to walk to the stone tower road. A 20-minute round trip from the valley is enough. The stone tower built on the stone tower road is quite large. Hopefully, the monk of Kumbong Ambassador Geumsuam began to build one by one, and now hundreds of stone towers have been built. The stone tower was erected on a monotonous and boring mountain path, making it a new attraction.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A stone tower road constructed by carefully stacking stones one by one - Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/218/2ef995ed-fa6a-4192-a65f-223838eff706.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A stone tower road constructed by carefully stacking stones one by one
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Jecheon City Hall Tourism Division
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     043-641-6703
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1.Nearby Restaurants
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Geumsusan Trout Market: Trout society / 41 Cheongpungho-ro 39-gil, Geumseong-myeon, Jecheon-si / 043-652-8833
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Zelkova Sashimi House: Trout Bibimbap / 4, Bashiron-ro, Cheongpung-myeon, Jecheon-si / 043-647-0089
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Yechon: Yakchaejeongsik / 30 Cheongpung Myeongwol-ro, Cheongpung-myeon, Jecheon-si / 043-647-3707
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Hama Garden: Chicken Baeksuk / 214-9 Sindam-gil, Geumseong-myeon, Jecheon-si / 043-651-5613
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2.Accommodation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Cheongpung Resort: 1763 Cheongpungho-ro, Cheongpung-myeon, Jecheon-si / 043-640-7000
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cheongpungresort.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;청풍리조트로 이동&#34;&gt;
     http://www.cheongpungresort.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Lake Landscape Pension: 1595-58 Cheongpungho-ro, Geumseong-myeon, Jecheon-si / 043-642-8049
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.greenlake.kr&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     www.greenlake.kr
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Pongnep Pension: Cheongpungho-ro, Cheongpung-myeon, Jecheon-si 2019 / 043-653-5566
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.pontneuf.kr&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     www.pontneuf.kr
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Reed Pension: 439 Cheongpung Myeongwol-ro, Cheongpung-myeon, Jecheon-si / 043-646-6646
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.galipso.com&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     www.galipso.com
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Neunggang Song Pension: 1050, Oksunbong-ro, Susan-myeon, Jecheon-si / 043-651-0033
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was created in May 2013, and may change later, so be sure to check it before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>