<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gangdong-gu on Every Corner of Korea</title>
    <link>https://codecorea.github.io/tags/gangdong-gu/</link>
    <description>Every Corner of Korea (Gangdong-gu)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 13:25:40 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="https://codecorea.github.io/tags/gangdong-gu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Tteokbokki, a delicious snack in the winter - Gangdong-gu, Seoul, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/tteokbokki-a-delicious-snack-in-the-winter-266/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 13:25:40 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/tteokbokki-a-delicious-snack-in-the-winter-266/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Gangdong-gu, Seoul, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;tteokbokki-a-delicious-snack-in-the-winter--266&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Instant Squid Tteokbokki from &amp;lt;One Way Tteokbokki&amp;gt; - Gangdong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/266/16d3d20e-d5ba-4eb0-a82e-76fc040eb87a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Instant Squid Tteokbokki from &amp;lt;One Way Tteokbokki&amp;gt;
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Tteokbokki, a delicious snack in the winter
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Gangdong-gu, Seoul, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The season of Tteokbokki is here. What is the spicy Tteokbokki taste that is eaten through the cold wind and wiping off the sweat that rises at the tip of the nose. Let&#39;s go to the world of infinite Tteokbokki, which is comparable to a solid meal from a national snack. From the restaurant of the memories in front of the school, the tteokbokki that the cool soup tastes awesome and the tteokbokki that the spicy don&#39;t know if they&#39;re stunned are waiting.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    First love The child liked Tteokbokki. When she wanted to see her, she would go around the Tteokbokki shop around the school. Then I could see the child eating Tteokbokki with a happy expression. Sometimes in a Tteokbokki shop next to a stationery store, and sometimes in a street stand in front of the school or in an instant Tteokbokki shop, wherever there was Tteokbokki. Tteokbokki, who was bitten by the thought of seeing the child&#39;s face, stayed with him for a long time after he left school, and kept his face in place of the blurred child.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    I think the pure affection for our national snack “Tteokbokki” might be similar to “first love” or “unrequited love” as a child. It was another delicacy when I ate Tteokbokki, Sundae or Tempura, which I shared with my friend Ha Hak-Gil in the spicy Tteokbokki soup. How can you forget the taste of Tteokbokki and tempura that you sneaked out during the night self-study time? Is it because these perfumes have been piled up and piled up again? Tteokbokki, which was a “snack” at that time, is expanding into a “hanki meal” from a certain moment. In the cold windy season, I would like to draw more tteokbokki that I think more, or tteokbokki that looks like my heart, but the world of tteokbokki is more endless than I thought! So I tried it. Among the many tteokbokki, the main characters selected are garlic tteokbokki &amp;lt;Self House&amp;gt; in front of the school, &amp;lt;one way street tteokbokki&amp;gt;, which is comparable to Haejang, and &amp;lt;Dongdaemun Yeopgi tteokbokki&amp;gt;, spicy and spicy as its name suggests. Wait tteokbokki!
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Dark garlic odor Solsol, in front of Youngpa Girls&#39; High School &amp;lt;Self House&amp;gt;
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &amp;lt;Self House&amp;gt; is located across from Youngpa Girls&#39; High School. It has been a popular food store for over 30 years, making garlic rice cakes that are cheap and serving the rice cakes in the neighborhood in front of Girls&#39; High School. When you open the door, the spicy garlic scent stings your nose. If it is close to school time, high school girls in school uniforms, and other times, customers of various ages, young and old, are seated. Garlic tteokbokki, also known as ‘well-being tteokbokki’ with plenty of garlic, has many tons of middle-aged people because of its added tonic and anti-cancer garlic and national snack tteokbokki.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Garlic Tteokbokki House &amp;lt;Self House&amp;gt; - Gangdong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/266/ae25ed28-09eb-4d15-bb38-c7a0109ee54f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Garlic Tteokbokki House &amp;lt;Self House&amp;gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    It looks like a neat neighborhood cafeteria, but in terms of career, this place, which is more than 30 years old, is remembered as a “cupcake of memory” for graduates of Youngpa Girls&#39; High School. There are still people who come to this store because they haven&#39;t forgotten the taste of it. If you haven&#39;t tasted the Tteokbokki yet, why don&#39;t you smell the garlic flavor this winter? After ordering, it is a system that calculates food first and tastes it. You can taste the fish cake soup only after you make it.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;hemp... - Gangdong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/266/9e026e28-835c-4414-a6a8-2e20636732b6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     hemp...
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Tteokbokki is served in a generous soup with a high viscosity. You can feel the value of garlic tteokbokki by scooping it with tteokbokki soup with a spoon rather than just tasting it. The soft and chewy wheat rice cake and the spicy and spicy sauce fill the mouth gently. The unique texture of wheat rice cake and the bulkiness of the thick sauce create a very nice taste. Garlic is added with pepper, and it is armed with a strong aroma and taste, but it is not bad. For two ordinary women, Sundae and Garlic Tteokbokki for 2,500 won is enough, but Tteokbokki enthusiasts are looking for a 1-person version. All menus can be packed. Closed on Sundays.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Tteokbokki crushed sundae - Gangdong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/266/da4e2ea8-cb8e-44b4-a92c-5d5bebba2358.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Tteokbokki crushed sundae
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p style=&#34;COLOR: #036071&#34;&gt;
    ▶ Subway Line 8 Gangdong-gu Office Station Exit 1 / 02-476-7063 / 10: 00 ~ 21: 30 (Closed on Sundays) / Garlic Tteokbokki 1500 won, 2500 won, 4000 won / Glutinous rice 3,000 won / Fish cake 500 won
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Garlic Tteokbokki - Gangdong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/266/62685b4c-2ac9-4c28-b59d-8cea2a646d8e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Garlic Tteokbokki
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   One whole squid in Haemultang broth &amp;lt;one-sided Tteokbokki&amp;gt;
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &amp;lt;One Way Passing Tteokbokki&amp;gt; is a word of mouth to the tteokbokki enthusiasts. This is a neighborhood Tteokbokki house located at the end of the one-way street behind Gangdong CGV.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Instantly tteokbokki with whole squid, which is a cool broth - Gangdong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/266/edacf1de-bff0-4b0d-914e-79dc7a05417d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Instantly tteokbokki with whole squid, which is a cool broth
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   This place is famous for its instant tteokbokki, which has a cool soup flavor, so it&#39;s a little unusual place for office workers around the world to go through during the daytime. The question of what is the relationship between Tteokbokki and Haejang is solved by listening to the boss&#39;s ex (?) Story. Haemultang restaurant was run before Tteokbokki. Thanks to this, the ingredients used in the seafood soup were added to make the tteokbokki broth.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The cool broth taste is thanks to the boss ’s former job - Gangdong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/266/3bb9a4e3-994b-4975-997e-dd5cd40bbeaf.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The cool broth taste is thanks to the boss ’s former job
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    There are several types of instant Tteokbokki that you can choose according to your preference. The most common assorted instant tteokbokki include ramen, chopped noodles, fish cakes, eggs and dumplings. You can choose whole squid if you want a crispy broth, cheese if you want a soft taste, and instant hotpot rice cake if you want a hot spicy taste. Adding homemade tempura to it, and then adding it to the fried rice, the white rice of the instant Tteokbokki, is a perfect meal.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Soft yet chewy wheat rice cake - Gangdong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/266/5582be7b-2308-4feb-b678-3f6095dec2d9.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Soft yet chewy wheat rice cake
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The spicy yet cool soup tastes like Tteokbokki. In particular, the instant Tteokbokki with whole squid has a great appearance and adds to the fun of eating with your eyes. People from nearby theaters and locals often come for a simple meal. In the small Tteokbokki restaurant, which has about three or four tables, the taste of the Tteokbokki tasted while watching the snow pouring out of the whole glass is awesome.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Fried homemade - Gangdong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/266/a40966b5-1222-4c9d-aad8-9ab628f0fbf0.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Fried homemade
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p style=&#34;COLOR: #036071&#34;&gt;
    ▶ Subway Line 8 Gangdong-gu Office Station Exit 3 / 070-8950-1019 / 11: 00 ~ 21: 30 (Closed on Mondays) / Tteokbokki 2500 won, Sundae 3000 won, Homemade Hand Fried 3000 won, Assorted Instant Tteokbokki (2 persons) 1 11,000 won, Whole squid Instant Tteokbokki 13,000 won, Hot blooded Instant Tteokbokki 11,000 won
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Instant rice cake finish, fried rice! - Gangdong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/266/24bfa058-430f-4ed9-b350-384f4dd4319e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Instant rice cake finish, fried rice!
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   My tongue is tingling and my sweat is cheolcheol! The highest peak of spiciness &amp;lt;Dongdaemun Yeopgi Tteokbokki&amp;gt;
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    If you really want a spicy taste, there is &amp;lt;Dongdaemun Yeopgi Tteokbokki&amp;gt; called &#34;Yeopteok&#34;. The tongue is spicy, but it doesn&#39;t stop and eats. After eating, you should be prepared to go in and out of the bathroom for about a day, but when stress increases, you can always think of &amp;lt;Dongdaemun Yeopgi Tteokbokki&amp;gt;. Some people are angry that there is some spicy, but once you step here, the taste will come back to you someday. The addictive spicy taste is a powerful taste that makes modern people suffering from stress forget all of them for a moment.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Stir-fried tteokbokki, steamed egg and rice ball set - Gangdong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/266/3b3e5b5a-0327-420a-b193-8ba0f962adbb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Stir-fried tteokbokki, steamed egg and rice ball set
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Steamed egg and rice ball are essential, and you have to add slush to it to soothe your mouth endlessly. When sweating, the anxiety disappears and the pain in the mouth and lips remains. Still, the idea of being delicious doesn&#39;t go away. However, no matter how motivated you are, it is better not to eat soup with spoon. Tteokbokki is expensive and high, but it has a lot. Adding one sari is enough for 3-4 people to eat. If you select the set menu, you can taste it at a little cheaper.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Steamed rice balls and eggs to soothe the spiciness - Gangdong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/266/ec471eb5-7639-43fe-8960-f12930d092fb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Steamed rice balls and eggs to soothe the spiciness
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p style=&#34;COLOR: #036071&#34;&gt;
    ▶ Subway Line 2, 6, Sindang Station Exit 10 / 02-2234-8592 / 24 hours / Yeopgi Tteokbokki &amp;amp; Yeopgi Oden from 14,000 won
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;red&#34;&gt;
    ※ The above information was created in December 2013, and may change later, so be sure to check it before you travel.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Tteokbokki with cheese that will soothe the spiciness - Gangdong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/266/fdcdd2c9-67c1-4165-9947-4ccc1c9dbbcb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Tteokbokki with cheese that will soothe the spiciness
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>