<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Yeongam-gun on Korea Tour</title>
    <link>https://codecorea.github.io/tags/yeongam-gun/</link>
    <description>Korea Tour (Yeongam-gun)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 20:08:15 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="https://codecorea.github.io/tags/yeongam-gun/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Yeongam-gun, Чоннам, Корея - Мощность сгорела! Kalaktang, Naejangtang и найм осьминога: освежающее путешествие в Yeongam.</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/power-burned-galaktang-nakjitangtang-and-octopus-horong-a-refreshing-journey-to-yeongam-39-ru/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 20:08:15 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/power-burned-galaktang-nakjitangtang-and-octopus-horong-a-refreshing-journey-to-yeongam-39-ru/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-title=&#34;power-burned-galaktang-nakjitangtang-and-octopus-horong-a-refreshing-journey-to-yeongam--39&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Gal Nak-tang - одно из лакомств Yeongam. - Yeongam-gun, Чоннам, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/39/ce689c6d-2113-4616-b16e-b29d53f2bb72.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Gal Nak-tang - одно из лакомств Yeongam.
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Мощность сгорела! Kalaktang, Naejangtang и найм осьминога: освежающее путешествие в Yeongam.
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Yeongam-gun, Чоннам, Корея
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   «Если вы покормите трех или четырех осьминогов падающей корове, у вас будет сильная сила».
   &lt;br/&gt;
   Это предложение объясняет осьминога в активе. Осьминог, который заставляет упасть упавшую корову. Прозвище «морской женьшень» содержит большое количество таурина и гистидина, которые превосходны в тониках. Это причина, почему он стал известен как выносливость для усталых людей. Сегодня мы отправились в освежающую поездку в Докчхон в Йонгаме, Чолланам-до, известную как «улица Осьминога». Обилие весенних пейзажей в Южной Корее является бонусом.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Племенной осьминог, подарок обильных южных островов приливных квартир
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Йонгам-гун, с его богатыми приливными квартирами в Намдо, был известен своим племенным осьминогом. Если вы посмотрите на карту некоторое время, Йонгам расположен вдоль западного побережья Восточного моря, которое ведет к Мокпо вдоль Хампёнга и Муана, которые также известны своим осьминогом из племени. Неудивительно, что трехголовый осьминог прославился на Земле Йонгам, где соленые и пресные воды западного побережья смешались вдоль ствола реки Йонсан в Намдо. Строительство реки Йонгсан Хаготдук в настоящее время утратило репутацию горного осьминога, производящего горы. Это потому, что однажды рай для осьминога был создан благодаря разработке различных рецептов для осьминога.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Улица Осьминог, ведущая к Докчеон 5-дневный рынок - Yeongam-gun, Чоннам, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/39/c13d11bc-aa77-4e03-b9e2-4225ad4308b7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Улица Осьминог, ведущая к Докчеон 5-дневный рынок
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Dokcheon Octopus Street находится в Докчеон-ри, Хаксан-Мён, Йонгам-гун, Чоннам. Более 30 специализированных магазинов осьминогов следуют за 5-дневным рынком Dokcheon. 5-дневный рынок Dokcheon, который проводится 4 и 9 числа каждого месяца, также является обязательным. Это место, где находилось пять или шесть специализированных магазинов осьминога, стало такой же улицей осьминога, поскольку люди собирались из уст в уста. Помимо говяжьих отбивных и говяжьего осьминога, они также предлагают разнообразные блюда из осьминога, включая Yeonpotang, Octopus Horong и Mountain Octopus.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Десятки магазинов осьминога - Yeongam-gun, Чоннам, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/39/57778b7c-5532-4fd6-93e9-147b63af50f2.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Десятки магазинов осьминога
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Племенной осьминог с восемью тонкими ногами, какой вкус?
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Прежде чем попробовать осьминога, давайте посмотрим на личность трехфутового осьминога. Что такое племенной осьминог? Когда я был молодым, я думал, что «трехметровый осьминог» был трехметровым осьминогом. Хотя я иногда смотрел по телевизору целого племенного осьминога, не было никаких сомнений, что его ноги будут &#34;тремя&#34;. Вера продолжалась, пока мы не поняли, что налог в трехметровом осьминоге был не налогом, а налогом.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Племенной осьминог, обычно называемый осьминогом, маленький, но нежный и имеет вкус на вкус. Целого или приготовленного осьминога можно попробовать, накрутив его на деревянные палочки для еды. Конечно, вы должны жевать осьминога, который говорит вам, что он все еще жив во рту.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Вкус Хансанга в специализированном магазине осьминога в Докчеоне Осьминог - Yeongam-gun, Чоннам, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/39/20509b1b-df2a-45f2-b5f1-c0a42ee6dfe6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Вкус Хансанга в специализированном магазине осьминога в Докчеоне Осьминог
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Свежее кунжутное масло, добавленное в кунжутное масло, восхитительно, но рецепты племенного осьминога разнообразны. Давайте разбить его на сырую и приготовленную пищу. В зависимости от вашего вкуса, он может немного отличаться, но вы должны попробовать живой осьминог. Сладкая и жевательная текстура жива. Он маленький и мягкий, поэтому его легко есть в сыром виде. В дополнение к осьминогу Tangtang (осьминога, вырезанного так, чтобы его было легко есть), некоторые из специализированных магазинов осьминога в Докчеоне выпускаются с насыщенным племенным осьминогом.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Накджитанг-тан нарезать живого осьминога - Yeongam-gun, Чоннам, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/39/0dc7c3c1-820e-4062-958e-ed54e18dad4f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Накджитанг-тан нарезать живого осьминога
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Вареные блюда из осьминога включают жареного осьминога, жареного осьминога и жареного осьминога, а также горячие блюда, представленные gal-nak и yeonpo-tang. Осьминог Хоронг - это пища, которую готовят, катаясь вокруг трех голов осьминога из палочек для еды. Испечь соус и запечь. В дополнение к обжаренному осьминогу и маринованному с редькой, добавляют Gal Naktang и Yeonpo Tang, которые считаются представителями Yeongam. Давайте внимательнее посмотрим на Гал Нактанг, одно из лакомств Йонгама.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Жареный осьминог с деревянными палочками - Yeongam-gun, Чоннам, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/39/1148f74d-23b2-46a6-b8af-87d936d08c62.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Жареный осьминог с деревянными палочками
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Yeongam Delicacy Суперзвезда, Гал Нактанг
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Galactam. Как следует из названия, это суп с ребрами и осьминогом. Если Yeonpotang варят только с осьминогом, говяжьи ребра добавляются к Galnaktang. Осьминог - это обильное место, осьминог, использующий осьминога, развился бы. Но откуда взялись ребра? Независимо от того, как вы думаете об этом, осьминог и ребра, кажется, не имеют значения.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Шпатель, Гал-Нактанг - Yeongam-gun, Чоннам, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/39/e2bc872a-0a47-44c2-84a3-3d42d3aff346.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Шпатель, Гал-Нактанг
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Любопытство было освобождено от названия деревни Докчеон. Это потому, что Деревня Докчеон вышла из «Яда телят». Деревня Докчеон была деревней, которая разводит хороший скот. Благодаря этому магазины осьминога продали свои ребра. Затем, когда цены на коров упали, они приготовили «Галлак-тан», который наполнен осьминогом, и вкус был удивительным. Ребра и осьминог встретятся, мясо станет мягче, а суп будет холоднее. Кроме того, две пищи, представляющие землю и море, встретились, поэтому не попали в пищу. Море и земля встречаются с Галумнактангом, который основан на его вкусе и питательных веществах.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Yeonpo-tang, приготовленный целиком в осьминоге - Yeongam-gun, Чоннам, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/39/e78de64f-66ac-4e64-912d-27a4b76ada74.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Yeonpo-tang, приготовленный целиком в осьминоге
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Где я могу попробовать коричневый лак и осьминога? На Dokcheon Octopus Street есть около 30 специализированных магазинов осьминогов, в том числе Dokcheon Restaurant, Haenam Restaurant и Jeonju Restaurant. Галнактанг и Йонпотанг стоят от 17 000 до 19 000 вон, в то время как корейские блюда, такие как суп из осьминога, жареный жареный осьминог и жареный осьминог, варьируются от 30 000 до 50 000 вон. Цена на еду варьируется незначительно в зависимости от размеров крупных, средних, маленьких и каждого магазина.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Осьминог Yeonpo-tang с мягкой текстурой - Yeongam-gun, Чоннам, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/39/aa5b1d41-c8a5-4fce-aeb1-30a85299a8dd.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Осьминог Yeonpo-tang с мягкой текстурой
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Информация о путешествии
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Близлежащие рестораны
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Ресторан Dokcheon: Докчеон-ро, Хаксан-Мён / Гал Нактанг, Осьминог / 061-472-4222
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.nakji1970.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.nakji1970.com/
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Зеленый ресторан: Докчеон-ро, Хаксан-Мён / Накджи-ри / 061-472-4128
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Cheil Octopus Yard: Докчеон-ри, Хаксан-Мён / Ресторан Осьминог / 061-472-3729
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Ресторан Nangju: Haksan-myeon Dokcheon-ri / Ресторан Octopus / 061-472-6925
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Размещение
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Илим Джаэмин B &amp;amp; B: Hakam-gil, Gunseo-myeon / 061-471-3104
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://cafe.daum.net/elimjai&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://cafe.daum.net/elimjai
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    На душу населения: Mojeong 1-gil, Gunseo-myeon / 061-471-7675
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.moonprint.co.kr/Index.aspx&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.moonprint.co.kr/Index.aspx
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Отель Hyundai: Daebul-ro, Samho-eup / 061-463-2233
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ Приведенная выше информация была обновлена в июне 2016 года. Впоследствии она может измениться, поэтому, пожалуйста, проверьте это перед поездкой.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Информация, такая как текст, фотографии и видео, используемые в этой статье, защищены авторским правом Корейской туристической организации, поэтому несанкционированное использование статьи запрещено.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yeongam-gun, Jeonnam, Corée - Puissance brûlée! Kalaktang, Naejangtang et Octopus Hiring: Un voyage rafraîchissant à Yeongam.</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/power-burned-galaktang-nakjitangtang-and-octopus-horong-a-refreshing-journey-to-yeongam-39-fr/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 20:06:06 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/power-burned-galaktang-nakjitangtang-and-octopus-horong-a-refreshing-journey-to-yeongam-39-fr/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-title=&#34;power-burned-galaktang-nakjitangtang-and-octopus-horong-a-refreshing-journey-to-yeongam--39&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Gal Nak-tang est l&#39;une des spécialités de Yeongam. - Yeongam-gun, Jeonnam, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/39/ce689c6d-2113-4616-b16e-b29d53f2bb72.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Gal Nak-tang est l&#39;une des spécialités de Yeongam.
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Puissance brûlée! Kalaktang, Naejangtang et Octopus Hiring: Un voyage rafraîchissant à Yeongam.
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Yeongam-gun, Jeonnam, Corée
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &#34;Si vous nourrissez trois ou quatre poulpes à une vache qui tombe, vous aurez un fort pouvoir.&#34;
   &lt;br/&gt;
   Ceci est une phrase expliquant Octopus dans Asset Asset. Une pieuvre qui fait sauter une vache tombée. Le surnom de «ginseng de mer» a une teneur élevée en taurine et histidine, qui est excellente en tonique. C&#39;est la raison pour laquelle il est devenu célèbre comme aliment d&#39;endurance pour les personnes fatiguées. Aujourd&#39;hui, nous avons fait un voyage rafraîchissant à Dokcheon à Yeongam, Jeollanam-do, connue sous le nom de «Octopus Street». L&#39;abondance de paysages printaniers en Corée du Sud est un bonus.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Tribal Octopus, un cadeau de marées abondantes de l&#39;île du sud
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Yeongam-gun, avec ses riches marées à Namdo, était célèbre pour sa pieuvre tribale. Si vous regardez la carte pendant un certain temps, Yeongam est situé le long de la côte ouest de la mer de l&#39;Est, qui mène à Mokpo le long de Hampyeong et de Muan, qui sont également célèbres pour leur poulpe tribal. Il n&#39;est pas étonnant que la pieuvre à trois têtes soit devenue célèbre dans la terre de Yeongam, où les eaux salées et fraîches de la côte ouest ont été mélangées le long de la tige de la rivière Yeongsan à Namdo. La construction de la rivière Yeongsan Hagotduk a maintenant perdu sa réputation de poulpe tribal produisant des montagnes. En effet, un jour, le paradis du poulpe a été créé par le développement de diverses recettes de poulpe.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Octopus street menant au marché de 5 jours de Dokcheon - Yeongam-gun, Jeonnam, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/39/c13d11bc-aa77-4e03-b9e2-4225ad4308b7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Octopus street menant au marché de 5 jours de Dokcheon
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   La rue Dokcheon Octopus est située à Dokcheon-ri, Haksan-myeon, Yeongam-gun, Jeonnam. Plus de 30 magasins spécialisés dans le poulpe suivent le marché de 5 jours de Dokcheon. Le marché de 5 jours de Dokcheon, qui a lieu tous les 4 et 9 de chaque mois, est également un incontournable. Cet endroit, où se trouvaient cinq ou six magasins spécialisés dans le poulpe, est devenu la même rue du poulpe depuis que les gens se rassemblaient de bouche à oreille. En plus des côtelettes de boeuf et du poulpe de boeuf, ils offrent également une variété de plats de poulpe, y compris Yeonpotang, Octopus Horong et Mountain Octopus.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Des dizaines de magasins de poulpe - Yeongam-gun, Jeonnam, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/39/57778b7c-5532-4fd6-93e9-147b63af50f2.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Des dizaines de magasins de poulpe
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Poulpe tribal à huit pattes fines, quel goût?
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Avant de goûter la pieuvre, jetons un coup d&#39;œil à l&#39;identité de la pieuvre de trois pieds. Qu&#39;est-ce qu&#39;une pieuvre tribale? Quand j&#39;étais jeune, je pensais que «poulpe de trois pieds» était une pieuvre de trois pieds. Même si je regardais parfois toute une pieuvre tribale à la télévision, il ne faisait aucun doute que ses pieds seraient «trois». La foi a continué jusqu&#39;à ce que nous réalisions que la taxe dans le poulpe de trois pieds n&#39;était pas une taxe, mais une taxe.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   La pieuvre tribale, communément appelée 뻘 pieuvre, est petite mais tendre et a un goût gustatif. La pieuvre entière ou cuite peut être dégustée en la roulant sur des baguettes en bois. Bien sûr, vous devez mâcher la pieuvre, qui vous dit qu&#39;elle est toujours vivante dans votre bouche.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Le goût de Hansang dans le magasin spécialisé de poulpe à Dokcheon Octopus - Yeongam-gun, Jeonnam, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/39/20509b1b-df2a-45f2-b5f1-c0a42ee6dfe6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Le goût de Hansang dans le magasin spécialisé de poulpe à Dokcheon Octopus
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   L&#39;huile de sésame fraîche ajoutée à l&#39;huile de sésame est délicieuse, mais les recettes tribales de poulpe sont variées. Décomposons-le en aliments crus et cuits. Selon votre goût, cela peut être un peu différent, mais votre première main est de goûter des poulpes vivants. La texture douce et moelleuse est vivante. Il est petit et doux, il est donc facile à manger cru. En plus de la pieuvre Tangtang (une pieuvre conçue pour être facile à manger), certains des magasins spécialisés dans la pieuvre à Dokcheon proposent une pieuvre tribale corsée.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Nakjitang-tang coupé en poulpe vivant - Yeongam-gun, Jeonnam, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/39/0dc7c3c1-820e-4062-958e-ed54e18dad4f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Nakjitang-tang coupé en poulpe vivant
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Les plats de poulpe bouillis comprennent le poulpe grillé, le poulpe sauté et le poulpe rôti, ainsi que les plats à trempette représentés par gal-nak et yeonpo-tang. Octopus horong est un aliment qui est cuit en roulant autour de trois têtes de poulpe à partir de baguettes. Cuire la sauce et cuire. En plus de la pieuvre sautée et marinée avec du radis, Gal Naktang et Yeonpo Tang, qui sont considérés comme des représentants de Yeongam, sont ajoutés. Examinons de plus près Gal Naktang, l&#39;une des spécialités de Yeongam.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Poulpe rôti avec des baguettes en bois - Yeongam-gun, Jeonnam, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/39/1148f74d-23b2-46a6-b8af-87d936d08c62.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Poulpe rôti avec des baguettes en bois
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Yeongam Delicacy Superstar, Gal Naktang
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Galactam. Comme son nom l&#39;indique, c&#39;est une soupe aux côtes levées et au poulpe. Si le Yeonpotang est bouilli uniquement avec du poulpe, les côtes de boeuf sont ajoutées au Galnaktang. Le poulpe est un endroit abondant, le poulpe utilisant le poulpe se serait développé. Mais d&#39;où venaient les côtes? Peu importe comment vous en pensez, le poulpe et les côtes ne semblent pas avoir d&#39;importance.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Spatule, Gal-naktang - Yeongam-gun, Jeonnam, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/39/e2bc872a-0a47-44c2-84a3-3d42d3aff346.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Spatule, Gal-naktang
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   La curiosité a été libérée du nom du village de Dokcheon. C&#39;est parce que le village de Dokcheon est sorti du «poison de veau». Le village de Dokcheon était un village qui élève du bon bétail. Grâce à cela, les magasins de poulpe ont vendu leurs côtes levées. Puis, comme le prix des vaches a chuté, ils ont cuisiné du «Gallak-tang», qui est rempli de poulpe, et le goût était incroyable. Les côtes levées et la pieuvre se rencontreront, la viande sera plus douce et la soupe plus fraîche. De plus, les deux aliments représentant la terre et la mer se sont rencontrés, ils ne sont donc pas tombés dans la nourriture. La mer et la terre rencontrent le Galumnaktang, qui est basé sur son goût et ses nutriments.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Yeonpo-tang entièrement cuit en poulpe - Yeongam-gun, Jeonnam, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/39/e78de64f-66ac-4e64-912d-27a4b76ada74.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Yeonpo-tang entièrement cuit en poulpe
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Où puis-je goûter la laque brune et la pieuvre? Il y a environ 30 magasins spécialisés dans le poulpe dans la rue Dokcheon Octopus, y compris le restaurant Dokcheon, le restaurant Haenam et le restaurant Jeonju. Le galnaktang et le yeonpotang coûtent entre 17 000 wons et 19 000 wons, tandis que les plats coréens tels que la soupe de poulpe, le poulpe rôti à long rôti et le poulpe frit varient de 30 000 wons à 50 000 wons. Le prix des aliments varie légèrement en fonction de la taille du grand, du moyen, du petit et de chaque magasin.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Octopus Yeonpo-tang avec une texture douce - Yeongam-gun, Jeonnam, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/39/aa5b1d41-c8a5-4fce-aeb1-30a85299a8dd.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Octopus Yeonpo-tang avec une texture douce
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Info voyage
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Restaurants à proximité
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Restaurant Dokcheon: Dokcheon-ro, Haksan-myeon / Gal Naktang, Octopus / 061-472-4222
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.nakji1970.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.nakji1970.com/
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Restaurant vert: Dokcheon-ro, Haksan-myeon / Nakji-ri / 061-472-4128
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Yard Octopus Yard: Dokcheon-ri, Haksan-myeon / Octopus Restaurant / 061-472-3729
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Restaurant Nangju: Haksan-myeon Dokcheon-ri / Restaurant Octopus / 061-472-6925
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Hébergement
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Ilim Jaemin B &amp;amp; B: Hakam-gil, Gunseo-myeon / 061-471-3104
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://cafe.daum.net/elimjai&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://cafe.daum.net/elimjai
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Par habitant: Mojeong 1-gil, Gunseo-myeon / 061-471-7675
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.moonprint.co.kr/Index.aspx&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.moonprint.co.kr/Index.aspx
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Hôtel Hyundai: Daebul-ro, Samho-eup / 061-463-2233
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ Les informations ci-dessus ont été mises à jour en juin 2016. Elles peuvent changer par la suite, veuillez donc vérifier avant de voyager.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Les informations telles que le texte, les photos et les vidéos utilisées dans cet article sont protégées par les droits d&#39;auteur de l&#39;Organisation coréenne du tourisme, de sorte que l&#39;utilisation non autorisée de l&#39;article est interdite.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yeongam-gun, Jeonnam, Corea - ¡Poder quemado! Contratación de Kalaktang, Naejangtang y Octopus: un viaje refrescante a Yeongam.</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/power-burned-galaktang-nakjitangtang-and-octopus-horong-a-refreshing-journey-to-yeongam-39-es/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 20:03:58 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/power-burned-galaktang-nakjitangtang-and-octopus-horong-a-refreshing-journey-to-yeongam-39-es/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-title=&#34;power-burned-galaktang-nakjitangtang-and-octopus-horong-a-refreshing-journey-to-yeongam--39&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Gal Nak-tang es una de las delicias de Yeongam. - Yeongam-gun, Jeonnam, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/39/ce689c6d-2113-4616-b16e-b29d53f2bb72.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Gal Nak-tang es una de las delicias de Yeongam.
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   ¡Poder quemado! Contratación de Kalaktang, Naejangtang y Octopus: un viaje refrescante a Yeongam.
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Yeongam-gun, Jeonnam, Corea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &#34;Si le das de comer tres o cuatro pulpos a una vaca que cae, tendrás un gran poder&#34;.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   Esta es una oración que explica Octopus en Asset Asset. Un pulpo que hace saltar a una vaca caída. El apodo de &#34;ginseng marino&#34; tiene un alto contenido de taurina e histidina, que es excelente en tónicos. Es la razón por la que se hizo famoso como alimento de resistencia para las personas cansadas. Hoy fuimos a un refrescante viaje a Dokcheon en Yeongam, Jeollanam-do, conocida como &#39;Octopus Street&#39;. La abundancia de paisajes de primavera en Corea del Sur es una ventaja.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Pulpo tribal, un regalo de abundantes llanuras de marea de las islas del sur
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Yeongam-gun, con sus ricas planicies de marea en Namdo, era famoso por su pulpo tribal. Si miras el mapa por un tiempo, Yeongam se encuentra a lo largo de la costa oeste del Mar del Este, que conduce a Mokpo a lo largo de Hampyeong y Muan, que también son famosos por su pulpo tribal. No es de extrañar que el pulpo de tres cabezas se hizo famoso en Yeongam Land, donde las aguas saladas y frescas de la costa oeste se mezclaron a lo largo del tallo del río Yeongsan en Namdo. La construcción del río Yeongsan Hagotduk ahora ha perdido su reputación como una montaña que produce pulpo tribal. Esto se debe a que un día, el paraíso del pulpo fue creado por el desarrollo de varias recetas de pulpo.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Calle del pulpo que conduce al mercado de 5 días de Dokcheon - Yeongam-gun, Jeonnam, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/39/c13d11bc-aa77-4e03-b9e2-4225ad4308b7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Calle del pulpo que conduce al mercado de 5 días de Dokcheon
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   La calle Dokcheon Octopus se encuentra en Dokcheon-ri, Haksan-myeon, Yeongam-gun, Jeonnam. Más de 30 tiendas especializadas en pulpo siguen el mercado de 5 días de Dokcheon. El mercado de 5 días de Dokcheon, que se celebra cada 4 y 9 de cada mes, también es una visita obligada. Este lugar, donde se ubicaban cinco o seis tiendas especializadas en pulpo, se convirtió en la misma calle de pulpo desde que la gente se reunió de boca en boca. Además de las chuletas y el pulpo de res, también ofrecen una variedad de platos de pulpo, incluidos Yeonpotang, Octopus Horong y Mountain Octopus.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Docenas de tiendas de pulpo - Yeongam-gun, Jeonnam, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/39/57778b7c-5532-4fd6-93e9-147b63af50f2.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Docenas de tiendas de pulpo
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Pulpo tribal con ocho patas delgadas, ¿qué gusto?
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Antes de probar el pulpo, echemos un vistazo a la identidad del pulpo de tres pies. ¿Qué es un pulpo tribal? Cuando era joven, pensaba que &#39;pulpo de tres pies&#39; era un pulpo de tres pies. Aunque a veces veía un pulpo tribal entero en la televisión, no había duda de que sus pies serían &#34;tres&#34;. La fe continuó hasta que nos dimos cuenta de que el impuesto en el pulpo de tres pies no era un impuesto, sino un impuesto.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   El pulpo tribal, comúnmente llamado 뻘 pulpo, es pequeño pero tierno y tiene un sabor del gusto. El pulpo entero o cocido se puede probar rodando sobre palillos de madera. Por supuesto, debes masticar el pulpo, que te dice que todavía está vivo en tu boca.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;El gusto de Hansang en la tienda especializada de pulpo en Dokcheon Octopus - Yeongam-gun, Jeonnam, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/39/20509b1b-df2a-45f2-b5f1-c0a42ee6dfe6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     El gusto de Hansang en la tienda especializada de pulpo en Dokcheon Octopus
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   El aceite de sésamo fresco agregado al aceite de sésamo es delicioso, pero las recetas tribales de pulpo son variadas. Vamos a dividirlo en alimentos crudos y cocidos. Dependiendo de su gusto, puede ser un poco diferente, pero su primera mano es probar el pulpo vivo. La textura dulce y masticable está viva. Es pequeño y suave, por lo que es fácil comerlo crudo. Además del pulpo Tangtang (un pulpo cortado para ser fácil de comer), algunas de las tiendas especializadas en pulpo de Dokcheon tienen un pulpo tribal con cuerpo.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Nakjitang-tang cortado en pulpo vivo - Yeongam-gun, Jeonnam, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/39/0dc7c3c1-820e-4062-958e-ed54e18dad4f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Nakjitang-tang cortado en pulpo vivo
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Los platos de pulpo hervido incluyen pulpo a la parrilla, pulpo salteado y pulpo asado, así como platos de salsa caliente representados por gal-nak y yeonpo-tang. Octopus horong es un alimento que se cocina enrollando alrededor de tres cabezas de pulpo de los palillos. Hornee la salsa y hornee. Además del pulpo salteado y marinado con rábano, se agregan Gal Naktang y Yeonpo Tang, que se consideran representantes de Yeongam. Echemos un vistazo más de cerca a Gal Naktang, una de las delicias de Yeongam.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Pulpo asado con palillos de madera - Yeongam-gun, Jeonnam, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/39/1148f74d-23b2-46a6-b8af-87d936d08c62.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Pulpo asado con palillos de madera
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Yeongam Delicacy Superstar, Gal Naktang
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Galactama Como su nombre indica, es una sopa con costillas y pulpo. Si Yeonpotang se hierve solo con pulpo, las costillas de ternera se agregan a Galnaktang. El pulpo es un lugar abundante, el pulpo que utiliza el pulpo se habría desarrollado. ¿Pero de dónde vienen las costillas? No importa cómo lo pienses, el pulpo y las costillas no parecen importar.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Espátula, Gal-naktang - Yeongam-gun, Jeonnam, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/39/e2bc872a-0a47-44c2-84a3-3d42d3aff346.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Espátula, Gal-naktang
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   La curiosidad fue liberada del nombre de Dokcheon Village. Esto se debe a que Dokcheon Village salió del &#34;Veneno para terneros&#34;. Dokcheon Village era un pueblo que cría buen ganado. Gracias a esto, las tiendas de pulpo vendieron sus costillas. Luego, cuando el precio de las vacas se desplomó, cocinaron &#34;Gallak-tang&#34;, que está lleno de pulpo, y el sabor fue increíble. Las costillas y el pulpo se encontrarán, la carne estará más suave y la sopa estará más fresca. Además, los dos alimentos que representan la tierra y el mar se encontraron, por lo que no cayeron en la comida. El mar y la tierra se encuentran con Galumnaktang, que se basa en su sabor y nutrientes.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Yeonpo-tang cocinado enteramente en pulpo - Yeongam-gun, Jeonnam, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/39/e78de64f-66ac-4e64-912d-27a4b76ada74.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Yeonpo-tang cocinado enteramente en pulpo
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   ¿Dónde puedo probar la laca marrón y el pulpo? Hay alrededor de 30 tiendas especializadas en pulpo en Dokcheon Octopus Street, que incluyen el restaurante Dokcheon, el restaurante Haenam y el restaurante Jeonju. Galnaktang y Yeonpotang cuestan entre 17,000 y 19,000 wones, mientras que los platos coreanos como la sopa de pulpo, el pulpo asado y el pulpo frito varían de 30,000 a 50,000 wones. El precio de los alimentos varía ligeramente según el tamaño de los grandes, medianos, pequeños y de cada tienda.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Pulpo Yeonpo-tang con una textura suave - Yeongam-gun, Jeonnam, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/39/aa5b1d41-c8a5-4fce-aeb1-30a85299a8dd.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Pulpo Yeonpo-tang con una textura suave
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Información de viaje
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Restaurantes cercanos
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Restaurante Dokcheon: Dokcheon-ro, Haksan-myeon / Gal Naktang, Octopus / 061-472-4222
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.nakji1970.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.nakji1970.com/
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Restaurante Verde: Dokcheon-ro, Haksan-myeon / Nakji-ri / 061-472-4128
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Cheil Octopus Yard: Dokcheon-ri, Haksan-myeon / Octopus Restaurant / 061-472-3729
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Restaurante Nangju: Haksan-myeon Dokcheon-ri / Restaurante Octopus / 061-472-6925
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Alojamiento
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Ilim Jaemin B &amp;amp; B: Hakam-gil, Gunseo-myeon / 061-471-3104
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://cafe.daum.net/elimjai&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://cafe.daum.net/elimjai
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Per cápita: Mojeong 1-gil, Gunseo-myeon / 061-471-7675
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.moonprint.co.kr/Index.aspx&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.moonprint.co.kr/Index.aspx
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Hotel Hyundai: Daebul-ro, Samho-eup / 061-463-2233
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ La información anterior se actualizó en junio de 2016. Puede cambiar después, así que verifique antes de viajar.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ La información como texto, fotos y videos utilizados en este artículo tiene copyright de la Organización de Turismo de Corea, por lo que está prohibido el uso no autorizado del artículo.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yeongam-gun, Jeonnam, Korea - Strom verbrannt! Kalaktang, Naejangtang und Octopus Hiring: Eine erfrischende Reise nach Yeongam.</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/power-burned-galaktang-nakjitangtang-and-octopus-horong-a-refreshing-journey-to-yeongam-39-de/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 20:01:40 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/power-burned-galaktang-nakjitangtang-and-octopus-horong-a-refreshing-journey-to-yeongam-39-de/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-title=&#34;power-burned-galaktang-nakjitangtang-and-octopus-horong-a-refreshing-journey-to-yeongam--39&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Gal Nak-tang ist eine der Köstlichkeiten von Yeongam. - Yeongam-gun, Jeonnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/39/ce689c6d-2113-4616-b16e-b29d53f2bb72.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Gal Nak-tang ist eine der Köstlichkeiten von Yeongam.
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Strom verbrannt! Kalaktang, Naejangtang und Octopus Hiring: Eine erfrischende Reise nach Yeongam.
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Yeongam-gun, Jeonnam, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &#34;Wenn Sie einer fallenden Kuh drei oder vier Tintenfische füttern, haben Sie eine starke Kraft.&#34;
   &lt;br/&gt;
   Dies ist ein Satz, der Octopus in Asset Asset erklärt. Ein Tintenfisch, der eine gefallene Kuh aufspringen lässt. Der Spitzname &#34;Sea Ginseng&#34; hat einen hohen Gehalt an Taurin und Histidin, was in Tonika ausgezeichnet ist. Es ist der Grund, warum es als Ausdauerfutter für müde Menschen berühmt wurde. Heute machten wir eine erfrischende Reise nach Dokcheon in Yeongam, Jeollanam-do, bekannt als &#34;Octopus Street&#34;. Die Fülle der Frühlingslandschaften in Südkorea ist ein Bonus.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Tribal Octopus, ein Geschenk reichlich vorhandener Wattflächen auf der Südinsel
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Yeongam-gun mit seinen reichen Wattflächen in Namdo war berühmt für seinen Stammeskraken. Wenn Sie sich die Karte für eine Weile ansehen, befindet sich Yeongam an der Westküste der Ostsee, die entlang Hampyeong und Muan nach Mokpo führt, die auch für ihren Stammeskraken bekannt sind. Es ist kein Wunder, dass der dreiköpfige Tintenfisch im Yeongam Land berühmt wurde, wo salziges und frisches Wasser der Westküste entlang des Stammes des Yeongsan in Namdo gemischt wurden. Der Bau des Hagongduk am Yeongsan hat inzwischen seinen Ruf als Bergkraken verloren. Dies liegt daran, dass eines Tages das Oktopus-Paradies durch die Entwicklung verschiedener Oktopus-Rezepte geschaffen wurde.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Octopus Street führt zum Dokcheon 5-Tage-Markt - Yeongam-gun, Jeonnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/39/c13d11bc-aa77-4e03-b9e2-4225ad4308b7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Octopus Street führt zum Dokcheon 5-Tage-Markt
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Die Dokcheon Octopus Street befindet sich in Dokcheon-ri, Haksan-myeon, Yeongam-gun, Jeonnam. Mehr als 30 Octopus-Fachgeschäfte folgen dem 5-Tage-Markt von Dokcheon. Der 5-Tage-Markt von Dokcheon, der jeden 4. und 9. eines jeden Monats stattfindet, ist ebenfalls ein Muss. Dieser Ort, an dem sich fünf oder sechs Octopus-Fachgeschäfte befanden, wurde zur gleichen Octopus-Straße, da sich die Menschen mündlich versammelten. Neben Rindfleischkoteletts und Rindfleischkraken bieten sie auch eine Vielzahl von Tintenfischgerichten an, darunter Yeonpotang, Octopus Horong und Mountain Octopus.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Dutzende von Tintenfischgeschäften - Yeongam-gun, Jeonnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/39/57778b7c-5532-4fd6-93e9-147b63af50f2.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Dutzende von Tintenfischgeschäften
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Stammeskrake mit acht dünnen Beinen, welcher Geschmack?
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Bevor wir den Oktopus probieren, werfen wir einen Blick auf die Identität des drei Fuß großen Oktopus. Was ist ein Stammeskrake? Als ich jung war, dachte ich, &#39;Drei-Fuß-Tintenfisch&#39; sei ein Drei-Fuß-Tintenfisch. Obwohl ich manchmal einen ganzen Stammeskraken im Fernsehen sah, gab es keinen Zweifel daran, dass seine Füße &#34;drei&#34; sein würden. Der Glaube ging weiter, bis wir erkannten, dass die Steuer im Drei-Fuß-Oktopus keine Steuer war, sondern eine Steuer.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Tribal Octopus, allgemein als 뻘 Octopus bezeichnet, ist klein, aber zart und schmeckt nach Geschmack. Ganze oder gekochte Tintenfische können durch Rollen auf Holzstäbchen verkostet werden. Natürlich müssen Sie auf dem Tintenfisch kauen, was Ihnen sagt, dass er in Ihrem Mund noch lebt.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Hansangs Geschmack im Octopus-Fachgeschäft in Dokcheon Octopus - Yeongam-gun, Jeonnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/39/20509b1b-df2a-45f2-b5f1-c0a42ee6dfe6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Hansangs Geschmack im Octopus-Fachgeschäft in Dokcheon Octopus
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Frisches Sesamöl, das dem Sesamöl zugesetzt wird, ist köstlich, aber die Rezepte für Stammeskraken sind vielfältig. Lassen Sie es uns in rohes und gekochtes Essen zerlegen. Abhängig von Ihrem Geschmack mag es etwas anders sein, aber Ihre erste Hand ist es, lebenden Tintenfisch zu probieren. Süße und zähe Textur lebt. Es ist klein und weich, so dass es leicht roh zu essen ist. Neben dem Tintenfisch Tangtang (ein Tintenfisch, der leicht zu essen ist) bieten einige der Tintenfischfachgeschäfte in Dokcheon einen vollmundigen Stammeskraken an.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Nakjitang-Tang in lebenden Tintenfisch geschnitten - Yeongam-gun, Jeonnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/39/0dc7c3c1-820e-4062-958e-ed54e18dad4f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Nakjitang-Tang in lebenden Tintenfisch geschnitten
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Zu den gekochten Tintenfischgerichten gehören gegrillter Tintenfisch, gebratener Tintenfisch und gerösteter Tintenfisch sowie Hot-Dip-Gerichte, die durch Gal-Nak und Yeonpo-Tang repräsentiert werden. Octopus Horong ist ein Lebensmittel, das durch Rollen von drei Tintenfischköpfen aus Stäbchen gekocht wird. Sauce backen und backen. Zusätzlich zu dem mit Radieschen gebratenen und marinierten Tintenfisch werden Gal Naktang und Yeonpo Tang hinzugefügt, die als Vertreter von Yeongam gelten. Schauen wir uns Gal Naktang, eine der Köstlichkeiten von Yeongam, genauer an.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Gebratener Tintenfisch mit Holzstäbchen - Yeongam-gun, Jeonnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/39/1148f74d-23b2-46a6-b8af-87d936d08c62.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Gebratener Tintenfisch mit Holzstäbchen
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Yeongam Delikatesse Superstar, Gal Naktang
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Galactam. Wie der Name schon sagt, handelt es sich um eine Suppe mit Rippen und Tintenfisch. Wenn Yeonpotang nur mit Tintenfisch gekocht wird, werden die Rindfleischrippen zu Galnaktang hinzugefügt. Oktopus ist reichlich vorhanden, der Oktopus, der den Oktopus verwendet, hätte sich entwickelt. Aber woher kamen die Rippen? Egal wie Sie darüber denken, Tintenfisch und Rippen scheinen keine Rolle zu spielen.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Spatel, Gal-Naktang - Yeongam-gun, Jeonnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/39/e2bc872a-0a47-44c2-84a3-3d42d3aff346.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Spatel, Gal-Naktang
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Die Neugier wurde aus dem Namen Dokcheon Village befreit. Dies liegt daran, dass Dokcheon Village aus dem „Calf Poison“ hervorgegangen ist. Dokcheon Village war ein Dorf, in dem gutes Vieh aufgezogen wird. Dank dessen verkauften die Tintenfischläden ihre Rippen. Dann, als der Preis für Kühe sank, kochten sie „Gallak-Tang“, der mit Tintenfisch gefüllt ist, und der Geschmack war erstaunlich. Die Rippen und der Tintenfisch treffen sich, das Fleisch wird weicher und die Suppe wird kühler. Außerdem trafen sich die beiden Lebensmittel, die das Land und das Meer repräsentierten, und fielen daher nicht in das Lebensmittel. Das Meer und das Land treffen auf Galumnaktang, das auf seinem Geschmack und seinen Nährstoffen basiert.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Yeonpo-Tang vollständig in Tintenfisch gekocht - Yeongam-gun, Jeonnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/39/e78de64f-66ac-4e64-912d-27a4b76ada74.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Yeonpo-Tang vollständig in Tintenfisch gekocht
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Wo kann ich braunen Lack und Tintenfisch probieren? In der Dokcheon Octopus Street gibt es etwa 30 Octopus-Fachgeschäfte, darunter das Dokcheon Restaurant, das Haenam Restaurant und das Jeonju Restaurant. Galnaktang und Yeonpotang kosten zwischen 17.000 Won und 19.000 Won, während koreanische Gerichte wie Tintenfischsuppe, gerösteter lang gerösteter Tintenfisch und gebratener Tintenfisch zwischen 30.000 Won und 50.000 Won liegen. Der Preis für Lebensmittel variiert geringfügig je nach Größe des großen, mittleren, kleinen und jedes Geschäfts.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Octopus Yeonpo-Tang mit einer weichen Textur - Yeongam-gun, Jeonnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/39/aa5b1d41-c8a5-4fce-aeb1-30a85299a8dd.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Octopus Yeonpo-Tang mit einer weichen Textur
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Reiseinformationen
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Restaurants in der Nähe
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Dokcheon Restaurant: Dokcheon-ro, Haksan-myeon / Gal Naktang, Octopus / 061-472-4222
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.nakji1970.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.nakji1970.com/
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Grünes Restaurant: Dokcheon-ro, Haksan-myeon / Nakji-ri / 061-472-4128
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Cheil Octopus Yard: Dokcheon-ri, Haksan-myeon / Octopus Restaurant / 061-472-3729
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Nangju Restaurant: Haksan-myeon Dokcheon-ri / Octopus Restaurant / 061-472-6925
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Unterkunft
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Ilim Jaemin B &amp;amp; B: Hakam-Gil, Gunseo-Myeon / 061-471-3104
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://cafe.daum.net/elimjai&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://cafe.daum.net/elimjai
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Pro Kopf: Mojeong 1 Gil, Gunseo-Myeon / 061-471-7675
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.moonprint.co.kr/Index.aspx&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.moonprint.co.kr/Index.aspx
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Hotel Hyundai: Daebul-ro, Samho-eup / 061-463-2233
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ Die oben genannten Informationen wurden im Juni 2016 aktualisiert. Sie können sich später ändern. Bitte überprüfen Sie dies, bevor Sie reisen.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Die in diesem Artikel verwendeten Informationen wie Text, Fotos und Videos sind von der Korea Tourism Organization urheberrechtlich geschützt. Daher ist die unbefugte Verwendung des Artikels untersagt.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>韩国全南市灵岩郡 - 功率烧毁了！ Kalaktang，Naejangtang和Octopus招聘：前往Yeongam的令人耳目一新的旅程。</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/power-burned-galaktang-nakjitangtang-and-octopus-horong-a-refreshing-journey-to-yeongam-39-zh-cn/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 19:59:32 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/power-burned-galaktang-nakjitangtang-and-octopus-horong-a-refreshing-journey-to-yeongam-39-zh-cn/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-title=&#34;power-burned-galaktang-nakjitangtang-and-octopus-horong-a-refreshing-journey-to-yeongam--39&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Gal Nak-tang是灵岩市的美味之一。 - 韩国全南市灵岩郡 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/39/ce689c6d-2113-4616-b16e-b29d53f2bb72.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Gal Nak-tang是灵岩市的美味之一。
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   功率烧毁了！ Kalaktang，Naejangtang和Octopus招聘：前往Yeongam的令人耳目一新的旅程。
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    韩国全南市灵岩郡
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   “如果你给掉下的母牛喂三到四个章鱼，你将拥有强大的力量。”
   &lt;br/&gt;
   这是解释八达通资产资产中的一句话。 使掉下的牛跳起来的章鱼。 “人参”的昵称是牛磺酸和组氨酸含量很高，在滋补品中也很出色。 这就是为什么它作为疲倦的人的耐力食品而闻名的原因。 今天，我们在全罗南道灵岩市的独岛进行了一次令人耳目一新的旅行，被称为“章鱼街”。 韩国丰富的春季风光是一大收获。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   部落章鱼，南部岛屿潮滩的丰厚礼物
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   灵岩郡在南道拥有丰富的滩涂，并以其章鱼闻名。 如果您看一会儿地图，灵岩位于东海西海岸，沿着咸平和务安通向木浦，而咸平和务安也以部落章鱼而闻名。 难怪三头章鱼在灵岩地带闻名，那里的南海岸的灵山河沿岸混合着西海岸的咸水和淡水。 现在，龙山河Hagotduk的建设已经失去了作为山区八达通章鱼的声誉。 这是因为有一天，章鱼天堂是由各种章鱼配方的开发创造的。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;通往德川5天市场的八达通街 - 韩国全南市灵岩郡 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/39/c13d11bc-aa77-4e03-b9e2-4225ad4308b7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     通往德川5天市场的八达通街
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   独岛章鱼街位于全南郡灵岩郡白山面独川里。 超过30天的八达通专卖店紧随独岛5天市场。 每个月的第4日和第9日举行的独岛5天市场也是必看的景点。 由于人们通过口口相传而聚集了五六家章鱼专卖店的地方，成了同一条章鱼街。 除了牛肉排骨和章鱼牛肉，它们还提供各种章鱼菜肴，包括Yeonpotang，章鱼和荣和章鱼山。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;八达通商店 - 韩国全南市灵岩郡 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/39/57778b7c-5532-4fd6-93e9-147b63af50f2.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     八达通商店
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   八爪瘦腿的部落章鱼，有什么味道？
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   在品尝章鱼之前，让我们看一下三英尺章鱼的身份。 什么是部落章鱼？ 小时候，我以为“三足章鱼”就是三足章鱼。 即使我有时在电视上看了整个部落的章鱼，也毫无疑问他的脚会“三”。 信念一直持续到我们意识到三英尺章鱼的税不是税，而是税。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   部落章鱼，通常称为八达通章鱼，虽然小但很嫩，有味道。 将整个或煮熟的章鱼放在木筷子上即可品尝。 当然，您必须咀嚼章鱼，这告诉您章鱼在嘴里还活着。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;汉川八达通章鱼八达通专卖店的味道 - 韩国全南市灵岩郡 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/39/20509b1b-df2a-45f2-b5f1-c0a42ee6dfe6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     汉川八达通章鱼八达通专卖店的味道
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   添加到麻油中的新鲜麻油很美味，但部落章鱼的食谱却多种多样。 让我们将其分解为生食和熟食。 根据您的口味，可能会有所不同，但是您的第一手便是品尝鲜活的章鱼。 甜而有嚼劲的质地还活着。 它又小又柔软，所以很容易生吃。 除了八达通章鱼（切成易于食用的八达通）外，独岛的一些八达通专卖店还带有浓郁的部落八达通。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;中式汤切成活章鱼 - 韩国全南市灵岩郡 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/39/0dc7c3c1-820e-4062-958e-ed54e18dad4f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     中式汤切成活章鱼
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   水煮章鱼包括烤章鱼，炒章鱼和烤章鱼，以及以gal-nak和yeonpo-tang为代表的热浸菜。 章鱼辣酱是通过用筷子在三头章鱼上滚动而制成的食品。 烤酱然后烤。 除了章鱼和萝卜腌制外，还加入了被认为是灵岩的代表的Gal Naktang和Yeonpo Tang。 让我们仔细看看Yeongam的美食之一Gal Naktang。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;用木筷子烤章鱼 - 韩国全南市灵岩郡 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/39/1148f74d-23b2-46a6-b8af-87d936d08c62.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     用木筷子烤章鱼
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Yeongam美味超级巨星，Gal Naktang
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   半乳酰胺。 顾名思义，它是排骨和章鱼的汤。 如果只用八爪鱼煮Yeonpotang，则将牛肉排加到Galnaktang中。 章鱼是个好地方，利用章鱼的章鱼会发达。 但是肋骨是从哪里来的呢？ 不管您如何考虑，章鱼和肋骨似乎都不重要。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Gal-Naktang锅铲 - 韩国全南市灵岩郡 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/39/e2bc872a-0a47-44c2-84a3-3d42d3aff346.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Gal-Naktang锅铲
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   好奇心从独岛村的名字中释放出来。 这是因为德川村从“小牛肉毒”中脱颖而出。 独村是一个饲养优质牛的村庄。 因此，章鱼商店出售了排骨。 然后，随着奶牛价格的暴跌，他们煮了“章鱼汤”，里面充满了章鱼，味道令人赞叹。 肋骨和章鱼会合，肉变软，汤变凉。 另外，代表陆地和海洋的两种食物相遇，因此没有落入食物中。 海洋和陆地汇合于Galumnaktang，这是基于其味道和营养成分。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;八宝汤完全用章鱼煮 - 韩国全南市灵岩郡 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/39/e78de64f-66ac-4e64-912d-27a4b76ada74.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     八宝汤完全用章鱼煮
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   在哪里可以品尝到棕色漆和章鱼？ 独岛八达通街约有30家章鱼专卖店，包括独岛餐厅，海南餐厅和全州餐厅。 Galnaktang和Yeonpotang的价格在17,000韩元至19,000韩元之间，而章鱼汤，长烤章鱼和油炸章鱼等韩国料理的价格在30,000韩元到50,000韩元之间。 食品的价格根据大，中，小和每个商店的大小而略有不同。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;质地柔软的八爪鱼延坡堂 - 韩国全南市灵岩郡 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/39/aa5b1d41-c8a5-4fce-aeb1-30a85299a8dd.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     质地柔软的八爪鱼延坡堂
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   旅游信息
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1.附近的餐馆
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    独岛餐厅：八善面独岛路/章鱼八角汤/ 061-472-4222
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.nakji1970.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.nakji1970.com/
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    绿色餐厅：白山面德川路/中智里/ 061-472-4128
    &lt;br/&gt;
    首尔章鱼场：鹤山面德川里/章鱼餐厅/ 061-472-3729
    &lt;br/&gt;
    南州餐厅：白山面德川里/章鱼餐厅/ 061-472-6925
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2.住宿
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Ilim Jaemin B＆B：冈西面Hakam-gil / 061-471-3104
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://cafe.daum.net/elimjai&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://cafe.daum.net/elimjai
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    人均：群山面Mojeong 1-gil / 061-471-7675
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.moonprint.co.kr/Index.aspx&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.moonprint.co.kr/Index.aspx
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    现代酒店：三宝邑大宝路/ 061-463-2233
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※以上信息于2016年6月更新。此后可能会发生变化，因此请在旅行前检查一下。
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※本文中使用的文字，照片和视频等信息受韩国旅游组织版权保护，因此禁止未经授权使用本文。
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yeongam-gun, Jeonnam, Korea - Power burned! Galaktang, Nakjitangtang, and Octopus Horong: A refreshing journey to Yeongam.</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/power-burned-galaktang-nakjitangtang-and-octopus-horong-a-refreshing-journey-to-yeongam-39/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 19:57:17 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/power-burned-galaktang-nakjitangtang-and-octopus-horong-a-refreshing-journey-to-yeongam-39/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-title=&#34;power-burned-galaktang-nakjitangtang-and-octopus-horong-a-refreshing-journey-to-yeongam--39&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Gal Nak-tang is one of Yeongam&#39;s delicacies. - Yeongam-gun, Jeonnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/39/ce689c6d-2113-4616-b16e-b29d53f2bb72.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Gal Nak-tang is one of Yeongam&#39;s delicacies.
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Power burned! Galaktang, Nakjitangtang, and Octopus Horong: A refreshing journey to Yeongam.
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Yeongam-gun, Jeonnam, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &#34;If you feed three or four octopus to a falling cow, you will have a strong power.&#34;
   &lt;br/&gt;
   This is a sentence explaining Octopus in Asset Asset. An octopus that makes a fallen cow jump up. The nickname of “sea ginseng” has a high content of taurine and histidine, which is excellent in tonics. It is the reason why it became famous as stamina food for tired people. Today, we went on a refreshing trip to Dokcheon in Yeongam, Jeollanam-do, known as &#39;Octopus Street&#39;. The abundance of springtime scenery in South Korea is a bonus.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Tribal Octopus, a gift of abundant southern island tidal flats
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Yeongam-gun, with its rich tidal flats in Namdo, was famous for its tribal octopus. If you look at the map for a while, Yeongam is located along the west coast of East Sea, which leads to Mokpo along Hampyeong and Muan, which are also famous for their tribal octopus. It is no wonder that the three-headed octopus became famous in Yeongam Land, where salty and fresh waters of the west coast were mixed along the stem of Yeongsan River in Namdo. The Yeongsan River Hagotduk construction has now lost its reputation as a mountain producing tribal octopus. This is because one day, octopus paradise was created by the development of various octopus recipes.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Octopus street leading to Dokcheon 5-day market - Yeongam-gun, Jeonnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/39/c13d11bc-aa77-4e03-b9e2-4225ad4308b7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Octopus street leading to Dokcheon 5-day market
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Dokcheon Octopus Street is located in Dokcheon-ri, Haksan-myeon, Yeongam-gun, Jeonnam. More than 30 octopus specialty shops follow the Dokcheon 5-day market. The Dokcheon 5-day Market, which is held every 4th and 9th of every month, is also a must-see. This place, where five or six octopus specialty shops were located, became the same octopus street since people gathered by word of mouth. In addition to beef chops and beef octopus, they also offer a variety of octopus dishes, including Yeonpotang, Octopus Horong, and Mountain Octopus.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Dozens of octopus shops - Yeongam-gun, Jeonnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/39/57778b7c-5532-4fd6-93e9-147b63af50f2.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Dozens of octopus shops
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Tribal octopus with eight thin legs, what taste?
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Before tasting the octopus, let&#39;s take a look at the identity of the three-foot octopus. What is a tribal octopus? When I was young, I thought &#39;three foot octopus&#39; was a three foot octopus. Even though I sometimes watched a whole tribal octopus on TV, there was no doubt that his feet would be &#34;three&#34;. Faith continued until we realized that the tax in the three-foot octopus was not a tax, but a tax.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Tribal octopus, commonly called 뻘 octopus, is small but tender and has a taste of taste. Whole or cooked octopus can be tasted by rolling it on wooden chopsticks. Of course, you must chew on the octopus, which tells you that it is still alive in your mouth.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Hansang&#39;s taste in octopus specialty shop in Dokcheon Octopus - Yeongam-gun, Jeonnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/39/20509b1b-df2a-45f2-b5f1-c0a42ee6dfe6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Hansang&#39;s taste in octopus specialty shop in Dokcheon Octopus
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Fresh sesame oil added to sesame oil is delicious, but the tribal octopus recipes are varied. Let&#39;s break it down into raw and cooked food. Depending on your taste, it may be a little different, but your first hand is to taste live octopus. Sweet and chewy texture is alive. It&#39;s small and soft, so it&#39;s easy to eat raw. In addition to the octopus Tangtang (an octopus cut out to be easy to eat), some of the octopus specialty stores in Dokcheon come out with a full-bodied tribal octopus.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Nakjitang-tang cut into live octopus - Yeongam-gun, Jeonnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/39/0dc7c3c1-820e-4062-958e-ed54e18dad4f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Nakjitang-tang cut into live octopus
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Boiled octopus dishes include grilled octopus, stir-fried octopus and roasted octopus, as well as hot-dip dishes represented by gal-nak and yeonpo-tang. Octopus horong is a food that is cooked by rolling around three heads of octopus from chopsticks. Bake the sauce and bake. In addition to the octopus stir-fried and marinated with radish, Gal Naktang and Yeonpo Tang, which are considered representatives of Yeongam, are added. Let&#39;s take a closer look at Gal Naktang, one of Yeongam&#39;s delicacies.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Roasted octopus with wood chopsticks - Yeongam-gun, Jeonnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/39/1148f74d-23b2-46a6-b8af-87d936d08c62.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Roasted octopus with wood chopsticks
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Yeongam Delicacy Superstar, Gal Naktang
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Galactam. As the name suggests, it is a soup with ribs and octopus. If Yeonpotang is boiled only with octopus, the beef ribs are added to Galnaktang. Octopus is abundant place, the octopus utilizing the octopus would have developed. But where did the ribs come from? No matter how you think about it, octopus and ribs don&#39;t seem to matter.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Spatula, Gal-naktang - Yeongam-gun, Jeonnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/39/e2bc872a-0a47-44c2-84a3-3d42d3aff346.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Spatula, Gal-naktang
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The curiosity was released from the name of Dokcheon Village. This is because Dokcheon Village came out of the “Calf Poison”. Dokcheon Village was a village that raises good cattle. Thanks to this, the octopus shops sold their ribs. Then, as the price of cows plummeted, they cooked “Gallak-tang,” which is filled with octopus, and the taste was amazing. The ribs and octopus will meet, the meat will be softer and the soup will be cooler. In addition, the two foods representing the land and the sea met, so did not fall into the food. The sea and land meets Galumnaktang, which is based on its taste and nutrients.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Yeonpo-tang cooked entirely in octopus - Yeongam-gun, Jeonnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/39/e78de64f-66ac-4e64-912d-27a4b76ada74.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Yeonpo-tang cooked entirely in octopus
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Where can I taste brown lacquer and octopus? There are about 30 octopus specialty shops in Dokcheon Octopus Street, including Dokcheon Restaurant, Haenam Restaurant, and Jeonju Restaurant. Galnaktang and Yeonpotang costs between 17,000 won and 19,000 won, while Korean dishes such as octopus soup, roasted long-roasted octopus, and fried octopus range from 30,000 won to 50,000 won. The price of food varies slightly depending on the size of the large, medium, small and each store.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Octopus Yeonpo-tang with a soft texture - Yeongam-gun, Jeonnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/39/aa5b1d41-c8a5-4fce-aeb1-30a85299a8dd.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Octopus Yeonpo-tang with a soft texture
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel info
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Nearby restaurants
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Dokcheon Restaurant: Dokcheon-ro, Haksan-myeon / Gal Naktang, Octopus / 061-472-4222
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.nakji1970.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.nakji1970.com/
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Green Restaurant: Dokcheon-ro, Haksan-myeon / Nakji-ri / 061-472-4128
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Cheil Octopus Yard: Dokcheon-ri, Haksan-myeon / Octopus Restaurant / 061-472-3729
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Nangju Restaurant: Haksan-myeon Dokcheon-ri / Octopus Restaurant / 061-472-6925
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Accommodation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Ilim Jaemin B &amp;amp; B: Hakam-gil, Gunseo-myeon / 061-471-3104
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://cafe.daum.net/elimjai&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://cafe.daum.net/elimjai
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Per capita: Mojeong 1-gil, Gunseo-myeon / 061-471-7675
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.moonprint.co.kr/Index.aspx&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.moonprint.co.kr/Index.aspx
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Hotel Hyundai: Daebul-ro, Samho-eup / 061-463-2233
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was updated in June 2016. It may change afterwards, so please check before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ The information such as text, photos and videos used in this article is copyrighted by Korea Tourism Organization, so unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>