<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sunchang-gun on Every Corner of Korea</title>
    <link>https://codecorea.github.io/tags/sunchang-gun/</link>
    <description>Every Corner of Korea (Sunchang-gun)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 11:03:40 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="https://codecorea.github.io/tags/sunchang-gun/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Korea - Put red pepper paste, beat rice cake, make rice, and experience Jangchang</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/put-red-pepper-paste-beat-rice-cake-make-rice-and-experience-jangchang-53/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 11:03:40 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/put-red-pepper-paste-beat-rice-cake-make-rice-and-experience-jangchang-53/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;put-red-pepper-paste-beat-rice-cake-make-rice-and-experience-jangchang--53&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Sunchang Paste Experience Center - Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/53d8f481-6dc8-49a9-b87a-46168c297966.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Sunchang Paste Experience Center
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Put red pepper paste, beat rice cake, make rice, and experience Jangchang
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &#39;Jang Jang Sunchang&#39; is Sunchang&#39;s slogan. This is a good expression of Sunchang, famous for gochujang. If you go to Sunchang Gochujang, gochujang is Sunchang. I made a traditional Jangjang paste of Sunchang, cooked foods made with soy sauce, and made a hands-on experience program to make healthy snacks. The children are very funny and even eat delicious. It is an experience where even adults grow happy.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Spicy rice cake pizza dough ~
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   10 am Saturday. As soon as you arrive at Sunchang Jangjang Experience Hall, you will be busy. The Jangjang experience program will take about 2 hours, including gochujang making, gochujang cooking, and seasoning of rice cakes and tofu.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Gochujang Bulgogi Pizza Making Experience - Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/f87c9666-904b-4b36-a2e5-ff96487f22d5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Gochujang Bulgogi Pizza Making Experience
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   To make an effective time arrangement, we first cooked the Jangjang, then make the Injeolmi and Tumbap outside, and finally, make Gochujang. Today&#39;s dish is made from gochujang pizza with gochujang bulgogi. In addition to Gochujang Bulgogi Pizza, you can choose from Kimchi, Gochujang Spaghetti, Cheonggukjang-jjigae, Cheese Tteokbokki, Gochujang Namul Gimbap, etc. What&#39;s interesting is that instead of pizza dough, cut the rice cake into thin pans like rice cake for rice cake soup. All you need to do is pour the dough on top so that the rice cakes don&#39;t fall and stick together. Place bulgogi seasoned with red pepper paste on top of rice cake dough and sprinkle chopped vegetables with topping. Sprinkle plenty of cheese on top and decorate with ketchup. Switch on the pan with the lid on and wait for it to finish.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Gochujang Bulgogi Pizza Making Experience - Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/e70b367f-c051-470e-aa49-1d0a104cc813.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Gochujang Bulgogi Pizza Making Experience
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Close your ears and say &#34;Yeah ~&#34;
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   While the pizza is ripe, go outside to make Injeolmi and rice. Injeolmi is the key to rice cake making. At first, adults have to take turns to crush rice grains. Tteokme is more fun and less difficult to stand and beat each other by hitting each other.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Injeolmi making experience - Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/b825354b-5195-4644-bd30-d26e2ab5368d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Injeolmi making experience
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   When the rice is crushed in moderation, change it to children&#39;s rice cake and give it to the children. Like a funny play, the children wait anxiously for their turn. After hitting three or four times, the sound of rice cakes is getting louder and louder. The black hot frying machine is turned gently to increase the pressure. The children are squeezed the handles so that they can see them once, but I&#39;m excited to know what&#39;s coming out. Finally, I&#39;m going to explode. The children close their ears tightly and look at the machine. &#34;뻥 ~!&#34; White steam is rising with a loud noise. The children rushed in when they put rice rice in a large basket. Fill your hands with greed and bury your face. It is fried quickly and its taste is very delicious. Children eat more rice than any snack.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Tempura making experience - Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/a410f73b-8f81-4797-b6c5-ae4b9ddddde0.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Tempura making experience
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In the meantime, Injeolmi is completed and soaked with soy flour. Child who slices rice cake, child who gets soybean powder, experience that is behind the scenes and busy to eat… . They enjoy making and eating in different ways. Injeolmi is a good combination of soybean flour mixed with chewy rice cakes. I made it and ate it right away, so the cuts of rice and the rice are delicious. It is not a taste of memories, but a taste that surpasses memories.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Tempura making experience - Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/8a5a586c-c153-44c9-8349-b43247edf372.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Tempura making experience
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Taste pizza and make gochujang
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   After the outdoor experience, go back into the experience room. A well baked pizza is waiting. Thanks to the red pepper paste on the dough made with rice cakes, the pizza is perfect for the taste of Koreans. Gochujang seasoning is a bit spicy, but it is eaten instantly. After the pizza tasting, the highlight of the day is the red pepper paste making experience.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Gochujang making experience - Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/db431458-a017-4f04-bc95-81583fd25ef8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Gochujang making experience
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   First, listen to why Sunchang Gochujang is delicious and how to make it. In other regions, square meju is used to make soy sauce, soybean paste, and red pepper paste. What is unusual is that the meju is usually picked in early winter, but Sunchang makes meju at the end of August. When the weather is hot, the microorganisms that add the rich flavor of red pepper paste multiply well. Another special feature of Sunchang is that it is not only made from soybeans but also mixed with rice at 6: 4 ratio. Soybean paste is soaked in winter and aged for more than 6 months.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Gochujang making experience - Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/1efcd5cf-a80c-48a5-90f8-4192beb0051b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Gochujang making experience
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   After listening to the explanation, take a moment to make a gochujang quiz. The experience is surprisingly simple. Distribute bowls of mew flour, red pepper powder, Sikhye, salt, and malt in the right proportions by team. The secret is to mix them well so that they don&#39;t clump together. Mix it up and dip it with your finger to taste it. It&#39;s a strange taste. Gochujang is not made right away because it needs to be aged. As time goes by, our traditional Jangjang, which tastes deeper, is truly slow food. If you leave the gochujang made by the visitors in the experience hall, they will gather them together and mix them well. Instead of making it on-site, you will receive a well-cooked gochujang one by one.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Gochujang making experience - Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/95a6900a-2f9b-435f-8f5f-ac2589bc5cd1.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Gochujang making experience
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Gochujang Village to preserve the traditional taste
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   After enjoying the Jangju experience, take a look around Gochujang Village. In Kochujang Village, Kochujang can be produced and sold only if you are recognized as a master of Kochujang. The merchandise in the market is almost reliable. All you see here is the red pepper paste shop, so it&#39;s as if you&#39;re in the red pepper paste country. Gochujang Nara is not a small Gochujang village, but it is enough to catch our taste.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sunchang Red Pepper Village - Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/908bc071-6100-44bd-b2bf-ebc3d5bf76b1.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sunchang Red Pepper Village
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In the yard, there are many jars of red pepper paste, miso and soy sauce, and the pickles smell like pol-pol in the store. Jangjang is good, but rice thief pickles are just as popular. There are many kinds of pickles such as plums, radishes, cucumbers, garlic seeds, sweet persimmons, sesame leaves, deodeok, scallops, oysters, etc. You can taste and choose different kinds of pickles.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sunchang Red Pepper Village - Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/96e7229a-930e-4e62-a485-4b6c7c33d26d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sunchang Red Pepper Village
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   There is also a rice wine jar next to it. The pickles that are eaten in the mouth are salty, but when you taste them after sipping the rice wine, &#34;kya&#34; sound comes out. Cheonggukjang smells very little and tastes so mild that children eat well. The steps are so great when you pick up pickles in a hot pepper paste made by a master.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sunchang Red Pepper Village - Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/3cfce9b9-5aa5-4e90-8aeb-da6ea03dbf5a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sunchang Red Pepper Village
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   I have tried making jang but I do not make delicious jang. How much effort do you compare to the workmanship of a master who has been in the market forever?
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sunchang Red Pepper Village - Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/c2a0a872-c44f-46b9-b2fa-acce17271754.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sunchang Red Pepper Village
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel info
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Sunchang Paste Experience Center
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Address: 55, Folk Village-gil, Sunchang-eup, Sunchang-gun, Jeollabuk-do
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Experience program: Make Soonchang Traditional Red Pepper Paste, Make Korean Cuisine, Make Injeol, Make Traditional Tofu
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -When using the experience program, you can use the accommodation facilities in the experience hall.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.janghada.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.janghada.com/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    ※ The above information was updated in March 2017 and may change afterwards, so please check before you travel.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    ※ The information such as text, photos and videos used in this article is copyrighted by Korea Tourism Organization, so unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>