<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sunchang-gun on Korea Tour</title>
    <link>https://codecorea.github.io/tags/sunchang-gun/</link>
    <description>Korea Tour (Sunchang-gun)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 11:14:50 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="https://codecorea.github.io/tags/sunchang-gun/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunchang-gun, Чонбук, Корея - Положите пасту из красного перца, взбейте рисовый пирог, сделайте рис и испытайте Jangchang</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/put-red-pepper-paste-beat-rice-cake-make-rice-and-experience-jangchang-53-ru/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 11:14:50 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/put-red-pepper-paste-beat-rice-cake-make-rice-and-experience-jangchang-53-ru/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;put-red-pepper-paste-beat-rice-cake-make-rice-and-experience-jangchang--53&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Sunchang Paste Experience Center - Sunchang-gun, Чонбук, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/53d8f481-6dc8-49a9-b87a-46168c297966.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Sunchang Paste Experience Center
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Положите пасту из красного перца, взбейте рисовый пирог, сделайте рис и испытайте Jangchang
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Sunchang-gun, Чонбук, Корея
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   «Jang Jang Sunchang» - лозунг Сунчана. Это хорошее выражение Суньчана, известного благодаря гочуджангу. Если вы отправляетесь в Сунчан, то Гочуджанг - это сунчан. Я сделал традиционную Jangjang пасту Sunchang, приготовил еду, приготовленную с соевым соусом, и сделал программу практического опыта, чтобы сделать здоровые закуски. Дети очень веселые и даже вкусно едят. Это опыт, когда даже взрослые становятся счастливыми.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Пряный рисовый пирог из теста для пиццы ~
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   10 утра суббота. Как только вы прибудете в Зал Опыта Сунчана, вы будете заняты. Программа обучения Jangjang займет около 2 часов, включая приготовление гочуджанга, приготовление гочуджанга и приправу рисовых лепешек и тофу.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Пицца Гочуджанг Булгоги - Sunchang-gun, Чонбук, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/f87c9666-904b-4b36-a2e5-ff96487f22d5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Пицца Гочуджанг Булгоги
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Чтобы сделать эффективную временную планировку, мы сначала приготовили Jangjang, затем сделали Injeolmi и Tumbap снаружи и, наконец, сделали Gochujang. Сегодняшнее блюдо готовится из пиццы гочуджан с гочуджан булгоги. В дополнение к пицце Gochujang Bulgogi, вы можете выбрать кимчи, спагетти Gochujang, Cheonggukjang-jjigae, сыр Tteokbokki, Gamujang Namul Gimbap и т. Д. Что интересно, вместо теста для пиццы нарежьте рисовый пирог на тонкие сковородки, как рисовый пирог для риса торт-суп. Все, что вам нужно сделать, это вылить тесто сверху, чтобы рисовые лепешки не упали и не слиплись. Поместите булгоги, приправленные пастой из красного перца, на тесто для рисового пирога и посыпьте нарезанные овощи сверху. Посыпать сверху большим количеством сыра и украсить кетчупом. Включите кастрюлю с крышкой и дождитесь ее окончания.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Пицца Гочуджанг Булгоги - Sunchang-gun, Чонбук, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/e70b367f-c051-470e-aa49-1d0a104cc813.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Пицца Гочуджанг Булгоги
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Закрой уши и скажи &#34;Да ~&#34;
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Пока пицца созрела, выйдите на улицу, чтобы приготовить Инжолми и рис. Injeolmi - ключ к изготовлению рисового пирога. Сначала взрослые должны по очереди измельчать рисовые зерна. Tteokme более забавный и менее трудный, чтобы стоять и бить друг друга, ударяя друг друга.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Injeolmi делает опыт - Sunchang-gun, Чонбук, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/b825354b-5195-4644-bd30-d26e2ab5368d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Injeolmi делает опыт
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Когда рис будет измельчен в меру, поменяйте его на детский рисовый пирог и дайте его детям. Как забавная пьеса, дети с нетерпением ждут своей очереди. После трех или четырех ударов звук рисовых лепешек становится все громче и громче. Черная горячая машина для жарки осторожно поворачивается, чтобы увеличить давление. Дети сжимают ручки, чтобы они могли их увидеть один раз, но я рад узнать, что выходит. Наконец я собираюсь взорваться. Дети плотно закрывают уши и смотрят на машину. &#34;뻥 ~!&#34; Белый пар поднимается с громким шумом. Дети ворвались, когда они положили рисовый рис в большую корзину. Наполните свои руки жадностью и похороните свое лицо. Жарится быстро, вкус очень вкусный. Дети едят больше риса, чем любые закуски.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Опыт изготовления темпуры - Sunchang-gun, Чонбук, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/a410f73b-8f81-4797-b6c5-ae4b9ddddde0.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Опыт изготовления темпуры
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Тем временем, Injeolmi укомплектован и пропитан соевой мукой. Ребенок, который нарезает рисовый пирог, ребенок, который получает соевый порошок, опыт, который находится за кадром и занят, чтобы поесть ... Они любят готовить и есть по-разному. Injeolmi - это хорошее сочетание соевой муки с жевательными рисовыми лепешками. Я сделал это и съел это сразу, таким образом, куски риса и рис восхитительны. Это не вкус воспоминаний, а вкус, который превосходит воспоминания.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Опыт изготовления темпуры - Sunchang-gun, Чонбук, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/8a5a586c-c153-44c9-8349-b43247edf372.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Опыт изготовления темпуры
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Попробуйте пиццу и приготовьте гочуджан
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   После опыта на свежем воздухе вернитесь в комнату опыта. Хорошо запеченная пицца ждет. Благодаря пасте из красного перца на тесте с рисовыми лепешками, пицца идеально подходит на вкус корейцев. Приправа кочучжан немного острая, но она съедается мгновенно. После дегустации пиццы основной момент дня - опыт приготовления пасты из красного перца.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Гочуджанг делает опыт - Sunchang-gun, Чонбук, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/db431458-a017-4f04-bc95-81583fd25ef8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Гочуджанг делает опыт
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Во-первых, послушайте, почему Sunchang Gochujang очень вкусный и как его приготовить. В других регионах для приготовления соевого соуса, пасты из соевых бобов и пасты из красного перца используют квадратный мейу. Что необычно, так это то, что меджу обычно собирают в начале зимы, но Суньчан делает меджу в конце августа. В жаркую погоду микроорганизмы, которые добавляют насыщенный вкус пасты из красного перца, хорошо размножаются. Еще одна особенность сунчанга заключается в том, что он не только сделан из соевых бобов, но и смешан с рисом в соотношении 6: 4. Соевая паста пропитывается зимой и выдерживается более 6 месяцев.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Гочуджанг делает опыт - Sunchang-gun, Чонбук, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/1efcd5cf-a80c-48a5-90f8-4192beb0051b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Гочуджанг делает опыт
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Выслушав объяснение, найдите время, чтобы сделать викторину по гочуджангу. Опыт на удивление прост. Распределите миски мякоти муки, порошка красного перца, сикхе, соли и солода в правильных пропорциях по команде. Секрет в том, чтобы смешать их хорошо, чтобы они не слипались. Смешайте это и опустите это пальцем, чтобы испытать это. Это странный вкус. Гочуджан не сделан сразу, потому что он должен быть в возрасте. С течением времени наш традиционный Jangjang, который имеет более глубокий вкус, является действительно медленной едой. Если вы оставите гочуджан, сделанный посетителями в зале опыта, они соберут их вместе и хорошо перемешают. Вместо того, чтобы делать это на месте, вы будете получать хорошо приготовленный gochujang один за другим.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Гочуджанг делает опыт - Sunchang-gun, Чонбук, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/95a6900a-2f9b-435f-8f5f-ac2589bc5cd1.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Гочуджанг делает опыт
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Деревня Гочуджан, чтобы сохранить традиционный вкус
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   После наслаждения опытом Чанджу, осмотрите деревню Гочуджанг. В деревне Кочуджанг Кочуджанг можно производить и продавать только в том случае, если вы признаны мастером Кочуджанга. Товар на рынке практически надежный. Все, что вы видите здесь, это магазин пасты из красного перца, так что вы как будто находитесь в стране пасты из красного перца. Гочуджанг Нара - не маленькая деревня Гочуджангов, но этого достаточно, чтобы уловить наш вкус.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sunchang Red Pepper Village - Sunchang-gun, Чонбук, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/908bc071-6100-44bd-b2bf-ebc3d5bf76b1.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sunchang Red Pepper Village
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Во дворе много банок пасты из красного перца, мисо и соевого соуса, а соленые огурцы пахнут как полпол в магазине. Jangjang хорош, но рисовые воры так же популярны. Существует много видов солений, таких как сливы, редька, огурцы, семена чеснока, сладкая хурма, листья кунжута, деодок, морские гребешки, устрицы и т. Д. Вы можете попробовать и выбрать различные виды солений.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sunchang Red Pepper Village - Sunchang-gun, Чонбук, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/96e7229a-930e-4e62-a485-4b6c7c33d26d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sunchang Red Pepper Village
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Рядом с ним находится банка с рисовым вином. Соленые огурцы, которые едят во рту, соленые, но когда вы попробуете их после того, как потягиваете рисовое вино, раздастся звук &#34;кя&#34;. Чеонгкуджанг очень мало пахнет и имеет такой мягкий вкус, что дети едят хорошо. Шаги так хороши, когда вы берете соленые огурцы в пасту из острого перца, приготовленную мастером.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sunchang Red Pepper Village - Sunchang-gun, Чонбук, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/3cfce9b9-5aa5-4e90-8aeb-da6ea03dbf5a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sunchang Red Pepper Village
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Я пробовал делать джанг, но я не делаю вкусный джанг. Сколько усилий вы сравниваете с мастерством мастера, который всегда был на рынке?
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sunchang Red Pepper Village - Sunchang-gun, Чонбук, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/c2a0a872-c44f-46b9-b2fa-acce17271754.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sunchang Red Pepper Village
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Информация о путешествии
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Sunchang Paste Experience Center
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Адрес: 55, Народная Деревня Гил, Сунчан-эуп, Сунчан-гун, Чоллабук-до
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Опытская программа: приготовить традиционную пасту из красного перца Soonchang, приготовить корейскую кухню, приготовить Injeol, приготовить традиционный тофу
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -При использовании программы опыта, вы можете использовать средства размещения в зале опыта.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.janghada.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.janghada.com/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    ※ Приведенная выше информация была обновлена в марте 2017 года и может впоследствии измениться, поэтому, пожалуйста, проверьте это перед поездкой.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    ※ Информация, такая как текст, фотографии и видео, используемые в этой статье, защищены авторским правом Корейской туристической организации, поэтому несанкционированное использование статьи запрещено.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Corée - Mettez de la pâte de poivron rouge, battez un gâteau de riz, faites du riz et découvrez Jangchang</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/put-red-pepper-paste-beat-rice-cake-make-rice-and-experience-jangchang-53-fr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 11:12:31 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/put-red-pepper-paste-beat-rice-cake-make-rice-and-experience-jangchang-53-fr/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;put-red-pepper-paste-beat-rice-cake-make-rice-and-experience-jangchang--53&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Centre d&#39;expérience Sunchang Paste - Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/53d8f481-6dc8-49a9-b87a-46168c297966.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Centre d&#39;expérience Sunchang Paste
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Mettez de la pâte de poivron rouge, battez un gâteau de riz, faites du riz et découvrez Jangchang
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Corée
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   «Jang Jang Sunchang» est le slogan de Sunchang. C&#39;est une bonne expression de Sunchang, célèbre pour gochujang. Si vous allez à Sunchang Gochujang, gochujang est Sunchang. J&#39;ai fait une pâte Jangjang traditionnelle de Sunchang, des aliments cuits à base de sauce soja et j&#39;ai fait un programme d&#39;expérience pratique pour faire des collations saines. Les enfants sont très drôles et mangent même délicieux. C&#39;est une expérience où même les adultes deviennent heureux.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Pâte à pizza au gâteau de riz épicé ~
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   10h samedi. Dès que vous arriverez au Sunchang Jangjang Experience Hall, vous serez occupé. Le programme d&#39;expérience Jangjang prendra environ 2 heures, y compris la fabrication du gochujang, la cuisine du gochujang et l&#39;assaisonnement des gâteaux de riz et du tofu.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Gochujang Bulgogi Pizza Making Experience - Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/f87c9666-904b-4b36-a2e5-ff96487f22d5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Gochujang Bulgogi Pizza Making Experience
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Pour faire un arrangement de temps efficace, nous avons d&#39;abord fait cuire le Jangjang, puis nous avons fait l&#39;Injeolmi et le Tumbap à l&#39;extérieur, et finalement, nous avons fait le Gochujang. Le plat d&#39;aujourd&#39;hui est fait de pizza au gochujang avec du bulgogi de gochujang. En plus de Gochujang Bulgogi Pizza, vous pouvez choisir parmi Kimchi, Gochujang Spaghetti, Cheonggukjang-jjigae, Cheese Tteokbokki, Gochujang Namul Gimbap, etc. soupe de gâteau. Tout ce que vous devez faire est de verser la pâte sur le dessus afin que les gâteaux de riz ne tombent pas et ne collent pas. Placer le bulgogi assaisonné de pâte de poivron rouge sur la pâte à gâteau au riz et saupoudrer de légumes hachés avec la garniture. Saupoudrer beaucoup de fromage sur le dessus et décorer avec du ketchup. Allumez la casserole avec le couvercle et attendez qu&#39;elle se termine.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Gochujang Bulgogi Pizza Making Experience - Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/e70b367f-c051-470e-aa49-1d0a104cc813.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Gochujang Bulgogi Pizza Making Experience
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   C
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Pendant que la pizza est mûre, sortez pour faire de l&#39;Injeolmi et du riz. Injeolmi est la clé de la fabrication de gâteaux de riz. Au début, les adultes doivent à tour de rôle écraser les grains de riz. Tteokme est plus amusant et moins difficile à se tenir debout et à se battre en se frappant.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Injeolmi faisant l&#39;expérience - Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/b825354b-5195-4644-bd30-d26e2ab5368d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Injeolmi faisant l&#39;expérience
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Lorsque le riz est écrasé avec modération, changez-le en gâteau de riz pour enfants et donnez-le aux enfants. Comme une pièce amusante, les enfants attendent avec impatience leur tour. Après avoir frappé trois ou quatre fois, le son des gâteaux de riz devient de plus en plus fort. La machine à frire à chaud noir est tournée doucement pour augmenter la pression. Les enfants sont serrés les poignées pour qu&#39;ils puissent les voir une fois, mais je suis excité de savoir ce qui va sortir. Enfin, je vais exploser. Les enfants ferment bien les oreilles et regardent la machine. &#34;뻥 ~!&#34; La vapeur blanche monte avec un bruit fort. Les enfants se sont précipités lorsqu&#39;ils ont mis du riz et du riz dans un grand panier. Remplissez vos mains de cupidité et enfouissez votre visage. Il est frit rapidement et son goût est très délicieux. Les enfants mangent plus de riz que n&#39;importe quelle collation.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Expérience de fabrication de tempura - Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/a410f73b-8f81-4797-b6c5-ae4b9ddddde0.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Expérience de fabrication de tempura
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   En attendant, Injeolmi est terminé et imbibé de farine de soja. Un enfant qui tranche un gâteau de riz, un enfant qui reçoit de la poudre de soja, une expérience en coulisses et occupée à manger…. Ils aiment faire et manger de différentes manières. Injeolmi est une bonne combinaison de farine de soja mélangée à des gâteaux de riz moelleux. Je l&#39;ai fait et l&#39;ai mangé tout de suite, donc les coupes de riz et le riz sont délicieux. Ce n&#39;est pas un goût de souvenirs, mais un goût qui dépasse les souvenirs.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Expérience de fabrication de tempura - Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/8a5a586c-c153-44c9-8349-b43247edf372.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Expérience de fabrication de tempura
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Goûtez la pizza et faites du gochujang
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Après l&#39;expérience en plein air, retournez dans la salle d&#39;expérience. Une pizza bien cuite vous attend. Grâce à la pâte de poivron rouge sur la pâte faite avec des gâteaux de riz, la pizza est parfaite pour le goût des Coréens. L&#39;assaisonnement Gochujang est un peu épicé, mais il se consomme instantanément. Après la dégustation de pizza, le point culminant de la journée est l&#39;expérience de fabrication de pâte de poivron rouge.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Gochujang faisant l&#39;expérience - Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/db431458-a017-4f04-bc95-81583fd25ef8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Gochujang faisant l&#39;expérience
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Tout d&#39;abord, écoutez pourquoi Sunchang Gochujang est délicieux et comment le faire. Dans d&#39;autres régions, le meju carré est utilisé pour faire de la sauce de soja, de la pâte de soja et de la pâte de poivron rouge. Ce qui est inhabituel, c&#39;est que le meju est généralement cueilli au début de l&#39;hiver, mais Sunchang fabrique du meju à la fin août. Lorsque le temps est chaud, les micro-organismes qui ajoutent la riche saveur de la pâte de poivron rouge se multiplient bien. Une autre particularité de Sunchang est qu&#39;il est non seulement fabriqué à partir de soja mais également mélangé avec du riz dans un rapport de 6: 4. La pâte de soja est trempée en hiver et vieillie pendant plus de 6 mois.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Gochujang faisant l&#39;expérience - Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/1efcd5cf-a80c-48a5-90f8-4192beb0051b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Gochujang faisant l&#39;expérience
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Après avoir écouté l&#39;explication, prenez un moment pour faire un quiz gochujang. L&#39;expérience est étonnamment simple. Distribuez des bols de farine de mew, de poudre de poivron rouge, de Sikhye, de sel et de malt dans les bonnes proportions par équipe. Le secret est de bien les mélanger pour qu&#39;ils ne s&#39;agglutinent pas. Mélangez-le et trempez-le avec votre doigt pour le goûter. C&#39;est un goût étrange. Gochujang n&#39;est pas fabriqué tout de suite car il a besoin d&#39;être vieilli. Au fil du temps, notre Jangjang traditionnel, qui a un goût plus profond, est vraiment un slow food. Si vous laissez le gochujang fait par les visiteurs dans la salle d&#39;expérience, ils les rassembleront et les mélangeront bien. Au lieu de le faire sur place, vous recevrez un gochujang bien cuit un par un.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Gochujang faisant l&#39;expérience - Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/95a6900a-2f9b-435f-8f5f-ac2589bc5cd1.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Gochujang faisant l&#39;expérience
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Gochujang Village pour préserver le goût traditionnel
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Après avoir profité de l&#39;expérience de Jangju, jetez un œil au village de Gochujang. Dans le village de Kochujang, le Kochujang ne peut être produit et vendu que si vous êtes reconnu comme un maître de Kochujang. La marchandise sur le marché est presque fiable. Tout ce que vous voyez ici est la boutique de pâte de poivron rouge, c&#39;est comme si vous étiez dans le pays de la pâte de poivron rouge. Gochujang Nara n&#39;est pas un petit village de Gochujang, mais c&#39;est suffisant pour attraper notre goût.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sunchang Red Pepper Village - Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/908bc071-6100-44bd-b2bf-ebc3d5bf76b1.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sunchang Red Pepper Village
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Dans la cour, il y a beaucoup de pots de pâte de poivron rouge, de miso et de sauce soja, et les cornichons sentent le pol-pol dans le magasin. Jangjang est bon, mais les cornichons voleurs de riz sont tout aussi populaires. Il existe de nombreux types de cornichons tels que prunes, radis, concombres, graines d&#39;ail, kakis sucrés, feuilles de sésame, deodeok, pétoncles, huîtres, etc. Vous pouvez déguster et choisir différents types de cornichons.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sunchang Red Pepper Village - Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/96e7229a-930e-4e62-a485-4b6c7c33d26d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sunchang Red Pepper Village
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Il y a aussi un pot de vin de riz à côté. Les cornichons que l&#39;on mange en bouche sont salés, mais lorsque vous les goûtez après avoir siroté le vin de riz, le son &#34;kya&#34; sort. Cheonggukjang sent très peu et a un goût si doux que les enfants mangent bien. Les étapes sont si grandes lorsque vous ramassez des cornichons dans une pâte de piment fort faite par un maître.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sunchang Red Pepper Village - Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/3cfce9b9-5aa5-4e90-8aeb-da6ea03dbf5a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sunchang Red Pepper Village
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   J&#39;ai essayé de faire du jang mais je ne fais pas de délicieux jang. Combien d&#39;efforts comparez-vous à l&#39;exécution d&#39;un maître qui est sur le marché depuis toujours?
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sunchang Red Pepper Village - Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/c2a0a872-c44f-46b9-b2fa-acce17271754.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sunchang Red Pepper Village
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Info voyage
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Centre d&#39;expérience Sunchang Paste
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Adresse: 55, Folk Village-gil, Sunchang-eup, Sunchang-gun, Jeollabuk-do
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Programme d&#39;expérience: faire de la pâte de poivron rouge traditionnelle de Soonchang, faire de la cuisine coréenne, faire de l&#39;injeol, faire du tofu traditionnel
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Lors de l&#39;utilisation du programme d&#39;expérience, vous pouvez utiliser les installations d&#39;hébergement dans la salle d&#39;expérience.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.janghada.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.janghada.com/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    ※ Les informations ci-dessus ont été mises à jour en mars 2017 et peuvent changer par la suite, veuillez donc vérifier avant de voyager.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    ※ Les informations telles que le texte, les photos et les vidéos utilisées dans cet article sont protégées par les droits d&#39;auteur de l&#39;Organisation coréenne du tourisme, de sorte que l&#39;utilisation non autorisée de l&#39;article est interdite.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Corea - Ponga pasta de pimiento rojo, bata el pastel de arroz, prepare arroz y experimente Jangchang</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/put-red-pepper-paste-beat-rice-cake-make-rice-and-experience-jangchang-53-es/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 11:10:19 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/put-red-pepper-paste-beat-rice-cake-make-rice-and-experience-jangchang-53-es/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;put-red-pepper-paste-beat-rice-cake-make-rice-and-experience-jangchang--53&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Centro de experiencia de pasta Sunchang - Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/53d8f481-6dc8-49a9-b87a-46168c297966.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Centro de experiencia de pasta Sunchang
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Ponga pasta de pimiento rojo, bata el pastel de arroz, prepare arroz y experimente Jangchang
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Corea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &#39;Jang Jang Sunchang&#39; es el eslogan de Sunchang. Esta es una buena expresión de Sunchang, famoso por gochujang. Si vas a Sunchang Gochujang, gochujang es Sunchang. Hice una pasta Jangjang tradicional de Sunchang, alimentos cocinados con salsa de soja e hice un programa de experiencia práctica para preparar bocadillos saludables. Los niños son muy divertidos e incluso comen deliciosos. Es una experiencia donde incluso los adultos se hacen felices.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Pastel de arroz picante masa de pizza ~
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   10 am el sábado. Tan pronto como llegue al Sunchang Jangjang Experience Hall, estará ocupado. El programa de experiencia de Jangjang tomará aproximadamente 2 horas, incluida la preparación de gochujang, la cocina de gochujang y el condimento de pasteles de arroz y tofu.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Experiencia de fabricación de pizza Gochujang Bulgogi - Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/f87c9666-904b-4b36-a2e5-ff96487f22d5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Experiencia de fabricación de pizza Gochujang Bulgogi
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Para hacer un arreglo de tiempo efectivo, primero cocinamos el Jangjang, luego hacemos el Injeolmi y Tumbap afuera, y finalmente, hacemos Gochujang. El plato de hoy está hecho de pizza gochujang con bulgogi gochujang. Además de Gochujang Bulgogi Pizza, puedes elegir entre Kimchi, Gochujang Spaghetti, Cheonggukjang-jjigae, Cheese Tteokbokki, Gochujang Namul Gimbap, etc. Lo interesante es que en lugar de masa para pizza, corta el pastel de arroz en moldes finos como el pastel de arroz para arroz Sopa de pastel. Todo lo que necesitas hacer es verter la masa encima para que los pasteles de arroz no se caigan y se peguen. Coloque el bulgogi sazonado con pasta de pimiento rojo sobre la masa de la torta de arroz y espolvoree las verduras picadas con la cobertura. Espolvorea un montón de queso encima y decora con salsa de tomate. Encienda la sartén con la tapa puesta y espere a que termine.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Experiencia de fabricación de pizza Gochujang Bulgogi - Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/e70b367f-c051-470e-aa49-1d0a104cc813.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Experiencia de fabricación de pizza Gochujang Bulgogi
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Cierra los oídos y di &#34;Sí ~&#34;
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Mientras la pizza está madura, sal a preparar Injeolmi y arroz. Injeolmi es la clave para hacer pasteles de arroz. Al principio, los adultos tienen que turnarse para machacar los granos de arroz. Tteokme es más divertido y menos difícil de soportar y vencer golpeándose entre sí.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Injeolmi haciendo experiencia - Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/b825354b-5195-4644-bd30-d26e2ab5368d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Injeolmi haciendo experiencia
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Cuando el arroz se triture con moderación, cámbielo a pastel de arroz para niños y déselo a los niños. Como una obra divertida, los niños esperan ansiosamente su turno. Después de golpear tres o cuatro veces, el sonido de los pasteles de arroz se hace cada vez más fuerte. La máquina de freír en caliente negra se gira suavemente para aumentar la presión. Los niños aprietan los mangos para que puedan verlos una vez, pero estoy emocionado de saber lo que está saliendo. Finalmente, voy a explotar. Los niños cierran los oídos con fuerza y miran la máquina. &#34;뻥 ~!&#34; El vapor blanco está aumentando con un ruido fuerte. Los niños entraron rápidamente cuando pusieron arroz con arroz en una canasta grande. Llena tus manos de codicia y entierra tu cara. Se fríe rápidamente y su sabor es muy delicioso. Los niños comen más arroz que cualquier merienda.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Tempura haciendo experiencia - Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/a410f73b-8f81-4797-b6c5-ae4b9ddddde0.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Tempura haciendo experiencia
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Mientras tanto, Injeolmi se completa y se empapa con harina de soja. Niño que corta pastel de arroz, niño que obtiene polvo de soja, experiencia que está detrás de escena y ocupada para comer ... Disfrutan haciendo y comiendo de diferentes maneras. Injeolmi es una buena combinación de harina de soja mezclada con pasteles de arroz masticables. Lo hice y lo comí de inmediato, así que los cortes de arroz y el arroz son deliciosos. No es un sabor de recuerdos, sino un sabor que los supera.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Tempura haciendo experiencia - Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/8a5a586c-c153-44c9-8349-b43247edf372.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Tempura haciendo experiencia
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Prueba pizza y prepara gochujang
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Después de la experiencia al aire libre, regrese a la sala de experiencias. Una pizza bien horneada está esperando. Gracias a la pasta de pimiento rojo en la masa hecha con pasteles de arroz, la pizza es perfecta para el gusto de los coreanos. El condimento de Gochujang es un poco picante, pero se come al instante. Después de la degustación de pizza, lo más destacado del día es la experiencia de hacer pasta de pimiento rojo.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Gochujang haciendo experiencia - Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/db431458-a017-4f04-bc95-81583fd25ef8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Gochujang haciendo experiencia
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Primero, escucha por qué Sunchang Gochujang es delicioso y cómo hacerlo. En otras regiones, el meju cuadrado se usa para hacer salsa de soja, pasta de soja y pasta de pimiento rojo. Lo inusual es que el meju generalmente se recolecta a principios de invierno, pero Sunchang hace meju a fines de agosto. Cuando hace calor, los microorganismos que agregan el rico sabor de la pasta de pimiento rojo se multiplican bien. Otra característica especial de Sunchang es que no solo está hecho de soja sino que también se mezcla con arroz en una proporción de 6: 4. La pasta de soja se empapa en invierno y se envejece durante más de 6 meses.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Gochujang haciendo experiencia - Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/1efcd5cf-a80c-48a5-90f8-4192beb0051b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Gochujang haciendo experiencia
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Después de escuchar la explicación, tómese un momento para hacer una prueba de gochujang. La experiencia es sorprendentemente simple. Distribuya tazones de harina de mew, polvo de pimiento rojo, Sikhye, sal y malta en las proporciones correctas por equipo. El secreto es mezclarlos bien para que no se agrupen. Mezclar y sumergirlo con el dedo para probarlo. Es un sabor extraño. Gochujang no se hace de inmediato porque necesita ser envejecido. A medida que pasa el tiempo, nuestro Jangjang tradicional, que sabe más profundo, es realmente una comida lenta. Si dejas el gochujang hecho por los visitantes en la sala de experiencias, los juntarán y mezclarán bien. En lugar de hacerlo en el sitio, recibirá un gochujang bien cocido uno por uno.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Gochujang haciendo experiencia - Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/95a6900a-2f9b-435f-8f5f-ac2589bc5cd1.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Gochujang haciendo experiencia
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Gochujang Village para preservar el sabor tradicional.
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Después de disfrutar la experiencia de Jangju, eche un vistazo a la aldea de Gochujang. En Kochujang Village, Kochujang puede ser producido y vendido solo si eres reconocido como un maestro de Kochujang. La mercancía en el mercado es casi confiable. Todo lo que ves aquí es la tienda de pasta de pimiento rojo, así que es como si estuvieras en el país de la pasta de pimiento rojo. Gochujang Nara no es un pequeño pueblo de Gochujang, pero es suficiente para captar nuestro gusto.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sunchang Red Pepper Village - Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/908bc071-6100-44bd-b2bf-ebc3d5bf76b1.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sunchang Red Pepper Village
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   En el patio, hay muchos frascos de pasta de pimiento rojo, miso y salsa de soja, y los encurtidos huelen a pol-pol en la tienda. Jangjang es bueno, pero los encurtidos de ladrón de arroz son igual de populares. Hay muchos tipos de encurtidos como ciruelas, rábanos, pepinos, semillas de ajo, caquis dulces, hojas de sésamo, deodeok, vieiras, ostras, etc. Puede probar y elegir diferentes tipos de encurtidos.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sunchang Red Pepper Village - Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/96e7229a-930e-4e62-a485-4b6c7c33d26d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sunchang Red Pepper Village
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   También hay una jarra de vino de arroz al lado. Los encurtidos que se comen en la boca son salados, pero cuando los prueba después de beber el vino de arroz, sale el sonido &#34;kya&#34;. Cheonggukjang huele muy poco y sabe tan suave que los niños comen bien. Los pasos son geniales cuando recoges pepinillos en una pasta de pimiento picante hecha por un maestro.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sunchang Red Pepper Village - Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/3cfce9b9-5aa5-4e90-8aeb-da6ea03dbf5a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sunchang Red Pepper Village
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   He intentado hacer jang pero no hago jang delicioso. ¿Cuánto esfuerzo compara con la mano de obra de un maestro que ha estado en el mercado desde siempre?
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sunchang Red Pepper Village - Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/c2a0a872-c44f-46b9-b2fa-acce17271754.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sunchang Red Pepper Village
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Información de viaje
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Centro de experiencia de pasta Sunchang
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Dirección: 55, Folk Village-gil, Sunchang-eup, Sunchang-gun, Jeollabuk-do
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Programa de experiencia: hacer la pasta de pimiento rojo tradicional de Soonchang, hacer cocina coreana, hacer inyecciones, hacer tofu tradicional
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Cuando use el programa de experiencia, puede usar las instalaciones de alojamiento en la sala de experiencias.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.janghada.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.janghada.com/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    ※ La información anterior se actualizó en marzo de 2017 y puede cambiar después, así que verifique antes de viajar.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    ※ La información como texto, fotos y videos utilizados en este artículo tiene copyright de la Organización de Turismo de Corea, por lo que está prohibido el uso no autorizado del artículo.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunchang-Pistole, Jeonbuk, Korea - Setzen Sie rote Pfefferpaste ein, schlagen Sie Reiskuchen, machen Sie Reis und erleben Sie Jangchang</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/put-red-pepper-paste-beat-rice-cake-make-rice-and-experience-jangchang-53-de/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 11:08:07 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/put-red-pepper-paste-beat-rice-cake-make-rice-and-experience-jangchang-53-de/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;put-red-pepper-paste-beat-rice-cake-make-rice-and-experience-jangchang--53&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Sunchang Paste Experience Center - Sunchang-Pistole, Jeonbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/53d8f481-6dc8-49a9-b87a-46168c297966.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Sunchang Paste Experience Center
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Setzen Sie rote Pfefferpaste ein, schlagen Sie Reiskuchen, machen Sie Reis und erleben Sie Jangchang
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Sunchang-Pistole, Jeonbuk, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &#34;Jang Jang Sunchang&#34; ist Sunchangs Slogan. Dies ist ein guter Ausdruck von Sunchang, berühmt für Gochujang. Wenn Sie nach Sunchang Gochujang gehen, ist Gochujang Sunchang. Ich machte eine traditionelle Jangjang-Paste aus Sunchang, kochte Lebensmittel mit Sojasauce und machte ein praktisches Erlebnisprogramm, um gesunde Snacks zuzubereiten. Die Kinder sind sehr lustig und essen sogar lecker. Es ist eine Erfahrung, in der auch Erwachsene glücklich werden.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Würziger Reiskuchen-Pizzateig ~
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Samstag 10 Uhr. Sobald Sie in der Sunchang Jangjang Experience Hall ankommen, sind Sie beschäftigt. Das Jangjang-Erlebnisprogramm dauert ca. 2 Stunden und umfasst die Herstellung von Gochujang, das Kochen von Gochujang sowie das Würzen von Reiskuchen und Tofu.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Gochujang Bulgogi Pizza machen Erfahrung - Sunchang-Pistole, Jeonbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/f87c9666-904b-4b36-a2e5-ff96487f22d5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Gochujang Bulgogi Pizza machen Erfahrung
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Um eine effektive Zeitvereinbarung zu treffen, haben wir zuerst den Jangjang gekocht, dann die Injeolmi und Tumbap draußen und schließlich Gochujang. Das heutige Gericht besteht aus Gochujang-Pizza mit Gochujang-Bulgogi. Neben Gochujang Bulgogi Pizza können Sie zwischen Kimchi, Gochujang Spaghetti, Cheonggukjang-Jjigae, Käse Tteokbokki, Gochujang Namul Gimbap usw. wählen. Interessant ist, dass Sie anstelle von Pizzateig den Reiskuchen in dünne Pfannen wie Reiskuchen für Reis schneiden Kuchensuppe. Alles was Sie tun müssen, ist den Teig darüber zu gießen, damit die Reiskuchen nicht fallen und zusammenkleben. Den mit roter Pfefferpaste gewürzten Bulgogi auf den Reiskuchenteig legen und das gehackte Gemüse mit Belag bestreuen. Mit viel Käse bestreuen und mit Ketchup dekorieren. Schalten Sie die Pfanne bei geschlossenem Deckel ein und warten Sie, bis sie fertig ist.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Gochujang Bulgogi Pizza machen Erfahrung - Sunchang-Pistole, Jeonbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/e70b367f-c051-470e-aa49-1d0a104cc813.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Gochujang Bulgogi Pizza machen Erfahrung
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Schließe deine Ohren und sage &#34;Yeah ~&#34;
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Während die Pizza reif ist, gehen Sie nach draußen, um Injeolmi und Reis zuzubereiten. Injeolmi ist der Schlüssel zur Herstellung von Reiskuchen. Zuerst müssen sich Erwachsene abwechseln, um Reiskörner zu zerkleinern. Tteokme macht mehr Spaß und ist weniger schwierig zu stehen und sich gegenseitig zu schlagen, indem man sich gegenseitig schlägt.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Injeolmi Erfahrung machen - Sunchang-Pistole, Jeonbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/b825354b-5195-4644-bd30-d26e2ab5368d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Injeolmi Erfahrung machen
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Wenn der Reis in Maßen zerkleinert ist, ändern Sie ihn in Kinderreiskuchen und geben Sie ihn den Kindern. Wie ein lustiges Stück warten die Kinder gespannt darauf, dass sie an die Reihe kommen. Nach drei- oder viermaligem Schlagen wird das Geräusch von Reiskuchen immer lauter. Die schwarze Heißbratmaschine wird vorsichtig gedreht, um den Druck zu erhöhen. Die Kinder werden auf die Griffe gedrückt, damit sie sie einmal sehen können, aber ich bin gespannt, was herauskommt. Schließlich werde ich explodieren. Die Kinder schließen fest die Ohren und schauen auf die Maschine. &#34;뻥 ~!&#34; Weißer Dampf steigt mit einem lauten Geräusch auf. Die Kinder stürmten herein, als sie Reisreis in einen großen Korb legten. Fülle deine Hände mit Gier und begrabe dein Gesicht. Es ist schnell gebraten und sein Geschmack ist sehr lecker. Kinder essen mehr Reis als jeder Snack.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Tempura Erfahrung machen - Sunchang-Pistole, Jeonbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/a410f73b-8f81-4797-b6c5-ae4b9ddddde0.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Tempura Erfahrung machen
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In der Zwischenzeit wird Injeolmi fertiggestellt und mit Sojamehl getränkt. Kind, das Reiskuchen schneidet, Kind, das Sojabohnenpulver bekommt, Erfahrung hinter den Kulissen und beschäftigt zu essen…. Sie genießen es, auf unterschiedliche Weise zuzubereiten und zu essen. Injeolmi ist eine gute Kombination aus Sojabohnenmehl und zähen Reiskuchen. Ich habe es gemacht und sofort gegessen, also sind die Reisstücke und der Reis köstlich. Es ist kein Geschmack von Erinnerungen, sondern ein Geschmack, der Erinnerungen übertrifft.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Tempura Erfahrung machen - Sunchang-Pistole, Jeonbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/8a5a586c-c153-44c9-8349-b43247edf372.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Tempura Erfahrung machen
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Probieren Sie Pizza und machen Sie Gochujang
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Gehen Sie nach dem Outdoor-Erlebnis zurück in den Erlebnisraum. Eine gut gebackene Pizza wartet. Dank der roten Pfefferpaste auf dem Teig aus Reiskuchen ist die Pizza perfekt für den Geschmack der Koreaner. Gochujang-Gewürze sind etwas scharf, werden aber sofort gegessen. Nach der Pizza-Verkostung ist der Höhepunkt des Tages das Erlebnis der Herstellung von Paprika-Paste.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Gochujang Erfahrung machen - Sunchang-Pistole, Jeonbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/db431458-a017-4f04-bc95-81583fd25ef8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Gochujang Erfahrung machen
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Hören Sie zuerst, warum Sunchang Gochujang köstlich ist und wie man es macht. In anderen Regionen wird aus quadratischem Meju Sojasauce, Sojabohnenpaste und rote Pfefferpaste hergestellt. Was ungewöhnlich ist, ist, dass der Meju normalerweise im frühen Winter gepflückt wird, aber Sunchang macht Meju Ende August. Bei heißem Wetter vermehren sich die Mikroorganismen, die den reichen Geschmack der roten Pfefferpaste hinzufügen, gut. Eine weitere Besonderheit von Sunchang ist, dass es nicht nur aus Sojabohnen hergestellt, sondern auch im Verhältnis 6: 4 mit Reis gemischt wird. Sojabohnenpaste wird im Winter eingeweicht und länger als 6 Monate gereift.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Gochujang Erfahrung machen - Sunchang-Pistole, Jeonbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/1efcd5cf-a80c-48a5-90f8-4192beb0051b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Gochujang Erfahrung machen
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   EIN
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Gochujang Erfahrung machen - Sunchang-Pistole, Jeonbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/95a6900a-2f9b-435f-8f5f-ac2589bc5cd1.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Gochujang Erfahrung machen
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Gochujang Village, um den traditionellen Geschmack zu bewahren
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Schauen Sie sich nach dem Jangju-Erlebnis im Dorf Gochujang um. Im Dorf Kochujang kann Kochujang nur hergestellt und verkauft werden, wenn Sie als Meister von Kochujang anerkannt sind. Die Ware auf dem Markt ist nahezu zuverlässig. Alles, was Sie hier sehen, ist der Laden mit roter Pfefferpaste. Es ist also, als wären Sie im Land der roten Pfefferpaste. Gochujang Nara ist kein kleines Gochujang-Dorf, aber es reicht aus, um unseren Geschmack zu fangen.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sunchang Red Pepper Village - Sunchang-Pistole, Jeonbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/908bc071-6100-44bd-b2bf-ebc3d5bf76b1.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sunchang Red Pepper Village
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Auf dem Hof gibt es viele Gläser mit roter Pfefferpaste, Miso und Sojasauce, und die Gurken riechen im Laden nach Pol-Pol. Jangjang ist gut, aber Reisdiebgurken sind genauso beliebt. Es gibt viele Arten von Gurken wie Pflaumen, Radieschen, Gurken, Knoblauchsamen, süße Kakis, Sesamblätter, Deodeok, Jakobsmuscheln, Austern usw. Sie können verschiedene Arten von Gurken probieren und auswählen.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sunchang Red Pepper Village - Sunchang-Pistole, Jeonbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/96e7229a-930e-4e62-a485-4b6c7c33d26d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sunchang Red Pepper Village
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Es gibt auch ein Reisweinglas daneben. Die Gurken, die im Mund gegessen werden, sind salzig, aber wenn Sie sie nach dem Schlürfen des Reisweins probieren, ertönt ein &#34;Kya&#34; -Ton. Cheonggukjang riecht sehr wenig und schmeckt so mild, dass Kinder gut essen. Die Schritte sind so großartig, wenn Sie Gurken in einer Paprika-Paste von einem Meister aufnehmen.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sunchang Red Pepper Village - Sunchang-Pistole, Jeonbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/3cfce9b9-5aa5-4e90-8aeb-da6ea03dbf5a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sunchang Red Pepper Village
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Ich habe versucht, Jang zu machen, aber ich mache keinen leckeren Jang. Wie viel Aufwand vergleichen Sie mit der Verarbeitung eines Meisters, der schon immer auf dem Markt war?
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sunchang Red Pepper Village - Sunchang-Pistole, Jeonbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/c2a0a872-c44f-46b9-b2fa-acce17271754.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sunchang Red Pepper Village
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Reiseinformationen
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Sunchang Paste Experience Center
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Adresse: 55, Folk Village-Gil, Sunchang-Eup, Sunchang-Gun, Jeollabuk-Do
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Erlebnisprogramm: Machen Sie Soonchang traditionelle rote Pfefferpaste, machen Sie koreanische Küche, machen Sie Injeol, machen Sie traditionellen Tofu
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Wenn Sie das Erlebnisprogramm nutzen, können Sie die Unterbringungsmöglichkeiten in der Erlebnishalle nutzen.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.janghada.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.janghada.com/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    ※ Die oben genannten Informationen wurden im März 2017 aktualisiert und können sich später ändern. Bitte überprüfen Sie dies, bevor Sie reisen.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    ※ Die in diesem Artikel verwendeten Informationen wie Text, Fotos und Videos sind von der Korea Tourism Organization urheberrechtlich geschützt. Daher ist die unbefugte Verwendung des Artikels untersagt.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>韩国全北新昌郡 - 放入红辣椒酱，打成年糕，做米饭，体验长场</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/put-red-pepper-paste-beat-rice-cake-make-rice-and-experience-jangchang-53-zh-cn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 11:05:55 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/put-red-pepper-paste-beat-rice-cake-make-rice-and-experience-jangchang-53-zh-cn/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;put-red-pepper-paste-beat-rice-cake-make-rice-and-experience-jangchang--53&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;新昌粘贴体验中心 - 韩国全北新昌郡 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/53d8f481-6dc8-49a9-b87a-46168c297966.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    新昌粘贴体验中心
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   放入红辣椒酱，打成年糕，做米饭，体验长场
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    韩国全北新昌郡
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   “张长孙昌”是孙昌的口号。 这是一个以gochujang闻名的Sunchang的很好表达。 如果去Sunchang Gochujang，gochujang就是Sunchang。 我制作了传统的昌昌酱姜酱，用酱油制成的熟食，并制作了动手体验程序来制作健康的零食。 孩子们很有趣，甚至吃得很好吃。 这是即使成年人也变得快乐的经历。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   香辣年糕披萨面团〜
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   星期六上午10点。 一到达新昌长章体验馆，您就会很忙。 Jangjang体验计划大约需要2个小时，包括gochujang的制作，gochujang的烹饪以及年糕和豆腐的调味。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Gochujang Bulgogi披萨制作经验 - 韩国全北新昌郡 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/f87c9666-904b-4b36-a2e5-ff96487f22d5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Gochujang Bulgogi披萨制作经验
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   为了安排有效的时间，我们首先煮了长酱，然后在外面煮了Injeolmi和Tumbap，最后再煮了Gochujang。 今天的菜是用gochujang披萨和gochujang烤肉制成的。 除了Gochujang Bulgogi Pizza之外，您还可以选择泡菜，Gochujang意大利面，Cheonggukjang-jjigae，Cheese Tteokbokki，Gochujang Namul紫菜包饭等。有趣的是，将米糕切成薄薄的锅（例如大米饭糕）代替了比萨面团 蛋糕汤。 您所需要做的就是将面团倒在上面，以免年糕掉落并粘在一起。 将用红辣椒酱调味的烤肉放在米糕面团上，并撒上切碎的蔬菜。 在上面撒上大量奶酪，并用番茄酱装饰。 打开锅盖并打开锅盖，等待其完成。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Gochujang Bulgogi披萨制作经验 - 韩国全北新昌郡 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/e70b367f-c051-470e-aa49-1d0a104cc813.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Gochujang Bulgogi披萨制作经验
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   闭上你的耳朵，说“是的〜”
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   比萨成熟后，出去做Injeolmi和米饭。 Injeolmi是制作年糕的关键。 首先，成年人必须轮流碾碎米粒。 Tteokme更有趣，站立和互相殴打也更容易。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Injeolmi制作经验 - 韩国全北新昌郡 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/b825354b-5195-4644-bd30-d26e2ab5368d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Injeolmi制作经验
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   将米适量压碎后，将其更改为儿童年糕，然后交给儿童。 孩子们像一个有趣的戏，焦急地等待着轮到他们。 打了三到四遍之后，年糕的声音越来越大。 轻轻转动黑色热油炸机以增加压力。 孩子们紧紧抓住手柄，这样他们就可以看到一次，但是我很高兴知道会发生什么。 最后，我要爆炸了。 孩子们紧紧地闭上耳朵，看着机器。 “뻥〜！” 白色的蒸汽以巨大的噪音升起。 孩子们把大米饭放在一个大篮子里时冲了进去。 充满贪婪的双手，掩埋脸庞。 它炸得很快，味道很鲜美。 孩子们吃的米饭比零食要多。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;天妇罗制作经验 - 韩国全北新昌郡 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/a410f73b-8f81-4797-b6c5-ae4b9ddddde0.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     天妇罗制作经验
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   同时，Injeolmi完成并用豆粉浸泡。 切年糕的孩子，得到大豆粉的孩子，幕后的经验和忙着吃饭……。 他们喜欢以不同的方式制作和饮食。 Injeolmi是将大豆粉与耐嚼的年糕相混合的良好组合。 我马上就吃了，所以米饭和米饭都很好吃。 它不是记忆的味道，而是超越记忆的味道。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;天妇罗制作经验 - 韩国全北新昌郡 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/8a5a586c-c153-44c9-8349-b43247edf372.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     天妇罗制作经验
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   品尝披萨，制作酱油
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   户外体验结束后，回到体验室。 一个烤好的比萨饼正在等待。 多亏了用年糕制成的面团上的红辣椒酱，所以比萨饼非常适合韩国人的口味。 Gochujang调味料有点辛辣，但可以立即食用。 品尝披萨后，当天的重头戏是制作红辣椒酱。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;辣椒酱制作经验 - 韩国全北新昌郡 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/db431458-a017-4f04-bc95-81583fd25ef8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     辣椒酱制作经验
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   首先，听听为什么Sunchang Gochujang很美味，以及如何制作。 在其他地区，方形梅酒用于制作酱油，大豆糊和红辣椒糊。 与众不同的是，冰酒通常在初冬采摘，而孙场则在8月底生产冰酒。 天气炎热时，添加红辣椒酱丰富风味的微生物繁殖良好。 Sunchang的另一个特色是它不仅由大豆制成，而且还与大米以6：4的比例混合。 冬季将大豆酱浸泡，并老化6个月以上。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;辣椒酱制作经验 - 韩国全北新昌郡 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/1efcd5cf-a80c-48a5-90f8-4192beb0051b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     辣椒酱制作经验
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   听完说明后，花点时间做一个测测测验。 体验非常简单。 团队按正确比例分配碗状的猫粉，红辣椒粉，锡克叶，盐和麦芽。 秘诀是将它们混合均匀，以免它们结块。 混合起来，用手指蘸一下即可品尝。 真奇怪 Gochujang不能立即制成，因为它需要老化。 随着时间的流逝，我们口味更深的传统长酱确实是慢食。 如果您将游客制作的gochujang留在体验馆中，他们会把它们聚集在一起并充分混合。 与其在现场进行制作，不如将其一步一步地送给您。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;辣椒酱制作经验 - 韩国全北新昌郡 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/95a6900a-2f9b-435f-8f5f-ac2589bc5cd1.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     辣椒酱制作经验
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Gochujang村保留传统风味
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   享受过济州岛的体验后，可以看看Gochujang村。 在Kochujang村，只有当您被公认是Kochujang的主人时，才能生产和销售Kochujang。 市场上的商品几乎是可靠的。 您在这里看到的只是红辣椒酱商店，就好像您在红辣椒酱国家一样。 Gochujang Nara不是Gochujang的小村庄，但是足以吸引我们的口味。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;孙昌红辣椒村 - 韩国全北新昌郡 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/908bc071-6100-44bd-b2bf-ebc3d5bf76b1.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     孙昌红辣椒村
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   在院子里，有很多罐红辣椒酱，味o和酱油，而酱菜的味道就像店里的波尔多波尔。 长酱很好，但米贼泡菜也很受欢迎。 酱菜种类繁多，例如李子，萝卜，黄瓜，大蒜种子，甜柿子，芝麻叶，deodeok，扇贝，牡蛎等。您可以品尝和选择不同种类的酱菜。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;孙昌红辣椒村 - 韩国全北新昌郡 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/96e7229a-930e-4e62-a485-4b6c7c33d26d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     孙昌红辣椒村
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   旁边还有一个黄酒缸。 口中吃的咸菜很咸，但是当您在喝黄酒后品尝它们时，会发出“ k”的声音。 清国酱闻起来很少，味道温和，以至于孩子们吃得很好。 当您在主人制作的辣椒酱中腌制泡菜时，步骤非常好。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;孙昌红辣椒村 - 韩国全北新昌郡 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/3cfce9b9-5aa5-4e90-8aeb-da6ea03dbf5a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     孙昌红辣椒村
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   我试过做章，但没有做好章。 您与永远在市场上的大师的做工相比要付出多少努力？
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;孙昌红辣椒村 - 韩国全北新昌郡 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/c2a0a872-c44f-46b9-b2fa-acce17271754.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     孙昌红辣椒村
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   旅游信息
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     新昌粘贴体验中心
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -地址：全罗北道新昌郡新昌邑民俗村街55
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -体验计划：制作顺昌传统红辣椒酱，制作韩国料理，制作Injeol，制作传统豆腐
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -使用体验计划时，您可以使用体验厅中的住宿设施。
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.janghada.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.janghada.com/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    ※以上信息为2017年3月更新的信息，之后可能会发生变化，因此请在旅行前确认。
    &lt;br/&gt;
    ※本文中使用的文字，照片和视频等信息受韩国旅游组织版权保护，因此禁止未经授权使用本文。
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Korea - Put red pepper paste, beat rice cake, make rice, and experience Jangchang</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/put-red-pepper-paste-beat-rice-cake-make-rice-and-experience-jangchang-53/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 11:03:40 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/put-red-pepper-paste-beat-rice-cake-make-rice-and-experience-jangchang-53/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;put-red-pepper-paste-beat-rice-cake-make-rice-and-experience-jangchang--53&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Sunchang Paste Experience Center - Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/53d8f481-6dc8-49a9-b87a-46168c297966.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Sunchang Paste Experience Center
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Put red pepper paste, beat rice cake, make rice, and experience Jangchang
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &#39;Jang Jang Sunchang&#39; is Sunchang&#39;s slogan. This is a good expression of Sunchang, famous for gochujang. If you go to Sunchang Gochujang, gochujang is Sunchang. I made a traditional Jangjang paste of Sunchang, cooked foods made with soy sauce, and made a hands-on experience program to make healthy snacks. The children are very funny and even eat delicious. It is an experience where even adults grow happy.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Spicy rice cake pizza dough ~
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   10 am Saturday. As soon as you arrive at Sunchang Jangjang Experience Hall, you will be busy. The Jangjang experience program will take about 2 hours, including gochujang making, gochujang cooking, and seasoning of rice cakes and tofu.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Gochujang Bulgogi Pizza Making Experience - Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/f87c9666-904b-4b36-a2e5-ff96487f22d5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Gochujang Bulgogi Pizza Making Experience
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   To make an effective time arrangement, we first cooked the Jangjang, then make the Injeolmi and Tumbap outside, and finally, make Gochujang. Today&#39;s dish is made from gochujang pizza with gochujang bulgogi. In addition to Gochujang Bulgogi Pizza, you can choose from Kimchi, Gochujang Spaghetti, Cheonggukjang-jjigae, Cheese Tteokbokki, Gochujang Namul Gimbap, etc. What&#39;s interesting is that instead of pizza dough, cut the rice cake into thin pans like rice cake for rice cake soup. All you need to do is pour the dough on top so that the rice cakes don&#39;t fall and stick together. Place bulgogi seasoned with red pepper paste on top of rice cake dough and sprinkle chopped vegetables with topping. Sprinkle plenty of cheese on top and decorate with ketchup. Switch on the pan with the lid on and wait for it to finish.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Gochujang Bulgogi Pizza Making Experience - Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/e70b367f-c051-470e-aa49-1d0a104cc813.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Gochujang Bulgogi Pizza Making Experience
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Close your ears and say &#34;Yeah ~&#34;
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   While the pizza is ripe, go outside to make Injeolmi and rice. Injeolmi is the key to rice cake making. At first, adults have to take turns to crush rice grains. Tteokme is more fun and less difficult to stand and beat each other by hitting each other.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Injeolmi making experience - Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/b825354b-5195-4644-bd30-d26e2ab5368d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Injeolmi making experience
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   When the rice is crushed in moderation, change it to children&#39;s rice cake and give it to the children. Like a funny play, the children wait anxiously for their turn. After hitting three or four times, the sound of rice cakes is getting louder and louder. The black hot frying machine is turned gently to increase the pressure. The children are squeezed the handles so that they can see them once, but I&#39;m excited to know what&#39;s coming out. Finally, I&#39;m going to explode. The children close their ears tightly and look at the machine. &#34;뻥 ~!&#34; White steam is rising with a loud noise. The children rushed in when they put rice rice in a large basket. Fill your hands with greed and bury your face. It is fried quickly and its taste is very delicious. Children eat more rice than any snack.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Tempura making experience - Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/a410f73b-8f81-4797-b6c5-ae4b9ddddde0.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Tempura making experience
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In the meantime, Injeolmi is completed and soaked with soy flour. Child who slices rice cake, child who gets soybean powder, experience that is behind the scenes and busy to eat… . They enjoy making and eating in different ways. Injeolmi is a good combination of soybean flour mixed with chewy rice cakes. I made it and ate it right away, so the cuts of rice and the rice are delicious. It is not a taste of memories, but a taste that surpasses memories.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Tempura making experience - Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/8a5a586c-c153-44c9-8349-b43247edf372.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Tempura making experience
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Taste pizza and make gochujang
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   After the outdoor experience, go back into the experience room. A well baked pizza is waiting. Thanks to the red pepper paste on the dough made with rice cakes, the pizza is perfect for the taste of Koreans. Gochujang seasoning is a bit spicy, but it is eaten instantly. After the pizza tasting, the highlight of the day is the red pepper paste making experience.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Gochujang making experience - Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/db431458-a017-4f04-bc95-81583fd25ef8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Gochujang making experience
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   First, listen to why Sunchang Gochujang is delicious and how to make it. In other regions, square meju is used to make soy sauce, soybean paste, and red pepper paste. What is unusual is that the meju is usually picked in early winter, but Sunchang makes meju at the end of August. When the weather is hot, the microorganisms that add the rich flavor of red pepper paste multiply well. Another special feature of Sunchang is that it is not only made from soybeans but also mixed with rice at 6: 4 ratio. Soybean paste is soaked in winter and aged for more than 6 months.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Gochujang making experience - Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/1efcd5cf-a80c-48a5-90f8-4192beb0051b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Gochujang making experience
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   After listening to the explanation, take a moment to make a gochujang quiz. The experience is surprisingly simple. Distribute bowls of mew flour, red pepper powder, Sikhye, salt, and malt in the right proportions by team. The secret is to mix them well so that they don&#39;t clump together. Mix it up and dip it with your finger to taste it. It&#39;s a strange taste. Gochujang is not made right away because it needs to be aged. As time goes by, our traditional Jangjang, which tastes deeper, is truly slow food. If you leave the gochujang made by the visitors in the experience hall, they will gather them together and mix them well. Instead of making it on-site, you will receive a well-cooked gochujang one by one.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Gochujang making experience - Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/95a6900a-2f9b-435f-8f5f-ac2589bc5cd1.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Gochujang making experience
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Gochujang Village to preserve the traditional taste
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   After enjoying the Jangju experience, take a look around Gochujang Village. In Kochujang Village, Kochujang can be produced and sold only if you are recognized as a master of Kochujang. The merchandise in the market is almost reliable. All you see here is the red pepper paste shop, so it&#39;s as if you&#39;re in the red pepper paste country. Gochujang Nara is not a small Gochujang village, but it is enough to catch our taste.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sunchang Red Pepper Village - Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/908bc071-6100-44bd-b2bf-ebc3d5bf76b1.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sunchang Red Pepper Village
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In the yard, there are many jars of red pepper paste, miso and soy sauce, and the pickles smell like pol-pol in the store. Jangjang is good, but rice thief pickles are just as popular. There are many kinds of pickles such as plums, radishes, cucumbers, garlic seeds, sweet persimmons, sesame leaves, deodeok, scallops, oysters, etc. You can taste and choose different kinds of pickles.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sunchang Red Pepper Village - Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/96e7229a-930e-4e62-a485-4b6c7c33d26d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sunchang Red Pepper Village
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   There is also a rice wine jar next to it. The pickles that are eaten in the mouth are salty, but when you taste them after sipping the rice wine, &#34;kya&#34; sound comes out. Cheonggukjang smells very little and tastes so mild that children eat well. The steps are so great when you pick up pickles in a hot pepper paste made by a master.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sunchang Red Pepper Village - Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/3cfce9b9-5aa5-4e90-8aeb-da6ea03dbf5a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sunchang Red Pepper Village
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   I have tried making jang but I do not make delicious jang. How much effort do you compare to the workmanship of a master who has been in the market forever?
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sunchang Red Pepper Village - Sunchang-gun, Jeonbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/53/c2a0a872-c44f-46b9-b2fa-acce17271754.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sunchang Red Pepper Village
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel info
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Sunchang Paste Experience Center
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Address: 55, Folk Village-gil, Sunchang-eup, Sunchang-gun, Jeollabuk-do
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Experience program: Make Soonchang Traditional Red Pepper Paste, Make Korean Cuisine, Make Injeol, Make Traditional Tofu
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -When using the experience program, you can use the accommodation facilities in the experience hall.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.janghada.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.janghada.com/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    ※ The above information was updated in March 2017 and may change afterwards, so please check before you travel.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    ※ The information such as text, photos and videos used in this article is copyrighted by Korea Tourism Organization, so unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>