<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Geoje-si on Every Corner of Korea</title>
    <link>https://codecorea.github.io/tags/geoje-si/</link>
    <description>Every Corner of Korea (Geoje-si)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 18:18:30 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="https://codecorea.github.io/tags/geoje-si/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The water delicacy “Mulgegi-tang” is the winter delicacy - Geoje-si, Gyeongnam, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/the-water-delicacy-mulgegitang-is-the-winter-delicacy-277/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 18:18:30 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/the-water-delicacy-mulgegitang-is-the-winter-delicacy-277/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Geoje-si, Gyeongnam, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;the-water-delicacy-mulgegitang-is-the-winter-delicacy--277&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Gujo La Village - Geoje-si, Gyeongnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/277/ff13d831-ddc4-4ccf-99b5-1a105353aeb1.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Gujo La Village
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   The water delicacy “Mulgegi-tang” is the winter delicacy
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Geoje-si, Gyeongnam, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    In winter, a special visitor comes to the fishing of the fishermen of Geoje Island. It is a guy called ‘meetchi’ or ‘water catfish’ that climbed from the deep sea to the coast during the spawning season from December to March. It is said that the water catfish was also called the &#39;water term bun.&#39; This is because when fish were caught, it was thrown into the sea, and the sound of “tumbang” sounded. It would be difficult for anyone who tasted the charm of water catfish to accept this myth.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    There are many sashimi restaurants and restaurants alongside Gujo-La Village&#39;s port and sea. The seasonal water catfish is having a short life in an aquarium. It looks like a soccer player&#39;s calf and a large body like a calf and a wide mouth like a catfish, but the eyes are so small ... If he is hungry, he eats the eggs of his own people, but he may not have been able to tell if they are eggs. When I take a picture and see it on a small camera screen, it looks like a tadpole. I am curious about the taste this fish will show.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    At least one piece of ‘Water Catfish Tang’ was written around the signboard. This is because water catfish is not a species caught throughout the four seasons. I entered a house and ordered a water catfish soup.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Fresh water catfish in a restaurant aquarium - Geoje-si, Gyeongnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/277/63a180bb-77db-4556-953f-a3844a9a0bd5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Fresh water catfish in a restaurant aquarium
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    If Geojedo is also a festival in Daegu, I asked the owner. “Which is better, Daegu-tang or Mulgi-tang?” “Daegu-tang is delicious, and water catfish-tang is also delicious. My home&#39;s Daegu-tang is more delicious. Did you come alone as you became more comfortable, and where did you come from? Questions are poured out one after another. And he willingly accepts the cooperation.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Fresh water catfish in a restaurant aquarium - Geoje-si, Gyeongnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/277/a14d0888-557e-4494-9ca0-afdd6eca32e5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Fresh water catfish in a restaurant aquarium
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    When he pulls out the guy who had attached the scaffold to the glass of the aquarium, it flickers twice, but the owner&#39;s arm is strong enough to shake. The freshness of water catfish is important because Geoje&#39;s water catfish soup is cooked clearly without kimchi or red pepper powder.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Water catfish - Geoje-si, Gyeongnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/277/fbf2bd17-c080-494c-84ca-f32ae22d22e2.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Water catfish
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Place a water catfish on a cutting board with a concave in the middle, and start cleaning. The sheath is cut between the head and the torso and peeled off in an instant to reveal translucent white skin. It is said that a strong water like jelly is a characteristic of a live water catfish.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Grooming a water catfish - Geoje-si, Gyeongnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/277/0899d4d6-4fd6-4a88-a97d-5792ba0e21c7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Grooming a water catfish
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   After cutting the hair, the internal organs are removed. In less than a minute, the water catfish has turned into a tasty 4-5 sliced soup. After washing in running water, put it in boiling broth with radish in advance.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Remove the skin and intestines and use it as a soup - Geoje-si, Gyeongnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/277/1e241f94-992e-4428-b6a2-416185b1f312.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Remove the skin and intestines and use it as a soup
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    There is no time or gap in adding a few pieces of chopped garlic, onion, green onion, and red pepper. Mulgi-tang, which boils clearly, is common, but in some parts of the East Sea, ripe kimchi is added to make it. The owner, who put all the ingredients and kicked the foam with a ladle, said, &#34;Would you like to drink some journalist?&#34; I was wondering if I was asked a lot of questions, but it is the moment when Mulgi-tang is the most delicious time to eat when the stomach is empty due to excessive drinking the day before.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The more you know the relationship between water catfish and alcohol, the more interesting it is. It is difficult to eat the circuit because the water catfish is tender. So, water catfish is semi-dried and eaten, which is perfect for a drink. He is a “bottle and give” guy who raises water catfish and drinks and soothes them later. For example, in Gangwon-do, if you say that mulmegi-tang is not delicious, you will hear a word saying, &#34;I&#39;m still drunk.&#34;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;14&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#39;&#34;If you boil it incorrectly, your flesh will break down.&#34; - Geoje-si, Gyeongnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#39; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/277/3e9206cd-d96a-4cb5-a3ca-6f1b10628610.jpg&#34; 끓이면=&#34;&#34; 다=&#34;&#34; 바스러져&#34;&#34;=&#34;&#34; 살이=&#34;&#34; 잘못=&#34;&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     &#34;If you boil it incorrectly, your flesh will break down.&#34;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   A water statue boiled on a weak fire and a Hansang with a Chan of Geoje in Gyeongnam were served. After taking the water catfish soup out once with a ladle, the fins and bones are applied, so the white and plump flesh is easy to eat. I pick it up with chopsticks, but it quickly breaks. Scooped the ingredients and flesh with a spoon and asked a bite.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;16&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Water catfish soup - Geoje-si, Gyeongnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/277/6786766e-da85-4749-b881-092d2259c74c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Water catfish soup
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    A little unfamiliar texture and taste makes the exclamation, but there is no point that remains impressive. There is no fishy feeling, and a slight knives with a few slices of pepper is left in the aftertaste. It&#39;s like knowing why it boils clearly and sticks to fresh, live fish. In order to preserve the unique taste of water catfish, the seasoning had to be minimized. Subsequently, as I ate it, sweat began to form on my forehead, and the warmth of my body turned into a pleasant feeling. I could see the reason why Mulgi-tang is famous for its cool taste.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;18&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;It is a quantity that 3 adults can enjoy. - Geoje-si, Gyeongnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/277/3a9e6cf0-b656-41f7-82f8-c5c997f6a84a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     It is a quantity that 3 adults can enjoy.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The pot quickly turned empty while eating without chewing several times. The feeling of satiety is not very large compared to the amount eaten. However, the soup in the pot that is left empty is not empty. The broth is full of crumbly water and peculiar flavor. Sprinkle the broth and roll with rice. If you want to taste a little flat, add kimchi or red pepper powder, and two bowls of rice are ready to eat.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Although this cool taste is attractive, it seems that fish called water catfish and food called water catfish aren&#39;t caught up in the popular food market. A while ago, a performer spit out the word ‘mechi-chi’ in an entertainment program, and a situation was broadcast to find out if this is actually a fish. The water texture and the peculiar texture of the water catfish act as a rejection for some people. When this reporter was young, he liked the soup, but he couldn&#39;t eat it easily. Then the adult around said, &#34;I am still young and I don&#39;t know the taste.&#34; And it&#39;s one of my favorite baths I can&#39;t eat right now
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;20&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The moderately boiled water catfish looks like this - Geoje-si, Gyeongnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/277/ecc46fa2-51b2-4dad-bd6b-dacb031735cf.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The moderately boiled water catfish looks like this
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    According to the owner, the yield of water catfish decreases every year. On the other hand, the number of foreigners looking for Mulgi-tang is increasing. . Increasingly, you can&#39;t believe the story that delicious fish has been called Multembang in the past.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     ** Interview cooperation **
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    [Yonhwa Sashimi Collection]
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    question. 055-681-1366
    &lt;br/&gt;
    address. Geoje-si Ilwoomyeon Gujora Beach (in front of Gujora Cruise Ship Pier)
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;22&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;When you open the broth, this crumb is full - Geoje-si, Gyeongnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/277/b216cafb-c764-47cb-94bb-b32752733a53.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     When you open the broth, this crumb is full
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1.Access
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     * Self-driving
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Daejeon Tongyeong Expressway Tongyeong IC, Geoje direction 14.9㎞ → Sagok three-way intersection, Geoje-myeon office (southern) direction 19.5㎞ → Gaengsam intersection, Gujora Beach 1.4 으로 direction → Gujora Village
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2.Accommodation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    W Motel: Ilwoomyeon Gujo Lari, 055-682-0454
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Tourist Hotel Imaginary House: Sodong-ri, Ilun-myeon, 055-682-5252
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Mongdol Beach Hotel: Hakdong-ri, Dongbu-myeon, 055-635-8883, 055-635-8884
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was created in January 2013, and may be changed later, so be sure to check it before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tour of Geojedo Gujo La Village. Geojedo, the head of a raised head - Geoje-si, Gyeongnam, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/tour-of-geojedo-gujo-la-village-geojedo-the-head-of-a-raised-head-207/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 00:08:28 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/tour-of-geojedo-gujo-la-village-geojedo-the-head-of-a-raised-head-207/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Geoje-si, Gyeongnam, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;tour-of-geojedo-gujo-la-village-geojedo-the-head-of-a-raised-head--207&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Gujo La Village Guide Map - Geoje-si, Gyeongnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/207/1717f594-2304-4cf8-8cb6-b596b63b0476.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Gujo La Village Guide Map
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Tour of Geojedo Gujo La Village. Geojedo, the head of a raised head
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Geoje-si, Gyeongnam, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Geojedo National Highway 14 is famous for its beautiful scenery. After passing Buksan Mountain and heading south to the sea, an impressive village appears. It is a gujo-la village that crosses the sea next to a land that looks as long as a giraffe&#39;s neck and thin like an ant&#39;s waist. There is a small mountain beyond the narrow and long town, so the impression that you want to look around is imminent. Entered the Gujo La Village as attracted by the strange charm.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    It&#39;s past winter, but the weather seems a bit winter, and it&#39;s too cold for spring, so it&#39;s the south side of the peninsula that shines. Jeju Island is fine, but Geoje Island is a good alternative when transportation is burdensome. It leads to Geoje Bridge, so it is easy to access and has a warm atmosphere.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Beyond Geoje Bridge, you can enjoy the scenery of Namhae next to it. There are peaceful seas, islands with grains of grain, roofs gathered on the shores of fishing villages, and ships anchored in the harbor. Among them, the unique features of Geoje Island are the complex Rias coastline and the surrounding landscape. It has become monotonous with people&#39;s hands, but the coastline, which is infrequent in nature, can be seen with its intricate coastline. Take the Geoje-daero along the coastline to the east of Geoje-do, and move south to Gujo-la Village.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Fishing Village on Jaramok
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    On the west side of Gujora Village, there is a fine sandy beach and a gentle curved beach, and on the east side is a port where ships anchor. This port has been used as a major base for maritime transportation in Japan since ancient times, and since it was designated as a national fishing port in 1971, it has a large port, such as Jang Seung-po, as well as a ballroom as a port. In addition, it has a high location as a tourist spot as it is possible to take a cruise ship through Naedo, Oedo, and Haegeum River, close to Gujora. In the daytime, don&#39;t miss the waves of the sea surfing in and out in the winter, and the night view of the harbor at night.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;View from the breakwater - Geoje-si, Gyeongnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/207/75af1d11-4c32-42b2-bddb-09130dcf37c9.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     View from the breakwater
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    There is a lot of anglers even though there is a strong winter breeze because the port breaks down and comes to the breakwater. It is said that Benedom is caught well, and various fish species such as horse mackerel and tochi are caught. A little further south along the coastline is a small pebble beach. And it is also the southern end of the sea where Crystal Mountain and the sea meet. You can see Naedo Island and Oedo Island in the distance. Just as the three sides of the Korean Peninsula are the sea, the structure is similar.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox type2 clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Pebble beach - Geoje-si, Gyeongnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/207/a1069516-5f54-462e-bbc9-a4ba29b29c95.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Pebble beach
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The breakwater had quite a lot of people coming for fishing. - Geoje-si, Gyeongnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/207/6557f790-24a1-4260-93bb-80a4e622f7f3.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The breakwater had quite a lot of people coming for fishing.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Zara Hair &#39;Soojeong Mountain&#39;
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The end of the road leads to the Sujeongsan Trail. There is no need for a guide as the breakwater, pebble beach, and crystal mountain line along the way from the port. If you just walk with the sea next to it, you will naturally go to every corner of Gujora Village. Crystal Mountain is a small mountain less than 150 meters above sea level, and is a mountain that rises before the southern veins of Buk Byeong Mountain in the north reach the sea. If it is Jinsan in Gujora Village, it will be Jinsan.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox type2 clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Breakwater and gravel beach area - Geoje-si, Gyeongnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/207/30155606-e68a-4cbd-9be4-0ddec3e91d21.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Breakwater and gravel beach area
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;It is easy to see the information board related to Sujeongsan. - Geoje-si, Gyeongnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/207/3361d0bc-8118-452a-b1ef-c6798b4a159a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     It is easy to see the information board related to Sujeongsan.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Around the ridge of the 4th part of Sujeongsan, there is a super experience center. The presence of a guard post here would mean a good location to watch the coast. To take advantage of the seats, an observatory was installed, and there was a signboard with the name of the island in the foreground.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox type2 clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;group - Geoje-si, Gyeongnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/207/b07307cb-0c62-480f-9456-112a2befc3a2.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     group
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Guncho Post Observatory - Geoje-si, Gyeongnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/207/ea7445f7-b75f-4dc8-9356-67b359b64d5f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Guncho Post Observatory
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The sea of the South Sea is more dazzling than summer. Even at noon, the sun and the dazzling sunshine of the sea are not too far from the horizon. When the cloudy clouds cover the sun, sunlight shining through the gaps of the clouds sits in the sea. The lumpy cloud doesn&#39;t have a moving tee if this place is good. Underneath, the sea and island scenery can be seen at a glance. I often describe the Namhae as my mother&#39;s arms, and it seems that the warmth is conveyed. It is as sweet as a movie because a fishing boat passes by in a landscape where the idea of &#39;it is really nature&#39; passes through.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Scenery from the observation deck - Geoje-si, Gyeongnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/207/575ef9f9-df7d-47e0-9ffe-81b431acfd5d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Scenery from the observation deck
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    30 minutes from guard post to summit is sufficient. If you look back while climbing the slope, the sea and islands spread out through the stiff branches of the winter mountain, so you don&#39;t feel hungry. There is also an observation deck at the summit of Mt. The sea is good to the south and the town is overlooking to the north.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox type3 clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sujeongsan Observatory - Geoje-si, Gyeongnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/207/2547f257-4b71-482f-9f18-50cd344d8af6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sujeongsan Observatory
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Gujo La Village overlooking - Geoje-si, Gyeongnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/207/aa6978dd-6d5d-49f2-9311-72361cf46f7c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Gujo La Village overlooking
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;You can see the surrounding islands in detail through the observation - Geoje-si, Gyeongnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/207/f4eccf25-34cd-4998-9c61-86cafd8d0613.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     You can see the surrounding islands in detail through the observation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The structure of the village on the waist, which is concave up and down between Sujeong and Bukbyeongsan, and concave to the left and right, is nice. Since ancient times, Sujeongsan was called the head of Zara, and the narrow land was the tree of Zara. To the north, Buksan Mountain rises sharply as if it has fanned out from side to side. I think Gujora Village has a very good place.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Scenery from the castle observatory - Geoje-si, Gyeongnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/207/1db24dde-2e08-4954-9933-99e59d94e031.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Scenery from the castle observatory
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   History in Gujora Castle, Legend in Yundol Island
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    As you descend the ridge in front of the village, you will encounter the castle wall, the trace of Gujouraseong. This castle was built to prevent dwarfs from the Joseon Dynasty, and is one of the Geoje Chiljins constructed in the first year of Seongjong. After the Imjin War, it was moved to the side of Okpojin and then returned to its current location and was named Gujorajin and is now designated as 204 Gyeongsangnam-do Monument.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Gujora Castle Wall - Geoje-si, Gyeongnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/207/2b554796-9d2c-4387-b17b-46ccc2155573.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Gujora Castle Wall
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    When you reach the middle point between Sujeongsan and the village along the castle wall, there is one small island floating in the sea of Gujora Beach, called &#39;Yundol Island&#39; and contains the legend of Hyoja&#39;s verses.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &#34;Once upon a time, a fisherman who had a family living with a beautiful woman named Haesun lived. One day, a sea fisherman who worked at the sea disappeared by a typhoon with a ship. After this day, the fisherman came out to the sea every night and called the sea boat every night and stared at the moon. Residents who watched this figure called the fisherman &#39;Mangwol&#39;.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    At this time, the widow and three of his sons settled on an island called Yundol Island. The old fisherman and the widow who became widowers became soothing each other. The island where the widow lived was only able to walk to the village at low tide, and each time the widow visited the widower without her son&#39;s knowledge. Knowing these relationships, the sons of Yun made a stepping stone by placing stones between the island and the village because they felt sorry for their mother heading to the village even after taking off their socks and getting wet in the sea in winter. &#34;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Yundol Island - Geoje-si, Gyeongnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/207/6f665e41-0dfe-4f86-86b5-78d22bde248c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Yundol Island
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Go through the bamboo breeze path and watch murals
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    As the wall ends and the village approaches, a bamboo forest grows densely. What was created as a windbreak forest is now being used as a walking trail with a pretty name called the breeze. The leaves flutter in the sea breeze, and it becomes fine. There is a scary story that even in the summer, this place is cool and ghosts come out. The phrase “Boiso” by the residents about this place is impressive.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;15&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A breeze - Geoje-si, Gyeongnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/207/468f2eb7-3ff6-4015-a07b-19fda32cc3d5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A breeze
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &#34;The breeze is the kind of windbreak path that goes from Denbak-dong to the hillside. It is a kind of windbreak forest planted to avoid the breeze. It was a kind of windbreak forest. Even though I couldn&#39;t go there, it&#39;s cool in the sun on a summer day, but it&#39;s so dark that it&#39;s so dark that the good-looking locals lie down on the mats on a summer night. It&#39;s very scary. Inza is all aware of it, and it&#39;s a little less frightening, but it&#39;s still a time when you&#39;re alone.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;16&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A breeze - Geoje-si, Gyeongnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/207/0e699baf-a066-4471-acb8-54a15149678e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A breeze
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    After passing through the bamboo forest, it continues naturally into the village. Here, murals are painted everywhere, and works of various concepts fill the village with high density, from cute murals that stir up concentricity to carefully painted feathers one by one.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;17&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Village mural - Geoje-si, Gyeongnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/207/61c3cbcd-fc21-4e00-a491-3179293c5bc0.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Village mural
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    I just walked around a small fishing village, feeling the warmth of the South Sea, drinking the sea breeze and refreshing the mountains. In addition, you could see the murals of the village through the bamboo tunnel through the history of the legends and Japanese wars related to the village. I don&#39;t think there are any treasures in Geoje Island.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;18&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Village mural - Geoje-si, Gyeongnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/207/f181f4cc-7939-42f6-ab24-9a22896be693.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Village mural
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    1.Access
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    * Self-driving
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Daejeon Tongyeong Expressway Tongyeong IC, Geoje direction 14.9㎞ → Sagok three-way intersection, Geoje-myeon office (south) direction 19.5㎞ → Gaengsam intersection, Gujora Beach 1.4㎞ direction → Gujora Village
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    2. Delicious
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Yeonhwa Sashimi Restaurant: Water Megitang, 055-681-1366
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Gangseong Sashimi Restaurant: Sea urchin bibimbap, 055-681-6289
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Seongpo Sashimi Restaurant: Dodari Mugwort Soup, 055-633-9960
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Million seats: Mengbibibimbap, 055-638-3300
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Unga Sashimi Restaurant: Grilled Rockfish, 055-632-7659
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    3.Accommodation
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    W Motel: Ilwoomyeon Gujo Lari, 055-682-0454
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Tourist Hotel Imaginary House: Sodong-ri, Ilun-myeon, 055-682-5252
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Mongdol Beach Hotel: Hakdong-ri, Dongbu-myeon, 055-635-8883, 055-635-8884
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    ※ The above information was created in February 2013, and may change later, so be sure to check it before you travel.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>