<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Yangju on Every Corner of Korea</title>
    <link>https://codecorea.github.io/tags/yangju/</link>
    <description>Every Corner of Korea (Yangju)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 23:08:26 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="https://codecorea.github.io/tags/yangju/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea - Enhance Art Sense by Following with Kwon Yul, Yangju Art Museum</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/enhance-art-sense-by-following-with-kwon-yul-yangju-art-museum-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 23:08:26 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/enhance-art-sense-by-following-with-kwon-yul-yangju-art-museum-17/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-title=&#34;enhance-art-sense-by-following-with-kwon-yul-yangju-art-museum--17&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Love by Kang Young-min installed at the beginning of Jangheung Art Park - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/d4c2c642-415c-495f-a8ad-f4af17caa572.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Love by Kang Young-min installed at the beginning of Jangheung Art Park
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Enhance Art Sense by Following with Kwon Yul, Yangju Art Museum
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   During the boom of mica, Yangju Ilyoung Amusement Park, Jangheung Amusement Park, and Songchu Amusement Park were named to the 4050 households as the Capital Region Drive Course. There are restaurants around the valley with football courts, so it was a good place for family outings. Now all are fading, but as much as Jangheung Amusement Park enters the famous art galleries, which makes the weekend drive fun.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Outing course in conjunction with art museums, cultural monuments and observatory
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Route 39, which connects Deoyang-gu, Goyang-si, and Suseong-dong, Uijeongbu-si, is called Pyeong-ro-ro. This road leads to Jangheung police box and meets a fork called Kwon Yul-ro. Kwon Yul-ro, named after General Kwon-yul, ends at the intersection of Jangheung Art Park, Jangheung Sculpture Park, Yangju City Jang Ukjin Art Museum (hereinafter referred to as Jang Ukjin Art Museum), Horsehead Pass, Ahn Sang-cheol Art Museum and Kisan Reservoir, and at the intersection of Yangju Culture and Arts Center.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;In front of Jang Ukjin Museum - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/2da5ba62-07c8-410b-8e9d-f6158f95d22f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     In front of Jang Ukjin Museum
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Kwon Yul General is located just past the entrance of Jang Ukjin Museum of Art. General Kwon Yul is one of the masters who saved the country during the Imjin War. The dish towel that led to victory is considered to be the Three Great Battalion, along with the Pearl Battling and the Hansan Island Battling. While passing through Kwon Yul-ro, his head is bowed to the general spirit and national ideology of the general. As such, the trip to the Yangju Museum of Art is a trip with cultural heritage. If you include the Songam Space Center, it is a good study outing course that combines astronomical studies. Awaken the sense of art through art museum visits, creating a sense of empathy between parents and children, and enriching stories. So going out to three art galleries in Kwon Yul-ro is not a simple drive.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Dome Theater at Songam Space Center - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/c539c1f7-f645-4878-9ee0-69a49fbb88f9.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Dome Theater at Songam Space Center
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Jangheung Art Park
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Departing from Gupabal, Gisan Reservoir is the final destination and Jangheung Art Park is the first art space to meet at Kwon Yul-ro. It has been bent since it was renamed several times since its establishment. Total Art Museum was first established in 1984, but in 2005, it changed to Jangheung Art Park due to management problems. Later in 2006, Japanese designer and architect Shigeru Uchida designed Art Park and structural designer Van Shigeru designed the venue. In May of that year, an exhibition hall, atelier, performance hall, art gallery, sculpture park, and children&#39;s experience center were completed.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Bourdel&#39;s Sculpture &amp;lt;Fruit&amp;gt; - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/57f0c167-ea11-4e39-ae48-799f2c41f51e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Bourdel&#39;s Sculpture &amp;lt;Fruit&amp;gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Jangheung Art Park is not an art museum dedicated to painting with a certain distance. It is a playground-friendly art space that touches works and displays works that children can ride on. The name of this garden is Bourdel Garden. Sculptures by the sculptor Bourdel, such as Fruits, a Crouching Sacred Woman and Roman Mother and Child, expressing the love of mother and child, welcome visitors from all over the lawn. French sculptor Bourdel is one of the three greatest masters of modern sculpture, along with Rodin and Mayol.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Bourdel&#39;s Sculpture &amp;lt;Our Lady with Offerings&amp;gt; - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/d50a5ceb-4e06-4053-86f3-8deddfc3cf73.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Bourdel&#39;s Sculpture &amp;lt;Our Lady with Offerings&amp;gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Picasso Children&#39;s Art Museum
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The Picasso Children&#39;s Art Museum is a must-see for adults. Although it is a replica, you can see the works and passionate lives of Picasso&#39;s soul (1881 ~ 1973) here. In particular, Picasso&#39;s photographs taken by photographer Andre Viller (1930 ~) are incredible, so they are more inspiring. The two first met in 1953. Since then, Biller has photographed many scenes, including Picasso&#39;s focus on his work and his thoughts. Picasso&#39;s passion in black and white photography and his desire for artistic life come alive.
   &lt;br/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Mark Quinn&#39;s Sculpture &amp;lt;Myth&amp;gt; - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/93e1a559-87ed-4179-a5cc-68a08caad74a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Mark Quinn&#39;s Sculpture &amp;lt;Myth&amp;gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Picasso&#39;s 11 portraits and family photos also catch the eye. In addition, you can appreciate Picasso&#39;s pottery, prints, drawings, and silver plates. Looking back before leaving the museum, Dad takes off his hat and climbs up a ladder in shorts to depict the naked woman&#39;s body in a straight line. The viewer&#39;s chest is refreshing.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Picasso working in the studio - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/b2ec457f-f052-420f-8d79-8c89de26bc19.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Picasso working in the studio
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In addition, Ryu In&#39;s Express Train-The Era of Times, Kim Taek Ki&#39;s Dream of Peace, Mark Quinn&#39;s Myth, and Kang Young Min&#39;s Love are the representative sculptures of Jangheung Art Park.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sculpture by Artist Ryu In &amp;lt;Express Train-The Era of Times&amp;gt; - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/44494ccb-4d14-4168-a6a0-21e59b9d0b75.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sculpture by Artist Ryu In &amp;lt;Express Train-The Era of Times&amp;gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Jang Ukjin Museum of Art
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Just a little up from Jangheung Art Park towards Kwon Yul General Cemetery, Yangju Museum of Art is displayed. The museum was designed after Jang Uk-jin&#39;s tiger painting and was opened in April 2014 and won the Kim Soo-geun Architecture Award that year. It is a great pride to have a large collection of genuine artists. More than 230 pieces of murals, oil paintings, prints, ink paintings, etc. are donated by the Jang Uk-Jin Art and Culture Foundation to display them by theme and period.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Yangju Museum of Art - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/b3eac18e-fc32-4ffc-95e5-111a9fcc141a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Yangju Museum of Art
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Painter Jang Uk-jin (1917 ~ 1990) is a master of Western painting that represents Korean modern art along with Park Soo-geun and Lee Joong-seop. Born in Yeong-gun, Chungcheongnam-do (now Sejong Special Self-Governing City), the story of his art museum entering Yangju was due to his studio in Deokso, once a land of Yangju County. Since then, he has continued his creative activities in the studios of Seoul Myeongryon-dong, Chungju Suanbo and Yongin Singal.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Visitors to &amp;lt;Animal Family&amp;gt; at Jang Ukjin Museum of Art - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/be1507be-1d67-4488-a964-68bcf9c010ef.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Visitors to &amp;lt;Animal Family&amp;gt; at Jang Ukjin Museum of Art
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   &amp;lt;Animal Family&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;Dining Table&amp;gt; painted on cement wall
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Admission is good to start from the second floor. In this way, you can meet the master&#39;s work first and reflect on his life once again in the first floor video room. &amp;lt;Animal Family&amp;gt; on the second floor is a work that is loved by visitors. Created in 1964, the work description attached to the side tells the old story with black and white photography. Animal Family was painted on the wall of the studio in Deokso, Gyeonggi-do. The warm gaze of the painter can be felt in the artwork where cows, chickens, pigs and dogs are harmoniously drawn like a family. In particular, the real cowcoats and warangs are hung on the murals to evoke local sentiments.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;5&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Jang Ukjin Museum of Art - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/f80bf391-f32c-46ff-9f7f-e93a3e8d2feb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Jang Ukjin Museum of Art
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The work that peeled off the painted wall is in the middle of the stairs connecting the basement and the first floor. The title is &amp;lt;Table&amp;gt;. Let&#39;s look at the description of the work. “The paintings show the modern life of an artist, and on the screen are forks and knives, spoons and rice bowls, coffee cups, water glasses, flounder and bones. After the painter completed this picture, &#39;he became. Today, let&#39;s replace one meal with this meal. &#39;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;5&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Mother and daughter resting in front of the cafe on the 1st floor of Jang Ukjin Museum of Art - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/8e708bf4-0235-438a-90b3-0b5fd365c6d8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Mother and daughter resting in front of the cafe on the 1st floor of Jang Ukjin Museum of Art
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The idea of using the gray cement wall as a canvas, and the simplicity and warmth of the canvas. Visitors find love for people and objects in each of their works, develop their imagination, and find themselves more generous. The beauty of a trip to a museum is this.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;5&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Jangheung Sculpture Park in front of Jang Ukjin Museum of Art - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/c1b3ec97-4d50-4813-b74c-7e10ad4ac1a6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Jangheung Sculpture Park in front of Jang Ukjin Museum of Art
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Ahn Sang-cheol Museum of Art Brings Kisan Reservoir to the Garden
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The trip to the museum following Kwon Yul-ro of Yangju-si ends at the An Sang-cheol Museum of Art, located next to Gisan Reservoir. Ahn Sang-cheol (1927-1993) is a painter who left many famous works in the field of oriental painting. He was a professor at Seorabol Art College and Sungshin Women&#39;s University. Ahn Sang-cheol, who became a national war star after winning the Minister of Education, Vice President&#39;s Award, and President&#39;s Award in 1959, married Na Hee-kyun, a contemporary student of Seoul National University and nephew of Na Hye-seok.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;6&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Kisan Reservoir from Ansangcheol Museum of Art - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/674eb3d2-6e04-4f5c-8c90-895a8de77c6e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Kisan Reservoir from Ansangcheol Museum of Art
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   At the entrance of the museum, you can follow Ahn&#39;s life and enter the exhibition space to see his works. It is a series of work titled &amp;lt;(靈)&amp;gt;, which has colored the old tree. He created this work with the thought that &#39;the spirit is a body that remains and is passed on by someone even when it dies.&#39;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;6&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Ahnsangcheol Museum of Art from the Lawn - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/2fe5a84b-a13c-4224-bdfa-878947a3123e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Ahnsangcheol Museum of Art from the Lawn
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The line of spectators continues in front of her works. Although he is an old man with 12 solo exhibitions, he is still actively engaged in creative activities. The copper line is a lawn, which leads to the Kisan Reservoir. The building of the museum is the work of Ahn Woo-sung, the son of Ahn Sang-cheol and the owner of Ongodang Architects. There is a studio with a glass window behind one flower garden. This is where Na Hee-kyun, a painter, sometimes stops to paint. The Ahn Sang-cheol Museum of Art will open until July 15.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;6&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;15&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Artist Lee Hee-kyun&#39;s work &amp;lt;My Mirina 2&amp;gt; - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/1a41d284-06fa-41a3-be91-deb0fb836c19.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Artist Lee Hee-kyun&#39;s work &amp;lt;My Mirina 2&amp;gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel info
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Jangheung Art Park
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Address: 117, Kwon Yul-ro, Jangheung-myeon, Yangju-si, Gyeonggi-do
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Contact: 031-877-0500
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.artpark.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.artpark.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Yangju Museum of Art
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Address: 211 Kwon Yul-ro, Jangheung-myeon, Yangju-si, Gyeonggi-do
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Contact: 031-8082-4245
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://changucchin.yangju.go.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://changucchin.yangju.go.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Ahn Sang Chul Museum of Art
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Address: 905 Kwon Yul-ro, Baekseok-eup, Yangju-si, Gyeonggi-do
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Contact: 031-874-0734
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.ahnsangchul.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.ahnsangchul.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Nearby restaurants
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Affiliated Restaurant: Hanwoo / 410, Gisan-ro, Baekseok-eup, Yangju-si / 031-871-9271
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Chosun Gomtang: Gomtang / 46, Deokjeong 14-gil, Yangju-si / 031-857-1445
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Yemogol: Steak / 442, Gamagol-ro, Jangheung-myeon, Yangju-si / 031-855-1891
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Accommodation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Buckingham Hotel: 462-1, Gisan-ro, Baekseok-eup, Yangju-si / 031-871-9441
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Pine Hill Motel: 305-33, Gwonryul-ro 309beon-gil, Jangheung-myeon, Yangju-si / 031-829-0711
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Palace: 492 Kwon Yul-ro, Jangheung-myeon, Yangju-si / 031-855-2900
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was made in June 2015. It may change afterwards, so please check before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Information such as text, photos, and videos used in this article is copyrighted by Korea Tourism Organization, so unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>