<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Yangju on Korea Tour</title>
    <link>https://codecorea.github.io/tags/yangju/</link>
    <description>Korea Tour (Yangju)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 00:42:51 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="https://codecorea.github.io/tags/yangju/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Янчжу, Кёнгидо, Корея - Повысить смысл искусства, следуя примеру Квон Юла, Художественный музей Янцзю</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/enhance-art-sense-by-following-with-kwon-yul-yangju-art-museum-17-ru/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 00:42:51 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/enhance-art-sense-by-following-with-kwon-yul-yangju-art-museum-17-ru/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-title=&#34;enhance-art-sense-by-following-with-kwon-yul-yangju-art-museum--17&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Love by Kang Young-min установлена в начале художественного парка Jangheung - Янчжу, Кёнгидо, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/d4c2c642-415c-495f-a8ad-f4af17caa572.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Love by Kang Young-min установлена в начале художественного парка Jangheung
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Повысить смысл искусства, следуя примеру Квон Юла, Художественный музей Янцзю
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Янчжу, Кёнгидо, Корея
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Во время бума слюды парк развлечений Yangju Ilyoung, парк развлечений Jangheung и парк развлечений Songchu были названы 4050 домохозяйствами в качестве столичного автомобильного маршрута. Вокруг долины есть рестораны с футбольными полями, так что это было хорошее место для семейных прогулок. Сейчас все исчезает, но парк развлечений Jangheung попадает в знаменитые художественные галереи, что делает поездку на выходных увлекательной.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Экскурсионный курс совместно с художественными музеями, памятниками культуры и обсерваторией
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Маршрут 39, который соединяет Деоян-гу, Гоян-си и Сусон-дон, Уиджеонгбу-си, называется Пхён-ро-ро. Эта дорога ведет к полицейскому участку Чанхын и встречает развилку по имени Квон Юл-ро. Квон Юл-ро, названный в честь генерала Квон-юла, заканчивается на пересечении Художественного парка Jangheung, Парка скульптур Jangheung, Городского художественного музея Jang Ukjin (в дальнейшем именуемого Художественным музеем Jang Ukjin), Horsehead Pass, Ahn Sang-cheol Art Музей и Кисанское водохранилище, а также на пересечении Центра культуры и искусств Янчжу.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Перед музеем Чан Укцзин - Янчжу, Кёнгидо, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/2da5ba62-07c8-410b-8e9d-f6158f95d22f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Перед музеем Чан Укцзин
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Отель Kwon Yul General расположен прямо у входа в Художественный музей Чан Укджин. Генерал Квон Юл является одним из мастеров, которые спасли страну во время войны с Имджином. Полотенце для посуды, которое привело к победе, считается Трех Великим Батальоном, наряду с Сражением с Жемчужиной и Сражением на Острове Хансан. Проходя через Квон Юл-ро, его голова склоняется перед общим духом и национальной идеологией генерала. Таким образом, поездка в Художественный музей Янчжу - это поездка с культурным наследием. Если вы включите Космический центр Сонгам, это хороший учебный курс, который сочетает в себе астрономические исследования. Пробудите чувство искусства через посещения художественного музея, создавая чувство сочувствия между родителями и детьми, и обогащая истории. Так что посещение трех художественных галерей в Квон Юл-ро - не простая поездка.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Домский Театр в Центре Сонгама - Янчжу, Кёнгидо, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/c539c1f7-f645-4878-9ee0-69a49fbb88f9.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Домский Театр в Центре Сонгама
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Jangheung Art Park
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Отправление из Гупабала, водохранилище Гисан является конечным пунктом назначения, а художественный парк Чанхын - первое художественное пространство, которое встретит в Квон Юл-ро. Он был изогнут с тех пор, как несколько раз переименовывался с момента его основания. Музей искусств Total был впервые создан в 1984 году, но в 2005 году из-за проблем с управлением он перешел в парк искусств Jangheung. Позже, в 2006 году, японский дизайнер и архитектор Сигеру Учида разработал Art Park, а дизайнер-конструктор Ван Сигеру - место проведения. В мае того же года были завершены работы выставочного зала, ателье, концертного зала, художественной галереи, парка скульптур и детского игрового центра.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Скульптура Бурделя &amp;lt;Фрукты&amp;gt; - Янчжу, Кёнгидо, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/57f0c167-ea11-4e39-ae48-799f2c41f51e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Скульптура Бурделя &amp;lt;Фрукты&amp;gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Jangheung Art Park - это не художественный музей, посвященный живописи с определенного расстояния. Это арт-пространство, подходящее для детских площадок, которое касается работ и показывает работы, на которых могут кататься дети. Название этого сада - Сад Бурделя. Скульптуры скульптора Бурделя, такие как «Фрукты», «Крадущаяся святая женщина» и «Римская мать и дитя», выражающие любовь матери и ребенка, приветствуют посетителей со всей лужайки. Французский скульптор Бурдель входит в тройку величайших мастеров современной скульптуры наряду с Роденом и Майолом.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Скульптура Бурделя &amp;lt;Богоматерь с подношениями&amp;gt; - Янчжу, Кёнгидо, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/d50a5ceb-4e06-4053-86f3-8deddfc3cf73.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Скульптура Бурделя &amp;lt;Богоматерь с подношениями&amp;gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Детский художественный музей Пикассо
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Детский художественный музей Пикассо является обязательным для взрослых. Хотя это точная копия, вы можете увидеть работы и страстные жизни души Пикассо (1881–1973) здесь. В частности, фотографии Пикассо, сделанные фотографом Андре Виллером (1930 ~), невероятны, поэтому они более вдохновляющие. Впервые они познакомились в 1953 году. С тех пор Биллер сфотографировал много сцен, включая внимание Пикассо к своей работе и его мысли. Страсть Пикассо к черно-белой фотографии и его стремление к художественной жизни оживают.
   &lt;br/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Скульптура Марка Куинна &amp;lt;Миф&amp;gt; - Янчжу, Кёнгидо, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/93e1a559-87ed-4179-a5cc-68a08caad74a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Скульптура Марка Куинна &amp;lt;Миф&amp;gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   11 портретов Пикассо и семейные фотографии также бросаются в глаза. Кроме того, вы можете оценить керамику Пикассо, гравюры, рисунки и серебряные тарелки. Оглядываясь назад, прежде чем покинуть музей, папа снимает шляпу и поднимается по лестнице в шортах, чтобы изобразить тело обнаженной женщины по прямой линии. Грудь зрителя освежает.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Пикассо работает в студии - Янчжу, Кёнгидо, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/b2ec457f-f052-420f-8d79-8c89de26bc19.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Пикассо работает в студии
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Кроме того, «Экспресс-поезд Рю Ин-эры времен», «Мечта о мире» Ким Тхэк Ки, «Миф Марка Куинна» и «Любовь Кан Юнга Мина» являются репрезентативными скульптурами художественного парка «Чанхын».
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Скульптура художника Рю В &amp;lt;Экспресс-эра времен&amp;gt; - Янчжу, Кёнгидо, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/44494ccb-4d14-4168-a6a0-21e59b9d0b75.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Скульптура художника Рю В &amp;lt;Экспресс-эра времен&amp;gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Художественный Музей Джанг Укджин
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Музей искусств Янцзю находится совсем немного от парка искусств Чанхын к общему кладбищу Квон Юл. Музей был спроектирован по мотивам тигровой росписи Чан Ук-цзин и был открыт в апреле 2014 года. В этом году он был удостоен архитектурной премии Ким Су Гын. Это большая гордость иметь большую коллекцию настоящих художников. Фонд искусств и культуры имени Чан Ук-Джина пожертвовал более 230 предметов фресок, картин, гравюр и т. Д., Чтобы показать их по темам и периодам.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Музей Искусств Янчжу - Янчжу, Кёнгидо, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/b3eac18e-fc32-4ffc-95e5-111a9fcc141a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Музей Искусств Янчжу
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Художник Джанг Ук-чжин (1917–1990) - мастер западной живописи, представляющий современное корейское искусство, а также Пак Су Гын и Ли Чжун Сеоп. История его художественного музея, входящего в Янчжу, родилась в Ён-гун, Чхунчхон-доу (ныне особый самоуправляемый город Сечжон), из-за его мастерской в Деоксо, когда-то являвшейся страной округа Янчжу. С тех пор он продолжил свою творческую деятельность в студиях Сеула Мёнгрён-донга, Чхунджу Суанбо и Йонгин Сингал.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Посетители &amp;lt;Animal Family&amp;gt; в художественном музее Чан Укджин - Янчжу, Кёнгидо, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/be1507be-1d67-4488-a964-68bcf9c010ef.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Посетители &amp;lt;Animal Family&amp;gt; в художественном музее Чан Укджин
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   &amp;lt;Animal Family&amp;gt; и &amp;lt;Обеденный стол&amp;gt; нарисованы на цементной стене
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Прием хорошо начать со второго этажа. Таким образом, вы можете сначала познакомиться с магистерской работой и еще раз подумать о его жизни в видео зале первого этажа. &amp;lt;Animal Family&amp;gt; на втором этаже - это работа, которую любят посетители. Описание работы, созданное в 1964 году, рассказывает старую историю с черно-белой фотографией. Семья животных была нарисована на стене студии в Деоксо, Кёнгидо. Теплый взгляд художника ощущается в произведениях искусства, где коровы, куры, свиньи и собаки гармонично изображены как семья. В частности, настоящие коровы и варанги вешают на фрески, чтобы вызвать местные чувства.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;5&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Художественный Музей Джанг Укджин - Янчжу, Кёнгидо, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/f80bf391-f32c-46ff-9f7f-e93a3e8d2feb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Художественный Музей Джанг Укджин
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Работа, которая слезла с окрашенной стены, находится в середине лестницы, соединяющей подвал и первый этаж. Название: &amp;lt;Таблица&amp;gt;. Давайте посмотрим на описание работы. «Картины показывают современную жизнь художника, а на экране - вилки и ножи, ложки и рисовые чаши, кофейные чашки, стаканы для воды, камбала и кости. После того, как художник завершил эту картину, он стал. Сегодня давайте заменим один прием пищи этим приемом пищи. &#39;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;5&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Мать и дочь отдыхают перед кафе на 1-м этаже музея искусств Чан Укцзин - Янчжу, Кёнгидо, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/8e708bf4-0235-438a-90b3-0b5fd365c6d8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Мать и дочь отдыхают перед кафе на 1-м этаже музея искусств Чан Укцзин
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Идея использования серой цементной стены в качестве холста, а также простота и тепло холста. Посетители находят любовь к людям и предметам в каждом из своих произведений, развивают свое воображение и считают себя более щедрыми. Прелесть поездки в музей в этом.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;5&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Парк скульптур Jangheung перед музеем искусств Jang Ukjin - Янчжу, Кёнгидо, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/c1b3ec97-4d50-4813-b74c-7e10ad4ac1a6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Парк скульптур Jangheung перед музеем искусств Jang Ukjin
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Музей Искусств Ан Санг Чхоль Приносит Кисанское Водохранилище в Сад
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Поездка в музей после Квон Юл-ро из Янцзю-си заканчивается в Музее искусств Ан Сан-Чхоль, расположенном рядом с водохранилищем Гисан. Ан Санг-Чхоль (1927-1993) - художник, оставивший много известных работ в области восточной живописи. Он был профессором в Сераболском художественном колледже и Женском университете Суншин. Ан Санг Чхоль, ставшая национальной звездой войны после завоевания в 1959 году министра образования, премии вице-президента и премии президента, вышла замуж за На Хи Кёна, современного студента Сеульского национального университета и племянника На Хе Сека.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;6&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Кисанское водохранилище от Художественного музея Ансангчхоль - Янчжу, Кёнгидо, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/674eb3d2-6e04-4f5c-8c90-895a8de77c6e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Кисанское водохранилище от Художественного музея Ансангчхоль
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   У входа в музей вы можете следить за жизнью Анна и войти в выставочное пространство, чтобы увидеть его работы. Это серия работ под названием &amp;lt;(靈)&amp;gt;, которая раскрасила старое дерево. Он создал эту работу с мыслью, что «дух - это тело, которое остается и передается кем-то, даже когда он умирает».
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;6&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Музей искусств Ahnsangcheol с газона - Янчжу, Кёнгидо, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/2fe5a84b-a13c-4224-bdfa-878947a3123e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Музей искусств Ahnsangcheol с газона
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Линия зрителей продолжается перед ее работами. Хотя он пожилой человек с 12 персональными выставками, он все еще активно занимается творческой деятельностью. Медная линия - это газон, который ведет к Кисанскому водохранилищу. Здание музея - работа Ан Ву Сунга, сына Ан Санг Чхела и владельца Ongodang Architects. Существует студия со стеклянным окном позади одного цветника. Здесь художник На Хи Кюн иногда останавливается, чтобы рисовать. Художественный музей Ан Санг Чхель будет открыт до 15 июля.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;6&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;15&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Работа художника Ли Хи Кёна &amp;lt;My Mirina 2&amp;gt; - Янчжу, Кёнгидо, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/1a41d284-06fa-41a3-be91-deb0fb836c19.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Работа художника Ли Хи Кёна &amp;lt;My Mirina 2&amp;gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Информация о путешествии
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Jangheung Art Park
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Адрес: 117, Квон Юл-ро, Чхангхён-Мён, Янчжу-си, Кёнгидо
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Контакт: 031-877-0500
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.artpark.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.artpark.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Музей Искусств Янчжу
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Адрес: 211 Kwon Yul-ro, Jangheung-myeon, Yangju-si, Gyeonggi-do
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Контакт: 031-8082-4245
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://changucchin.yangju.go.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://changucchin.yangju.go.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Музей Искусств Ан Санг Чул
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Адрес: 905 Квон Юл-ро, Baekseok-eup, Yangju-si, Gyeonggi-do
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Контакт: 031-874-0734
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.ahnsangchul.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.ahnsangchul.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Близлежащие рестораны
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Аффилированный ресторан: Hanwoo / 410, Gisan-ro, Baekseok-eup, Yangju-si / 031-871-9271
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Чосон Гомтанг: Гомтанг / 46, Деокджонг 14-й гиль, Янцзю-си / 031-857-1445
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Yemogol: стейк / 442, Gamagol-ро, Jangheung-Myeon, Yangju-си / 031-855-1891
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Размещение
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Buckingham Hotel: 462-1, Gisan-ro, Baekseok-eup, Yangju-si / 031-871-9441
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Pine Hill Motel: 305-33, Gwonryul-ro 309beon-gil, Jangheung-myeon, Yangju-si / 031-829-0711
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Дворец: 492 Квон Юл-ро, Чхангхён-Мён, Янцзю-си / 031-855-2900
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ Приведенная выше информация была сделана в июне 2015 года. Впоследствии она может измениться, поэтому, пожалуйста, проверьте это перед поездкой.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Информация, такая как текст, фотографии и видео, используемые в этой статье, защищены авторским правом Корейской туристической организации, поэтому несанкционированное использование статьи запрещено.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Corée - Améliorez le sens de l&#39;art en suivant avec Kwon Yul, Yangju Art Museum</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/enhance-art-sense-by-following-with-kwon-yul-yangju-art-museum-17-fr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 00:39:41 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/enhance-art-sense-by-following-with-kwon-yul-yangju-art-museum-17-fr/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-title=&#34;enhance-art-sense-by-following-with-kwon-yul-yangju-art-museum--17&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Love by Kang Young-min installé au début du parc d&#39;art de Jangheung - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/d4c2c642-415c-495f-a8ad-f4af17caa572.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Love by Kang Young-min installé au début du parc d&#39;art de Jangheung
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Améliorez le sens de l&#39;art en suivant avec Kwon Yul, Yangju Art Museum
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Corée
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Pendant l&#39;essor du mica, le parc d&#39;attractions Yangju Ilyoung, le parc d&#39;attractions Jangheung et le parc d&#39;attractions Songchu ont été nommés parmi les 4050 ménages en tant que cours d&#39;entraînement de la région de la capitale. Il y a des restaurants autour de la vallée avec des terrains de football, donc c&#39;était un bon endroit pour des sorties en famille. Maintenant, tous se fanent, mais autant que le parc d&#39;attractions Jangheung pénètre dans les célèbres galeries d&#39;art, ce qui rend le week-end amusant.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Stage de sortie en collaboration avec les musées d&#39;art, les monuments culturels et l&#39;observatoire
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   La route 39, qui relie Deoyang-gu, Goyang-si et Suseong-dong, Uijeongbu-si, s&#39;appelle Pyeong-ro-ro. Cette route mène au box de police de Jangheung et rencontre une fourche appelée Kwon Yul-ro. Kwon Yul-ro, du nom du général Kwon-yul, se termine à l&#39;intersection de Jangheung Art Park, Jangheung Sculpture Park, Yangju City Jang Ukjin Art Museum (ci-après dénommé Jang Ukjin Art Museum), Horsehead Pass, Ahn Sang-cheol Art Musée et réservoir de Kisan, et à l&#39;intersection du Centre culturel et artistique de Yangju.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Devant le musée Jang Ukjin - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/2da5ba62-07c8-410b-8e9d-f6158f95d22f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Devant le musée Jang Ukjin
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Le général Kwon Yul est situé juste après l&#39;entrée du musée d&#39;art Jang Ukjin. Le général Kwon Yul est l&#39;un des maîtres qui a sauvé le pays pendant la guerre d&#39;Imjin. Le torchon qui a mené à la victoire est considéré comme le Three Great Battalion, avec le Pearl Battling et le Hansan Island Battling. En passant par Kwon Yul-ro, sa tête est inclinée devant l&#39;esprit général et l&#39;idéologie nationale du général. En tant que tel, le voyage au Musée d&#39;art de Yangju est un voyage avec un héritage culturel. Si vous incluez le Songam Space Center, c&#39;est un bon cours d&#39;étude qui combine des études astronomiques. Éveillez le sens de l&#39;art à travers des visites de musées d&#39;art, créant un sentiment d&#39;empathie entre les parents et les enfants et enrichissant les histoires. Sortir dans trois galeries d&#39;art à Kwon Yul-ro n&#39;est pas un simple trajet.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Théâtre Dome au Songam Space Center - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/c539c1f7-f645-4878-9ee0-69a49fbb88f9.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Théâtre Dome au Songam Space Center
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Parc d&#39;art de Jangheung
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Au départ de Gupabal, le réservoir de Gisan est la destination finale et le parc d&#39;art de Jangheung est le premier espace d&#39;art à se rencontrer à Kwon Yul-ro. Il a été plié depuis qu&#39;il a été renommé plusieurs fois depuis sa création. Total Art Museum a été créé en 1984, mais en 2005, il a changé pour Jangheung Art Park en raison de problèmes de gestion. Plus tard en 2006, le concepteur et architecte japonais Shigeru Uchida a conçu Art Park et le concepteur structurel Van Shigeru a conçu le lieu. En mai de la même année, un hall d&#39;exposition, un atelier, une salle de spectacle, une galerie d&#39;art, un parc de sculptures et un centre d&#39;expérience pour les enfants ont été achevés.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sculpture de Bourdel &amp;lt;Fruit&amp;gt; - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/57f0c167-ea11-4e39-ae48-799f2c41f51e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sculpture de Bourdel &amp;lt;Fruit&amp;gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Le parc d&#39;art de Jangheung n&#39;est pas un musée d&#39;art dédié à la peinture à une certaine distance. Il s&#39;agit d&#39;un espace artistique adapté aux terrains de jeux qui touche des œuvres et expose des œuvres sur lesquelles les enfants peuvent monter. Le nom de ce jardin est le jardin Bourdel. Des sculptures du sculpteur Bourdel, telles que Fruits, une femme sacrée accroupie et une mère et un enfant romains, exprimant l&#39;amour de la mère et de l&#39;enfant, accueillent des visiteurs de partout sur la pelouse. Le sculpteur français Bourdel est l&#39;un des trois plus grands maîtres de la sculpture moderne, avec Rodin et Mayol.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sculpture de Bourdel &amp;lt;Notre-Dame aux offrandes&amp;gt; - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/d50a5ceb-4e06-4053-86f3-8deddfc3cf73.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sculpture de Bourdel &amp;lt;Notre-Dame aux offrandes&amp;gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Musée d&#39;art pour enfants Picasso
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Le musée d&#39;art pour enfants Picasso est un incontournable pour les adultes. Bien qu&#39;il s&#39;agisse d&#39;une réplique, vous pouvez voir ici les œuvres et les vies passionnées de l&#39;âme de Picasso (1881 ~ 1973). En particulier, les photographies de Picasso prises par le photographe André Viller (1930 ~) sont incroyables, elles sont donc plus inspirantes. Les deux se sont rencontrés pour la première fois en 1953. Depuis lors, Biller a photographié de nombreuses scènes, y compris l&#39;accent de Picasso sur son travail et ses pensées. La passion de Picasso pour la photographie en noir et blanc et son envie de vie artistique prennent vie.
   &lt;br/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sculpture de Mark Quinn &amp;lt;Myth&amp;gt; - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/93e1a559-87ed-4179-a5cc-68a08caad74a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sculpture de Mark Quinn &amp;lt;Myth&amp;gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Les 11 portraits et photos de famille de Picasso attirent également le regard. De plus, vous pourrez apprécier la poterie, les gravures, les dessins et les plaques d&#39;argent de Picasso. En regardant en arrière avant de quitter le musée, papa enlève son chapeau et monte une échelle en short pour représenter le corps de la femme nue en ligne droite. La poitrine du spectateur est rafraîchissante.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Picasso travaillant en studio - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/b2ec457f-f052-420f-8d79-8c89de26bc19.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Picasso travaillant en studio
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   De plus, Express Train-The Era of Times de Ryu In, Dream of Peace de Kim Taek Ki, Myth de Mark Quinn et Love de Kang Young Min sont les sculptures représentatives du parc d&#39;art de Jangheung.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sculpture de l&#39;artiste Ryu dans &amp;lt;Express Train-The Era of Times&amp;gt; - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/44494ccb-4d14-4168-a6a0-21e59b9d0b75.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sculpture de l&#39;artiste Ryu dans &amp;lt;Express Train-The Era of Times&amp;gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Musée d&#39;art Jang Ukjin
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Juste à côté du parc d&#39;art de Jangheung en direction du cimetière général de Kwon Yul, le musée d&#39;art de Yangju est affiché. Le musée a été conçu d&#39;après la peinture du tigre de Jang Uk-jin et a été ouvert en avril 2014 et a remporté le prix d&#39;architecture Kim Soo-geun cette année-là. C&#39;est une grande fierté d&#39;avoir une grande collection d&#39;artistes authentiques. Plus de 230 pièces de peintures murales, peintures à l&#39;huile, gravures, peintures à l&#39;encre, etc. sont données par la Fondation Jang Uk-Jin pour la culture et l&#39;art afin de les afficher par thème et par période.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Musée d&#39;art de Yangju - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/b3eac18e-fc32-4ffc-95e5-111a9fcc141a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Musée d&#39;art de Yangju
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Le peintre Jang Uk-jin (1917 ~ 1990) est un maître de la peinture occidentale qui représente l&#39;art moderne coréen avec Park Soo-geun et Lee Joong-seop. Né à Yeong-gun, Chungcheongnam-do (maintenant Sejong Special Self-Governing City), l&#39;histoire de son musée d&#39;art entrant à Yangju était due à son atelier à Deokso, autrefois une terre du comté de Yangju. Depuis, il a poursuivi ses activités créatives dans les studios de Seoul Myeongryon-dong, Chungju Suanbo et Yongin Singal.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Visiteurs de la &amp;lt;Famille d&#39;animaux&amp;gt; au Musée d&#39;art Jang Ukjin - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/be1507be-1d67-4488-a964-68bcf9c010ef.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Visiteurs de la &amp;lt;Famille d&#39;animaux&amp;gt; au Musée d&#39;art Jang Ukjin
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   &amp;lt;Famille d&#39;animaux&amp;gt; et &amp;lt;Table à manger&amp;gt; peintes sur un mur de ciment
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   L&#39;entrée est bonne pour commencer au deuxième étage. De cette façon, vous pouvez d&#39;abord rencontrer le travail du maître et réfléchir à nouveau sur sa vie dans la salle vidéo du premier étage. &amp;lt;Famille d&#39;animaux&amp;gt; au deuxième étage est une œuvre appréciée des visiteurs. Créée en 1964, la description de travail attachée sur le côté raconte la vieille histoire avec la photographie en noir et blanc. Animal Family a été peint sur le mur du studio de Deokso, Gyeonggi-do. Le regard chaleureux du peintre se ressent dans l&#39;œuvre d&#39;art où vaches, poulets, cochons et chiens sont harmonieusement dessinés comme une famille. En particulier, les véritables cowcoats et warangs sont accrochés aux peintures murales pour évoquer les sentiments locaux.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;5&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Musée d&#39;art Jang Ukjin - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/f80bf391-f32c-46ff-9f7f-e93a3e8d2feb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Musée d&#39;art Jang Ukjin
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   L&#39;œuvre qui a décollé le mur peint est au milieu de l&#39;escalier reliant le sous-sol et le premier étage. Le titre est &amp;lt;Table&amp;gt;. Regardons la description du travail. «Les peintures montrent la vie moderne d&#39;un artiste, et sur l&#39;écran se trouvent des fourchettes et des couteaux, des cuillères et des bols à riz, des tasses à café, des verres à eau, des flets et des os. Après que le peintre a terminé cette image, il est devenu. Aujourd&#39;hui, remplaçons un repas par ce repas. &#34;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;5&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Mère et fille se reposant devant le café au 1er étage du Jang Ukjin Museum of Art - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/8e708bf4-0235-438a-90b3-0b5fd365c6d8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Mère et fille se reposant devant le café au 1er étage du Jang Ukjin Museum of Art
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   L&#39;idée d&#39;utiliser le mur de ciment gris comme toile, et la simplicité et la chaleur de la toile. Les visiteurs trouvent l&#39;amour pour les personnes et les objets dans chacune de leurs œuvres, développent leur imagination et se retrouvent plus généreux. La beauté d&#39;un voyage dans un musée est la suivante.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;5&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Parc de sculptures de Jangheung en face du musée d&#39;art Jang Ukjin - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/c1b3ec97-4d50-4813-b74c-7e10ad4ac1a6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Parc de sculptures de Jangheung en face du musée d&#39;art Jang Ukjin
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Le musée d&#39;art Ahn Sang-cheol amène le réservoir Kisan au jardin
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Le voyage au musée après Kwon Yul-ro de Yangju-si se termine au musée d&#39;art An Sang-cheol, situé à côté du réservoir Gisan. Ahn Sang-cheol (1927-1993) est un peintre qui a laissé de nombreuses oeuvres célèbres dans le domaine de la peinture orientale. Il était professeur au Seorabol Art College et à la Sungshin Women&#39;s University. Ahn Sang-cheol, qui est devenue une star de guerre nationale après avoir remporté le ministre de l&#39;Éducation, le prix du vice-président et le prix du président en 1959, a épousé Na Hee-kyun, étudiante contemporaine de l&#39;Université nationale de Séoul et neveu de Na Hye-seok.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;6&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Réservoir Kisan du musée d&#39;art d&#39;Ansangcheol - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/674eb3d2-6e04-4f5c-8c90-895a8de77c6e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Réservoir Kisan du musée d&#39;art d&#39;Ansangcheol
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   À l&#39;entrée du musée, vous pouvez suivre la vie d&#39;Ahn et entrer dans l&#39;espace d&#39;exposition pour voir ses œuvres. Il s&#39;agit d&#39;une série de travaux intitulée &amp;lt;(靈)&amp;gt;, qui a coloré le vieil arbre. Il a créé ce travail avec la pensée que «l&#39;esprit est un corps qui reste et est transmis par quelqu&#39;un même lorsqu&#39;il meurt.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;6&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Musée d&#39;art d&#39;Ahnsangcheol de la pelouse - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/2fe5a84b-a13c-4224-bdfa-878947a3123e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Musée d&#39;art d&#39;Ahnsangcheol de la pelouse
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   La file des spectateurs continue devant ses oeuvres. Bien qu&#39;il soit un vieil homme avec 12 expositions personnelles, il est toujours activement engagé dans des activités créatives. La ligne de cuivre est une pelouse qui mène au réservoir Kisan. Le bâtiment du musée est l&#39;œuvre d&#39;Ahn Woo-sung, le fils d&#39;Ahn Sang-cheol et le propriétaire des architectes Ongodang. Il y a un studio avec une fenêtre en verre derrière un jardin fleuri. C&#39;est là que Na Hee-kyun, un peintre, s&#39;arrête parfois pour peindre. Le musée d&#39;art Ahn Sang-cheol ouvrira ses portes jusqu&#39;au 15 juillet.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;6&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;15&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Œuvre de l&#39;artiste Lee Hee-kyun &amp;lt;My Mirina 2&amp;gt; - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/1a41d284-06fa-41a3-be91-deb0fb836c19.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Œuvre de l&#39;artiste Lee Hee-kyun &amp;lt;My Mirina 2&amp;gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Info voyage
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Parc d&#39;art de Jangheung
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Adresse: 117, Kwon Yul-ro, Jangheung-myeon, Yangju-si, Gyeonggi-do
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Contact: 031-877-0500
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.artpark.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.artpark.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Musée d&#39;art de Yangju
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Adresse: 211 Kwon Yul-ro, Jangheung-myeon, Yangju-si, Gyeonggi-do
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Contact: 031-8082-4245
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://changucchin.yangju.go.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://changucchin.yangju.go.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Musée d&#39;art Ahn Sang Chul
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Adresse: 905 Kwon Yul-ro, Baekseok-eup, Yangju-si, Gyeonggi-do
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Contact: 031-874-0734
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.ahnsangchul.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.ahnsangchul.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Restaurants à proximité
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Restaurant affilié: Hanwoo / 410, Gisan-ro, Baekseok-eup, Yangju-si / 031-871-9271
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Chosun Gomtang: Gomtang / 46, Deokjeong 14 gils, Yangju-si / 031-857-1445
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Yemogol: Steak / 442, Gamagol-ro, Jangheung-myeon, Yangju-si / 031-855-1891
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Hébergement
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Buckingham Hotel: 462-1, Gisan-ro, Baekseok-eup, Yangju-si / 031-871-9441
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Pine Hill Motel: 305-33, Gwonryul-ro 309beon-gil, Jangheung-myeon, Yangju-si / 031-829-0711
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Palais: 492 Kwon Yul-ro, Jangheung-myeon, Yangju-si / 031-855-2900
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ Les informations ci-dessus ont été fournies en juin 2015. Elles peuvent changer par la suite, veuillez donc vérifier avant de voyager.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Les informations telles que le texte, les photos et les vidéos utilisées dans cet article sont protégées par les droits d&#39;auteur de l&#39;Organisation coréenne du tourisme, de sorte que l&#39;utilisation non autorisée de l&#39;article est interdite.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Corea - Mejore el sentido del arte siguiendo con Kwon Yul, Yangju Art Museum</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/enhance-art-sense-by-following-with-kwon-yul-yangju-art-museum-17-es/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 00:36:32 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/enhance-art-sense-by-following-with-kwon-yul-yangju-art-museum-17-es/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-title=&#34;enhance-art-sense-by-following-with-kwon-yul-yangju-art-museum--17&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Love by Kang Young-min instalado al comienzo del parque de arte Jangheung - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/d4c2c642-415c-495f-a8ad-f4af17caa572.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Love by Kang Young-min instalado al comienzo del parque de arte Jangheung
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Mejore el sentido del arte siguiendo con Kwon Yul, Yangju Art Museum
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Corea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Durante el auge de la mica, el parque de atracciones Yangju Ilyoung, el parque de atracciones Jangheung y el parque de atracciones Songchu fueron nombrados entre los 4050 hogares como el curso de conducción de la región capital. Hay restaurantes en todo el valle con canchas de fútbol, por lo que fue un buen lugar para salidas familiares. Ahora todos se están desvaneciendo, pero tanto como Jangheung Amusement Park ingresa a las famosas galerías de arte, lo que hace que el fin de semana sea divertido.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Curso de excursión en conjunto con museos de arte, monumentos culturales y observatorio.
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   La ruta 39, que conecta Deoyang-gu, Goyang-si y Suseong-dong, Uijeongbu-si, se llama Pyeong-ro-ro. Este camino conduce a la caja de policía de Jangheung y se encuentra con un tenedor llamado Kwon Yul-ro. Kwon Yul-ro, llamado así por el general Kwon-yul, termina en la intersección del parque de arte Jangheung, el parque de esculturas Jangheung, el museo de arte Jang Ukjin de la ciudad de Yangju (en lo sucesivo denominado Museo de arte Jang Ukjin), Horsehead Pass, Ahn Sang-cheol Art Museo y embalse de Kisan, y en la intersección del Centro de Cultura y Artes de Yangju.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Frente al museo Jang Ukjin - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/2da5ba62-07c8-410b-8e9d-f6158f95d22f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Frente al museo Jang Ukjin
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Kwon Yul General se encuentra justo después de la entrada del Museo de Arte Jang Ukjin. El general Kwon Yul es uno de los maestros que salvó al país durante la Guerra Imjin. El trapo de cocina que condujo a la victoria se considera el Gran Batallón Tres, junto con la Batalla de Perlas y la Batalla de la Isla Hansan. Mientras pasa por Kwon Yul-ro, su cabeza se inclina ante el espíritu general y la ideología nacional del general. Como tal, el viaje al Museo de Arte de Yangju es un viaje con patrimonio cultural. Si incluye el Centro Espacial Songam, es un buen curso de estudio que combina estudios astronómicos. Despierta el sentido del arte a través de visitas a museos de arte, creando una sensación de empatía entre padres e hijos e historias enriquecedoras. Entonces, salir a tres galerías de arte en Kwon Yul-ro no es un simple viaje.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Teatro Dome en el Centro Espacial Songam - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/c539c1f7-f645-4878-9ee0-69a49fbb88f9.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Teatro Dome en el Centro Espacial Songam
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Parque de arte Jangheung
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Partiendo de Gupabal, Gisan Reservoir es el destino final y Jangheung Art Park es el primer espacio de arte en encontrarse en Kwon Yul-ro. Se ha doblado desde que se le cambió el nombre varias veces desde su creación. Total Art Museum se estableció por primera vez en 1984, pero en 2005, cambió a Jangheung Art Park debido a problemas de gestión. Más tarde, en 2006, el diseñador y arquitecto japonés Shigeru Uchida diseñó Art Park y el diseñador estructural Van Shigeru diseñó el lugar. En mayo de ese año, se completaron una sala de exposiciones, un taller, una sala de espectáculos, una galería de arte, un parque de esculturas y un centro de experiencias para niños.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Escultura de Bourdel &amp;lt;Fruta&amp;gt; - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/57f0c167-ea11-4e39-ae48-799f2c41f51e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Escultura de Bourdel &amp;lt;Fruta&amp;gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Jangheung Art Park no es un museo de arte dedicado a pintar a cierta distancia. Es un espacio de arte apto para juegos que toca obras y muestra obras en las que los niños pueden montar. El nombre de este jardín es Bourdel Garden. Las esculturas del escultor Bourdel, como Fruits, a Crouching Sacred Woman y Roman Mother and Child, que expresan el amor de la madre y el niño, dan la bienvenida a visitantes de todo el césped. El escultor francés Bourdel es uno de los tres grandes maestros de la escultura moderna, junto con Rodin y Mayol.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Escultura de Bourdel &amp;lt;Nuestra Señora con Ofrendas&amp;gt; - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/d50a5ceb-4e06-4053-86f3-8deddfc3cf73.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Escultura de Bourdel &amp;lt;Nuestra Señora con Ofrendas&amp;gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Museo de arte infantil Picasso
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   El Museo de Arte Infantil Picasso es una visita obligada para adultos. Aunque es una réplica, puedes ver las obras y la vida apasionada del alma de Picasso (1881 ~ 1973) aquí. En particular, las fotografías de Picasso tomadas por el fotógrafo Andre Viller (1930 ~) son increíbles, por lo que son más inspiradoras. Los dos se conocieron en 1953. Desde entonces, Biller ha fotografiado muchas escenas, incluido el enfoque de Picasso en su trabajo y sus pensamientos. La pasión de Picasso por la fotografía en blanco y negro y su deseo por la vida artística cobran vida.
   &lt;br/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Escultura de Mark Quinn &amp;lt;Mito&amp;gt; - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/93e1a559-87ed-4179-a5cc-68a08caad74a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Escultura de Mark Quinn &amp;lt;Mito&amp;gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Los 11 retratos y fotos familiares de Picasso también llaman la atención. Además, puede apreciar la cerámica, los grabados, los dibujos y las planchas de plata de Picasso. Mirando hacia atrás antes de abandonar el museo, papá se quita el sombrero y sube una escalera en pantalones cortos para representar el cuerpo de la mujer desnuda en línea recta. El cofre del espectador es refrescante.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Picasso trabajando en el estudio - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/b2ec457f-f052-420f-8d79-8c89de26bc19.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Picasso trabajando en el estudio
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Además, el Tren expreso de Ryu In: La era de los tiempos, El sueño de la paz de Kim Taek Ki, El mito de Mark Quinn y El amor de Kang Young Min son las esculturas representativas del Parque de Arte Jangheung.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Escultura del artista Ryu en &amp;lt;Tren expreso-La era de los tiempos&amp;gt; - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/44494ccb-4d14-4168-a6a0-21e59b9d0b75.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Escultura del artista Ryu en &amp;lt;Tren expreso-La era de los tiempos&amp;gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Museo de arte de Jang Ukjin
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Apenas un poco más arriba del Parque de Arte Jangheung hacia el Cementerio General de Kwon Yul, se muestra el Museo de Arte de Yangju. El museo fue diseñado después de la pintura del tigre de Jang Uk-jin y se inauguró en abril de 2014 y ganó el Premio de Arquitectura Kim Soo-geun ese año. Es un gran orgullo tener una gran colección de artistas genuinos. La Fundación de Arte y Cultura de Jang Uk-Jin dona más de 230 piezas de murales, pinturas al óleo, grabados, pinturas de tinta, etc. para mostrarlas por tema y período.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Museo de arte de Yangju - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/b3eac18e-fc32-4ffc-95e5-111a9fcc141a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Museo de arte de Yangju
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   El pintor Jang Uk-jin (1917 ~ 1990) es un maestro de la pintura occidental que representa el arte moderno coreano junto con Park Soo-geun y Lee Joong-seop. Nacido en Yeong-gun, Chungcheongnam-do (ahora Sejong Special Self-Governing City), la historia de su museo de arte que ingresó a Yangju se debió a su estudio en Deokso, una vez una tierra del condado de Yangju. Desde entonces, ha continuado sus actividades creativas en los estudios de Seúl Myeongryon-dong, Chungju Suanbo y Yongin Singal.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Visitantes de &amp;lt;Animal Family&amp;gt; en el Museo de Arte Jang Ukjin - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/be1507be-1d67-4488-a964-68bcf9c010ef.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Visitantes de &amp;lt;Animal Family&amp;gt; en el Museo de Arte Jang Ukjin
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   &amp;lt;Familia de animales&amp;gt; y &amp;lt;Mesa de comedor&amp;gt; pintados en la pared de cemento
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   La entrada es buena para comenzar desde el segundo piso. De esta manera, puedes conocer primero el trabajo del maestro y reflexionar sobre su vida una vez más en la sala de video del primer piso. &amp;lt;Animal Family&amp;gt; en el segundo piso es un trabajo que es amado por los visitantes. Creada en 1964, la descripción del trabajo adjunta al lado cuenta la vieja historia con fotografía en blanco y negro. Animal Family fue pintado en la pared del estudio en Deokso, Gyeonggi-do. La cálida mirada del pintor se puede sentir en la obra de arte donde las vacas, gallinas, cerdos y perros se dibujan armoniosamente como una familia. En particular, los verdaderos abrigos y vaqueros se cuelgan en los murales para evocar sentimientos locales.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;5&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Museo de arte de Jang Ukjin - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/f80bf391-f32c-46ff-9f7f-e93a3e8d2feb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Museo de arte de Jang Ukjin
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   El trabajo que se despegó de la pared pintada está en el medio de las escaleras que conectan el sótano y el primer piso. El título es &amp;lt;Table&amp;gt;. Veamos la descripción del trabajo. “Las pinturas muestran la vida moderna de un artista, y en la pantalla hay tenedores y cuchillos, cucharas y cuencos de arroz, tazas de café, vasos de agua, platija y huesos. Después de que el pintor completó esta imagen, se convirtió. Hoy, reemplacemos una comida con esta comida. &#39;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;5&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Madre e hija descansando frente a la cafetería en el primer piso del Museo de Arte Jang Ukjin - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/8e708bf4-0235-438a-90b3-0b5fd365c6d8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Madre e hija descansando frente a la cafetería en el primer piso del Museo de Arte Jang Ukjin
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   La idea de usar la pared de cemento gris como lienzo, y la simplicidad y calidez del lienzo. Los visitantes encuentran amor por las personas y los objetos en cada una de sus obras, desarrollan su imaginación y se vuelven más generosos. La belleza de un viaje a un museo es esta.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;5&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Parque de esculturas Jangheung frente al Museo de Arte Jang Ukjin - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/c1b3ec97-4d50-4813-b74c-7e10ad4ac1a6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Parque de esculturas Jangheung frente al Museo de Arte Jang Ukjin
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   El Museo de Arte Ahn Sang-cheol lleva el embalse de Kisan al jardín
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   El viaje al museo siguiendo a Kwon Yul-ro de Yangju-si termina en el Museo de Arte An Sang-cheol, ubicado junto al embalse de Gisan. Ahn Sang-cheol (1927-1993) es un pintor que dejó muchas obras famosas en el campo de la pintura oriental. Fue profesor en Seorabol Art College y Sungshin Women&#39;s University. Ahn Sang-cheol, quien se convirtió en una estrella de guerra nacional después de ganar el Ministro de Educación, el Premio del Vicepresidente y el Premio del Presidente en 1959, se casó con Na Hee-kyun, un estudiante contemporáneo de la Universidad Nacional de Seúl y sobrino de Na Hye-seok.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;6&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Embalse de Kisan del Museo de Arte Ansangcheol - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/674eb3d2-6e04-4f5c-8c90-895a8de77c6e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Embalse de Kisan del Museo de Arte Ansangcheol
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   En la entrada del museo, puedes seguir la vida de Ahn y entrar al espacio de exhibición para ver sus obras. Es una serie de trabajos titulada &amp;lt;(靈)&amp;gt;, que ha coloreado el viejo árbol. Creó este trabajo con la idea de que &#34;el espíritu es un cuerpo que permanece y es transmitido por alguien incluso cuando muere&#34;.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;6&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Museo de Arte Ahnsangcheol desde el césped - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/2fe5a84b-a13c-4224-bdfa-878947a3123e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Museo de Arte Ahnsangcheol desde el césped
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   La línea de espectadores continúa frente a sus obras. Aunque es un anciano con 12 exposiciones individuales, todavía participa activamente en actividades creativas. La línea de cobre es un césped, que conduce al embalse de Kisan. El edificio del museo es obra de Ahn Woo-sung, hijo de Ahn Sang-cheol y propietario de Ongodang Architects. Hay un estudio con una ventana de vidrio detrás de un jardín de flores. Aquí es donde Na Hee-kyun, un pintor, a veces se detiene a pintar. El Museo de Arte Ahn Sang-cheol abrirá hasta el 15 de julio.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;6&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;15&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;El trabajo del artista Lee Hee-kyun &amp;lt;My Mirina 2&amp;gt;(남성) - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/1a41d284-06fa-41a3-be91-deb0fb836c19.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     El trabajo del artista Lee Hee-kyun &amp;lt;My Mirina 2&amp;gt;(남성)
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Información de viaje
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Parque de arte Jangheung
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Dirección: 117, Kwon Yul-ro, Jangheung-myeon, Yangju-si, Gyeonggi-do
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Contacto: 031-877-0500
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.artpark.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.artpark.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Museo de arte de Yangju
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Dirección: 211 Kwon Yul-ro, Jangheung-myeon, Yangju-si, Gyeonggi-do
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Contacto: 031-8082-4245
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://changucchin.yangju.go.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://changucchin.yangju.go.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Museo de Arte Ahn Sang Chul
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Dirección: 905 Kwon Yul-ro, Baekseok-eup, Yangju-si, Gyeonggi-do
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Contacto: 031-874-0734
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.ahnsangchul.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.ahnsangchul.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Restaurantes cercanos
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Restaurante afiliado: Hanwoo / 410, Gisan-ro, Baekseok-eup, Yangju-si / 031-871-9271
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Chosun Gomtang: Gomtang / 46, Deokjeong 14-gil, Yangju-si / 031-857-1445
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Yemogol: Filete / 442, Gamagol-ro, Jangheung-myeon, Yangju-si / 031-855-1891
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Alojamiento
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Hotel Buckingham: 462-1, Gisan-ro, Baekseok-eup, Yangju-si / 031-871-9441
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Pine Hill Motel: 305-33, Gwonryul-ro 309beon-gil, Jangheung-myeon, Yangju-si / 031-829-0711
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Palacio: 492 Kwon Yul-ro, Jangheung-myeon, Yangju-si / 031-855-2900
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ La información anterior se realizó en junio de 2015. Puede cambiar después, así que verifique antes de viajar.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ La información como texto, fotos y videos utilizados en este artículo tiene copyright de la Organización de Turismo de Corea, por lo que está prohibido el uso no autorizado del artículo.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea - Verbessern Sie den Kunstsinn, indem Sie Kwon Yul, Yangju Art Museum, folgen</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/enhance-art-sense-by-following-with-kwon-yul-yangju-art-museum-17-de/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 00:33:22 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/enhance-art-sense-by-following-with-kwon-yul-yangju-art-museum-17-de/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-title=&#34;enhance-art-sense-by-following-with-kwon-yul-yangju-art-museum--17&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Love by Kang Young-min wurde am Anfang des Jangheung Art Park installiert - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/d4c2c642-415c-495f-a8ad-f4af17caa572.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Love by Kang Young-min wurde am Anfang des Jangheung Art Park installiert
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Verbessern Sie den Kunstsinn, indem Sie Kwon Yul, Yangju Art Museum, folgen
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Während des Glimmerbooms wurden der Vergnügungspark Yangju Ilyoung, der Vergnügungspark Jangheung und der Vergnügungspark Songchu zu den 4050 Haushalten als Capital Region Drive Course ernannt. Es gibt Restaurants rund um das Tal mit Fußballplätzen, daher war es ein guter Ort für Familienausflüge. Jetzt verblassen alle, aber so sehr der Vergnügungspark Jangheung die berühmten Kunstgalerien betritt, macht das Fahren am Wochenende Spaß.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Ausflugskurs in Verbindung mit Kunstmuseen, Kulturdenkmälern und Observatorium
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Die Route 39, die Deoyang-gu, Goyang-si und Suseong-dong, Uijeongbu-si, verbindet, heißt Pyeong-ro-ro. Diese Straße führt zur Polizeikiste von Jangheung und trifft auf eine Gabelung namens Kwon Yul-ro. Kwon Yul-ro, benannt nach General Kwon-yul, endet an der Kreuzung von Jangheung Art Park, Jangheung Sculpture Park, Jang Ukjin Art Museum (im Folgenden als Jang Ukjin Art Museum bezeichnet), Horsehead Pass, Ahn Sang-cheol Art Museum und Kisan-Stausee sowie an der Kreuzung des Kultur- und Kunstzentrums Yangju.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Vor dem Jang Ukjin Museum - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/2da5ba62-07c8-410b-8e9d-f6158f95d22f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Vor dem Jang Ukjin Museum
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Das Kwon Yul General befindet sich direkt hinter dem Eingang des Jang Ukjin Kunstmuseums. General Kwon Yul ist einer der Meister, die das Land während des Imjin-Krieges gerettet haben. Das Geschirrtuch, das zum Sieg führte, gilt neben dem Pearl Battling und dem Hansan Island Battling als das Three Great Battalion. Während er durch Kwon Yul-ro geht, neigt sein Kopf zum allgemeinen Geist und zur nationalen Ideologie des Generals. Insofern ist die Reise zum Yangju Museum of Art eine Reise mit kulturellem Erbe. Wenn Sie das Songam Space Center mit einbeziehen, ist es ein guter Studienausflug, der astronomische Studien kombiniert. Erwecken Sie den Sinn für Kunst durch Besuche in Kunstmuseen, schaffen Sie ein Gefühl von Empathie zwischen Eltern und Kindern und bereichern Sie Geschichten. Der Besuch von drei Kunstgalerien in Kwon Yul-ro ist also keine einfache Fahrt.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Kuppeltheater im Songam Space Center - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/c539c1f7-f645-4878-9ee0-69a49fbb88f9.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Kuppeltheater im Songam Space Center
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Jangheung Kunstpark
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Von Gupabal aus ist der Gisan-Stausee das Endziel und der Jangheung Art Park ist der erste Kunstraum, der sich in Kwon Yul-ro trifft. Es wurde gebogen, seit es seit seiner Gründung mehrmals umbenannt wurde. Das Total Art Museum wurde 1984 gegründet und 2005 aufgrund von Managementproblemen in den Jangheung Art Park umgewandelt. Später im Jahr 2006 entwarf der japanische Designer und Architekt Shigeru Uchida den Art Park und der Konstrukteur Van Shigeru den Veranstaltungsort. Im Mai dieses Jahres wurden eine Ausstellungshalle, ein Atelier, eine Aufführungshalle, eine Kunstgalerie, ein Skulpturenpark und ein Kindererlebniszentrum fertiggestellt.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Bourdels Skulptur &amp;lt;Frucht&amp;gt; - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/57f0c167-ea11-4e39-ae48-799f2c41f51e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Bourdels Skulptur &amp;lt;Frucht&amp;gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Der Jangheung Art Park ist kein Kunstmuseum, das sich der Malerei mit einer gewissen Entfernung widmet. Es ist ein spielplatzfreundlicher Kunstraum, der Werke berührt und Werke zeigt, auf denen Kinder reiten können. Der Name dieses Gartens ist Bourdel Garden. Skulpturen des Bildhauers Bourdel wie Fruits, eine hockende heilige Frau und römische Mutter und Kind, die die Liebe von Mutter und Kind zum Ausdruck bringen, heißen Besucher aus aller Welt willkommen. Der französische Bildhauer Bourdel ist neben Rodin und Mayol einer der drei größten Meister der modernen Bildhauerei.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Bourdels Skulptur &amp;lt;Unsere Liebe Frau mit Opfergaben&amp;gt; - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/d50a5ceb-4e06-4053-86f3-8deddfc3cf73.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Bourdels Skulptur &amp;lt;Unsere Liebe Frau mit Opfergaben&amp;gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Picasso Kinderkunstmuseum
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Das Picasso Kinderkunstmuseum ist ein Muss für Erwachsene. Obwohl es sich um eine Nachbildung handelt, können Sie hier die Werke und das leidenschaftliche Leben von Picassos Seele (1881 ~ 1973) sehen. Insbesondere Picassos Fotografien des Fotografen Andre Viller (1930 ~) sind unglaublich und daher inspirierender. Die beiden trafen sich 1953 zum ersten Mal. Seitdem hat Biller viele Szenen fotografiert, darunter Picassos Fokus auf seine Arbeit und seine Gedanken. Picassos Leidenschaft für die Schwarzweißfotografie und sein Wunsch nach künstlerischem Leben werden lebendig.
   &lt;br/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Mark Quinns Skulptur &amp;lt;Myth&amp;gt; - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/93e1a559-87ed-4179-a5cc-68a08caad74a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Mark Quinns Skulptur &amp;lt;Myth&amp;gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Picassos 11 Porträts und Familienfotos fallen ebenfalls auf. Darüber hinaus können Sie Picassos Keramik, Drucke, Zeichnungen und Silberteller bewundern. Dad blickt zurück, bevor er das Museum verlässt, nimmt seinen Hut ab und steigt in kurzen Hosen eine Leiter hinauf, um den Körper der nackten Frau in einer geraden Linie darzustellen. Die Brust des Betrachters ist erfrischend.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Picasso arbeitet im Studio - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/b2ec457f-f052-420f-8d79-8c89de26bc19.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Picasso arbeitet im Studio
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Darüber hinaus sind Ryu In&#39;s Expresszug - Die Ära der Zeiten, Kim Taek Kis Traum vom Frieden, Mark Quinns Mythos und Kang Young Min&#39;s Love die repräsentativen Skulpturen des Jangheung Art Park.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Skulptur des Künstlers Ryu In &amp;lt;Express Train-The Era of Times&amp;gt; - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/44494ccb-4d14-4168-a6a0-21e59b9d0b75.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Skulptur des Künstlers Ryu In &amp;lt;Express Train-The Era of Times&amp;gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Jang Ukjin Kunstmuseum
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Nur ein kleines Stück vom Jangheung Art Park in Richtung Kwon Yul General Cemetery befindet sich das Yangju Museum of Art. Das Museum wurde nach dem Tigerbild von Jang Uk-jin entworfen und im April 2014 eröffnet. In diesem Jahr wurde es mit dem Kim Soo-geun Architecture Award ausgezeichnet. Es ist ein großer Stolz, eine große Sammlung echter Künstler zu haben. Mehr als 230 Wandgemälde, Ölgemälde, Drucke, Tuschemalereien usw. werden von der Kunst- und Kulturstiftung Jang Uk-Jin gespendet, um sie nach Thema und Zeit zu zeigen.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Yangju Kunstmuseum - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/b3eac18e-fc32-4ffc-95e5-111a9fcc141a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Yangju Kunstmuseum
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Der Maler Jang Uk-jin (1917 ~ 1990) ist ein Meister der westlichen Malerei, der zusammen mit Park Soo-geun und Lee Joong-seop die moderne koreanische Kunst repräsentiert. Geboren in Yeong-gun, Chungcheongnam-do (heute Sejong Special Self-Governing City), war die Geschichte seines Kunstmuseums in Yangju seinem Atelier in Deokso zu verdanken, das einst ein Land des Landkreises Yangju war. Seitdem hat er seine kreativen Aktivitäten in den Studios von Seoul Myeongryon-dong, Chungju Suanbo und Yongin Singal fortgesetzt.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Besucher der &amp;lt;Tierfamilie&amp;gt; im Jang Ukjin Museum of Art - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/be1507be-1d67-4488-a964-68bcf9c010ef.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Besucher der &amp;lt;Tierfamilie&amp;gt; im Jang Ukjin Museum of Art
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   &amp;lt;Tierfamilie&amp;gt; und &amp;lt;Esstisch&amp;gt; auf Betonwand gemalt
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Der Eintritt ist gut, um vom zweiten Stock zu beginnen. Auf diese Weise können Sie zuerst die Arbeit des Meisters treffen und im Videoraum im ersten Stock noch einmal über sein Leben nachdenken. &amp;lt;Tierfamilie&amp;gt; im zweiten Stock ist eine Arbeit, die von Besuchern geliebt wird. Die 1964 erstellte Arbeitsbeschreibung, die 1964 erstellt wurde, erzählt die alte Geschichte mit Schwarzweißfotografie. Animal Family wurde an die Wand des Studios in Deokso, Gyeonggi-do, gemalt. Der warme Blick des Malers ist in dem Kunstwerk zu spüren, in dem Kühe, Hühner, Schweine und Hunde wie eine Familie harmonisch gezeichnet sind. Insbesondere die echten Cowcoats und Warangs werden an die Wandbilder gehängt, um lokale Gefühle hervorzurufen.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;5&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Jang Ukjin Kunstmuseum - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/f80bf391-f32c-46ff-9f7f-e93a3e8d2feb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Jang Ukjin Kunstmuseum
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Die Arbeit, die sich von der bemalten Wand löste, befindet sich in der Mitte der Treppe, die den Keller und den ersten Stock verbindet. Der Titel lautet &amp;lt;Tabelle&amp;gt;. Schauen wir uns die Beschreibung der Arbeit an. „Die Bilder zeigen das moderne Leben eines Künstlers und auf dem Bildschirm sind Gabeln und Messer, Löffel und Reisschüsseln, Kaffeetassen, Wassergläser, Flunder und Knochen zu sehen. Nachdem der Maler dieses Bild fertiggestellt hatte, wurde er. Lassen Sie uns heute eine Mahlzeit durch diese Mahlzeit ersetzen. &#39;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;5&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Mutter und Tochter ruhen vor dem Café im 1. Stock des Jang Ukjin Kunstmuseums - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/8e708bf4-0235-438a-90b3-0b5fd365c6d8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Mutter und Tochter ruhen vor dem Café im 1. Stock des Jang Ukjin Kunstmuseums
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Die Idee, die graue Betonwand als Leinwand zu verwenden, und die Einfachheit und Wärme der Leinwand. Besucher finden in jedem ihrer Werke Liebe zu Menschen und Gegenständen, entwickeln ihre Fantasie und finden sich großzügiger. Das Schöne an einem Museumsausflug ist dies.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;5&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Jangheung Skulpturenpark vor dem Jang Ukjin Kunstmuseum - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/c1b3ec97-4d50-4813-b74c-7e10ad4ac1a6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Jangheung Skulpturenpark vor dem Jang Ukjin Kunstmuseum
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Das Kunstmuseum Ahn Sang-cheol bringt den Kisan-Stausee in den Garten
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Die Reise zum Museum nach Kwon Yul-ro von Yangju-si endet im An Sang-cheol Kunstmuseum neben dem Gisan-Stausee. Ahn Sang-cheol (1927-1993) ist ein Maler, der viele berühmte Werke auf dem Gebiet der orientalischen Malerei hinterlassen hat. Er war Professor am Seorabol Art College und an der Sungshin Women&#39;s University. Ahn Sang-cheol, der nach dem Gewinn des Bildungsministers, des Vizepräsidentenpreises und des Präsidentenpreises 1959 zum nationalen Kriegsstar wurde, heiratete Na Hee-kyun, einen zeitgenössischen Studenten der Seoul National University und Neffen von Na Hye-seok.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;6&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Kisan Reservoir vom Ansangcheol Museum of Art - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/674eb3d2-6e04-4f5c-8c90-895a8de77c6e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Kisan Reservoir vom Ansangcheol Museum of Art
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Am Eingang des Museums können Sie Ahns Leben verfolgen und den Ausstellungsraum betreten, um seine Werke zu sehen. Es ist eine Reihe von Arbeiten mit dem Titel &amp;lt;(靈)&amp;gt;, die den alten Baum gefärbt haben. Er schuf diese Arbeit mit dem Gedanken, dass &#34;der Geist ein Körper ist, der bleibt und von jemandem weitergegeben wird, selbst wenn er stirbt&#34;.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;6&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Ahnsangcheol Kunstmuseum vom Rasen - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/2fe5a84b-a13c-4224-bdfa-878947a3123e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Ahnsangcheol Kunstmuseum vom Rasen
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Die Zuschauerlinie setzt sich vor ihren Arbeiten fort. Obwohl er ein alter Mann mit 12 Einzelausstellungen ist, engagiert er sich immer noch aktiv für kreative Aktivitäten. Die Kupferleitung ist ein Rasen, der zum Kisan-Stausee führt. Das Gebäude des Museums ist das Werk von Ahn Woo-sung, dem Sohn von Ahn Sang-cheol und Eigentümer von Ongodang Architects. Hinter einem Blumengarten befindet sich ein Studio mit einem Glasfenster. Hier hört Na Hee-kyun, ein Maler, manchmal auf zu malen. Das Kunstmuseum Ahn Sang-cheol ist bis zum 15. Juli geöffnet.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;6&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;15&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Die Arbeit des Künstlers Lee Hee-kyun &amp;lt;My Mirina 2&amp;gt; - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/1a41d284-06fa-41a3-be91-deb0fb836c19.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Die Arbeit des Künstlers Lee Hee-kyun &amp;lt;My Mirina 2&amp;gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Reiseinformationen
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Jangheung Kunstpark
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Adresse: 117, Kwon Yul-ro, Jangheung-myeon, Yangju-si, Gyeonggi-do
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Kontakt: 031-877-0500
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.artpark.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.artpark.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Yangju Kunstmuseum
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Adresse: 211 Kwon Yul-ro, Jangheung-myeon, Yangju-si, Gyeonggi-do
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Kontakt: 031-8082-4245
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://changucchin.yangju.go.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://changucchin.yangju.go.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Ahn Sang Chul Kunstmuseum
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Adresse: 905 Kwon Yul-ro, Baekseok-eup, Yangju-si, Gyeonggi-do
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Kontakt: 031-874-0734
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.ahnsangchul.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.ahnsangchul.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Restaurants in der Nähe
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Verbundenes Restaurant: Hanwoo / 410, Gisan-ro, Baekseok-eup, Yangju-si / 031-871-9271
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Chosun Gomtang: Gomtang / 46, Deokjeong 14-Gil, Yangju-Si / 031-857-1445
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Yemogol: Steak / 442, Gamagol-ro, Jangheung-myeon, Yangju-si / 031-855-1891
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Unterkunft
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Buckingham Hotel: 462-1, Gisan-ro, Baekseok-eup, Yangju-si / 031-871-9441
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Pine Hill Motel: 305-33, Gwonryul-ro 309beon-gil, Jangheung-myeon, Yangju-si / 031-829-0711
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Palast: 492 Kwon Yul-ro, Jangheung-myeon, Yangju-si / 031-855-2900
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ Die oben genannten Informationen wurden im Juni 2015 erstellt. Sie können sich später ändern. Bitte überprüfen Sie dies, bevor Sie reisen.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Informationen wie Text, Fotos und Videos, die in diesem Artikel verwendet werden, sind von der Korea Tourism Organization urheberrechtlich geschützt. Daher ist die unbefugte Verwendung des Artikels verboten.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>韩国京畿道良州 - 跟随杨裕艺术馆的权裕一起提高艺术感</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/enhance-art-sense-by-following-with-kwon-yul-yangju-art-museum-17-zh-cn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 00:30:02 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/enhance-art-sense-by-following-with-kwon-yul-yangju-art-museum-17-zh-cn/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-title=&#34;enhance-art-sense-by-following-with-kwon-yul-yangju-art-museum--17&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;姜永民的爱情装在长兴艺术公园一开始 - 韩国京畿道良州 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/d4c2c642-415c-495f-a8ad-f4af17caa572.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    姜永民的爱情装在长兴艺术公园一开始
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   跟随杨裕艺术馆的权裕一起提高艺术感
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    韩国京畿道良州
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   在云母热潮期间，杨州一岭游乐园，长兴游乐园和松竹游乐园被命名为4050户的首都地区驾车路线。 山谷周围有带足球场的餐厅，因此这里是家庭郊游的好地方。 现在一切都在逐渐消退，但是随着长兴游乐园进入著名的美术馆之多，这使周末的旅行变得很有趣。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   结合美术馆，文化古迹和天文台的郊游课程
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   连接高阳市德阳区和上井市寿城洞的39号公路被称为平路。 这条路通向长兴警察局，并遇到一个叫做权裕路的叉子。 以权尤将军命名的权玉路在长兴艺术公园，长兴雕塑公园，杨州市张玉珍美术馆（以下简称张玉珍美术馆），马头山口，安相哲艺术的交汇处结束 博物馆和岐山水库，以及杨州文化艺术中心的交叉路口。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;张玉珍博物馆前 - 韩国京畿道良州 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/2da5ba62-07c8-410b-8e9d-f6158f95d22f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     张玉珍博物馆前
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   权裕将军就位于张玉珍艺术博物馆入口附近。 权裕将军是在临津战争期间拯救该国的大师之一。 导致胜利的洗碗巾被认为是三大营，以及珍珠作战和汉山岛作战。 通过权裕路时，他的头向一般的精神和国民的民族思想低下。 因此，去杨州美术馆的旅行是具有文化遗产的旅行。 如果您包括Songam航天中心，那么它是结合天文研究的不错的学习郊游课程。 通过参观博物馆唤醒艺术感，在父母与孩子之间建立同情心，并丰富故事。 因此，前往权贵路的三个美术馆并非易事。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Songam航天中心的圆顶剧院 - 韩国京畿道良州 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/c539c1f7-f645-4878-9ee0-69a49fbb88f9.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Songam航天中心的圆顶剧院
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   长兴艺术公园
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   吉桑水库是从古巴巴尔出发的最终目的地，而长兴艺术公园则是在权裕路见到的第一个艺术空间。 自成立以来多次重命名，因此它一直处于弯曲状态。 美术馆成立于1984年，但由于管理上的问题，于2005年改名为长兴美术馆。 2006年下半年，日本设计师兼建筑师内田茂（Shigeru Uchida）设计了艺术公园，而结构设计师范茂（Van Shigeru）设计了该场地。 当年5月，展览厅，工作室，表演厅，美术馆，雕塑公园和儿童体验中心竣工。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;布尔德尔的雕塑&amp;lt;水果&amp;gt; - 韩国京畿道良州 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/57f0c167-ea11-4e39-ae48-799f2c41f51e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     布尔德尔的雕塑&amp;lt;水果&amp;gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   长兴美术馆不是专门从事绘画的美术馆。 这是一个游乐场友好型艺术空间，它触及作品并展示儿童可以骑乘的作品。 这个花园的名字叫布尔德尔花园。 雕塑家布尔德尔的雕塑作品，例如《水果》，《蹲下的神圣女人》和《罗马母子》，表达了母子的爱，欢迎来自草坪的游客。 法国雕塑家布尔德尔（Bourdel）与罗丹（Rodin）和马约尔（Mayol）一样，是三大现代雕塑大师之一。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;布尔德尔的雕塑&amp;lt;有祭品的圣母&amp;gt; - 韩国京畿道良州 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/d50a5ceb-4e06-4053-86f3-8deddfc3cf73.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     布尔德尔的雕塑&amp;lt;有祭品的圣母&amp;gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   毕加索儿童艺术博物馆
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   毕加索儿童艺术博物馆是成人必看的景点。 尽管它是复制品，但您可以在这里看到毕加索灵魂（1881〜1973）的作品和热情的生活。 特别是摄影师安德烈·维勒（Andre Viller，1930〜）拍摄的毕加索照片令人难以置信，因此更具启发性。 两人于1953年首次见面。从那时起，比勒拍摄了许多场景，包括毕加索对他的作品和思想的关注。 毕加索对黑白摄影的热情以及对艺术生活的渴望都变得生动起来。
   &lt;br/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;马克·奎因的雕塑&amp;lt;神话&amp;gt; - 韩国京畿道良州 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/93e1a559-87ed-4179-a5cc-68a08caad74a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     马克·奎因的雕塑&amp;lt;神话&amp;gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   毕加索的11张肖像和全家福也引起了人们的注意。 此外，您还可以欣赏毕加索的陶器，版画，素描和银盘。 在离开博物馆前回首，爸爸脱下帽子，爬上一条短裤的梯子，以一条直线描绘了裸体女人的身体。 观众的胸口清爽。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;毕加索在工作室里工作 - 韩国京畿道良州 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/b2ec457f-f052-420f-8d79-8c89de26bc19.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     毕加索在工作室里工作
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   此外，柳仁的《时代快车》，金泽基的《和平之梦》，马克·奎因的《神话》和姜英敏的《爱》是长兴美术馆的代表雕塑。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;艺术家Ryu的雕塑在&amp;lt;特快列车-时代&amp;gt; - 韩国京畿道良州 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/44494ccb-4d14-4168-a6a0-21e59b9d0b75.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     艺术家Ryu的雕塑在&amp;lt;特快列车-时代&amp;gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   张玉珍美术馆
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   从长兴艺术公园到权裕综合公墓仅几步之遥，这里展示了杨州美术馆。 该博物馆是根据张玉珍的老虎画而设计的，于2014年4月开放，并于当年获得金水根建筑奖。 拥有大量真正的艺术家是我们的骄傲。 张玉珍艺术文化基金会捐赠了230多幅壁画，油画，版画，水墨画等，按主题和时期进行展示。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;杨州美术馆 - 韩国京畿道良州 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/b3eac18e-fc32-4ffc-95e5-111a9fcc141a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     杨州美术馆
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   画家张玉珍（1917年至1990年）是西方绘画大师，与朴秀根和李重硕一起代表韩国现代艺术。 他的美术馆进入扬州的故事是出生在忠清南道（现在的世宗特别自治市）荣郡的，这要归功于他在曾经是扬州县土地的德索的工作室。 从那以后，他继续在首尔明洞洞，忠州水bo和龙仁辛加（Yongin Singal）的工作室从事创作活动。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;张玉珍美术馆的&amp;lt;动物家庭&amp;gt;参观者 - 韩国京畿道良州 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/be1507be-1d67-4488-a964-68bcf9c010ef.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     张玉珍美术馆的&amp;lt;动物家庭&amp;gt;参观者
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   水泥墙上画的&amp;lt;动物家族&amp;gt;和&amp;lt;餐桌&amp;gt;
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   从二楼开始入场是件好事。 这样，您可以首先遇到主人的工作，并在一楼的视频室中再次反思他的生活。 二楼的&amp;lt;动物大家庭&amp;gt;是深受游客喜爱的作品。 创作于1964年，侧面的作品描述通过黑白摄影讲述了古老的故事。 在京畿道德索工作室的墙上画有动物家族。 在像家庭一样和谐地画牛，鸡，猪和狗的艺术品中，可以感受到画家的温暖目光。 特别是，在壁画上挂着真正的牛仔和warangs，以唤起当地的情感。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;5&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;张玉珍美术馆 - 韩国京畿道良州 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/f80bf391-f32c-46ff-9f7f-e93a3e8d2feb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     张玉珍美术馆
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   剥落粉刷墙壁的工作在连接地下室和第一层的楼梯中间。 标题是&amp;lt;Table&amp;gt;。 让我们看一下对作品的描述。 “这些画作展现了一位艺术家的现代生活，在屏幕上是叉子和刀子，汤匙和饭碗，咖啡杯，水杯，比目鱼和骨头。 画家完成这幅画后，他成了。 今天，让我们用这顿饭代替一顿饭。 &#39;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;5&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;张玉珍美术馆一楼咖啡厅前休息的母女 - 韩国京畿道良州 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/8e708bf4-0235-438a-90b3-0b5fd365c6d8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     张玉珍美术馆一楼咖啡厅前休息的母女
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   使用灰色水泥墙作为画布的想法，以及画布的简洁和温暖。 参观者在每件作品中都发现了对人和事物的热爱，发展了想象力，并发现自己更加慷慨。 参观博物馆的美丽在于此。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;5&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;张玉珍美术馆前的长兴雕塑公园 - 韩国京畿道良州 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/c1b3ec97-4d50-4813-b74c-7e10ad4ac1a6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     张玉珍美术馆前的长兴雕塑公园
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   安相哲艺术博物馆将齐山水库带到花园
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   跟随杨州权权一郎参观博物馆的行程结束于位于Gisan水库旁边的An Sang-cheol艺术博物馆。 安尚哲（1927-1993）是一位画家，在东方绘画领域留下了许多著名的作品。 他曾是Seorabol艺术学院和Sungshin女子大学的教授。 1959年获得教育部长，副总统奖和总统奖后，安相哲成为了国家战争之星。他与首尔国立大学当代学生，Na Hye-seok的侄子Na Hee-kyun结婚。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;6&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Ansangcheol艺术博物馆的Kisan水库 - 韩国京畿道良州 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/674eb3d2-6e04-4f5c-8c90-895a8de77c6e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Ansangcheol艺术博物馆的Kisan水库
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   在博物馆的入口，您可以跟随安的生活，进入展览空间观看他的作品。 这是一系列名为&amp;lt;（灵）&amp;gt;的作品，为老树上色。 他以“精神是一个存在的遗体，即使它死了也被别人传承”的思想创作了这部作品。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;6&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;草坪的阿尚哲艺术博物馆 - 韩国京畿道良州 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/2fe5a84b-a13c-4224-bdfa-878947a3123e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     草坪的阿尚哲艺术博物馆
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   观众排在她作品的前面。 尽管他是个老头，参加过12个个展，但他仍积极从事创意活动。 铜线是草坪，通往基桑水库。 博物馆的建筑是安相哲的儿子，翁高堂建筑事务所的所有者安宇成的作品。 在一个花园后面有一个带玻璃窗的工作室。 画家Na Hee-kyun在这里有时停止绘画。 安相哲艺术博物馆将开放至7月15日。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;6&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;15&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;艺术家李熙yun的作品&amp;lt;我的米丽娜2&amp;gt; - 韩国京畿道良州 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/1a41d284-06fa-41a3-be91-deb0fb836c19.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     艺术家李熙yun的作品&amp;lt;我的米丽娜2&amp;gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   旅游信息
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      长兴艺术公园
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     地址：京畿道良州市长兴面权裕路117
     &lt;br/&gt;
     联络号码：031-877-0500
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.artpark.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.artpark.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      杨州美术馆
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     地址：京畿道良州市长兴面权裕路211
     &lt;br/&gt;
     联络号码：031-8082-4245
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://changucchin.yangju.go.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://changucchin.yangju.go.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      安相哲艺术博物馆
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     地址：京畿道梁州市白石邑权裕路905
     &lt;br/&gt;
     联系电话：031-874-0734
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.ahnsangchul.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.ahnsangchul.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1.附近的餐馆
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    关联餐厅：杨州市白石邑岐山路韩宇/ 410 / 031-871-9271
    &lt;br/&gt;
    朝鲜贡塘：贡塘/杨州市德寿14街46号/ 031-857-1445
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Yemogol：牛排/杨州市长兴面Gamagol-ro 442 / 031-855-1891
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2.住宿
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    白金汉饭店：杨州市白石邑岐山路462-1 / 031-871-9441
    &lt;br/&gt;
    松山汽车旅馆：杨州市长兴面广龙路309号街305-33号/ 031-829-0711
    &lt;br/&gt;
    宫殿：杨州市长兴面权裕路492号/ 031-855-2900
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※以上信息为2015年6月的信息。之后可能会发生变化，因此请在旅行前确认。
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※本文中使用的文字，照片和视频等信息均受韩国旅游组织版权保护，因此禁止未经授权使用本文。
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea - Enhance Art Sense by Following with Kwon Yul, Yangju Art Museum</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/enhance-art-sense-by-following-with-kwon-yul-yangju-art-museum-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 23:08:26 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/enhance-art-sense-by-following-with-kwon-yul-yangju-art-museum-17/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-title=&#34;enhance-art-sense-by-following-with-kwon-yul-yangju-art-museum--17&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Love by Kang Young-min installed at the beginning of Jangheung Art Park - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/d4c2c642-415c-495f-a8ad-f4af17caa572.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Love by Kang Young-min installed at the beginning of Jangheung Art Park
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Enhance Art Sense by Following with Kwon Yul, Yangju Art Museum
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   During the boom of mica, Yangju Ilyoung Amusement Park, Jangheung Amusement Park, and Songchu Amusement Park were named to the 4050 households as the Capital Region Drive Course. There are restaurants around the valley with football courts, so it was a good place for family outings. Now all are fading, but as much as Jangheung Amusement Park enters the famous art galleries, which makes the weekend drive fun.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Outing course in conjunction with art museums, cultural monuments and observatory
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Route 39, which connects Deoyang-gu, Goyang-si, and Suseong-dong, Uijeongbu-si, is called Pyeong-ro-ro. This road leads to Jangheung police box and meets a fork called Kwon Yul-ro. Kwon Yul-ro, named after General Kwon-yul, ends at the intersection of Jangheung Art Park, Jangheung Sculpture Park, Yangju City Jang Ukjin Art Museum (hereinafter referred to as Jang Ukjin Art Museum), Horsehead Pass, Ahn Sang-cheol Art Museum and Kisan Reservoir, and at the intersection of Yangju Culture and Arts Center.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;In front of Jang Ukjin Museum - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/2da5ba62-07c8-410b-8e9d-f6158f95d22f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     In front of Jang Ukjin Museum
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Kwon Yul General is located just past the entrance of Jang Ukjin Museum of Art. General Kwon Yul is one of the masters who saved the country during the Imjin War. The dish towel that led to victory is considered to be the Three Great Battalion, along with the Pearl Battling and the Hansan Island Battling. While passing through Kwon Yul-ro, his head is bowed to the general spirit and national ideology of the general. As such, the trip to the Yangju Museum of Art is a trip with cultural heritage. If you include the Songam Space Center, it is a good study outing course that combines astronomical studies. Awaken the sense of art through art museum visits, creating a sense of empathy between parents and children, and enriching stories. So going out to three art galleries in Kwon Yul-ro is not a simple drive.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Dome Theater at Songam Space Center - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/c539c1f7-f645-4878-9ee0-69a49fbb88f9.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Dome Theater at Songam Space Center
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Jangheung Art Park
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Departing from Gupabal, Gisan Reservoir is the final destination and Jangheung Art Park is the first art space to meet at Kwon Yul-ro. It has been bent since it was renamed several times since its establishment. Total Art Museum was first established in 1984, but in 2005, it changed to Jangheung Art Park due to management problems. Later in 2006, Japanese designer and architect Shigeru Uchida designed Art Park and structural designer Van Shigeru designed the venue. In May of that year, an exhibition hall, atelier, performance hall, art gallery, sculpture park, and children&#39;s experience center were completed.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Bourdel&#39;s Sculpture &amp;lt;Fruit&amp;gt; - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/57f0c167-ea11-4e39-ae48-799f2c41f51e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Bourdel&#39;s Sculpture &amp;lt;Fruit&amp;gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Jangheung Art Park is not an art museum dedicated to painting with a certain distance. It is a playground-friendly art space that touches works and displays works that children can ride on. The name of this garden is Bourdel Garden. Sculptures by the sculptor Bourdel, such as Fruits, a Crouching Sacred Woman and Roman Mother and Child, expressing the love of mother and child, welcome visitors from all over the lawn. French sculptor Bourdel is one of the three greatest masters of modern sculpture, along with Rodin and Mayol.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Bourdel&#39;s Sculpture &amp;lt;Our Lady with Offerings&amp;gt; - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/d50a5ceb-4e06-4053-86f3-8deddfc3cf73.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Bourdel&#39;s Sculpture &amp;lt;Our Lady with Offerings&amp;gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Picasso Children&#39;s Art Museum
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The Picasso Children&#39;s Art Museum is a must-see for adults. Although it is a replica, you can see the works and passionate lives of Picasso&#39;s soul (1881 ~ 1973) here. In particular, Picasso&#39;s photographs taken by photographer Andre Viller (1930 ~) are incredible, so they are more inspiring. The two first met in 1953. Since then, Biller has photographed many scenes, including Picasso&#39;s focus on his work and his thoughts. Picasso&#39;s passion in black and white photography and his desire for artistic life come alive.
   &lt;br/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Mark Quinn&#39;s Sculpture &amp;lt;Myth&amp;gt; - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/93e1a559-87ed-4179-a5cc-68a08caad74a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Mark Quinn&#39;s Sculpture &amp;lt;Myth&amp;gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Picasso&#39;s 11 portraits and family photos also catch the eye. In addition, you can appreciate Picasso&#39;s pottery, prints, drawings, and silver plates. Looking back before leaving the museum, Dad takes off his hat and climbs up a ladder in shorts to depict the naked woman&#39;s body in a straight line. The viewer&#39;s chest is refreshing.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Picasso working in the studio - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/b2ec457f-f052-420f-8d79-8c89de26bc19.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Picasso working in the studio
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In addition, Ryu In&#39;s Express Train-The Era of Times, Kim Taek Ki&#39;s Dream of Peace, Mark Quinn&#39;s Myth, and Kang Young Min&#39;s Love are the representative sculptures of Jangheung Art Park.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sculpture by Artist Ryu In &amp;lt;Express Train-The Era of Times&amp;gt; - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/44494ccb-4d14-4168-a6a0-21e59b9d0b75.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sculpture by Artist Ryu In &amp;lt;Express Train-The Era of Times&amp;gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Jang Ukjin Museum of Art
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Just a little up from Jangheung Art Park towards Kwon Yul General Cemetery, Yangju Museum of Art is displayed. The museum was designed after Jang Uk-jin&#39;s tiger painting and was opened in April 2014 and won the Kim Soo-geun Architecture Award that year. It is a great pride to have a large collection of genuine artists. More than 230 pieces of murals, oil paintings, prints, ink paintings, etc. are donated by the Jang Uk-Jin Art and Culture Foundation to display them by theme and period.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Yangju Museum of Art - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/b3eac18e-fc32-4ffc-95e5-111a9fcc141a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Yangju Museum of Art
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Painter Jang Uk-jin (1917 ~ 1990) is a master of Western painting that represents Korean modern art along with Park Soo-geun and Lee Joong-seop. Born in Yeong-gun, Chungcheongnam-do (now Sejong Special Self-Governing City), the story of his art museum entering Yangju was due to his studio in Deokso, once a land of Yangju County. Since then, he has continued his creative activities in the studios of Seoul Myeongryon-dong, Chungju Suanbo and Yongin Singal.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Visitors to &amp;lt;Animal Family&amp;gt; at Jang Ukjin Museum of Art - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/be1507be-1d67-4488-a964-68bcf9c010ef.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Visitors to &amp;lt;Animal Family&amp;gt; at Jang Ukjin Museum of Art
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   &amp;lt;Animal Family&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;Dining Table&amp;gt; painted on cement wall
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Admission is good to start from the second floor. In this way, you can meet the master&#39;s work first and reflect on his life once again in the first floor video room. &amp;lt;Animal Family&amp;gt; on the second floor is a work that is loved by visitors. Created in 1964, the work description attached to the side tells the old story with black and white photography. Animal Family was painted on the wall of the studio in Deokso, Gyeonggi-do. The warm gaze of the painter can be felt in the artwork where cows, chickens, pigs and dogs are harmoniously drawn like a family. In particular, the real cowcoats and warangs are hung on the murals to evoke local sentiments.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;5&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Jang Ukjin Museum of Art - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/f80bf391-f32c-46ff-9f7f-e93a3e8d2feb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Jang Ukjin Museum of Art
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The work that peeled off the painted wall is in the middle of the stairs connecting the basement and the first floor. The title is &amp;lt;Table&amp;gt;. Let&#39;s look at the description of the work. “The paintings show the modern life of an artist, and on the screen are forks and knives, spoons and rice bowls, coffee cups, water glasses, flounder and bones. After the painter completed this picture, &#39;he became. Today, let&#39;s replace one meal with this meal. &#39;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;5&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Mother and daughter resting in front of the cafe on the 1st floor of Jang Ukjin Museum of Art - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/8e708bf4-0235-438a-90b3-0b5fd365c6d8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Mother and daughter resting in front of the cafe on the 1st floor of Jang Ukjin Museum of Art
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The idea of using the gray cement wall as a canvas, and the simplicity and warmth of the canvas. Visitors find love for people and objects in each of their works, develop their imagination, and find themselves more generous. The beauty of a trip to a museum is this.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;5&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Jangheung Sculpture Park in front of Jang Ukjin Museum of Art - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/c1b3ec97-4d50-4813-b74c-7e10ad4ac1a6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Jangheung Sculpture Park in front of Jang Ukjin Museum of Art
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Ahn Sang-cheol Museum of Art Brings Kisan Reservoir to the Garden
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The trip to the museum following Kwon Yul-ro of Yangju-si ends at the An Sang-cheol Museum of Art, located next to Gisan Reservoir. Ahn Sang-cheol (1927-1993) is a painter who left many famous works in the field of oriental painting. He was a professor at Seorabol Art College and Sungshin Women&#39;s University. Ahn Sang-cheol, who became a national war star after winning the Minister of Education, Vice President&#39;s Award, and President&#39;s Award in 1959, married Na Hee-kyun, a contemporary student of Seoul National University and nephew of Na Hye-seok.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;6&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Kisan Reservoir from Ansangcheol Museum of Art - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/674eb3d2-6e04-4f5c-8c90-895a8de77c6e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Kisan Reservoir from Ansangcheol Museum of Art
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   At the entrance of the museum, you can follow Ahn&#39;s life and enter the exhibition space to see his works. It is a series of work titled &amp;lt;(靈)&amp;gt;, which has colored the old tree. He created this work with the thought that &#39;the spirit is a body that remains and is passed on by someone even when it dies.&#39;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;6&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Ahnsangcheol Museum of Art from the Lawn - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/2fe5a84b-a13c-4224-bdfa-878947a3123e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Ahnsangcheol Museum of Art from the Lawn
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The line of spectators continues in front of her works. Although he is an old man with 12 solo exhibitions, he is still actively engaged in creative activities. The copper line is a lawn, which leads to the Kisan Reservoir. The building of the museum is the work of Ahn Woo-sung, the son of Ahn Sang-cheol and the owner of Ongodang Architects. There is a studio with a glass window behind one flower garden. This is where Na Hee-kyun, a painter, sometimes stops to paint. The Ahn Sang-cheol Museum of Art will open until July 15.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;6&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;15&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Artist Lee Hee-kyun&#39;s work &amp;lt;My Mirina 2&amp;gt; - Yangju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/17/1a41d284-06fa-41a3-be91-deb0fb836c19.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Artist Lee Hee-kyun&#39;s work &amp;lt;My Mirina 2&amp;gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel info
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Jangheung Art Park
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Address: 117, Kwon Yul-ro, Jangheung-myeon, Yangju-si, Gyeonggi-do
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Contact: 031-877-0500
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.artpark.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.artpark.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Yangju Museum of Art
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Address: 211 Kwon Yul-ro, Jangheung-myeon, Yangju-si, Gyeonggi-do
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Contact: 031-8082-4245
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://changucchin.yangju.go.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://changucchin.yangju.go.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Ahn Sang Chul Museum of Art
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Address: 905 Kwon Yul-ro, Baekseok-eup, Yangju-si, Gyeonggi-do
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Contact: 031-874-0734
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.ahnsangchul.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.ahnsangchul.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Nearby restaurants
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Affiliated Restaurant: Hanwoo / 410, Gisan-ro, Baekseok-eup, Yangju-si / 031-871-9271
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Chosun Gomtang: Gomtang / 46, Deokjeong 14-gil, Yangju-si / 031-857-1445
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Yemogol: Steak / 442, Gamagol-ro, Jangheung-myeon, Yangju-si / 031-855-1891
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Accommodation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Buckingham Hotel: 462-1, Gisan-ro, Baekseok-eup, Yangju-si / 031-871-9441
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Pine Hill Motel: 305-33, Gwonryul-ro 309beon-gil, Jangheung-myeon, Yangju-si / 031-829-0711
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Palace: 492 Kwon Yul-ro, Jangheung-myeon, Yangju-si / 031-855-2900
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was made in June 2015. It may change afterwards, so please check before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Information such as text, photos, and videos used in this article is copyrighted by Korea Tourism Organization, so unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>