<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pohang on Every Corner of Korea</title>
    <link>https://codecorea.github.io/tags/pohang/</link>
    <description>Every Corner of Korea (Pohang)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 16:04:25 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="https://codecorea.github.io/tags/pohang/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Pohang Drive 100km along the coast - Pohang, Gyeongbuk, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/pohang-drive-100km-along-the-coast-157/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 16:04:25 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/pohang-drive-100km-along-the-coast-157/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Pohang, Gyeongbuk, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;pohang-drive-100km-along-the-coast--157&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Pohang Beach can be found anywhere on the coast of Pohang - Pohang, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/157/031e06ce-9137-4f38-8b01-7d8729d28d79.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Pohang Beach can be found anywhere on the coast of Pohang
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Pohang Drive 100km along the coast
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Pohang, Gyeongbuk, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The coastal road of Pohang stretches 100km from Yangpo Port down there to Hwajin Beach above it, centering on the protruding Homigot. As you run along the road, famous beaches and sunrise spots, as well as unknown beaches and harbors, each with its own colorful seas awaiting the tired travelers.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Near sea, far sea, exotic sea
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The city facing the sea is attractive in many ways. The sea wearing colorful clothes presents a time of comfort and healing. That&#39;s why it&#39;s also the reason to seek the sea when your heart is stuffy. Pohang, which we know very well, is a city that embraces Yeongildae Beach, which overlooks the sunrise spot, Homigot, Guryongpo, famous for Guamegi, and Posco. However, besides this, Pohang presents a mysterious landscape with hidden gem-like beaches and harbors all over the long coast.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;On the coast of Pohang, there are alternating ports and beaches. - Pohang, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/157/eda04d65-08fb-4614-86f4-f240f2d1442d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     On the coast of Pohang, there are alternating ports and beaches.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The beaches of Pohang, which seem to have been seen somewhere and seemed unfamiliar, stimulate travelers&#39; sensibility and touch the hearts of those who are tired of everyday life. It is narrower and winding than a new road that is wide and straight, but it is fun to run on the old road where the forest and the sea take off.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Yangpo Port with beautiful sea - Pohang, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/157/bf448741-8bde-4f2f-b7fa-8de99caafa27.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Yangpo Port with beautiful sea
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The coastline of Pohang is longer than expected. The coastal road adjacent to the sea runs along the East Sea, sometimes spontaneously and sometimes pleasantly. When driving along the coastal road of Pohang, which is 100km long, you will encounter various Pohang depending on the topography of the coast, the shape of the village, and the weather. Coastal roads with beaches and harbors are cool in their own way. At the center of the Pohang coastal road, there is the Yeongildae Beach, which borders the city. Based on this, the coastal road can be divided into two.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;After driving, you can stop anywhere and enjoy swimming. - Pohang, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/157/9d9aa5a6-3c4e-4f97-a719-09a86ea267cb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     After driving, you can stop anywhere and enjoy swimming.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Starting from Yangpo Port, the lowest part of Pohang&#39;s coast, and passing through Janggil-ri, Guryongpo, and Homigot, you can taste the charming harbor and beaches, and run along the winding road. This is a road where you can enjoy the romance of the old road by following National Road 31 and Local Road 929. A small harbor and beach alternately appear right next to the road where the car passes. You can enjoy the peaceful and peaceful mood passing through the small towns by the sea. You can even drive your car, stop where you want, and have your own time.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Local road 929, passing Homigot and into the city - Pohang, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/157/1053df71-f34b-4f93-9ca2-615f80a46bc1.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Local road 929, passing Homigot and into the city
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   As you pass through the charming harbors and beaches, you will encounter a unique marine park. There is a complex fishing park in Janggi-ri, which is located far from Guryongpo Port. As a marine park for anglers, there are floating fishing grounds and marine pensions. There is also a 170m long bridge and a marine observatory that leads to the small stone island of the island, which is a lot of fish. If you walk to the end of the bridge, you will feel as if you are standing on a pavilion on the sea. Those who spend a leisurely time sitting on a mat and having a picnic are also noticeable. The sea, people and facilities are harmoniously harmonized.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Janggil-ri Fishing Village Complex Park with Marine Park - Pohang, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/157/0a5eff6d-071c-4307-aef9-3c221d3bb8ae.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Janggil-ri Fishing Village Complex Park with Marine Park
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   On the other hand, the coastal road at the top of Yeongildae Beach is different from that of the coastal road, providing the pleasure of a coastal drive. The coastal road above Yeongildae Beach, which runs on prefectural road 20, has a cooler taste. Unlike the lower coastal road that runs along the town and harbor, it stretches relatively straight up and down hills.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;13&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Marine Pension located in Jangili Fishing Village Park - Pohang, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/157/21b0fd2f-a92c-45c9-9ced-2a32f546b6bc.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Marine Pension located in Jangili Fishing Village Park
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The upper coastal road past Yeongil Bay Port and the main beaches such as Chilpo, Wolpo, and Hwajin is refreshing and cool. As the coastline is long, the spectrum of fun is wide.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;15&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Pohang&#39;s Romantic Coastal Drive - Pohang, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/157/965ba9f9-a974-4a2f-916c-b9caac4a2a2a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Pohang&#39;s Romantic Coastal Drive
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Among famous beaches, there are hidden spots such as Igari Beach and Odori Beach. There are fewer people than the big beach, but the landscape is not far behind. It is also enough to quietly enjoy swimming or fishing without being hit by people.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;17&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Beach near Igari Port - Pohang, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/157/4335ba6f-69ed-4b55-b578-95e04e21749a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Beach near Igari Port
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Enjoy a variety of beaches to your liking
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Pohang&#39;s beaches can be divided into three categories. One is a beach that has more views of the season than water, adjacent to the city, and the other is a secluded beach with an inaccurate name sandwiched between famous beaches and ports. Lastly, it is a beach mostly visited by people who enjoy summer bathing in the summer with Songlim and a large white sandy beach.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Pohang&#39;s most popular beaches, most visited by tourists from other regions, are also bathing beaches with pine trees and white sand. Chilpo Beach, Wolpo Beach, and Hwajin Beach are representative of Yeongil Bay Port. These three beaches are packed with various amenities and accommodations for the guests in a beach with a large white sandy beach. You can also relax by renting tubes, flats, parasols, or enjoy marine leisure activities such as peanut boats, banana boats, and jet skis.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Chilpo Beach with white sandy beach - Pohang, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/157/64abafbf-487b-4dd1-bdb4-4a1f3156afb2.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Chilpo Beach with white sandy beach
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Chilpo Beach, 2km long and 70m wide, is not only close to downtown Pohang, but is also popular with families as it has bungalows and large condominium accommodation. At the Chilpo Beach, a jazz festival is held every summer on the sandy beach.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Wolpo Beach where you can enjoy various marine leisure sports - Pohang, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/157/5bcc4f1c-34bf-47fd-9f3e-36f19ff9c5ff.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Wolpo Beach where you can enjoy various marine leisure sports
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Wolpo Beach, located on top of it, is a great place to enjoy various marine leisure sports. That is why a lot of young summer seekers visit. Unlike Chilpo Beach, an independent beach, the village is naturally formed near Wolpo Beach, so there are many convenient facilities such as restaurants and shops.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Hwajin Beach is a great place to enjoy camping in a pine forest. - Pohang, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/157/cdde8f98-f946-4f1b-abb5-d16211462c8a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Hwajin Beach is a great place to enjoy camping in a pine forest.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Meanwhile, people who want to enjoy the forest with the sea go to Hwajin Beach. It&#39;s a great place to enjoy camping and picnicking in tents and camping in the pine forest.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Odo Beach, suitable for quiet water fun - Pohang, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/157/3c174fda-b5f0-43ad-9e45-b72341d680ba.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Odo Beach, suitable for quiet water fun
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Pohang&#39;s unmissable taste, Mori noodles and sashimi
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   No matter how beautiful the beach drive is, if the stomach is empty, it is a trip that is not enough. If you come to Pohang, you need to eat a bowl of water, and it is worth trying to find Mori noodles that are only in Pohang. Both are perfect for seasons where there is no appetite.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   First, the water sashimi is a menu that goes anywhere in Pohang, but the way to eat and eat the water sashimi varies from house to house. At Jukdo Market, there is a unique sea cucumber water sashimi of &#39;Harmaesilbi Sashimi House&#39;, which rolls sea cucumber into soy sauce. In Wolpo, there is an old sashimi restaurant called &#39;Baekbun Sashimi House,&#39; which is said to be followed by Pohang people. The taste of water sashimi depends on the type of fish, freshness, seasoning, etc. The 100 times sashimi is made with seasoned red pepper paste.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;It&#39;s a regretful thing to take out of the Pohang trip - Pohang, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/157/7b968ce7-ba04-4e47-9bcf-3c82aefa74fd.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     It&#39;s a regretful thing to take out of the Pohang trip
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The Mori noodles at &#39;Chowon Restaurant&#39; in Guryongpo are also special. Mori noodles have a similar taste to fish soup noodles, and boil the fish like fish soup to dry the kalguksu. The sharp taste makes the heat away from heat. After eating a bowl, the mouth feels pleasant and the body feels healthy.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   The way to enjoy summer in Pohang is simple. You don&#39;t have to worry much about where to go or what to do. After driving along the long coastline, you can go down to your favorite place and enjoy swimming or fishing. Alternatively, you can take a nap by challenging the marine reporters you have longed for, or taking a book as a pillow. There are many choices in Pohang, a beach that you can choose according to your preference.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Guryongpo&#39;s specialty, Mori noodles - Pohang, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/157/74691ea0-c1b3-49b9-857a-bfc054a286b2.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Guryongpo&#39;s specialty, Mori noodles
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Related website address
     &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    -Pohang City Cultural Tourism, Inquiries: 054-270-8282 (Pohang City Representative Number)
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Restaurants near
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Hallmaesilbi Sashimi: Sea cucumber water / 36-15 Jukdo Market 1-gil, Buk-gu, Pohang-si / 054-242-0585
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Steppe Restaurant: Mori noodles / 102-1, Guryongpo-gil, Guryongpo-eup, Nam-gu, Pohang-si / 054-276-5579
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Rooms
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Galaxy Tourist Hotel: 93 Haean-ro, Buk-gu, Pohang-si / 054-251-9988
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.galaxyhotel.kr/ko/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.galaxyhotel.kr/ko/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Benikea Hotel Pohang: 128, Jungang-ro, Nam-gu, Pohang-si / 054-282-2700
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Homigot Pension: 78, Guman-gil, Homigot-myeon, Nam-gu, Pohang-si / 054-284-0226
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.homigotpension.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.homigotpension.com/
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was updated in July 2019, and may be changed later, so please check before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comfort and hope to all with the new light! The 21st Pohang Homigot Korean National Sunrise Festival - Pohang, Gyeongbuk, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/comfort-and-hope-to-all-with-the-new-light-the-21st-pohang-homigot-korean-national-sunrise-festival-93/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 13:39:24 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/comfort-and-hope-to-all-with-the-new-light-the-21st-pohang-homigot-korean-national-sunrise-festival-93/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Pohang, Gyeongbuk, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;comfort-and-hope-to-all-with-the-new-light-the-21st-pohang-homigot-korean-national-sunrise-festival--93&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Majestic Homigot Sunrise - Pohang, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/93/11b6e95b-2841-4fbe-a6f0-304611f4c002.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Majestic Homigot Sunrise
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Comfort and hope to all with the new light! The 21st Pohang Homigot Korean National Sunrise Festival
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Pohang, Gyeongbuk, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   On the first day of the new year, the &#39;Homi Cape Korean People&#39;s Celebration&#39; is held at Pomi Homigot Square.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Homigot Sunrise, a new hope for all
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Homi Cape, located in Nam-gu, Pohang, is the tail of the Korean peninsula, the Korean peninsula. Speaking of tails often comes to mind negative meanings such as end and back. Like the crowned crown, it can be used to mean incompleteness such as failure or abandonment.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Homigot&#39;s morning dawn - Pohang, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/93/3e0ad471-13bf-4e1b-a2c9-56e894162ae0.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Homigot&#39;s morning dawn
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   But tails are very important to animals. Especially for predators of carnivores, the tail is directly linked to survival. When hunting, the tail turns and balances. The tiger runs with the power of the tail, and conducts the flock with the tail. This is why the tiger tail is regarded as a symbol of national fortune and national security. Homigot New Year&#39;s first sunrise, which will be comforting and hopeful for everyone, is more meaningful.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sculpture representing the Korean Peninsula in the form of a tiger - Pohang, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/93/a5c53c86-6b8d-4fef-b4fc-b7524fd57716.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sculpture representing the Korean Peninsula in the form of a tiger
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The sunrise spot of Pohang is by far the Homigot Sunrise Square. The New Millennium Memorial Hall, the Korea Tourism Luxury Museum, and the Yeon Orang Seon Statue were built around the square.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Win-Win Hand Golden Sun Rising Through Fingers - Pohang, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/93/65e06258-acb9-499f-a754-316aa6510410.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Win-Win Hand Golden Sun Rising Through Fingers
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The win-win hand, the symbol of the Homigot Sunrise Square, is the two hands on the sea and land facing the palms.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Foreign tourists enjoy watching sunrise at Cape Homi - Pohang, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/93/cc93db39-7c56-4df0-8740-5f5707758a0b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Foreign tourists enjoy watching sunrise at Cape Homi
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In front of the left hand on the ground is a torch and a thousand-year-old pupil. The embers in the eyes of the millennium are kept in the &#39;Eternal Embers&#39;, which combines the last 20th century embers cultivated on the Byeonsan Peninsula, the embers of the earth cultivated in Fiji South Pacific, the Zhuhai Sea embers cultivated in Dokdo, and the beginnings of the new millenniums cultivated at Homigot. It is.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Win-win hands and eyes of a thousand years - Pohang, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/93/446c5367-501c-444f-bc88-4b5475a21bb5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Win-win hands and eyes of a thousand years
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   On December 31, at the sunrise, Haeoreum Busking Festival, Changhyeon Street Karaoke &amp;lt;Homi Hen&amp;gt;, Madang Play &amp;lt;Homi Cape Hyo Woman Shim Cheong Jeon&amp;gt;, 퐝! 퐝! Various programs are held, including the fireworks festival and Daewol Hanmadang. Additional events such as Homie Freemarket and Homie Visible Radio are also held.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;13&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Yeon-ang Rang O - Pohang, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/93/ae319f03-b6c4-43aa-ad24-6c2cef7e3b9f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Yeon-ang Rang O
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The Sunrise Hope Radio, 70th Anniversary! There will be a painting of North Korea and a performance of &amp;lt;The Year of Visit to Pohang&amp;gt;. In addition, `` Feast of rice cake soup is a pig &#39;&#39; event, which is made with rice cake soup in the largest pot in Korea and shares the first meal of the new year, is also held. The 2019 Homigot New Year sunrise is 7:33.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;15&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Yeongildae Beach, a night view spot in Pohang - Pohang, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/93/193e7a89-71ca-4012-9c32-65ec41bd66fb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Yeongildae Beach, a night view spot in Pohang
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Many things to see and do around Cape Homi
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you have been deeply impressed by the sunrise of Homigot Sunrise Square, it is time to look around. The first place to visit is the National Lighthouse Museum. Located at Homigot Sunrise Square, the National Lighthouse Museum is Korea&#39;s only lighthouse museum. The National Lighthouse Museum provides a variety of information about the lighthouse, including the history of the lighthouse, including Korea, as well as the types and principles of the lighthouse.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Homigot Lighthouse, the tallest in Korea - Pohang, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/93/2028f2d0-0e53-46a5-968b-c2a9e2f02e14.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Homigot Lighthouse, the tallest in Korea
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   There are many interesting exhibits, such as a diorama, which reproduces the life of the lighthouse keeper called the lighthouse keeper, and the experience of making Morse code using a touch screen. It is also interesting to look at the history and history of Korea&#39;s lighthouse. Korea&#39;s first lighthouse is Palmido Lighthouse in Palmido, Incheon. The Homigot Lighthouse, which can be found at the National Lighthouse Museum, is the tallest lighthouse in Korea.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;National Lighthouse Museum is Korea&#39;s only lighthouse museum - Pohang, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/93/ad8605d5-0ce7-4608-894f-6bb7729e385d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     National Lighthouse Museum is Korea&#39;s only lighthouse museum
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Don&#39;t miss the Millennium Memorial Hall, which embodies the round sun. The Millennium Memorial Hall is an exhibition center where visitors can meet Pohang&#39;s geographic characteristics, history, and future vision with various panels and dioramas, and about 2,000 rare marine life fossils, including the world&#39;s first photosynthetic organism, stromatolite and fossil fossils. There is a museum and the Korea Seokpo Pohang Museum where 300 rare heads are gathered together.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Homigot Sunrise Square from the roof of the Millennium Memorial Hall - Pohang, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/93/4958f8dc-d8ed-4bf6-860d-9a0d21dd5bd5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Homigot Sunrise Square from the roof of the Millennium Memorial Hall
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Climb up to the rooftop observatory on the 3rd floor and you&#39;ll see Homigot Square and the blue East Sea.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Ammonite fossils displayed at the Marine Natural History Museum - Pohang, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/93/26c6dc2f-32cc-4fe1-b0d0-6e672019ce32.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Ammonite fossils displayed at the Marine Natural History Museum
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Pohang&#39;s best gourmet in winter
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Guryongpo, about 10 km from Cape Homi, is home to Guamegi. When talking about Pohang&#39;s winter, Guamegi does not fall with the sunrise. Guamegi originated from shrubs that were herringed through her eyes and is now in season. It&#39;s a bit weird to eat lettuce and seaweed, and it&#39;s a bit grotesque to eat with chopped guamegi and chopped green onions. The texture is chewy and chewy. If you are a liquor lover, you can have a cup of Pohang&#39;s representative makgeolli, “Young-ilman Friends,” made with Pohang rice and rice cakes. Darakbang, Guamegi Restaurant, located in Yanghakcheon-ro, Buk-gu, Pohang-si, is famous for aging over 10 months.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Guamegi is full of luster now. - Pohang, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/93/3283a7d6-e40a-4c34-aae1-3c45da16b3d8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Guamegi is full of luster now.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you enjoyed the taste of savory guamegi, it&#39;s time to learn about it. As Gumaegi&#39;s hometown, there is Guamegi Cultural Center in Guryongpo. The official name is &#39;Pohang Guryongpo Guamegi Cultural Center&#39;. Guamegi Cultural Center is located in the back of Kowloon Park, where Kowloon Pohang is located, and was opened in May 2016. The four-story cultural hall includes the Guamegi Research Center, a public relations hall, an ocean experience center, and an ocean hall.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Pohang Guryongpo Guamegi Cultural Center - Pohang, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/93/9b15dc76-cd81-4417-9192-c171adee542c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Pohang Guryongpo Guamegi Cultural Center
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The origin and efficacy of Guamegi are also reproduced, as well as the famous Guryongpo fishing village houses and the famous saury fishing boat built in 1945. Touch pool where you can touch fish such as willowfish and albino trout, and VR video experience space that virtually experiences the Arctic is popular with children.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Exhibition of drying Guamegi - Pohang, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/93/5625a15b-5529-4096-8b21-2c57bb888cde.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Exhibition of drying Guamegi
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel info
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     21st Homigot Korean National Celebration
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Address: Homigot Sunrise Square, Homigot-myeon, Nam-gu, Pohang-si, Gyeongbuk
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Date: December 31, 2018 (18:00) ~ January 1, 2019 (Sunrise 07: 33 ~)
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Inquiries: 054-289-7851 (Pohang Foundation for Festival Management)
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://phcf.or.kr/kr/main.do&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://phcf.or.kr/kr/main.do
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     National Lighthouse Museum
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Address: 20 Haetim-ro 150beon-gil, Homigot-myeon, Nam-gu, Pohang-si, Gyeongbuk
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Contact: 054-284-4857
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Opening hours: 09: 00 ~ 18: 00 (Closed every Monday, but open on January 1st)
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Admission Fee: Free
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.lighthouse-museum.or.kr/kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.lighthouse-museum.or.kr/kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Millennium Memorial Hall
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Address: 136 Haetgi-ro, Homigot-myeon, Nam-gu, Pohang-si, Gyeongbuk
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Contact: 054-284-5026
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Opening hours: 09: 00 ~ 18: 00 (Closed every Monday)
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Admission Fee: Adults 3,000 won, Teenagers 1000 won, Children 500 won
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Pohang Guryongpo Guamegi Cultural Center
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Address: 28-8, Guryongpo-gil 117beon-gil, Guryongpo-eup, Nam-gu, Pohang-si, Gyeongbuk
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Contact: 054-270-2861
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Opening hours: 09: 00 ~ 18: 00 (Closed on Mondays, January 1st, and Chuseok)
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Admission Fee: Free
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://gmg.pohang.go.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://gmg.pohang.go.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Restaurants near
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Darakbang Guamegi: Guamegi / 39, Yanghakcheon-ro, Jukdo-dong, Buk-gu, Pohang-si, Gyeongbuk / 054-283-1915
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Haikou Restaurant: Guamegi / 18, Jungangsangga 2-gil, Buk-gu, Pohang-si, Gyeongbuk / 054-247-5801
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Gayoung Lodge: Tongue Pork Barbecue / 223 Jamyeong-ro, Yeonil-eup, Nam-gu, Pohang-si, Gyeongbuk / 054-278-9477
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Rooms
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Apple Tree Hotel: 7-5, Jungheung-ro 100beon-gil, Nam-gu, Pohang-si, Gyeongbuk / 054-241-1234
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://appletreehotels.com/pohang&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://appletreehotels.com/pohang
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Eco Hotel: 430, Posco-daero, Nam-gu, Pohang, Gyeongbuk / 054-282-8787
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.ecobusinesshotel.co.kr&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.ecobusinesshotel.co.kr
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was updated in December 2018 and may change afterwards, so please check before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;/font&gt;
    &lt;span style=&#34;color: rgb(204, 0, 0);&#34;&gt;
     ※ The information such as text, photos and videos used in this article is copyrighted by Korea Tourism Organization, so unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/span&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>