<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Seongnam-si on Every Corner of Korea</title>
    <link>https://codecorea.github.io/tags/seongnam-si/</link>
    <description>Every Corner of Korea (Seongnam-si)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 23:27:19 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="https://codecorea.github.io/tags/seongnam-si/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A hot oil field in the city center, Seongnam Moran Folk Oil Market - Seongnam-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/a-hot-oil-field-in-the-city-center-seongnam-moran-folk-oil-market-233/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 23:27:19 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/a-hot-oil-field-in-the-city-center-seongnam-moran-folk-oil-market-233/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Seongnam-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;a-hot-oil-field-in-the-city-center-seongnam-moran-folk-oil-market--233&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Peony folk oil field scenery - Seongnam-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/233/45fdbf46-8a3c-4346-8249-c515ed9e095a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Peony folk oil field scenery
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   A hot oil field in the city center, Seongnam Moran Folk Oil Market
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Seongnam-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    As time goes by, the reality is that the old things are gradually forgotten or disappeared. Moreover, I feel sorry for even forgetting the nostalgia for the old. Though there are no exceptions for the old market, the peony market in Seongnam, Gyeonggi-do, shows the face of the nation&#39;s best folk market even in a short history. The peony is an oil field that stands in a crowded city center, and it is enough to inspire nostalgia and curiosity for those who are looking for a market place. The marketplace in the city, there are no objects in it, and there are as many people as there are items for sale. The oil field enjoyed in the city center gives a different scenery.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Korea&#39;s largest folk oil market
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Peony is a place that was given after reclaiming the wasteland around Seongnam in the 1960s and is the place where the history of the peony is held every five days. Busy streets, long tailed vehicles, busy people… . The daily life around Moran Station is no different from any other city, but when the oil field spreads around Moran Station, the city is full of energy. Whether it&#39;s at the entrance of a subway station, at a bus stop, or in the corner of an alley, it&#39;s a market place. This is the largest peony in Korea.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Peony Market&#39;s history is surprisingly short. Unlike the famous oil field with a long history, it is only about 40 years old. The peony market started with Nam-han Kim Chang-suk, who left his mother in Pyongyang. After enlisting in the military, he went through the Korean War and reorganized as a colonel. When people started to gather one by one, they were given the name &#39;Moran&#39;, symbolizing Pyongyang, where their mother lives. After that, as life problems emerged, an oil field was opened, which is said to be the beginning of a peony field.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    It was in the 1980s that the peonies became famous. As the uniqueness of traditional markets in the city became known by word of mouth, many people began to look for it. It is a rumor that is passed from mouth to mouth, so the number of people who want to live and who sells must have increased. Not only that, the peony is more overwhelming in terms of size and items than any other marketplace, and it is hard to even pass by people who fill the marketplace.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Peony folk oil tour
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The peony field is an oil field held on the 4th and 9th on the 12,000m2 Daewoncheon Bokgaeji. At Exit 5 of Moran Station on the Bundang Line, a noisy field opens. The Peony Folklore Field extends from east to west, and its length exceeds 300m. When you look down from the roof of the building across the main street, you can see the peony folk garden covered in colorful parasols at a glance. It is said that tens of thousands of merchants registered at the Moran Folklore Merchant Association count more than 1,500 people, including those from each region. Moreover, the marketplace is always crowded with customers and visitors who visit the peony market.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The peony field is accurately divided into 14 departments, making shopping easy. Starting with the first flower meet at the market entrance, four to five roads extend from east to west, in the order of grains, herbs, clothing, shoes, sundries, fish, vegetables, food, peppers, dogs, and poultry.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    At the far end of the Moran Folk Farm, the red pepper market forms a block with garlic. It comes from nearby Icheon, Yeoju, and Cheonan, as well as wholesalers, which are quite large compared to other markets. In the 1980s, about 80 merchants gathered and sold peppers in the 1980s. At one time, it was famous enough to say, &#34;The price of red pepper in the metropolitan area is determined at the peony market.&#34; Nowadays, the number of merchants has decreased, but Korean peppers are sold cheaper than those on the market, making Kim Jang-cheol a city.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Chilli Market in Peony Folk Oil Market - Seongnam-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/233/d449f48a-01da-4f26-8fdd-fe322857aced.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Chilli Market in Peony Folk Oil Market
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The fishery exhibition is divided into fish and freshwater fish. The plate is full of fresh fish, including mackerel that is woven from straw in Mokpo, fresh shrimp that has just been brought from Incheon, and mackerel, reference, and bottlefish. On the other hand, freshwater fish feel the vitality. Zara, carp, crucian carp, sesame, mulfish, loach, and catfish flutter in a red rubber basin.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox type2 clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Peony Folk Oil Market - Seongnam-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/233/7909e2fd-d89d-4d8e-957f-3be4a74e04b1.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Peony Folk Oil Market
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Peony Folk Oil Market - Seongnam-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/233/8d870fc3-3cc2-4ba7-8d03-3a8c4a4c3369.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Peony Folk Oil Market
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The chestnuts piled up on the floor are considered to be the best and are the best princess chestnuts. In order to save the consumer&#39;s trouble, the overnight machine runs continuously. A chestnut that costs 3,000 won per bag comes with a peeling service. Herbs from Paldo, such as Jeollado Gordon, Cheonnamul in Jeju Island, Gondrenamul in Gangwon-do, and Eolsoon, Gyeongsang-do, etc., are packed in red rubber basins, waiting for guests. The name of the herb and the origin of the white corrugated cardboard with bold magic is good. There are some shrimps in good condition in a large plastic bag. It is a barley shrimp from Ganghwa Island. It is said to sell around Goyang, Seongnam, and Anseong in Gyeonggi-do. Even if you just eat it, the barley prawn, which has a savory taste, is topped with more than one fist.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox type3 clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Herbs from all over the country - Seongnam-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/233/2b9abbe4-5137-4da7-9609-700cd99008b4.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Herbs from all over the country
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Barley Shrimp and Merchant from Ganghwa Island - Seongnam-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/233/ccf22d68-ed2e-4c40-b80c-4a1b620841c9.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Barley Shrimp and Merchant from Ganghwa Island
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Homemade acorn jelly and Umu made from salt - Seongnam-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/233/bb5172df-bc7b-42ea-81cd-c505548c316e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Homemade acorn jelly and Umu made from salt
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Oil alley full of savory smell and peony sauce
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    A stinky smell stings the nose. It smells of oil from the oil alley, one of the largest wholesale markets in Korea. There are oils lined up one by one across the house, as well as sesame oil and perilla oil. More than 40 places have started over 40 years ago. In the past, sesame oil was made with domestic sesame seeds, but now mainly made in China. Among 100 bottles of sesame oil, domestic sesame oil is said to be only 1 to 2 bottles. Due to the difference in sesame yield and price, the price of domestic sesame oil is about three times higher than that of Chinese.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Looking inside the oil house of the oil alley is very busy. A machine that roasts sesame seeds to squeeze the oil will run continuously. Most of them use machines, but the operation of bottling oil is semi-mechanical.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox type2 clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Moran Folk Oil Field - Seongnam-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/233/f89126f1-7416-406b-a042-951bfdace5d7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Moran Folk Oil Field
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A bottle of sesame oil - Seongnam-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/233/684eed17-6b74-433d-9b75-38656b29fa6e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A bottle of sesame oil
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Food cannot be missed in the marketplace. The best food in the peony market is Son Kalguksu. Most of the food department, which has over 40 restaurants, sells hand knife noodles. Knead directly with wheat flour, and if you eat Cheongyang pepper and seasoning sauce, the soup is crisp and crisp and chewy noodles stick to your tongue. In addition to hand kalguksu, you can enjoy various kinds of snacks such as red bean kalguksu, feast noodle soup, mandu kalguksu, and other kinds of snacks such as sundae gukbap, pork shells, minority crab, and steamed stingray. On a hot day like this, cold beef radish and cold bean noodles are considered delicacies.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox type3 clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Cold beef radish tasted at Lan Folk Oil Market - Seongnam-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/233/f58a9ba2-5a50-4f28-a996-3280a6f9ac97.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Cold beef radish tasted at Lan Folk Oil Market
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Kalguksu at Ranmin Folk Oil Market - Seongnam-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/233/e737f4d3-6ac6-4997-9495-ac52de3836d4.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Kalguksu at Ranmin Folk Oil Market
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;How to make Kalguksu noodles - Seongnam-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/233/30797ecb-ce31-4e5b-b390-37d72cd01e0e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     How to make Kalguksu noodles
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Chicken fried in a cauldron is also essential. The fried chicken is cut with scissors, but the price is also good at 5,000 won per head. There are also Chimak people, who lined up for a long time to pack, and served cold beer with whole chicken in the whole chicken house after a market visit.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    The Peony Folk Oil Market, with its many interesting attractions and a variety of food, takes around 2 hours to explore. It is the largest folk oil field in the city center, and it is a living educational center for children and a marketplace to soothe nostalgia for adults. The peonies are held every 9th and 9th from 9 am to 7 pm.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Cauldron whole chicken that can be tasted at peony folk oil field - Seongnam-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/233/7997ba8b-89a5-43e5-bd39-73b7d83bad05.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Cauldron whole chicken that can be tasted at peony folk oil field
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    1.Access
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    * Self-driving
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Seongnam IC on the outer ring road → turn right toward Seongnam at Yeosu intersection → Moran Folk Oil Market
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Urban Expressway between Bundang and Suseo → Turn right toward Seongnam and Gwangju → Turn right at Moran Intersection → Moran Folk Oil Market
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    * public transport
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Bundang Line Moran Station Exit 5
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    2. Restaurants around
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Obok House: Gochujang Ribs / 27, Angol-ro, Bundang-gu, Seongnam-si / 031-701-1944 /
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.shinhwaifood.co.kr&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;오복집으로 이동&#34;&gt;
     http://www.shinhwaifood.co.kr
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Gam Mi-ok: Seolleongtang / 181 Tancheon-ro, Bundang-gu, Seongnam-si / 031-709-9448
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Seokcheon Sashimi Restaurant: Sashimi / 45 Bulmal-ro, Bundang-gu, Seongnam-si / 031-704-2988
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    One day duck: Ducks, Duck Jumul Luck / 109 Gwangmyeong-ro, Jungwon-gu, Seongnam-si / 031-754-8337
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    3.Accommodation
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Hotel Gallery: 321 Hwangsaeul-ro, Bundang-gu, Seongnam-si / 031-702-8200 /
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.galleryhotel.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;호텔 갤러리로 이동&#34;&gt;
     http://www.galleryhotel.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    SR Hotel: 9, Hwangsaeul-ro 319beon-gil, Bundang-gu, Seongnam-si / 031-702-6565 /
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.srhotel.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;분당SR(에스알)호텔로 이동&#34;&gt;
     http://www.srhotel.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Hwangtobang Motel: 154 Sanseong-daero, Jungwon-gu, Seongnam-si / 031-757-5185
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    ※ The above information was created in August 2013, and may be changed later, so be sure to check it before you travel.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>