<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>County on Korea Tour</title>
    <link>https://codecorea.github.io/tags/county/</link>
    <description>Korea Tour (County)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 19:17:25 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="https://codecorea.github.io/tags/county/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Buyeo County, Chungnam, Южная Корея - Куда просить осенние листья, лучшее время года</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/where-to-ask-for-autumn-leaves-the-best-season-73-ru/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 19:17:25 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/where-to-ask-for-autumn-leaves-the-best-season-73-ru/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Buyeo County, Chungnam, South Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;where-to-ask-for-autumn-leaves-the-best-season--73&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Яркие боевые искусства осенью - Buyeo County, Chungnam, Южная Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/58937cfd-a1a2-47c6-9a4b-d211eec767b1.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Яркие боевые искусства осенью
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Куда просить осенние листья, лучшее время года
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Buyeo County, Chungnam, Южная Корея
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Чтобы поймать конец осени, он похоронил мертвых воинов, чтобы похоронить в прошлом сезоне. Юн Дэ Нён, написавший роман, назвал Мурьянгу «джанджи (сезон), где тонут сезоны». Когда листья закончатся, это будет напоминать печаль года. Однако горечь осени, которая изобилует золотом, сразу же проглатывается. Можем ли мы спросить о сезоне, который прошел в Буео-Мурьянге, где Ким Си-рён, ветер и гениальный поэт Чосон, провел свои последние годы? ,
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Кориандр
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Эта укушенная осень отправляется в Буео через месяц, потому что листья опадают рано. К счастью, боевые искусства еще не полностью остановили падение. Прошлым летом еще много энергии. Пройдя через билетную кассу, скоро будет один заказ. На лбу одного ордена есть большая доска под названием «Мансусан Муралоса». Это гармоничное сочетание «непостоянства», означающего неизмеримое, и названия горы «Мансу», что означает наслаждение долгой жизнью. Храм Мурьянга - это тысячелетний храм, который был основан во времена короля Мунсона (Объединение 839 ~ 857). Однако, как и большинство храмов и архитектурных культурных ценностей в Корее, все боевые искусства исчезли во время войны с Имджином, но были восстановлены в 1623 году (ст. 1), чтобы достичь сегодня.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Один заказ - Buyeo County, Chungnam, Южная Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/3a1d7526-7d10-4029-bfd6-affc28fccf4f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Один заказ
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Пройдя через небольшую долину и дойдя до ворот Чонвангмун, красивый владелец вечеринки приветствует посетителей справа. Проведение вечеринки означает удлиненный столб, на котором висел флаг храма, или место для удержания, поддерживающее вечеринку слева направо. Это признак того, что основания храма начинаются здесь.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Муги Корп - Buyeo County, Chungnam, Южная Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/2c5651cf-35af-4569-a629-22642c259afa.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Муги Корп
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Поднимаясь к воротам Чонвангмун, райский уголок храма Муйонгса, Пятиэтажная пагода и далее находятся в квадратной рамке Чхонвангмуна. Слишком стабильный угол. Даже если вы не специализируетесь на фотографии, вы можете естественным образом поднять камеру. Но дизайнер, создавший этот потрясающий вид, не раскрыл 100% рая, сердца храма. Райская крыша была слегка покрыта сосновой и зельковой ветвями. Я сидел и стоял, пытаясь сфотографировать, чтобы избежать ветвей. 1 минута осталась? Ах! Поймите, что это был чудесный кусочек кориандра, чтобы покрыть жилище Будды. Разве эту ветку не было бы здорово увидеть сквозь рай? Скорее ветви деревьев добавляют в тайный райский рай.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Райский вид с Чонванмун - Buyeo County, Chungnam, Южная Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/02b188aa-0cf4-4f56-adba-8b2b37f8d365.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Райский вид с Чонванмун
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Медленно приближайтесь к раю. Когда вы доберетесь до сосны, покрывающей крышу, вы увидите каменные фонари, пятиэтажную пагоду и рай. Каменные фонари, пятиэтажная пагода и рай Мурьюкса - все это национальные сокровища. Может показаться, что это культурное достояние, но история культурных ценностей, наполненных знаками, и знание истории искусства, похоже, не помогают этой осенью. Поэтому я не буду вдаваться в подробности. Пыль знаний в моей голове, кажется, сидит на поверхности липких эмоций. Просто посмотрите на три сокровища на расстоянии. С большой точки зрения взгляд, исходящий из земли, поднимает ощущение вознесения через каменные фонари и верхушку пагоды, ведущей к райскому хребту. Кроме того, пятьсот одна тысяча лет истории, без серьезных повреждений и повреждений, добавляет достоинства.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Государство и место величественной райской войны - Buyeo County, Chungnam, Южная Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/ef01d9af-0a62-4f68-9e2d-552a072a2617.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Государство и место величественной райской войны
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Наблюдайте за раем слева направо. Лодки столбов, поддерживающих эксцентричную райскую структуру, чрезвычайно выпуклые. Это обычно называется пролить столбец. Внешность выглядит как два этажа, но внутренняя часть рая представляет собой слоистую структуру без слоев. Видно, что эта конструкция предназначена не для фактического использования второго этажа, а для формальности и достоинства здания.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Столб надгробия - Buyeo County, Chungnam, Южная Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/67f1e89f-86dc-47a2-bc0f-d1a6b169aece.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Столб надгробия
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Обернитесь вокруг райского двора и встаньте под клен перед оградой с правой стороны здания. Удачи приехать в последний день боевых искусств. Солнце начало подниматься к западу от Мансусана, и теплое осеннее полуденное солнце обильно покрывает землю. Под кленом подсветка покрыта кленовыми листьями и спуск затвора. Нет ничего плохого в том, чтобы делать фотографии ногами. Как только монах проходит мимо.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;13&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;На территории храма боевых искусств справа - Buyeo County, Chungnam, Южная Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/0e2cb43e-59b9-4c6e-b10e-8592536501cb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     На территории храма боевых искусств справа
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Ким Си-сук, бедный гениальный писатель или обладатель свободной души
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Есть один человек, которого вы должны встретить в храме Мурьянга. Ким Си-сеон (1435–1493) - ежемесячный лидер, которого всегда знакомят с такими прозвищами, как Пунг Ун А, гениальный автор и Шин Донг. Пройдите через рай и переправьтесь через небольшой ручей налево, чтобы увидеть портрет Ким Си-Сеоп в Йончжонгаке. Ким Си-сук не признавала захват трона и жила как монах и жена навсегда. Он покинул мир в возрасте 21 года и бродил по всей стране.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Давайте посмотрим на портрет Ким Чен Шика. Yeongjung отличается от интенсивного основного цветового разногласия, обычно встречающегося в стихах. Это также отличается от портрета эскадрильи Чосон, красиво одетой в Кванбок. Ким Си-сеоп в руках Ёнджуна аккуратно лежит в рукаве, но он хмурится хмурым взглядом. Вот почему многие критики говорят, что они уловили черты недовольных интеллектуалов, которые недовольны миром. Ты это видишь. В двадцать один год, когда король Сехо вступил на престол, он сжег все книги, которые прочитал, покинул мир и стал монахом. Однако жизнь Кима не наполнена невезением, накоплением и критикой общества.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   Он покинул мир и совершил поездку по Канто и Хунани, наслаждаясь пейзажами и сочиняя стихи. В свои тридцать лет он провел шесть лет в Кёнджу Кымозан, нынешнем Кёнджу Намсане, посвятившем себя своей работе. Результатом погружения является миф о Кум-о, который считается первым китайским романом в Корее. Был ли Ким Си-сук бедным гением, который ошибся со временем? Или он владелец свободной души? В конце концов он видит в своем странствии отчуждение от власти и мейнстрима или волю свободной жизни. Я даю небольшой намек на эту непростую проблему. Ким Си-Сеоп пишет мотив побродить в предисловии к «Дому каждого месяца»
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Юнг Си Ким - Buyeo County, Chungnam, Южная Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/db703360-cf34-443e-989c-e887c38d15e9.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Юнг Си Ким
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;font color=&#34;#367100&#34;&gt;
    «Я… Чтобы побродить по горам и найти хороший вид, я бы похвастался, что мои друзья наслаждаются стихотворением, но я не думал о том, чтобы войти в офис с предложением. Обидно, что однажды после будучи разбитым (узурпацией трона) человеком, человек может родиться в этом мире и идти по дороге ».
   &lt;/font&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Монах подметает листья - Buyeo County, Chungnam, Южная Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/c8dc4b05-d3fc-4362-b7aa-4d88cfe56a97.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Монах подметает листья
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Легкий путь, путь в Тэджоам
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   После изучения территории вернитесь на одну неделю для более глубокой осенней прогулки.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;1 - Buyeo County, Chungnam, Южная Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/3834472d-88b3-400f-8857-b1cfe1526199.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     1
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Прежде чем достигнуть ордена, налево до Тэджоама и Досолама слева. Широкая открытая площадка ведет к хорошо проложенной дороге налево. Дорога длится 1,2 км до скалы Taejo.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Дорога в Тэджоам - это хороший способ для прогулок. - Buyeo County, Chungnam, Южная Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/07b01060-3850-4036-91de-ada290ad79d7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Дорога в Тэджоам - это хороший способ для прогулок.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Вскоре после входа на улицу слева от вас есть место для боевых искусств.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Скамья по дороге в Тэджоам - Buyeo County, Chungnam, Южная Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/d063e688-3a31-4265-851a-c4f1ea083213.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Скамья по дороге в Тэджоам
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Теперь он покрыт пампасной травой, сорняками и кустарниками, но раскопки в 2000 году подтвердили подиум, надгробие и престижный флаг с надписью «Muyangsa».
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Старый сайт боевых искусств - Buyeo County, Chungnam, Южная Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/8af3da53-f771-4615-ae11-f33d3822bf57.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Старый сайт боевых искусств
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Путь снова. Он немедленно проходит через Досолам и достигает Тэджоам. Только два туалета и скамейки разбросаны по пути в Тэджоам. На этой дороге нет сороки, но только красные хурмы висят на деревьях хурмы, у которых нет листьев. Это гладкий, но простой способ совершить тихую прогулку. Проходя через сад справа от Taejoam начинается полномасштабная пешеходная тропа. Если вы планируете подняться на гору Мансу, вы можете подняться по тропе Тэджоам.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Мансусанская горная тропа начинается в Тэджоаме - Buyeo County, Chungnam, Южная Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/1765c925-3dfb-4c35-9071-6d2f43308c1b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Мансусанская горная тропа начинается в Тэджоаме
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Выйдите из Taejoam и полностью покиньте храм. Есть еще одна вещь, которую стоит увидеть перед тем, как идти на парковку. Посетителю, который хочет уйти, Мурьянга представляет банкротство Ким Си-сук. Тот факт, что есть много буддизма, могил, где похоронены буддийские монахи, означает, что они произвели много монахов.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;13&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Храм Муранга Будо-гун - Buyeo County, Chungnam, Южная Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/89fe1dbc-3e46-481a-b086-843a3ea86cae.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Храм Муранга Будо-гун
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Мурьянга Будо-гун находится на пути в Муджинам. Из всех дефолтов банкротство Ким Си-сук является самым высоким. И размер, и внешний вид являются наиболее полными. По умолчанию Ким Си-сук - двойное основание. Узор дракона ярко проявляется на поверхности второго подиумного камня (средний камень), который украшен цветком лотоса. Это очень хорошо для каменных реликвий Chosun Electric.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;15&#34; id3=&#34;15&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Банкротство Ким Си-Сук - Buyeo County, Chungnam, Южная Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/2e38fdd9-f508-4669-bc00-df4dc988ba76.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Банкротство Ким Си-Сук
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Так есть ли здесь сари Ким Си-Сури? Во время японского колониального периода тайфун сместился, и окружающие деревья упали. В это время Будо также рухнул, и было найдено сари Ким Си-сук. Сари Ким в настоящее время экспонируется в Национальном музее Буйо.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;17&#34; id3=&#34;16&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Дракон рисунок Ким Си-сеоп Будо среднего камня - Buyeo County, Chungnam, Южная Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/3e13f9fe-55c2-4d47-809c-7833fbb11c87.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Дракон рисунок Ким Си-сеоп Будо среднего камня
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Информация о путешествии
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;span style=&#34;color: rgb(33, 33, 33);&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong style=&#34;&#34;&gt;
      Боевые искусства
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Адрес: 203, Мурьянг-ро, Эзан-Мён, Буё-гун, Чунгнам.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Запросы: офис Muryangsa 041-836-5066
    &lt;/span&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://tour.buyeo.go.kr/html/tour/info/info_010108.html&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://tour.buyeo.go.kr/html/tour/info/info_010108.html
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Близлежащие рестораны
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Дом Пэкче: Рис Ёнлиф, Mabab / 22, Heukcheon-ro 8beon-gil, Buyeo-eup, Buyeo-gun / 041-834-1212
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Jangwon Makguksu: Makguksu / 20, Narutero 62beon-gil, Buyeo-eup, Buyeo-gun / 041-835-6561
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Гудраедол Ссамбап: Дол Самбап / 31, Нарут-ро, Буе-эуп, Буе-пушка / 041-836-9259
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Размещение
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Lotte Resort Buyeo: 400 Baekjemun-ro, Gyuam-myeon, Buyeo-gun / 041-939-1000
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.lottebuyeoresort.com/kor/index.asp&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.lottebuyeoresort.com/kor/index.asp
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Туристический отель Baekje: 108 Bukpo-ro, Buyeo-eup, Buyeo-gun / 041-835-0870
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://백제관광호텔.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://백제관광호텔.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Samjung Yeo Youth Hostel: Нарут-ро 50, Буе-эуп, Буе-гун / 041-835-3101
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.buyeoyh.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.buyeoyh.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34; style=&#34;font-weight: bold;&#34;&gt;
     ※ Приведенная выше информация была обновлена в сентябре 2017 года и может впоследствии измениться. Пожалуйста, проверьте перед путешествием.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Информация, такая как текст, фотографии и видео, используемые в этой статье, защищены авторским правом Корейской туристической организации, поэтому несанкционированное использование статьи запрещено.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comté de Buyeo, Chungnam, Corée du Sud - Où demander des feuilles d&#39;automne, la meilleure saison</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/where-to-ask-for-autumn-leaves-the-best-season-73-fr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 19:14:13 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/where-to-ask-for-autumn-leaves-the-best-season-73-fr/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Buyeo County, Chungnam, South Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;where-to-ask-for-autumn-leaves-the-best-season--73&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Motifs d&#39;arts martiaux lumineux en automne - Comté de Buyeo, Chungnam, Corée du Sud (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/58937cfd-a1a2-47c6-9a4b-d211eec767b1.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Motifs d&#39;arts martiaux lumineux en automne
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Où demander des feuilles d&#39;automne, la meilleure saison
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Comté de Buyeo, Chungnam, Corée du Sud
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Pour attraper la fin de l&#39;automne, il a enterré les guerriers morts pour enterrer la saison dernière. Yun Dae-nyeong, qui a écrit le roman, a appelé Muryangsa comme «le jangji (saison) où les saisons s&#39;enfoncent». Lorsque les feuilles s&#39;épuisent, cela rappellera la tristesse d&#39;un an. Cependant, l&#39;amertume de l&#39;automne, plus abondante que l&#39;or, est engloutie d&#39;un coup. Peut-on s&#39;interroger sur la saison qui s&#39;est écoulée depuis Buyeo Muryangsa où Kim Si-ryong, la chance au vent et poète de génie de Joseon, a passé ses dernières années? .
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Coriandre
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Cet automne, qui a été mordu, va à Buyeo dans un mois car les feuilles tombent tôt. Heureusement, les arts martiaux n&#39;ont pas encore complètement abandonné l&#39;automne. Il y a encore beaucoup d&#39;énergie l&#39;été dernier. Passer par la billetterie est une commande bientôt. Sur le front d&#39;une commande, il y a une grande planche appelée &#39;Mansusan Muralosa&#39;. C&#39;est une combinaison harmonieuse de `` non-quantité &#39;&#39;, qui signifie incommensurable, et du nom de la montagne, `` Mansu &#39;&#39;, qui signifie profiter d&#39;une longue vie. Le temple Muryangsa est un temple millénaire fondé pendant le roi Munseong King (Unification 839 ~ 857). Cependant, comme la plupart des temples et des biens culturels architecturaux en Corée, tous les arts martiaux ont disparu pendant la guerre d&#39;Imjin, mais ont été reconstruits en 1623 (art. 1) pour atteindre aujourd&#39;hui.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Une commande - Comté de Buyeo, Chungnam, Corée du Sud (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/3a1d7526-7d10-4029-bfd6-affc28fccf4f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Une commande
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Traversant une petite vallée et atteignant la porte de Cheonwangmun, un beau détenteur de fête accueille les visiteurs sur la droite. La tenue du parti signifie un poteau allongé qui pendait le drapeau du temple, ou un siège qui soutenait le parti de gauche à droite. C&#39;est un signe que les motifs du temple commencent ici.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Mugi Corp - Comté de Buyeo, Chungnam, Corée du Sud (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/2c5651cf-35af-4569-a629-22642c259afa.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Mugi Corp
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   En montant à la porte de Cheonwangmun, le paradis du temple Muyongsa, de la pagode à cinq étages et au-delà se trouve dans le cadre carré de Cheonwangmun. Angle trop stable. Même si vous n&#39;êtes pas spécialisé dans la photographie, vous pouvez naturellement soulever l&#39;appareil photo. Mais le concepteur qui a conçu cette vue imprenable n&#39;a pas exposé 100% du paradis, le cœur du temple. Le toit paradisiaque était légèrement recouvert de branches de pin et de zelkova. Je me suis assis et j&#39;ai essayé de prendre une photo pour éviter les branches. Il reste 1 minute? Ah! Sachez que c&#39;était un merveilleux morceau de coriandre pour couvrir la demeure du Bouddha. Cette branche n&#39;aurait-elle pas été cool de voir à travers le paradis? Au contraire, les branches d&#39;arbres ajoutent au paradis secret du paradis.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Vue paradisiaque depuis le Cheonwangmun - Comté de Buyeo, Chungnam, Corée du Sud (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/02b188aa-0cf4-4f56-adba-8b2b37f8d365.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Vue paradisiaque depuis le Cheonwangmun
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Approche lente du paradis. Lorsque vous atteignez le pin qui couvrait le toit, vous pouvez voir les lanternes en pierre, la pagode à cinq étages et le paradis. Les lanternes de pierre, la pagode à cinq étages et le paradis de Muryuksa sont tous des trésors nationaux. Cela peut sembler être un bien culturel, mais l&#39;histoire des biens culturels remplie de signes et la connaissance de l&#39;histoire de l&#39;art ne semblent pas aider cet automne. Je ne vais donc pas délibérément en détail. La poussière de connaissance dans ma tête semble reposer sur la surface de l&#39;émotion collante. Regardez les trois trésors à distance. D&#39;un point de vue large, le regard provenant du sol suscite un sentiment d&#39;ascension à travers les lanternes de pierre et le sommet de la pagode, menant à la crête paradisiaque. En outre, cinq cent mille ans d&#39;histoire, sans dommages ni dommages graves, ajoutent de la dignité.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;État et siège de la majestueuse guerre du paradis - Comté de Buyeo, Chungnam, Corée du Sud (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/ef01d9af-0a62-4f68-9e2d-552a072a2617.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     État et siège de la majestueuse guerre du paradis
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Regardez le paradis rond de gauche à droite. Les bateaux des piliers soutenant la structure excentrique du paradis sont extraordinairement bombés. Il s&#39;agit d&#39;une colonne de délestage communément appelée. L&#39;extérieur ressemble à deux étages, mais l&#39;intérieur du paradis est une structure en couches sans couches. On peut voir que cette structure n&#39;est pas pour l&#39;usage réel du deuxième étage, mais pour la formalité et la dignité du bâtiment.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Pilier de pierre tombale - Comté de Buyeo, Chungnam, Corée du Sud (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/67f1e89f-86dc-47a2-bc0f-d1a6b169aece.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Pilier de pierre tombale
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Faites demi-tour dans le jardin paradisiaque et placez-vous sous l&#39;érable devant la clôture sur le côté droit du bâtiment. C&#39;est une bonne chance de venir au dernier après-midi d&#39;arts martiaux. Le soleil a commencé à se diriger vers l&#39;ouest de Mansusan, et le chaud soleil d&#39;automne de l&#39;après-midi couvre abondamment le terrain. Sous l&#39;érable, le rétro-éclairage est recouvert de feuilles d&#39;érable et l&#39;obturateur est déclenché. Il n&#39;est pas faux de dire «prenez des photos avec vos pieds». Dès que le moine passe.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;13&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Les motifs du temple des arts martiaux depuis la droite - Comté de Buyeo, Chungnam, Corée du Sud (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/0e2cb43e-59b9-4c6e-b10e-8592536501cb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Les motifs du temple des arts martiaux depuis la droite
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Kim Si-sook, pauvre écrivain de génie ou propriétaire d&#39;une âme libre
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Il y a une personne que vous devez rencontrer dans le temple de Muryangsa. Kim Si-seon (1435 ~ 1493) est un leader mensuel qui est toujours présenté avec des surnoms tels que Pung Un Ah, auteur de génie, et Shin Dong. Passez le paradis et traversez le petit ruisseau à gauche pour voir le portrait de Kim Si-seop à Yeongjeonggak. Kim Si-sook n&#39;a pas reconnu la saisie du trône et a vécu comme moine et femme pour toujours. Il a quitté le monde à 21 ans et a erré dans tout le pays.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Jetons un coup d&#39;œil au portrait de Kim Jung-shik. Yeongjung diffère de la discorde intense des couleurs primaires que l&#39;on trouve couramment dans les versets. Il diffère également du portrait de l&#39;escadron Joseon qui s&#39;habillait joliment à Gwanbok. Kim Si-seop dans les mains de Yeongjung est bien tenu dans la manche, mais il fronce les sourcils. C&#39;est pourquoi de nombreux critiques disent qu&#39;ils ont capturé les caractéristiques d&#39;intellectuels insatisfaits qui sont insatisfaits du monde. Tu peux voir ça. À vingt et un ans, lorsque le roi Sejo accède au trône, il brûle tous les livres qu&#39;il a lus et quitte le monde et devient moine. Cependant, la vie de Kim n&#39;est pas remplie de malchance, de thésaurisation et de critique de la société.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   Il a quitté le monde et a visité Kanto et Hunan, appréciant les paysages et écrivant des poèmes. Dans la trentaine, il a passé six ans à Gyeongju Geumosan, l&#39;actuel Gyeongju Namsan, dédié à son travail. Le résultat de l&#39;immersion est Kum-O Myth, qui est considéré comme le premier roman chinois de Corée. Kim Si-sook était-elle un pauvre génie qui avait mal rencontré le temps? Ou était-il le propriétaire d&#39;une âme libre? Finalement, il voit son errance comme une aliénation du pouvoir et du courant dominant ou une volonté de vie libre. Je donne un petit indice à ce problème pas facile. Kim Si-seop écrit le motif de l&#39;errance dans la préface de `` Every Month House &#39;&#39;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Young Si Kim - Comté de Buyeo, Chungnam, Corée du Sud (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/db703360-cf34-443e-989c-e887c38d15e9.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Young Si Kim
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;font color=&#34;#367100&#34;&gt;
    &#34;Je ... Afin de me promener dans les montagnes et de trouver une bonne vue, je me vanterais de mes amis pour apprécier le poème, mais je n&#39;ai pas pensé à entrer au bureau avec une phrase. C&#39;est dommage qu&#39;un jour, après étant submergé (l&#39;usurpation du trône) par un homme, un homme peut naître dans ce monde et marcher sur la route. &#34;
   &lt;/font&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Un moine balaie les feuilles - Comté de Buyeo, Chungnam, Corée du Sud (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/c8dc4b05-d3fc-4362-b7aa-4d88cfe56a97.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Un moine balaie les feuilles
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   La voie légère, la route de Taejoam
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Après avoir exploré le domaine, revenez une semaine en arrière pour une promenade d&#39;automne plus profonde.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;1,2 km du temple Mouyangsa à Taejoam - Comté de Buyeo, Chungnam, Corée du Sud (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/3834472d-88b3-400f-8857-b1cfe1526199.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     1,2 km du temple Mouyangsa à Taejoam
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Avant d&#39;atteindre l&#39;ordre, à gauche vers Taejoam et Dosolam à gauche. Un large espace ouvert mène à une route bien pavée à gauche. La route dure 1,2 km jusqu&#39;à Taejo Rock.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;L&#39;allée de Taejoam est un bon moyen de marcher. - Comté de Buyeo, Chungnam, Corée du Sud (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/07b01060-3850-4036-91de-ada290ad79d7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     L&#39;allée de Taejoam est un bon moyen de marcher.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Peu de temps après être entré dans la rue, il y a un ancien site d&#39;arts martiaux sur votre gauche.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Banc sur le chemin de Taejoam - Comté de Buyeo, Chungnam, Corée du Sud (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/d063e688-3a31-4265-851a-c4f1ea083213.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Banc sur le chemin de Taejoam
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Il est maintenant recouvert d&#39;herbe de pampa, de mauvaises herbes et d&#39;arbustes, mais les fouilles de 2000 ont confirmé le podium, la pierre tombale et le prestigieux drapeau estampillé «Muyangsa».
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Ancien site d&#39;arts martiaux - Comté de Buyeo, Chungnam, Corée du Sud (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/8af3da53-f771-4615-ae11-f33d3822bf57.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Ancien site d&#39;arts martiaux
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Aller de nouveau Il passe immédiatement par Dosolam et atteint Taejoam. Seuls deux toilettes et bancs sont placés peu sur le chemin de Taejoam. Il n&#39;y a pas de pies sur cette route, mais seuls des kakis rouges sont accrochés aux kaki qui sont à court de feuilles. C&#39;est une façon élégante mais simple de faire une promenade tranquille. Passer le jardin à droite de Taejoam commence le sentier de randonnée à grande échelle. Si vous prévoyez de gravir la montagne Mansu, vous pouvez grimper le long du sentier Taejoam.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Début du Mansusan Mountain Trail à Taejoam - Comté de Buyeo, Chungnam, Corée du Sud (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/1765c925-3dfb-4c35-9071-6d2f43308c1b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Début du Mansusan Mountain Trail à Taejoam
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Sortez de Taejoam et quittez complètement le temple. Il y a encore une chose à voir avant d&#39;aller au parking. Au visiteur qui veut partir, Muryangsa présente la faillite de Kim Si-sook. Le fait qu&#39;il y ait beaucoup de bouddhisme, les tombes où les moines bouddhistes sont enterrés, signifie qu&#39;ils ont produit beaucoup de moines.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;13&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Pistolet Budo Temple Murangsa - Comté de Buyeo, Chungnam, Corée du Sud (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/89fe1dbc-3e46-481a-b086-843a3ea86cae.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Pistolet Budo Temple Murangsa
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Muryangsa Budo-gun est en route pour Mujinam. De tous les défauts, la faillite de Kim Si-sook est la plus élevée. La taille et l&#39;apparence sont les plus complètes. La valeur par défaut de Kim Si-sook est une double base. Le motif du dragon est vif à la surface de la pierre de robe du deuxième podium (pierre moyenne), qui est décorée d&#39;une fleur de lotus. C&#39;est très bon pour les reliques de pierre de Chosun Electric.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;15&#34; id3=&#34;15&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Faillite de Kim Si-sook - Comté de Buyeo, Chungnam, Corée du Sud (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/2e38fdd9-f508-4669-bc00-df4dc988ba76.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Faillite de Kim Si-sook
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Y a-t-il vraiment un sari de Kim Si-suri ici? Pendant la période coloniale japonaise, le typhon a balayé et les arbres environnants sont tombés. À cette époque, le Budo s&#39;est également effondré et le sari de Kim Si-sook a été retrouvé. Le sari de Kim est actuellement exposé au National Buyeo Museum.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;17&#34; id3=&#34;16&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Motif dragon de Kim Si-seop Budo pierre centrale - Comté de Buyeo, Chungnam, Corée du Sud (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/3e13f9fe-55c2-4d47-809c-7833fbb11c87.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Motif dragon de Kim Si-seop Budo pierre centrale
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Info voyage
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;span style=&#34;color: rgb(33, 33, 33);&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong style=&#34;&#34;&gt;
      Arts martiaux
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Adresse: 203, Muryang-ro, Oesan-myeon, Buyeo-gun, Chungnam
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Renseignements: Bureau de Muryangsa 041-836-5066
    &lt;/span&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://tour.buyeo.go.kr/html/tour/info/info_010108.html&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://tour.buyeo.go.kr/html/tour/info/info_010108.html
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Restaurants à proximité
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Maison de Baekje: Yeonleaf Rice, Mabab / 22, Heukcheon-ro 8beon-gil, Buyeo-eup, Buyeo-gun / 041-834-1212
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Jangwon Makguksu: Makguksu / 20, Narutero 62beon-gil, Buyeo-eup, Buyeo-gun / 041-835-6561
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Gudraedol Ssambap: Dol Sambap / 31, Narut-ro, Buyeo-eup, Buyeo-gun / 041-836-9259
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Hébergement
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Lotte Resort Buyeo: 400 Baekjemun-ro, Gyuam-myeon, Buyeo-gun / 041-939-1000
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.lottebuyeoresort.com/kor/index.asp&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.lottebuyeoresort.com/kor/index.asp
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Baekje Tourist Hotel: 108 Bukpo-ro, Buyeo-eup, Buyeo-gun / 041-835-0870
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://백제관광호텔.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://백제관광호텔.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Auberge de jeunesse Samjung Yeo: 50 Narut-ro, Buyeo-eup, Buyeo-gun / 041-835-3101
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.buyeoyh.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.buyeoyh.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34; style=&#34;font-weight: bold;&#34;&gt;
     ※ Les informations ci-dessus ont été mises à jour en septembre 2017 et peuvent changer par la suite. Veuillez vérifier avant de voyager.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Les informations telles que le texte, les photos et les vidéos utilisées dans cet article sont protégées par les droits d&#39;auteur de l&#39;Organisation coréenne du tourisme, de sorte que l&#39;utilisation non autorisée de l&#39;article est interdite.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Condado de Buyeo, Chungnam, Corea del Sur - Donde pedir hojas de otoño, la mejor temporada</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/where-to-ask-for-autumn-leaves-the-best-season-73-es/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 19:11:06 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/where-to-ask-for-autumn-leaves-the-best-season-73-es/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Buyeo County, Chungnam, South Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;where-to-ask-for-autumn-leaves-the-best-season--73&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Brillantes jardines de artes marciales en otoño - Condado de Buyeo, Chungnam, Corea del Sur (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/58937cfd-a1a2-47c6-9a4b-d211eec767b1.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Brillantes jardines de artes marciales en otoño
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Donde pedir hojas de otoño, la mejor temporada
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Condado de Buyeo, Chungnam, Corea del Sur
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Para alcanzar el final de la caída, enterró a los guerreros muertos para enterrar la última temporada. Yun Dae-nyeong, quien escribió la novela, llamó a Muryangsa como &#34;el jangji (estación) donde las estaciones se hunden&#34;. Cuando se agoten las hojas, recordará la tristeza de un año. Sin embargo, la amargura del otoño, que es más abundante que el oro, se traga de inmediato. ¿Podemos preguntar sobre la temporada que pasó desde Buyeo Muryangsa donde Kim Si-ryong, el poeta de la suerte del viento y genio de Joseon, pasó sus últimos años? .
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Cilantro
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Este otoño, que ha sido mordido, llega a Buyeo en un mes porque las hojas caen temprano. Afortunadamente, las artes marciales aún no han caído por completo la caída. Todavía hay mucha energía el verano pasado. Pasar por la taquilla es un pedido pronto. En la parte frontal de una orden, hay una gran placa llamada &#39;Mansusan Muralosa&#39;. Es una combinación armoniosa de &#34;cantidad&#34;, que significa inconmensurable, y el nombre de la montaña, &#34;Mansu&#34;, que significa disfrutar de una larga vida. El Templo Muryangsa es un templo milenario que fue fundado durante el Rey Rey Munseong (Unificación 839 ~ 857). Sin embargo, como la mayoría de los templos y bienes culturales arquitectónicos en Corea, todas las artes marciales desaparecieron durante la Guerra de Imjin, pero fueron reconstruidas en 1623 (Art. 1) para llegar a la actualidad.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Una orden - Condado de Buyeo, Chungnam, Corea del Sur (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/3a1d7526-7d10-4029-bfd6-affc28fccf4f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Una orden
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Al atravesar un pequeño valle y llegar a la puerta de Cheonwangmun, un guapo organizador de la fiesta da la bienvenida a los visitantes a la derecha. La celebración de la fiesta significa un poste alargado que colgaba la bandera del templo, o un asiento de sujeción que sostenía a la fiesta de izquierda a derecha. Esta es una señal de que los terrenos del templo comienzan aquí.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Mugi Corp - Condado de Buyeo, Chungnam, Corea del Sur (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/2c5651cf-35af-4569-a629-22642c259afa.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Mugi Corp
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Ascendiendo a la Puerta de Cheonwangmun, el paraíso del Templo de Muyongsa, la Pagoda de cinco pisos y más allá se encuentran en el marco cuadrado de Cheonwangmun. Ángulo demasiado estable. Incluso si no te especializas en fotografía, puedes levantar la cámara naturalmente. Pero el diseñador que diseñó esta impresionante vista no expuso el 100% del paraíso, el corazón del templo. El techo del paraíso estaba ligeramente cubierto con ramas de pino y zelkova. Me senté y estuve tratando de tomar una foto para evitar las ramas. Queda 1 minuto? Ah! Date cuenta de que era una maravillosa pieza de cilantro para cubrir la morada del Buda. ¿No habría sido genial ver esa rama a través del paraíso? Más bien, las ramas de los árboles se suman al paraíso secreto del paraíso.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Vista del paraíso desde el Cheonwangmun - Condado de Buyeo, Chungnam, Corea del Sur (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/02b188aa-0cf4-4f56-adba-8b2b37f8d365.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Vista del paraíso desde el Cheonwangmun
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Acercarse lentamente al paraíso. Cuando llegas al pino que cubría el techo, puedes ver las linternas de piedra, la pagoda de cinco pisos y el paraíso. Las linternas de piedra, la pagoda de cinco pisos y el paraíso de Muryuksa son tesoros nacionales. Puede parecer que es un activo cultural, pero la historia de los activos culturales llenos de signos y el conocimiento de la historia del arte no parecen ayudar este otoño. Así que no voy en detalle deliberadamente. El polvo del conocimiento en mi cabeza parece asentarse en la superficie de la emoción pegajosa. Solo mira los tres tesoros a distancia. Desde una perspectiva amplia, la mirada que se originó en el suelo genera una sensación de ascenso a través de las linternas de piedra y la parte superior de la pagoda, que conduce a la cresta del paraíso. Además, quinientos mil años de historia, sin daños y daños serios, agrega dignidad.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Estado y sede de la majestuosa guerra del paraíso - Condado de Buyeo, Chungnam, Corea del Sur (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/ef01d9af-0a62-4f68-9e2d-552a072a2617.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Estado y sede de la majestuosa guerra del paraíso
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Mira la ronda del paraíso de izquierda a derecha. Los botes de los pilares que sostienen la estructura excéntrica del paraíso son extraordinariamente abultados. Es una columna comúnmente llamada shedding. El exterior parece dos pisos, pero el interior del paraíso es una estructura en capas sin capas. Se puede ver que esta estructura no es para el uso real del segundo piso, sino para la formalidad y dignidad del edificio.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Pilar de lápida - Condado de Buyeo, Chungnam, Corea del Sur (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/67f1e89f-86dc-47a2-bc0f-d1a6b169aece.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Pilar de lápida
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Dé la vuelta al paraíso paradisíaco y párese debajo del árbol de arce frente a la cerca en el lado derecho del edificio. Es buena suerte venir a la última tarde de artes marciales. El sol ha comenzado a dirigirse al oeste de Mansusan, y el cálido sol de la tarde de otoño cubre abundantemente el terreno. Debajo del árbol de arce, la luz de fondo está cubierta con hojas de arce y se abre el obturador. No está mal decir &#39;tomar fotos con los pies&#39;. Tan pronto como el monje pasa.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;13&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Los terrenos del templo de artes marciales desde la derecha - Condado de Buyeo, Chungnam, Corea del Sur (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/0e2cb43e-59b9-4c6e-b10e-8592536501cb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Los terrenos del templo de artes marciales desde la derecha
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Kim Si-sook, un escritor de genio pobre o dueño de un alma libre
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Hay una persona que debes conocer en el Templo Muryangsa. Kim Si-seon (1435 ~ 1493) es un líder mensual que siempre se presenta con apodos como Pung Un Ah, autor genio y Shin Dong. Pase el paraíso y cruce el pequeño arroyo a la izquierda para ver el retrato de Kim Si-seop en Yeongjeonggak. Kim Si-sook no reconoció la toma del trono y vivió como monje y esposa para siempre. Dejó el mundo a los 21 años y vagó por todo el país.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Echemos un vistazo al retrato de Kim Jung-shik. Yeongjung difiere de la intensa discordia del color primario que se encuentra comúnmente en los versos. También es diferente del retrato del Escuadrón Joseon que se vistió muy bien en Gwanbok. Kim Si-seop en las manos de Yeongjung se mantiene cuidadosamente en la manga, pero frunce el ceño con el ceño fruncido. Es por eso que muchos críticos dicen que han capturado las características de los intelectuales insatisfechos que no están satisfechos con el mundo. Puedes ver eso. A los veintiún años de edad, cuando el Rey Sejo llegó al trono, quemó todos los libros que había leído y dejó el mundo y se convirtió en monje. Sin embargo, la vida de Kim no está llena de mala suerte, acaparamiento y críticas a la sociedad.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   Dejó el mundo y recorrió Kanto y Hunan, disfrutando del paisaje y escribiendo poemas. En sus treinta años, pasó seis años en Gyeongju Geumosan, el actual Gyeongju Namsan, dedicado a su trabajo. El resultado de la inmersión es Kum-O Myth, considerada la primera novela china de Corea. ¿Era Kim Si-sook un genio pobre que se enfrentaba mal a los tiempos? ¿O era el dueño de un alma libre? Eventualmente, ve su deambular como una alienación del poder y la corriente principal o una voluntad de vida libre. Doy una pequeña pista a ese problema no fácil. Kim Si-seop escribe el motivo de deambular en el prefacio de `` Every Month House &#39;&#39;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Young Si Kim - Condado de Buyeo, Chungnam, Corea del Sur (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/db703360-cf34-443e-989c-e887c38d15e9.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Young Si Kim
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;font color=&#34;#367100&#34;&gt;
    &#34;Yo ... Para pasear por las montañas y encontrar una buena vista, me jactaría de mis amigos para disfrutar el poema, pero no pensé en llegar al cargo con una oración. Es una pena que un día, después de ser abrumado (la usurpación del trono) por un hombre, un hombre puede nacer en este mundo y caminar en el camino &#34;.
   &lt;/font&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Un monje está barriendo hojas - Condado de Buyeo, Chungnam, Corea del Sur (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/c8dc4b05-d3fc-4362-b7aa-4d88cfe56a97.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Un monje está barriendo hojas
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   El camino de la luz, el camino a Taejoam
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Después de explorar los jardines, regresa una semana para una caminata más profunda en otoño.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;1.2 km del Templo Mouyangsa a Taejoam - Condado de Buyeo, Chungnam, Corea del Sur (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/3834472d-88b3-400f-8857-b1cfe1526199.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     1.2 km del Templo Mouyangsa a Taejoam
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Antes de llegar a la orden, se fue a Taejoam y Dosolam a la izquierda. Un área abierta conduce a un camino bien pavimentado a la izquierda. El camino dura 1,2 km hasta la roca Taejo.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;El camino de entrada a Taejoam es una buena manera de caminar. - Condado de Buyeo, Chungnam, Corea del Sur (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/07b01060-3850-4036-91de-ada290ad79d7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     El camino de entrada a Taejoam es una buena manera de caminar.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Poco después de entrar a la calle, hay un antiguo sitio de artes marciales a su izquierda.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Banco camino a Taejoam - Condado de Buyeo, Chungnam, Corea del Sur (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/d063e688-3a31-4265-851a-c4f1ea083213.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Banco camino a Taejoam
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Ahora está cubierto de hierba de pampa, malezas y arbustos, pero las excavaciones en 2000 confirmaron el podio, la lápida y la prestigiosa bandera estampada con &#34;Muyangsa&#34;.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Antiguo sitio de artes marciales - Condado de Buyeo, Chungnam, Corea del Sur (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/8af3da53-f771-4615-ae11-f33d3822bf57.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Antiguo sitio de artes marciales
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Yendo de nuevo de nuevo Pasa inmediatamente por Dosolam y llega a Taejoam. Solo dos inodoros y bancos se colocan escasamente en el camino a Taejoam. No hay urracas en este camino, pero solo los caquis rojos se cuelgan en los árboles de caqui que se han quedado sin hojas. Es una forma elegante pero sencilla de dar un paseo tranquilo. Al pasar el jardín a la derecha de Taejoam comienza la ruta de senderismo a gran escala. Si planea escalar la montaña Mansu, puede escalar a lo largo del sendero Taejoam.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Mansusan Mountain Trail comienza en Taejoam - Condado de Buyeo, Chungnam, Corea del Sur (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/1765c925-3dfb-4c35-9071-6d2f43308c1b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Mansusan Mountain Trail comienza en Taejoam
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Sal de Taejoam y abandona el templo por completo. Hay una cosa más que ver antes de ir al estacionamiento. Para el visitante que quiere irse, Muryangsa presenta la bancarrota de Kim Si-sook. El hecho de que haya mucho budismo, las tumbas donde están enterrados los monjes budistas, significa que han producido muchos monjes.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;13&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Budo-pistola del templo Murangsa - Condado de Buyeo, Chungnam, Corea del Sur (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/89fe1dbc-3e46-481a-b086-843a3ea86cae.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Budo-pistola del templo Murangsa
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Muryangsa Budo-gun está en camino a Mujinam. De todos los incumplimientos, la bancarrota de Kim Si-sook es la más alta. Tanto el tamaño como la apariencia son los más completos. El valor predeterminado de Kim Si-sook es una base doble. El patrón del dragón es vívido en la superficie de la piedra del vestido del segundo podio (piedra mediana), que está decorada con una flor de loto. Es muy bueno para las reliquias de piedra de Chosun Electric.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;15&#34; id3=&#34;15&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Quiebra de Kim Si-sook - Condado de Buyeo, Chungnam, Corea del Sur (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/2e38fdd9-f508-4669-bc00-df4dc988ba76.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Quiebra de Kim Si-sook
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Entonces, ¿hay realmente una sari Kim Si-suri aquí? Durante el período colonial japonés, el tifón barrió y los árboles circundantes cayeron. En ese momento, el Budo también se derrumbó y se encontró el sari de Kim Si-sook. El sari de Kim se encuentra actualmente en exhibición en el Museo Nacional de Buyeo.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;17&#34; id3=&#34;16&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Patrón de dragón de piedra media de Kim Si-seop Budo - Condado de Buyeo, Chungnam, Corea del Sur (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/3e13f9fe-55c2-4d47-809c-7833fbb11c87.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Patrón de dragón de piedra media de Kim Si-seop Budo
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Información de viaje
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;span style=&#34;color: rgb(33, 33, 33);&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong style=&#34;&#34;&gt;
      Artes marciales
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Dirección: 203, Muryang-ro, Oesan-myeon, Buyeo-gun, Chungnam
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Consultas: Oficina Muryangsa 041-836-5066
    &lt;/span&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://tour.buyeo.go.kr/html/tour/info/info_010108.html&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://tour.buyeo.go.kr/html/tour/info/info_010108.html
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Restaurantes cercanos
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Casa de Baekje: Yeonleaf Rice, Mabab / 22, Heukcheon-ro 8beon-gil, Buyeo-eup, Buyeo-gun / 041-834-1212
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Jangwon Makguksu: Makguksu / 20, Narutero 62beon-gil, Buyeo-eup, Buyeo-gun / 041-835-6561
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Gudraedol Ssambap: Dol Sambap / 31, Narut-ro, Buyeo-eup, Buyeo-gun / 041-836-9259
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Alojamiento
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Lotte Resort Buyeo: 400 Baekjemun-ro, Gyuam-myeon, Buyeo-gun / 041-939-1000
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.lottebuyeoresort.com/kor/index.asp&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.lottebuyeoresort.com/kor/index.asp
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Baekje Tourist Hotel: 108 Bukpo-ro, Buyeo-eup, Buyeo-gun / 041-835-0870
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://백제관광호텔.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://백제관광호텔.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Samjung Yeo Youth Hostel: 50 Narut-ro, Buyeo-eup, Buyeo-gun / 041-835-3101
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.buyeoyh.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.buyeoyh.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34; style=&#34;font-weight: bold;&#34;&gt;
     ※ La información anterior se actualizó en septiembre de 2017 y puede cambiar después. Por favor verifique antes de viajar.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ La información como texto, fotos y videos utilizados en este artículo tiene copyright de la Organización de Turismo de Corea, por lo que está prohibido el uso no autorizado del artículo.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buyeo County, Chungnam, Südkorea - Wo kann man nach Herbstlaub fragen, der besten Jahreszeit?</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/where-to-ask-for-autumn-leaves-the-best-season-73-de/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 19:08:01 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/where-to-ask-for-autumn-leaves-the-best-season-73-de/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Buyeo County, Chungnam, South Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;where-to-ask-for-autumn-leaves-the-best-season--73&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Helle Kampfsportstätten im Herbst - Buyeo County, Chungnam, Südkorea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/58937cfd-a1a2-47c6-9a4b-d211eec767b1.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Helle Kampfsportstätten im Herbst
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Wo kann man nach Herbstlaub fragen, der besten Jahreszeit?
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Buyeo County, Chungnam, Südkorea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Um das Ende des Sturzes zu erreichen, begrub er die toten Krieger, um die letzte Staffel zu begraben. Yun Dae-nyeong, der den Roman schrieb, nannte Muryangsa „das Jangji (Jahreszeit), in der die Jahreszeiten sinken“. Wenn die Blätter ausgehen, erinnert es an die Traurigkeit eines Jahres. Die Bitterkeit des Herbstes, die häufiger als Gold ist, wird jedoch sofort verschluckt. Können wir nach der Jahreszeit fragen, die von Buyeo Muryangsa vergangen ist, in der Kim Si-ryong, der Windglücks- und Genie-Dichter von Joseon, seine letzten Jahre verbracht hat? .
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Koriander
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Dieser gebissene Herbst geht in einem Monat nach Buyeo, weil die Blätter früh fallen. Glücklicherweise haben die Kampfkünste den Sturz noch nicht vollständig fallen lassen. Im letzten Sommer gibt es noch viel Energie. Das Durchlaufen der Kasse ist eine Bestellung in Kürze. Auf der Stirn eines Ordens befindet sich eine große Tafel namens &#39;Mansusan Muralosa&#39;. Es ist eine harmonische Kombination aus &#34;Unquantity&#34;, was &#34;unermesslich&#34; bedeutet, und dem Namen des Berges &#34;Mansu&#34;, was bedeutet, ein langes Leben zu genießen. Der Muryangsa-Tempel ist ein tausendjähriger Tempel, der während des Königs Munseong King (Vereinigung 839 ~ 857) gegründet wurde. Wie die meisten Tempel und architektonischen Kulturgüter in Korea verschwanden jedoch alle Kampfkünste während des Imjin-Krieges, wurden jedoch 1623 (Art. 1) wieder aufgebaut, um bis heute zu erreichen.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Eine Bestellung - Buyeo County, Chungnam, Südkorea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/3a1d7526-7d10-4029-bfd6-affc28fccf4f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Eine Bestellung
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Auf dem Weg durch ein kleines Tal und bis zum Cheonwangmun-Tor begrüßt ein hübscher Partyinhaber die Besucher auf der rechten Seite. Das Festhalten der Partei bedeutet eine längliche Stange, an der die Flagge des Tempels aufgehängt ist, oder einen Haltesitz, der die Partei von links nach rechts stützt. Dies ist ein Zeichen dafür, dass das Gelände des Tempels hier beginnt.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Mugi Corp. - Buyeo County, Chungnam, Südkorea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/2c5651cf-35af-4569-a629-22642c259afa.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Mugi Corp.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Der Aufstieg zum Cheonwangmun-Tor, dem Paradies des Muyongsa-Tempels, der fünfstöckigen Pagode und darüber hinaus befindet sich im quadratischen Rahmen von Cheonwangmun. Zu stabiler Winkel. Auch wenn Sie sich nicht auf Fotografie spezialisiert haben, können Sie die Kamera natürlich anheben. Aber der Designer, der diese atemberaubende Aussicht entworfen hat, hat das Paradies, das Herz des Tempels, nicht zu 100% freigelegt. Das Paradiesdach war leicht mit Kiefern- und Zelkova-Zweigen bedeckt. Ich saß und stand und versuchte ein Foto zu machen, um den Ästen auszuweichen. Noch 1 Minute? Ah! Erkenne, dass es ein wunderbares Stück Koriander war, den Wohnort des Buddha zu bedecken. Wäre es nicht cool gewesen, diesen Zweig durch das Paradies zu sehen? Vielmehr tragen die Äste zum geheimen Paradies des Paradieses bei.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Paradiesblick vom Cheonwangmun - Buyeo County, Chungnam, Südkorea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/02b188aa-0cf4-4f56-adba-8b2b37f8d365.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Paradiesblick vom Cheonwangmun
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Nähere dich langsam dem Paradies. Wenn Sie die Kiefer erreichen, die das Dach bedeckte, können Sie die Steinlaternen, die fünfstöckige Pagode und das Paradies sehen. Die Steinlaternen, die fünfstöckige Pagode und das Paradies von Muryuksa sind allesamt nationale Schätze. Es mag scheinen, als wäre es ein Kulturgut, aber die Geschichte der mit Zeichen gefüllten Kulturgüter und das Wissen der Kunstgeschichte scheinen diesen Herbst nicht zu helfen. Ich gehe also nicht absichtlich ins Detail. Der Staub des Wissens in meinem Kopf scheint auf der Oberfläche der klebrigen Emotionen zu sitzen. Schauen Sie sich die drei Schätze aus der Ferne an. Aus einer großen Perspektive weckt der Blick, der vom Boden ausgeht, ein Gefühl des Aufstiegs durch die Steinlaternen und die Spitze der Pagode, die zum Paradieskamm führt. Darüber hinaus trägt eine fünfhunderttausendjährige Geschichte ohne ernsthaften Schaden und Schaden zur Würde bei.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Staat und Sitz des majestätischen Paradieskrieges - Buyeo County, Chungnam, Südkorea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/ef01d9af-0a62-4f68-9e2d-552a072a2617.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Staat und Sitz des majestätischen Paradieskrieges
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Beobachten Sie das Paradies von links nach rechts. Die Boote der Säulen, die die exzentrische Struktur des Paradieses tragen, sind außerordentlich prall. Es ist eine allgemein als Schuppensäule bezeichnete Säule. Das Äußere sieht aus wie zwei Stockwerke, aber das Innere des Paradieses ist eine geschichtete Struktur ohne Schichten. Es ist ersichtlich, dass diese Struktur nicht für die tatsächliche Nutzung des zweiten Stockwerks bestimmt ist, sondern für die Formalität und Würde des Gebäudes.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Grabstein-Säule - Buyeo County, Chungnam, Südkorea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/67f1e89f-86dc-47a2-bc0f-d1a6b169aece.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Grabstein-Säule
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Drehen Sie sich um den paradiesischen Hinterhof und stellen Sie sich unter den Ahornbaum vor den Zaun auf der rechten Seite des Gebäudes. Es ist ein Glück, zum letzten Kampfkunstnachmittag zu kommen. Die Sonne hat begonnen, westlich von Mansusan zu gehen, und die warme Herbstnachmittagssonne bedeckt das Gelände reichlich. Unter dem Ahornbaum ist die Hintergrundbeleuchtung mit Ahornblättern bedeckt und der Verschluss wird ausgelöst. Es ist nicht falsch zu sagen, &#34;mache Fotos mit deinen Füßen&#34;. Sobald der Mönch vorbeikommt.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;13&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Das Gelände des Kampfsporttempels von rechts - Buyeo County, Chungnam, Südkorea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/0e2cb43e-59b9-4c6e-b10e-8592536501cb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Das Gelände des Kampfsporttempels von rechts
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Kim Si-sook, ein armer genialer Schriftsteller oder Besitzer einer freien Seele
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Es gibt eine Person, die Sie im Muryangsa-Tempel treffen müssen. Kim Si-seon (1435 ~ 1493) ist ein monatlicher Anführer, dem immer Spitznamen wie Pung Un Ah, genialer Autor, und Shin Dong vorgestellt werden. Fahren Sie am Paradies vorbei und überqueren Sie den kleinen Bach links, um das Porträt von Kim Si-seop in Yeongjeonggak zu sehen. Kim Si-sook erkannte die Thronbesteigung nicht und lebte für immer als Mönch und Ehefrau. Mit 21 Jahren verließ er die Welt und wanderte durch das ganze Land.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Schauen wir uns das Porträt von Kim Jung-shik an. Yeongjung unterscheidet sich von der intensiven Zwietracht in der Primärfarbe, die häufig in Versen vorkommt. Es unterscheidet sich auch von dem Porträt der Joseon-Staffel, die sich gut in Gwanbok gekleidet hat. Kim Si-seop in Yeongjungs Händen wird ordentlich im Ärmel gehalten, aber er runzelt die Stirn mit gerunzelter Stirn. Deshalb sagen viele Kritiker, dass sie die Merkmale unzufriedener Intellektueller erfasst haben, die mit der Welt unzufrieden sind. Sie können sehen, dass. Mit einundzwanzig Jahren, als König Sejo auf den Thron kam, verbrannte er alle Bücher, die er gelesen hatte, und verließ die Welt und wurde Mönch. Kims Leben ist jedoch nicht voller Pech, Horten und Kritik an der Gesellschaft.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   Er verließ die Welt und tourte durch Kanto und Hunan, genoss die Landschaft und schrieb Gedichte. In seinen Dreißigern verbrachte er sechs Jahre in Gyeongju Geumosan, dem heutigen Gyeongju Namsan, der sich seiner Arbeit widmete. Das Ergebnis des Eintauchens ist Kum-O Mythos, der als Koreas erster chinesischer Roman gilt. War Kim Si-sook ein armes Genie, das die Zeiten falsch getroffen hat? Oder war er der Besitzer einer freien Seele? Schließlich sieht er sein Wandern als Entfremdung von Macht und Mainstream oder als Willen des freien Lebens. Ich gebe einen kleinen Hinweis auf dieses nicht einfache Problem. Kim Si-seop schreibt das Motiv des Wanderns im Vorwort von &#34;Every Month House&#34;.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Der junge Si Kim - Buyeo County, Chungnam, Südkorea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/db703360-cf34-443e-989c-e887c38d15e9.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Der junge Si Kim
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;font color=&#34;#367100&#34;&gt;
    &#34;Ich ... Um durch die Berge zu wandern und eine gute Aussicht zu finden, würde ich mich meiner Freunde rühmen, das Gedicht zu genießen, aber ich dachte nicht daran, mit einem Satz ins Amt zu kommen. Es ist eine Schande, dass eines Tages danach Wenn ein Mann von einem Mann überwältigt wird (die Usurpation des Throns), kann er in dieser Welt geboren werden und auf der Straße gehen. &#34;
   &lt;/font&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Ein Mönch fegt Blätter - Buyeo County, Chungnam, Südkorea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/c8dc4b05-d3fc-4362-b7aa-4d88cfe56a97.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Ein Mönch fegt Blätter
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Der leichte Weg, der Weg nach Taejoam
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Nach der Erkundung des Geländes können Sie eine Woche lang einen tieferen Herbstspaziergang unternehmen.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;1,2 km vom Mouyangsa-Tempel nach Taejoam - Buyeo County, Chungnam, Südkorea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/3834472d-88b3-400f-8857-b1cfe1526199.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     1,2 km vom Mouyangsa-Tempel nach Taejoam
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Bevor Sie den Befehl erreichen, fahren Sie links nach Taejoam und Dosolam nach links. Ein weitläufiger offener Bereich führt zu einer gut asphaltierten Straße auf der linken Seite. Die Straße dauert 1,2 km bis zum Taejo Rock.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Die Auffahrt nach Taejoam ist ein guter Weg zu Fuß. - Buyeo County, Chungnam, Südkorea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/07b01060-3850-4036-91de-ada290ad79d7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Die Auffahrt nach Taejoam ist ein guter Weg zu Fuß.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Kurz nach dem Betreten der Straße befindet sich zu Ihrer Linken eine alte Kampfkunststätte.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Bank auf dem Weg nach Taejoam - Buyeo County, Chungnam, Südkorea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/d063e688-3a31-4265-851a-c4f1ea083213.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Bank auf dem Weg nach Taejoam
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Es ist jetzt mit Pampasgras, Unkraut und Sträuchern bedeckt, aber Ausgrabungen im Jahr 2000 bestätigten das Podium, den Grabstein und die prestigeträchtige Flagge mit dem Stempel „Muyangsa“.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Alte Kampfkunststätte - Buyeo County, Chungnam, Südkorea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/8af3da53-f771-4615-ae11-f33d3822bf57.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Alte Kampfkunststätte
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Wieder auf dem Weg Es geht sofort durch Dosolam und erreicht Taejoam. Nur zwei Toiletten und Bänke sind auf dem Weg nach Taejoam spärlich aufgestellt. Auf dieser Straße gibt es keine Elstern, aber nur rote Kakis hängen an Kakibäumen, denen die Blätter ausgegangen sind. Es ist eine elegante, aber einfache Möglichkeit, einen ruhigen Spaziergang zu machen. Vorbei am Garten rechts von Taejoam beginnt der Wanderweg in Originalgröße. Wenn Sie den Mansu-Berg besteigen möchten, können Sie den Taejoam Trail entlang klettern.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Der Mansusan Mountain Trail beginnt in Taejoam - Buyeo County, Chungnam, Südkorea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/1765c925-3dfb-4c35-9071-6d2f43308c1b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Der Mansusan Mountain Trail beginnt in Taejoam
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Verlasse Taejoam und verlasse den Tempel vollständig. Bevor Sie zum Parkplatz gehen, müssen Sie noch etwas sehen. Dem Besucher, der gehen will, präsentiert Muryangsa die Insolvenz von Kim Si-sook. Die Tatsache, dass es viel Buddhismus gibt, die Gräber, in denen buddhistische Mönche begraben sind, bedeutet, dass sie viele Mönche hervorgebracht haben.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;13&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Murangsa Tempel Budo-Pistole - Buyeo County, Chungnam, Südkorea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/89fe1dbc-3e46-481a-b086-843a3ea86cae.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Murangsa Tempel Budo-Pistole
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Muryangsa Budo-gun ist auf dem Weg nach Mujinam. Von allen Standardeinstellungen ist die Insolvenz von Kim Si-sook die höchste. Sowohl Größe als auch Aussehen sind am vollständigsten. Die Standardeinstellung von Kim Si-sook ist eine doppelte Basis. Das Drachenmuster ist auf der Oberfläche des Kleidersteins des zweiten Podiums (mittlerer Stein), der mit einer Lotusblume verziert ist, lebendig. Es ist sehr gut für die Steinrelikte von Chosun Electric.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;15&#34; id3=&#34;15&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Insolvenz von Kim Si-sook - Buyeo County, Chungnam, Südkorea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/2e38fdd9-f508-4669-bc00-df4dc988ba76.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Insolvenz von Kim Si-sook
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Gibt es hier wirklich einen Kim Si-suri Saree? Während der japanischen Kolonialzeit fegte der Taifun weg und die umliegenden Bäume fielen. Zu dieser Zeit war auch der Budo zusammengebrochen und der Sari von Kim Si-sook wurde gefunden. Kims Sari ist derzeit im National Buyeo Museum ausgestellt.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;17&#34; id3=&#34;16&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Drachenmuster von Kim Si-seop Budo Mittelstein - Buyeo County, Chungnam, Südkorea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/3e13f9fe-55c2-4d47-809c-7833fbb11c87.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Drachenmuster von Kim Si-seop Budo Mittelstein
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Reiseinformationen
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;span style=&#34;color: rgb(33, 33, 33);&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong style=&#34;&#34;&gt;
      Kampfkunst
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Adresse: 203, Muryang-ro, Oesan-myeon, Buyeo-gun, Chungnam
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Anfragen: Muryangsa Office 041-836-5066
    &lt;/span&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://tour.buyeo.go.kr/html/tour/info/info_010108.html&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://tour.buyeo.go.kr/html/tour/info/info_010108.html
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Restaurants in der Nähe
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Baekjes Haus: Yeonleaf Rice, Mabab / 22, Heukcheon-ro 8beon-gil, Buyeo-eup, Buyeo-gun / 041-834-1212
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Jangwon Makguksu: Makguksu / 20, Narutero 62beon-gil, Buyeo-eup, Buyeo-gun / 041-835-6561
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Gudraedol Ssambap: Dol Sambap / 31, Narut-ro, Buyeo-eup, Buyeo-gun / 041-836-9259
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Unterkunft
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Lotte Resort Buyeo: 400 Baekjemun-ro, Gyuam-myeon, Buyeo-gun / 041-939-1000
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.lottebuyeoresort.com/kor/index.asp&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.lottebuyeoresort.com/kor/index.asp
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Baekje Tourist Hotel: 108 Bukpo-ro, Buyeo-eup, Buyeo-gun / 041-835-0870
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://백제관광호텔.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://백제관광호텔.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Samjung Yeo Jugendherberge: 50 Narut-ro, Buyeo-eup, Buyeo-gun / 041-835-3101
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.buyeoyh.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.buyeoyh.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34; style=&#34;font-weight: bold;&#34;&gt;
     ※ Die oben genannten Informationen wurden im September 2017 aktualisiert und können sich danach ändern. Bitte überprüfen Sie vor Reiseantritt.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Die in diesem Artikel verwendeten Informationen wie Text, Fotos und Videos sind von der Korea Tourism Organization urheberrechtlich geschützt. Daher ist die unbefugte Verwendung des Artikels untersagt.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>韩国忠南市扶余县 - 哪里要求秋叶，最好的季节</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/where-to-ask-for-autumn-leaves-the-best-season-73-zh-cn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 19:04:55 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/where-to-ask-for-autumn-leaves-the-best-season-73-zh-cn/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Buyeo County, Chungnam, South Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;where-to-ask-for-autumn-leaves-the-best-season--73&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;在秋天的明亮武术场 - 韩国忠南市扶余县 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/58937cfd-a1a2-47c6-9a4b-d211eec767b1.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    在秋天的明亮武术场
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   哪里要求秋叶，最好的季节
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    韩国忠南市扶余县
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   为了赶上秋天的结束，他埋葬了死去的战士以埋葬上个赛季。 写这本书的尹大宁称“ Muryangsa”为“四季消沉的季节”。 当树叶枯竭时，让人想起一年的悲伤。 但是，比黄金更丰富的秋天的苦味立刻被吞没了。 我们能问一下朝鲜扶桑风水诗人，天才诗人金时龙在扶余Muryangsa经历的那个季节吗？ 。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   香菜
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   这个秋天已经被咬了，秋天不到一个月就到了扶余，因为树叶早落了。 幸运的是，武术还没有完全消失。 去年夏天仍然有很多精力。 通过售票处很快是一个订单。 一个订单的额头上有一块大木板，叫做“ Mansusan Muralosa”。 它是“数量”（意味不可估量）和山的名字“ Mansu”（这意味着享受长寿）的和谐组合。 Muryangsa庙是千年的庙宇，建于文成王（统一839〜857）期间。 但是，像韩国的大多数寺庙和建筑文化资产一样，在临津战争期间所有武术都消失了，但在1623年（第1条）进行了重建，直至今天。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;一单 - 韩国忠南市扶余县 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/3a1d7526-7d10-4029-bfd6-affc28fccf4f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     一单
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   一个英俊的宴会聚会者穿过一个小山谷到达天王门，欢迎右边的游客。 宴会举行是指细长的杆子，上面挂着庙宇的旗帜，或者是一个从左到右支撑宴会的座位。 这标志着圣殿从这里开始。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Mugi Corp - 韩国忠南市扶余县 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/2c5651cf-35af-4569-a629-22642c259afa.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Mugi Corp
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   在天王门的方形框架中，上升到天王门，木用寺的天堂，五层宝塔和更远的地方。 角度太稳定。 即使您不擅长摄影，也可以自然地抬起相机。 但是，设计出这种令人惊叹的景观的设计师并没有暴露出天堂的100％，即圣殿的心脏。 天堂的屋顶上覆盖着松树和榉树的树枝。 我坐着站着拍照，以避开树枝。 还剩1分钟？ 啊! 意识到覆盖住佛陀的住所真是个绝妙的香菜。 透过天堂看那个分支会不会很酷？ 而是，树枝增加了天堂的秘密天堂。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;天王门的天堂景 - 韩国忠南市扶余县 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/02b188aa-0cf4-4f56-adba-8b2b37f8d365.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     天王门的天堂景
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   慢慢进入天堂。 当您到达覆盖屋顶的松树时，您会看到石灯笼，五层宝塔和天堂。 石灯笼，五层宝塔和穆留沙的天堂都是国宝。 看起来它似乎是一种文化资产，但是这个充满标志的文化资产的历史和对艺术史的了解似乎对今年秋天没有帮助。 因此，我没有刻意详细介绍。 我脑海中的知识尘埃似乎停留在粘滞的情绪上。 远看三处宝藏。 从大角度看，源自地面的凝视通过石灯笼和宝塔顶部提升了升华感，通往天堂的山脊。 此外，五十一千年的历史没有造成严重的破坏和破坏，却增添了尊严。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;雄伟的天堂之州和所在地 - 韩国忠南市扶余县 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/ef01d9af-0a62-4f68-9e2d-552a072a2617.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     雄伟的天堂之州和所在地
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   从左到右观看天堂。 支撑天堂的偏心结构的支柱船异常鼓鼓。 它通常被称为脱落柱。 外观看起来像两层楼，但是天堂的内部是一个没有层的分层结构。 可以看出，这种结构不是为二层的实际使用，而是为建筑的形式和尊严。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;墓碑柱 - 韩国忠南市扶余县 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/67f1e89f-86dc-47a2-bc0f-d1a6b169aece.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     墓碑柱
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   转过天堂后院，站在建筑物右侧栅栏前面的枫树下。 到最后一个武术下午很幸运。 太阳已经开始向曼苏珊（Mansusan）的西侧移动，温暖的秋天午后的阳光充足地覆盖了地面。 在枫树下，背光灯被枫叶覆盖，并释放快门。 说“用脚拍照”是没有错的。 和尚一路过。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;13&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;右边的武术神庙的理由 - 韩国忠南市扶余县 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/0e2cb43e-59b9-4c6e-b10e-8592536501cb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     右边的武术神庙的理由
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   金思淑（Kim Si-sook），可怜的天才作家或自由灵魂的拥有者
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   您必须在Muryangsa Temple遇到一个人。 金时善（1435〜1493）是每月的领导人，总是被昵称为天才作家Pung Un Ah和Shin Dong。 穿过天堂，越过小溪向左看，就可以看到荣正阁的金石se肖像。 金时淑不承认王位被夺取，并永远作为僧侣和妻子生活。 他在21岁时离开了世界，在全国各地徘徊。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   让我们看一下金正植的画像。 永宗不同于经文中常见的强烈原色不和谐。 它也不同于在光复穿得好看的朝鲜中队的肖像。 永宗手中的金思se被整齐地放在袖子里，但他皱着眉头皱着眉头。 这就是为什么许多评论家说他们抓住了不满世界的不满知识分子的特征的原因。 您可以看到。 二十岁时，世祖国王登基，他烧毁了所有读过的书，离开了世界，成为了和尚。 但是，金正日的生活充满了不幸、,积和对社会的批评。
   &lt;br/&gt;
   他离开了世界，游览了关东和湖南，欣赏风景和写诗。 三十岁时，他在现为庆州南山的庆州九三山工作了六年。 沉浸的结果是《 Kum-O Myth》，这是韩国第一部中国小说。 金时淑是个可怜的天才，错误地相遇了吗？ 还是他是自由灵魂的主人？ 最终，他认为自己的徘徊是对权力和主流的疏离，或者对自由生活的渴望。 我给这个不容易的问题提供了一个小提示。 金思se（Kim Si-seop）在``每个月的房子&#39;&#39;的序言中写道流浪的动机
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;杨思金 - 韩国忠南市扶余县 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/db703360-cf34-443e-989c-e887c38d15e9.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     杨思金
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;font color=&#34;#367100&#34;&gt;
    “我……为了在山间漫步并欣赏美景，我会吹嘘我的朋友们喜欢这首诗，但我没想到要一句话就职。那天过后 一个男人被一个男人淹没（篡夺王位），他可以在这个世界上出生并走在路上。”
   &lt;/font&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;和尚正在扫树叶 - 韩国忠南市扶余县 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/c8dc4b05-d3fc-4362-b7aa-4d88cfe56a97.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     和尚正在扫树叶
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   灯火通明
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   在探究了理由之后，回头一周进行更深的秋季散步。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;从牟阳寺到太祖寺1.2公里 - 韩国忠南市扶余县 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/3834472d-88b3-400f-8857-b1cfe1526199.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     从牟阳寺到太祖寺1.2公里
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   在到达订单之前，先左移至Taejoam，然后向左移至Dosolam。 宽阔的开放区域可通往左侧的铺砌好的道路。 这条路到Taejo Rock的路程为1.2公里。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;进入Taejoam的车道是步行的好方法。 - 韩国忠南市扶余县 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/07b01060-3850-4036-91de-ada290ad79d7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     进入Taejoam的车道是步行的好方法。
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   进入街道后不久，您的左侧便是一个古老的武术场所。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;在通向跆拳道的路上 - 韩国忠南市扶余县 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/d063e688-3a31-4265-851a-c4f1ea083213.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     在通向跆拳道的路上
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   现在，这里布满了南美大草原草，杂草和灌木丛，但在2000年的发掘中证实了登上领奖台，墓碑和带有“ Muyangsa”字样的著名国旗。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;老武术网站 - 韩国忠南市扶余县 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/8af3da53-f771-4615-ae11-f33d3822bf57.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     老武术网站
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   再次行进它立即经过Dosolam到达Taejoam。 在去Taejoam的路上，只有两个厕所和长凳稀疏放置。 这条路上没有喜,，只有红色的柿子挂在树叶已经枯竭的柿子树上。 这是一种时尚却简单的安静散步方式。 经过Taejoam右侧的花园，即可开始全尺寸的远足径。 如果您打算攀登Mansu Mountain，可以沿着Taejoam Trail攀登。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;曼苏山登山步道始于太祖 - 韩国忠南市扶余县 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/1765c925-3dfb-4c35-9071-6d2f43308c1b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     曼苏山登山步道始于太祖
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   退出跆拳道，完全离开寺庙。 去停车场之前，还要看一件事。 对于想要离开的游客，Muryangsa提出了金思淑的破产申请。 佛教很多，而佛教僧侣被埋葬的坟墓这一事实，意味着他们产生了许多僧侣。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;13&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;室兰寺武道郡 - 韩国忠南市扶余县 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/89fe1dbc-3e46-481a-b086-843a3ea86cae.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     室兰寺武道郡
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Muryangsa Budo-gun正在前往Mujinam。 在所有违约中，金时淑的破产率最高。 尺寸和外观都最完整。 Kim Si-sook的默认设置是双重基准。 在第二个讲台上的长袍石（中号石头）的表面上形成了生动的龙图案，上面装饰着莲花。 朝鲜电气的石器非常好。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;15&#34; id3=&#34;15&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;金Si淑破产 - 韩国忠南市扶余县 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/2e38fdd9-f508-4669-bc00-df4dc988ba76.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     金Si淑破产
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   那么，这里真的有Kim Si-suri纱丽吗？ 在日本殖民时期，台风席卷而来，周围的树木倒下了。 那时，武道也倒塌了，金斯淑的纱丽被发现了。 金的纱丽目前在国家扶余博物馆展出。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;17&#34; id3=&#34;16&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;金世se武道中间石的龙纹 - 韩国忠南市扶余县 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/3e13f9fe-55c2-4d47-809c-7833fbb11c87.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     金世se武道中间石的龙纹
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   旅游信息
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;span style=&#34;color: rgb(33, 33, 33);&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong style=&#34;&#34;&gt;
      武术
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     地址：忠清南面扶余郡上山面村阳路203
     &lt;br/&gt;
     咨询处：室梁寺办事处041-836-5066
    &lt;/span&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://tour.buyeo.go.kr/html/tour/info/info_010108.html&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://tour.buyeo.go.kr/html/tour/info/info_010108.html
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1.附近的餐馆
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    百济故居：Yeonleaf Rice，Mabab / 22，扶余郡扶余邑鹤川路8beon-gil / 041-834-1212
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Jangwon Makguksu：Makguksu /扶余郡扶余邑纳鲁特罗62be-gil 20 / 041-835-6561
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Gudraedol Ssambap：Dol Sambap /扶余郡扶余邑纳鲁特路31号/ 041-836-9259
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2.住宿
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    扶余乐天渡假村：扶余郡久安面百济门路400号/ 041-939-1000
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.lottebuyeoresort.com/kor/index.asp&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.lottebuyeoresort.com/kor/index.asp
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    百济旅游饭店：扶余郡扶余邑北浦路108号/ 041-835-0870
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://백제관광호텔.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://백제관광호텔.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    三荣杨青年旅舍：扶余郡扶余邑纳鲁路50号/ 041-835-3101
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.buyeoyh.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.buyeoyh.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34; style=&#34;font-weight: bold;&#34;&gt;
     ※以上信息于2017年9月更新，之后可能更改。 请在旅行前检查。
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※本文中使用的文字，照片和视频等信息受韩国旅游组织版权保护，因此禁止未经授权使用本文。
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buyeo County, Chungnam, South Korea - Where to ask for autumn leaves, the best season</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/where-to-ask-for-autumn-leaves-the-best-season-73/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 19:01:46 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/where-to-ask-for-autumn-leaves-the-best-season-73/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Buyeo County, Chungnam, South Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;where-to-ask-for-autumn-leaves-the-best-season--73&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Bright martial arts grounds in autumn - Buyeo County, Chungnam, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/58937cfd-a1a2-47c6-9a4b-d211eec767b1.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Bright martial arts grounds in autumn
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Where to ask for autumn leaves, the best season
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Buyeo County, Chungnam, South Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   To catch the end of the fall, he buryed the dead warriors to bury the last season. Yun Dae-nyeong, who wrote the novel, called Muryangsa as “the jangji (season) where the seasons sink.” When the leaves run out, it will be reminiscent of the sadness of a year. However, the bitterness of autumn, which is more abundant than gold, is swallowed up at once. Can we ask about the season that passed from Buyeo Muryangsa where Kim Si-ryong, the wind luck and genius poet of Joseon, spent his last years? .
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Coriander
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   This fall, which has been bitten, goes to Buyeo in a month because the leaves are falling early. Fortunately, martial arts haven&#39;t completely dropped the fall yet. There&#39;s still a lot of energy last summer. Passing through the ticket office is one order soon. On the forehead of one order, there is a large board called &#39;Mansusan Muralosa&#39;. It is a harmonious combination of &#39;unquantity&#39;, meaning immeasurable, and the name of the mountain, &#39;Mansu,&#39; which means enjoying a long life. Muryangsa Temple is a millennial temple that was founded during King Munseong King (Unification 839 ~ 857). However, like most temples and architectural cultural assets in Korea, all martial arts disappeared during the Imjin War, but were rebuilt in 1623 (Art. 1) to reach today.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;One order - Buyeo County, Chungnam, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/3a1d7526-7d10-4029-bfd6-affc28fccf4f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     One order
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Passing through a small valley and reaching the Cheonwangmun gate, a handsome party holder welcomes visitors to the right. The party holding means an elongated pole that hung the flag of the temple, or a holding seat that supported the party from left to right. This is a sign that the grounds of the temple begin here.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Mugi Corp - Buyeo County, Chungnam, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/2c5651cf-35af-4569-a629-22642c259afa.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Mugi Corp
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Ascending to the Cheonwangmun Gate, the paradise of Muyongsa Temple, the Five-storied Pagoda, and beyond are in the square frame of Cheonwangmun. Too stable angle. Even if you don&#39;t specialize in photography, you can naturally lift the camera. But the designer who designed this stunning view did not expose 100% of the paradise, the heart of the temple. The paradise roof was slightly covered with pine and zelkova branches. I sat and stood trying to take a picture to avoid the branches. 1 minute left? Ah! Realize that it was a wonderful piece of coriander to cover the Buddha&#39;s dwelling place. Wouldn&#39;t that branch have been cool to see through the paradise? Rather, the tree branches add to the secret paradise of paradise.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Paradise view from the Cheonwangmun - Buyeo County, Chungnam, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/02b188aa-0cf4-4f56-adba-8b2b37f8d365.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Paradise view from the Cheonwangmun
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Slowly approach to paradise. When you reach the pine tree that covered the roof, you can see the stone lanterns, the five-storied pagoda, and the paradise. The stone lanterns, five-storied pagoda, and paradise of Muryuksa are all national treasures. It may seem as if it is a cultural asset, but the history of the cultural assets filled with signs and the knowledge of art history do not seem to help this autumn. So I don&#39;t deliberately go in detail. The dust of knowledge in my head seems to sit on the surface of the sticky emotion. Just look at the three treasures at a distance. From a large perspective, the gaze that originated from the ground raises a sense of ascension through the stone lanterns and the top of the pagoda, leading to the paradise ridge. In addition, five hundred and one thousand years of history, without serious damage and damage, adds dignity.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;State and seat of majestic paradise war - Buyeo County, Chungnam, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/ef01d9af-0a62-4f68-9e2d-552a072a2617.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     State and seat of majestic paradise war
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Watch the paradise round from left to right. The boats of the pillars supporting the eccentric structure of the paradise are extraordinarily bulging. It is a commonly called shedding column. The exterior looks like two floors, but the inside of the paradise is a layered structure with no layers. It can be seen that this structure is not for the actual use of the second floor, but for the formality and dignity of the building.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Tombstone Pillar - Buyeo County, Chungnam, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/67f1e89f-86dc-47a2-bc0f-d1a6b169aece.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Tombstone Pillar
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Turn around the paradise backyard and stand under the maple tree in front of the fence on the right side of the building. It&#39;s good luck to come to the last martial arts afternoon. The sun has started to head west of Mansusan, and the warm autumn afternoon sun plentifully covers the grounds. Under the maple tree, the backlight is covered with maple leaves and the shutter is released. It&#39;s not wrong to say &#39;take photos with your feet&#39;. As soon as the monk passes by.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;13&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The grounds of martial arts temple from the right - Buyeo County, Chungnam, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/0e2cb43e-59b9-4c6e-b10e-8592536501cb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The grounds of martial arts temple from the right
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Kim Si-sook, a poor genius writer or owner of a free soul
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   There is one person you must meet in Muryangsa Temple. Kim Si-seon (1435 ~ 1493) is a monthly leader who is always introduced with nicknames such as Pung Un Ah, genius author, and Shin Dong. Pass the paradise and cross the small stream to the left to see the portrait of Kim Si-seop in Yeongjeonggak. Kim Si-sook did not recognize the seizure of the throne and lived as a monk and wife forever. He left the world at age 21 and wandered all over the country.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Let&#39;s take a look at the portrait of Kim Jung-shik. Yeongjung differs from the intense primary color discord commonly found in verses. It is also different from the portrait of the Joseon Squadron who dressed nicely in Gwanbok. Kim Si-seop in Yeongjung&#39;s hands are kept neatly in the sleeve, but he is frowning with frowns. That is why many critics say that they have captured the features of dissatisfied intellectuals who are dissatisfied with the world. You can see that. At twenty-one years of age, when King Sejo came to the throne, he burned all the books he had read and left the world and became a monk. However, Kim&#39;s life is not filled with bad luck, hoarding and criticism of society.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   He left the world and toured Kanto and Hunan, enjoying scenery and writing poems. In his thirties, he spent six years in Gyeongju Geumosan, the current Gyeongju Namsan, dedicated to his work. The result of the immersion is Kum-O Myth, which is regarded as Korea&#39;s first Chinese novel. Was Kim Si-sook a poor genius who met the times wrongly? Or was he the owner of a free soul? Eventually, he sees his wandering as an alienation from power and mainstream or a will of free life. I give a small hint to that not easy problem. Kim Si-seop writes the motive of wandering in the preface of `` Every Month House &#39;&#39;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Young Si Kim - Buyeo County, Chungnam, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/db703360-cf34-443e-989c-e887c38d15e9.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Young Si Kim
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;font color=&#34;#367100&#34;&gt;
    &#34;I … In order to wander through the mountains and find a good view, I would boast of my friends to enjoy the poem, but I didn&#39;t think of getting into office with a sentence. It is a shame that one day, after being overwhelmed (the usurpation of the throne) by a man, a man can be born in this world and walk on the road. &#34;
   &lt;/font&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A monk is sweeping leaves - Buyeo County, Chungnam, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/c8dc4b05-d3fc-4362-b7aa-4d88cfe56a97.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A monk is sweeping leaves
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   The light way, the way to Taejoam
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   After exploring the grounds, head back one week for a deeper autumn walk.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;1.2 km from Mouyangsa Temple to Taejoam - Buyeo County, Chungnam, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/3834472d-88b3-400f-8857-b1cfe1526199.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     1.2 km from Mouyangsa Temple to Taejoam
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Before reaching the order, left to Taejoam and Dosolam to the left. A wide open area leads to a well-paved road to the left. The road lasts 1.2 km to Taejo Rock.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The driveway into Taejoam is a good way to walk. - Buyeo County, Chungnam, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/07b01060-3850-4036-91de-ada290ad79d7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The driveway into Taejoam is a good way to walk.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Shortly after entering the street, there is an old martial arts site on your left.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Bench on the way to Taejoam - Buyeo County, Chungnam, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/d063e688-3a31-4265-851a-c4f1ea083213.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Bench on the way to Taejoam
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It is now covered with pampas grass, weeds, and shrubs, but excavations in 2000 confirmed the podium, headstone, and prestigious flag stamped with “Muyangsa”.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Old martial arts site - Buyeo County, Chungnam, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/8af3da53-f771-4615-ae11-f33d3822bf57.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Old martial arts site
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Going way again It immediately passes through Dosolam and reaches Taejoam. Only two toilets and benches are placed sparsely on the way to Taejoam. There are no magpies on this road, but only red persimmons are hung on persimmon trees that have run out of leaves. It&#39;s a sleek but simple way to take a quiet walk. Passing the garden to the right of Taejoam begins the full-scale hiking trail. If you plan to climb Mansu Mountain, you can climb along Taejoam Trail.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Mansusan Mountain Trail begins in Taejoam - Buyeo County, Chungnam, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/1765c925-3dfb-4c35-9071-6d2f43308c1b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Mansusan Mountain Trail begins in Taejoam
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Exit Taejoam and leave the temple completely. There is one more thing to see before going to the parking lot. To the visitor who wants to leave, Muryangsa presents Kim Si-sook&#39;s bankruptcy. The fact that there are a lot of Buddhism, the tombs where Buddhist monks are buried, means that they have produced a lot of monks.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;13&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Murangsa Temple Budo-gun - Buyeo County, Chungnam, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/89fe1dbc-3e46-481a-b086-843a3ea86cae.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Murangsa Temple Budo-gun
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Muryangsa Budo-gun is on the way to Mujinam. Of all the defaults, Kim Si-sook&#39;s bankruptcy is the tallest. Both size and appearance are the most complete. The default of Kim Si-sook is a double base. The dragon pattern is vivid on the surface of the second podium&#39;s gown stone (medium stone), which is decorated with a lotus flower. It is very good for the stone relics of Chosun Electric.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;15&#34; id3=&#34;15&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Bankruptcy of Kim Si-sook - Buyeo County, Chungnam, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/2e38fdd9-f508-4669-bc00-df4dc988ba76.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Bankruptcy of Kim Si-sook
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   So is there really a Kim Si-suri saree here? During the Japanese colonial period, the typhoon swept away and the surrounding trees fell. At that time, the Budo was also collapsed, and the sari of Kim Si-sook was found. Kim&#39;s sari is currently on display at the National Buyeo Museum.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;17&#34; id3=&#34;16&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Dragon pattern of Kim Si-seop Budo middle stone - Buyeo County, Chungnam, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/3e13f9fe-55c2-4d47-809c-7833fbb11c87.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Dragon pattern of Kim Si-seop Budo middle stone
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel info
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;span style=&#34;color: rgb(33, 33, 33);&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong style=&#34;&#34;&gt;
      Martial arts
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Address: 203, Muryang-ro, Oesan-myeon, Buyeo-gun, Chungnam
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Inquiries: Muryangsa Office 041-836-5066
    &lt;/span&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://tour.buyeo.go.kr/html/tour/info/info_010108.html&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://tour.buyeo.go.kr/html/tour/info/info_010108.html
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Nearby restaurants
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Baekje&#39;s House: Yeonleaf Rice, Mabab / 22, Heukcheon-ro 8beon-gil, Buyeo-eup, Buyeo-gun / 041-834-1212
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Jangwon Makguksu: Makguksu / 20, Narutero 62beon-gil, Buyeo-eup, Buyeo-gun / 041-835-6561
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Gudraedol Ssambap: Dol Sambap / 31, Narut-ro, Buyeo-eup, Buyeo-gun / 041-836-9259
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Accommodation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Lotte Resort Buyeo: 400 Baekjemun-ro, Gyuam-myeon, Buyeo-gun / 041-939-1000
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.lottebuyeoresort.com/kor/index.asp&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.lottebuyeoresort.com/kor/index.asp
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Baekje Tourist Hotel: 108 Bukpo-ro, Buyeo-eup, Buyeo-gun / 041-835-0870
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://백제관광호텔.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://백제관광호텔.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Samjung Yeo Youth Hostel: 50 Narut-ro, Buyeo-eup, Buyeo-gun / 041-835-3101
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.buyeoyh.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.buyeoyh.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34; style=&#34;font-weight: bold;&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was updated in September 2017 and may change afterwards. Please check before traveling.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ The information such as text, photos and videos used in this article is copyrighted by Korea Tourism Organization, so unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>