<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>County on Every Corner of Korea</title>
    <link>https://codecorea.github.io/tags/county/</link>
    <description>Every Corner of Korea (County)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 19:01:46 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="https://codecorea.github.io/tags/county/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Buyeo County, Chungnam, South Korea - Where to ask for autumn leaves, the best season</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/where-to-ask-for-autumn-leaves-the-best-season-73/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 19:01:46 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/where-to-ask-for-autumn-leaves-the-best-season-73/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Buyeo County, Chungnam, South Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;where-to-ask-for-autumn-leaves-the-best-season--73&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Bright martial arts grounds in autumn - Buyeo County, Chungnam, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/58937cfd-a1a2-47c6-9a4b-d211eec767b1.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Bright martial arts grounds in autumn
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Where to ask for autumn leaves, the best season
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Buyeo County, Chungnam, South Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   To catch the end of the fall, he buryed the dead warriors to bury the last season. Yun Dae-nyeong, who wrote the novel, called Muryangsa as “the jangji (season) where the seasons sink.” When the leaves run out, it will be reminiscent of the sadness of a year. However, the bitterness of autumn, which is more abundant than gold, is swallowed up at once. Can we ask about the season that passed from Buyeo Muryangsa where Kim Si-ryong, the wind luck and genius poet of Joseon, spent his last years? .
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Coriander
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   This fall, which has been bitten, goes to Buyeo in a month because the leaves are falling early. Fortunately, martial arts haven&#39;t completely dropped the fall yet. There&#39;s still a lot of energy last summer. Passing through the ticket office is one order soon. On the forehead of one order, there is a large board called &#39;Mansusan Muralosa&#39;. It is a harmonious combination of &#39;unquantity&#39;, meaning immeasurable, and the name of the mountain, &#39;Mansu,&#39; which means enjoying a long life. Muryangsa Temple is a millennial temple that was founded during King Munseong King (Unification 839 ~ 857). However, like most temples and architectural cultural assets in Korea, all martial arts disappeared during the Imjin War, but were rebuilt in 1623 (Art. 1) to reach today.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;One order - Buyeo County, Chungnam, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/3a1d7526-7d10-4029-bfd6-affc28fccf4f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     One order
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Passing through a small valley and reaching the Cheonwangmun gate, a handsome party holder welcomes visitors to the right. The party holding means an elongated pole that hung the flag of the temple, or a holding seat that supported the party from left to right. This is a sign that the grounds of the temple begin here.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Mugi Corp - Buyeo County, Chungnam, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/2c5651cf-35af-4569-a629-22642c259afa.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Mugi Corp
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Ascending to the Cheonwangmun Gate, the paradise of Muyongsa Temple, the Five-storied Pagoda, and beyond are in the square frame of Cheonwangmun. Too stable angle. Even if you don&#39;t specialize in photography, you can naturally lift the camera. But the designer who designed this stunning view did not expose 100% of the paradise, the heart of the temple. The paradise roof was slightly covered with pine and zelkova branches. I sat and stood trying to take a picture to avoid the branches. 1 minute left? Ah! Realize that it was a wonderful piece of coriander to cover the Buddha&#39;s dwelling place. Wouldn&#39;t that branch have been cool to see through the paradise? Rather, the tree branches add to the secret paradise of paradise.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Paradise view from the Cheonwangmun - Buyeo County, Chungnam, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/02b188aa-0cf4-4f56-adba-8b2b37f8d365.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Paradise view from the Cheonwangmun
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Slowly approach to paradise. When you reach the pine tree that covered the roof, you can see the stone lanterns, the five-storied pagoda, and the paradise. The stone lanterns, five-storied pagoda, and paradise of Muryuksa are all national treasures. It may seem as if it is a cultural asset, but the history of the cultural assets filled with signs and the knowledge of art history do not seem to help this autumn. So I don&#39;t deliberately go in detail. The dust of knowledge in my head seems to sit on the surface of the sticky emotion. Just look at the three treasures at a distance. From a large perspective, the gaze that originated from the ground raises a sense of ascension through the stone lanterns and the top of the pagoda, leading to the paradise ridge. In addition, five hundred and one thousand years of history, without serious damage and damage, adds dignity.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;State and seat of majestic paradise war - Buyeo County, Chungnam, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/ef01d9af-0a62-4f68-9e2d-552a072a2617.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     State and seat of majestic paradise war
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Watch the paradise round from left to right. The boats of the pillars supporting the eccentric structure of the paradise are extraordinarily bulging. It is a commonly called shedding column. The exterior looks like two floors, but the inside of the paradise is a layered structure with no layers. It can be seen that this structure is not for the actual use of the second floor, but for the formality and dignity of the building.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Tombstone Pillar - Buyeo County, Chungnam, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/67f1e89f-86dc-47a2-bc0f-d1a6b169aece.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Tombstone Pillar
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Turn around the paradise backyard and stand under the maple tree in front of the fence on the right side of the building. It&#39;s good luck to come to the last martial arts afternoon. The sun has started to head west of Mansusan, and the warm autumn afternoon sun plentifully covers the grounds. Under the maple tree, the backlight is covered with maple leaves and the shutter is released. It&#39;s not wrong to say &#39;take photos with your feet&#39;. As soon as the monk passes by.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;13&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The grounds of martial arts temple from the right - Buyeo County, Chungnam, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/0e2cb43e-59b9-4c6e-b10e-8592536501cb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The grounds of martial arts temple from the right
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Kim Si-sook, a poor genius writer or owner of a free soul
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   There is one person you must meet in Muryangsa Temple. Kim Si-seon (1435 ~ 1493) is a monthly leader who is always introduced with nicknames such as Pung Un Ah, genius author, and Shin Dong. Pass the paradise and cross the small stream to the left to see the portrait of Kim Si-seop in Yeongjeonggak. Kim Si-sook did not recognize the seizure of the throne and lived as a monk and wife forever. He left the world at age 21 and wandered all over the country.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Let&#39;s take a look at the portrait of Kim Jung-shik. Yeongjung differs from the intense primary color discord commonly found in verses. It is also different from the portrait of the Joseon Squadron who dressed nicely in Gwanbok. Kim Si-seop in Yeongjung&#39;s hands are kept neatly in the sleeve, but he is frowning with frowns. That is why many critics say that they have captured the features of dissatisfied intellectuals who are dissatisfied with the world. You can see that. At twenty-one years of age, when King Sejo came to the throne, he burned all the books he had read and left the world and became a monk. However, Kim&#39;s life is not filled with bad luck, hoarding and criticism of society.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   He left the world and toured Kanto and Hunan, enjoying scenery and writing poems. In his thirties, he spent six years in Gyeongju Geumosan, the current Gyeongju Namsan, dedicated to his work. The result of the immersion is Kum-O Myth, which is regarded as Korea&#39;s first Chinese novel. Was Kim Si-sook a poor genius who met the times wrongly? Or was he the owner of a free soul? Eventually, he sees his wandering as an alienation from power and mainstream or a will of free life. I give a small hint to that not easy problem. Kim Si-seop writes the motive of wandering in the preface of `` Every Month House &#39;&#39;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Young Si Kim - Buyeo County, Chungnam, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/db703360-cf34-443e-989c-e887c38d15e9.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Young Si Kim
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;font color=&#34;#367100&#34;&gt;
    &#34;I … In order to wander through the mountains and find a good view, I would boast of my friends to enjoy the poem, but I didn&#39;t think of getting into office with a sentence. It is a shame that one day, after being overwhelmed (the usurpation of the throne) by a man, a man can be born in this world and walk on the road. &#34;
   &lt;/font&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A monk is sweeping leaves - Buyeo County, Chungnam, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/c8dc4b05-d3fc-4362-b7aa-4d88cfe56a97.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A monk is sweeping leaves
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   The light way, the way to Taejoam
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   After exploring the grounds, head back one week for a deeper autumn walk.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;1.2 km from Mouyangsa Temple to Taejoam - Buyeo County, Chungnam, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/3834472d-88b3-400f-8857-b1cfe1526199.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     1.2 km from Mouyangsa Temple to Taejoam
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Before reaching the order, left to Taejoam and Dosolam to the left. A wide open area leads to a well-paved road to the left. The road lasts 1.2 km to Taejo Rock.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The driveway into Taejoam is a good way to walk. - Buyeo County, Chungnam, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/07b01060-3850-4036-91de-ada290ad79d7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The driveway into Taejoam is a good way to walk.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Shortly after entering the street, there is an old martial arts site on your left.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Bench on the way to Taejoam - Buyeo County, Chungnam, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/d063e688-3a31-4265-851a-c4f1ea083213.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Bench on the way to Taejoam
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It is now covered with pampas grass, weeds, and shrubs, but excavations in 2000 confirmed the podium, headstone, and prestigious flag stamped with “Muyangsa”.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Old martial arts site - Buyeo County, Chungnam, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/8af3da53-f771-4615-ae11-f33d3822bf57.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Old martial arts site
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Going way again It immediately passes through Dosolam and reaches Taejoam. Only two toilets and benches are placed sparsely on the way to Taejoam. There are no magpies on this road, but only red persimmons are hung on persimmon trees that have run out of leaves. It&#39;s a sleek but simple way to take a quiet walk. Passing the garden to the right of Taejoam begins the full-scale hiking trail. If you plan to climb Mansu Mountain, you can climb along Taejoam Trail.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Mansusan Mountain Trail begins in Taejoam - Buyeo County, Chungnam, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/1765c925-3dfb-4c35-9071-6d2f43308c1b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Mansusan Mountain Trail begins in Taejoam
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Exit Taejoam and leave the temple completely. There is one more thing to see before going to the parking lot. To the visitor who wants to leave, Muryangsa presents Kim Si-sook&#39;s bankruptcy. The fact that there are a lot of Buddhism, the tombs where Buddhist monks are buried, means that they have produced a lot of monks.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;13&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Murangsa Temple Budo-gun - Buyeo County, Chungnam, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/89fe1dbc-3e46-481a-b086-843a3ea86cae.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Murangsa Temple Budo-gun
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Muryangsa Budo-gun is on the way to Mujinam. Of all the defaults, Kim Si-sook&#39;s bankruptcy is the tallest. Both size and appearance are the most complete. The default of Kim Si-sook is a double base. The dragon pattern is vivid on the surface of the second podium&#39;s gown stone (medium stone), which is decorated with a lotus flower. It is very good for the stone relics of Chosun Electric.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;15&#34; id3=&#34;15&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Bankruptcy of Kim Si-sook - Buyeo County, Chungnam, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/2e38fdd9-f508-4669-bc00-df4dc988ba76.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Bankruptcy of Kim Si-sook
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   So is there really a Kim Si-suri saree here? During the Japanese colonial period, the typhoon swept away and the surrounding trees fell. At that time, the Budo was also collapsed, and the sari of Kim Si-sook was found. Kim&#39;s sari is currently on display at the National Buyeo Museum.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;17&#34; id3=&#34;16&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Dragon pattern of Kim Si-seop Budo middle stone - Buyeo County, Chungnam, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/73/3e13f9fe-55c2-4d47-809c-7833fbb11c87.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Dragon pattern of Kim Si-seop Budo middle stone
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel info
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;span style=&#34;color: rgb(33, 33, 33);&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong style=&#34;&#34;&gt;
      Martial arts
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Address: 203, Muryang-ro, Oesan-myeon, Buyeo-gun, Chungnam
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Inquiries: Muryangsa Office 041-836-5066
    &lt;/span&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://tour.buyeo.go.kr/html/tour/info/info_010108.html&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://tour.buyeo.go.kr/html/tour/info/info_010108.html
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Nearby restaurants
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Baekje&#39;s House: Yeonleaf Rice, Mabab / 22, Heukcheon-ro 8beon-gil, Buyeo-eup, Buyeo-gun / 041-834-1212
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Jangwon Makguksu: Makguksu / 20, Narutero 62beon-gil, Buyeo-eup, Buyeo-gun / 041-835-6561
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Gudraedol Ssambap: Dol Sambap / 31, Narut-ro, Buyeo-eup, Buyeo-gun / 041-836-9259
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Accommodation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Lotte Resort Buyeo: 400 Baekjemun-ro, Gyuam-myeon, Buyeo-gun / 041-939-1000
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.lottebuyeoresort.com/kor/index.asp&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.lottebuyeoresort.com/kor/index.asp
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Baekje Tourist Hotel: 108 Bukpo-ro, Buyeo-eup, Buyeo-gun / 041-835-0870
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://백제관광호텔.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://백제관광호텔.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Samjung Yeo Youth Hostel: 50 Narut-ro, Buyeo-eup, Buyeo-gun / 041-835-3101
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.buyeoyh.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.buyeoyh.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34; style=&#34;font-weight: bold;&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was updated in September 2017 and may change afterwards. Please check before traveling.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ The information such as text, photos and videos used in this article is copyrighted by Korea Tourism Organization, so unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>