<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Seocheon-gun on Every Corner of Korea</title>
    <link>https://codecorea.github.io/tags/seocheon-gun/</link>
    <description>Every Corner of Korea (Seocheon-gun)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2020 10:34:17 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="https://codecorea.github.io/tags/seocheon-gun/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Beautiful harmony of migratory birds and reeds Seocheon - Seocheon-gun, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/beautiful-harmony-of-migratory-birds-and-reeds-seocheon-301/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2020 10:34:17 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/beautiful-harmony-of-migratory-birds-and-reeds-seocheon-301/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Seocheon-gun, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;beautiful-harmony-of-migratory-birds-and-reeds-seocheon--301&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Relaxing Seocheon Maryangpogu - Seocheon-gun, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/301/316606be-f0f5-4b24-a004-f334e9eb64cb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Relaxing Seocheon Maryangpogu
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Beautiful harmony of migratory birds and reeds Seocheon
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Seocheon-gun, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Seocheon is an impressive place with only the unique and quiet scenery unique to the countryside. The Geum River, which flows gently, crosses the body of Seocheon, and seagulls fly freely in the small muzzle. Maryangpo wakes up the morning with a throbbing sound. The Seocheon Botanical Arts Center is equipped with simple yet elegant bonsais, and you can experience the maze park and various agricultural cultures. Seosan&#39;s Hansan Ramie is one of the major essences of our national culture, which is important enough to be registered as a National Intangible Cultural Heritage No. 14 and listed as a UNESCO human intangible cultural heritage (28 November 2011). By this time, you can see the fantastic military service of migratory birds traveling to distant foreign countries. You can also whisper love in the reed forest in Sinseong-ri, where you can watch 100,000 sky up close.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The rustling wind sweeps through the reed forest. Seocheon is a place where the reed tells a rich feeling. The people of Seocheon call their place Amenity Seocheon. Amenity is said to mean all economic resources in the countryside that can satisfy people without harming the natural landscape. In other words, it will mean that we will give the best satisfaction to everyone who visits Seocheon through the unique natural scenery and cultural heritage of the countryside. Even without relying on the meaning of the dictionary, Seocheon is an impressive place with only the unique and quiet scenery unique to the countryside. The Geum River, which flows gently, crosses the body of Seocheon, and seagulls fly freely in the small muzzle. At dawn, the sound of a boat wakes up in the morning. Seosan&#39;s pride, Hansan ramie, is still the best specialty. Is that all? By this time, you can see the fantastic military service of migratory birds traveling to distant foreign countries. You can also whisper love in the reed forest in Sinseong-ri, where you can watch 100,000 shimmers up close. If you want to keep all this scenery in your mind, head out to Seocheon this weekend. A fragrant country scent will dig into your heart.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Misty morning in Seocheon Reed Forest - Seocheon-gun, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/301/952b361d-3edd-4fa6-bfdc-f338df3c3461.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Misty morning in Seocheon Reed Forest
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Seocheon is a place that gives the impression of a perfect countryside. As you walk along the street, a small house suddenly comes out and a longing comes from the smoke of cooking. Soft and static. Fluffy clouds are hanging over the roofs of the countryside.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Literature - Seocheon-gun, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/301/d9c591c1-7b36-44bc-a26f-ea72cd71576e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Literature
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Seocheon&#39;s exotic experience village lies in a cozy and cozy valley at the foot of Hwayang Mountain.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Literature - Seocheon-gun, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/301/b5d08c85-68ae-4000-a2ff-c566f82390e1.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Literature
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Mok-eun, who was a supportive Confucian scholar who did not serve the two kings, is the place where the literature scribe, where the teacher of Saek-suk bloomed, is also a place where you can experience unique and touching experiences.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Literature - Seocheon-gun, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/301/8793f75e-2951-4589-ae82-fd8f1b4eac59.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Literature
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Because you can experience two different experiences, you can learn and experience different cultures and styles.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Literature - Seocheon-gun, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/301/5d62fbdb-5509-4590-ab88-ca43d2cdddc8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Literature
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The unique village of Seocheon Botanical Arts Center (041-951-1072), which became famous when the director Kim Jae-wan, who retired from the principal of the elementary school, released the Onggi, Sodadae, and Bonsai collected for over 40 years, became the base, and the entire village was transformed into an experience village. did. In the Seocheon Botanical Arts Center, expensive bonsai is not on display, but there are many bonsais that are simple but feel the elegance of Mr. Kim. Next to the Bonsai Art Museum is the Onggi Exhibition Hall, where over 1,000 ceramic bowls collected by Kim Won-jang have been placed in various forms.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;13&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Seocheon Bizarre Experience Village - Seocheon-gun, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/301/b408065b-a5b6-4e98-b2ee-23b56a286fc8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Seocheon Bizarre Experience Village
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In the labyrinth garden, there is a uniquely shaped labyrinth, and you can also visit the agricultural museum where you can trace the history of agricultural culture. When it&#39;s time to eat during the market season, you can immerse yourself in the different flavors by eating bicolor kalguksu, which is good for your body.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;15&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Seocheon Bizarre Experience Village - Seocheon-gun, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/301/e777aea0-c7ce-4b27-aec6-3a10fc472d7e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Seocheon Bizarre Experience Village
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The reed forest in Seocheon is called the 4th reed forest nationwide along with the reed forest in Suncheon Bay, Jeollanam-do. It is also considered as the &#39;Korean Reed 7&#39; by the Korea Tourism Organization. The size of the reed field, as well as the sight of the reed swaying in the wind, is truly spectacular. The landscape of the reed field was so difficult that it was the background of the movie JSA. The scene of Lee Byung-hun&#39;s first encounter with North Korean soldier Song Kang-ho takes place in this reed field. It is also the location of the TV drama Chuno, Sorry. The reed field is harmonious with the Geumgang water and the sunlight. It is also famous for its migratory colony. During the winter, Goni and Mallards swarm in reed forests.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;17&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sinseong-ri Reed Field - Seocheon-gun, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/301/2a3b6337-1929-4bb6-834b-90a2442b00eb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sinseong-ri Reed Field
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Seocheon is home to many wetlands and reed forests. In addition to the reed forests in Sinseong-ri, you can easily find the flowers blooming in colonies of fishing villages and gaet villages along the Seocheon coast. Seocheon has a different appearance in each season. In spring, the sound of life tumbling in the forest of reeds. In summer, the cool river breeze that has passed through the lush leaves cools the heat, and in the fall, the reed, with its head bowed at the end of the wind, feels the weight. In winter, it is sad and sad.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;19&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sinseong-ri Reed Field - Seocheon-gun, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/301/14abb07b-efc8-4524-8bf8-b00315a2e3d4.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sinseong-ri Reed Field
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The time to taste the essence of reed forest is also autumn. Among them, from late October to November, you can fully enjoy the reeds. Benches and trails are provided between the reed forests, allowing you to enjoy the reeds comfortably.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;21&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sinseong-ri Reed Field - Seocheon-gun, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/301/8b4fddcd-0680-493f-81b3-2b50ce68cc93.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sinseong-ri Reed Field
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The Hansan Mosikan also has a special feeling. Seocheon is a place where ramie was developed from the past. Hansan ramie is a high-grade sashimi produced in the area of Hansan-myeon, Seocheon-gun, Chungcheongnam-do. It is the fusion of the wisdom of our nation that can overcome the heat with a cool linen of red and red ginseng on a summer day. Seosan&#39;s Hansan Ramie is one of the major essences of our national culture, which is important enough to be registered as a National Intangible Cultural Heritage No. 14 and listed as a UNESCO human intangible cultural heritage (28 November 2011).
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;23&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Hansan City Hall - Seocheon-gun, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/301/78a8e14a-2227-4b56-888e-d7a52c577b9f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Hansan City Hall
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The tangled narrative of Hansan Moshi dates back to the Three Kingdoms period. An old man climbed a medicinal herb to Mt. Geonji and found ramie grass. It started to cultivate ramie, and in the Joseon Dynasty, it was designated as a tribute to souvenirs from the Hansan area. If you make a loom on the loom, it looks like ramie will come out, but in fact, ramie is a fabric that requires a great deal of labor. Peel the skin from the stem of the linen, pick out only the soft flesh, dry it in the sun, and soak it in water for 1 to 2 hours to make a very soft tamoshi. Tamoshi is placed between the teeth, scraped into small pieces, and then placed on the mold with linen fibers and then glued together using the saliva of each lip to make soshigut.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;25&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Inside the Hansan Mosikan - Seocheon-gun, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/301/23faa3fe-4729-40ab-b8e1-0ef01246f66a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Inside the Hansan Mosikan
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It doesn&#39;t end there. Loosen the ramie good, wind the thread enough to squeeze the ramie, put the ramie thread and feed the soybean grass to make the ramie smooth. It is only necessary to put this on a loom to complete Hanpil&#39;s ramie. It is very painful to squeeze the arm, and the tooth hurts to tear off the mossy. The process of making Taemoshi, putting it in a loom, and weaving it was a process of labor, so it was said that &#39;a dead tree is a man&#39;. So tradition was born and passed on.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;27&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Statue of Hansan Mosikan - Seocheon-gun, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/301/9efc7442-757c-410d-bbc7-93d49b2f987e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Statue of Hansan Mosikan
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   When the sunset glows red, the scenery of the Geum River Estuary is superb. The Geumgang Estuary Bank is a dam constructed by blocking the 401 km of the estuary of the Geum River originating from Ongdalsam, Jangsu-gun, Jeollabuk-do.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;29&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Geum River Estuary - Seocheon-gun, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/301/c5fe4845-138a-4c90-a79c-000db97641aa.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Geum River Estuary
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In winter, migratory birds, which embroider the sky in black, form a tripod, leaving for a distant foreign country.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;31&#34; id3=&#34;15&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Geum River Estuary - Seocheon-gun, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/301/553e0a62-7b31-4905-9343-4827f56c43cf.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Geum River Estuary
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Migratory birds become a moving picture. The migratory birds flying on the water and on the ground sometimes stir up strange emotions.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;33&#34; id3=&#34;16&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Seocheon Bird Ecology Center - Seocheon-gun, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/301/425a27f7-d064-4751-9851-edd5f0f3cf80.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Seocheon Bird Ecology Center
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The day of Seocheon, where more beautiful people live in beautiful nature, flowed down in the red twilight.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;35&#34; id3=&#34;17&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Seocheon Bird Ecological Center - Seocheon-gun, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/301/db53eb34-9145-48eb-a6bd-ad1cec86e864.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Seocheon Bird Ecological Center
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Literature
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Address: 66 Seowon-ro 172beon-gil, Gisan-myeon, Seocheon-gun, Chungcheongnam-do
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Inquiries: 041-953-5895
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://munheon.org/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://munheon.org/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Seocheon Botanical Arts Center
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Address: 19, Hoechul-gil 42beon-gil, Gisan-myeon, Seocheon-gun, Chungcheongnam-do
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Inquiries: 041-951-1072, 041-951-0020
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.artrees.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.artrees.com/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Sinseong-ri Reed Field
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Address: Geumgang, Sinseong-ri, Hansan-myeon, Seocheon-gun, Chungcheongnam-do
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Inquiries: 041-952-9525
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Hansan City Hall
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Address: 1089, Chungjeol-ro, Hansan-myeon, Seocheon-gun, Chungcheongnam-do
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Inquiries: 041-951-4100
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.hansanmosi.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.hansanmosi.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Bird Ecological Exhibition
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Address: 916 Jangsan-ro, Maseo-myeon, Seocheon-gun, Chungcheongnam-do
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Inquiries: 041-956-4002
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://bird.seocheon.go.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://bird.seocheon.go.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Restaurants near
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Deoksugung Seafood Kalguksu: Kalguksu / 5 Jangsan-ro 855beon-gil, Maseo-myeon, Seocheon-gun, Chungcheongnam-do / 041-956-7066
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Halmae Onjeongjip: Agui cuisine / 20 Jangseo-ro 47beon-gil, Janghang-eup, Seocheon-gun, Chungcheongnam-do / 041-956-4860, 3868
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.onjungjib.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.onjungjib.com/
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Gangbyeon sashimi: Hoe / 714 Jangsan-ro, Maseo-myeon, Seocheon-gun, Chungcheongnam-do / 041-956-8874
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Jangbeol Seolleongtang: Gomtang, Seolleongtang / 699 Seoin-ro, Seomyeon-gun, Seocheon-gun, Chungcheongnam-do / 041-952-8993
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Seocheon Seohaean Sashimi Restaurant: Gwangeohoe, Maeuntang / 1, Maryang-ri, Seomyeon-gun, Seocheon-gun, Chungcheongnam-do / 041-952-3177
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Rooms
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -C Art Hotel: 233, Chungseo-ro, Jongcheon-myeon, Seocheon-gun, Chungcheongnam-do / 041-952-8012
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Seaside Pension Motel: 39 Seomyeon Chunjang-daero 151beon-gil, Seocheon-gun, Chungcheongnam-do / 041-952-0737
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Hu Motel: 273 Busa-ro, Seomyeon-gun, Chungcheongnam-do / 041-952-0077
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was created in January 2013, and may be changed later, so be sure to check it before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ All contents (text, photos, videos, etc.) of this article are protected by copyright law, and unauthorized reproduction, copying, distribution, etc. are prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Autumn trip to the west coast with the Three Musketeers - Seocheon-gun, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/autumn-trip-to-the-west-coast-with-the-three-musketeers-170/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 20:16:53 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/autumn-trip-to-the-west-coast-with-the-three-musketeers-170/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Seocheon-gun, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;autumn-trip-to-the-west-coast-with-the-three-musketeers--170&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Grilled autumn trout without words - Seocheon-gun, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/170/718ab10a-9e9c-4c5f-9a5a-d51a6d91d43c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Grilled autumn trout without words
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Autumn trip to the west coast with the Three Musketeers
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Seocheon-gun, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Every fall, a delicious festival representing Hongwon Port, a natural fish and crab festival, is held in Hongwon Port, Seocheon, Chungnam. Introducing a delicacy trip to the west coast that is overflowing with delicious festivals that just pass by.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Keywords for enjoying the autumn west coast are fish, blue crab, and daeha. Delicious things that cannot be overlooked! Starting from the Daeha Festival of Namseong Port in Hongseong (8.24 ~ 9.15), the Seocheon Hongwon Port Natural Fish &amp;amp; Crab Festival (9.21 ~ 10.6) and Muchangpo Mysterious Sea Road Daeha · Jeonje Festival (9.21 ~ 10.13) followed by Anmyeondo White Sands Festival (9.29 ~ 10.14) To finish.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Best for a day trip! West Coast Autumn Delicacy Tour
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   As you may have noticed, the main characters are all similar. For a date, I recommend the calm sea of Anmyeondo or Muchangpo, and the Hongseong Namdang Port or Seocheon Hongwon Port for seniors&#39; dinner parties or family meal trips.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Seocheon Hongwon Port Maryangpogu Sunset - Seocheon-gun, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/170/e01d4e41-e352-425f-846e-e0ae2cdb361d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Seocheon Hongwon Port Maryangpogu Sunset
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Hongwon Port, located in Seocheon, the southernmost point of Chungnam, is located in Gunsan, Jeollabuk-do. It is recommended for those who want to travel to Namdo or to eat, eat and eat again.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Seocheon Hongwon Port - Seocheon-gun, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/170/93576e2f-9c65-456c-8b1b-6b2ef01ce491.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Seocheon Hongwon Port
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   On the way back, if you have the time and mind to withstand the pressure of the West Coast Expressway, you might want to try several of these.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Don&#39;t miss walking around the muzzle - Seocheon-gun, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/170/9526dab5-baa8-4c9c-b702-4599a53301e4.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Don&#39;t miss walking around the muzzle
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The destination of this trip was to select Hongwon Port&#39;s natural fish and crab festival. This is because I wanted to taste both the fish and the blue crab, and I wanted to see the fall of Maryangpogu. On the weekend, the West Coast Expressway requires strong mentality, so those with a glass heart are advised to leave at 7 am (at the metropolitan area) at the latest and enjoy a little early lunch and come up. If you want both a day trip and a relaxing weekend evening.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Hongwon Port Natural Fish and Blue Crab Festival - Seocheon-gun, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/170/50f5c5d9-5d4c-456c-bc15-4917540ab443.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Hongwon Port Natural Fish and Blue Crab Festival
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Although it is Chungnam in the administrative district, Hongcheon Port in Seocheon, which is directly in contact with Jeonbuk, must be run. The home of Giza, located in the northeastern corner of Seoul, is 230km away from Seoul&#39;s home (290km from Seoul Station to Daegu Station). Still, my shoulders are shaking because I want to taste the savory fish. &#34;wait! It must be! ” Run with the golden fields.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Hongwon Port Natural Fish and Blue Crab Festival - Seocheon-gun, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/170/7e00bdd7-8cdb-4f8e-9d72-a93cfa032003.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Hongwon Port Natural Fish and Blue Crab Festival
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Although he ran diligently, the parking lot of Hongwon Port was already full of vehicles even before lunch time began. There are no great events similar to other West Coast Food Festivals. On a small stage, you can enjoy events such as singing celebrities and manfishing at 2 pm on the weekend. You can also buy Seocheon specialties such as Hansan Sogokju and Hansan Mositteok.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;13&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Hongwon Fishing Village - Seocheon-gun, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/170/e2ac1c69-ef8c-4f5e-a12c-f5c0744557ce.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Hongwon Fishing Village
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The restaurant continues from the beginning of the parking lot. As you continue along the road, you will see a nameplate indicating the live fish market. Fresh blue crabs, fish, and lobsters flutter.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;15&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A restaurant on the second floor where you can eat the creatures you buy when you pay for it. - Seocheon-gun, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/170/2bee50e5-9402-4770-8a9d-e4283c0f149c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A restaurant on the second floor where you can eat the creatures you buy when you pay for it.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   The legendary autumn fish caught by the daughter-in-law
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   First, let&#39;s meet the autumn eel. An autumn dish boasting ‘the savory taste that a daughter-in-law will return home’! This year around the west coast, a fishing festival is held around the west coast. The bone is soft and the flesh is rich in fat, so the savory taste is the best. Even if you eat the circuit, the savory comes before the fishy, and the more you bake, the more the sue.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sue Jeonhoe - Seocheon-gun, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/170/ee4e08c0-01b7-4cab-9c59-7b1af5f7d730.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sue Jeonhoe
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   To understand the phrase ‘Autumn tuna is a sesame,’ you just have to taste autumn tuna. Thanks to the soft bones, there is not much to taste even the whole fish. As the weather gets colder and colder, the bones will shrivel. Let&#39;s check the bone condition slightly, rather than chewing it whole. If you really want to enjoy the autumn of the west coast, overflowing with delicious food.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sashimi sashimi flavored with garlic and chili - Seocheon-gun, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/170/f8396048-15f5-4688-9618-4324a0dce0f6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sashimi sashimi flavored with garlic and chili
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Now it&#39;s time to hear the past of the best-loved eel as an autumn delicacy. In the past, it was a natural duckling that came up on a net of natural lobster. Even now, the status of the natural body of the precious body has not changed (we rarely taste the natural treatment. They are too precious, expensive, and impatient, they lose their world when polluted on the net).
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Grilled autumn trout that the daughter-in-law also turned - Seocheon-gun, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/170/115faad8-2f9c-4bee-8dea-6ec2c345575b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Grilled autumn trout that the daughter-in-law also turned
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The word is different. Fish that has been mixed up on the Daeha Net. The fish, which were so common that they didn&#39;t even think about eating, crushed them without removing them from the net. Then someone sold the fish and the people smelled of it because of the savory smell of grilling it.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;“I am the right word!” - Seocheon-gun, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/170/43414a18-80c9-4849-93cc-6833267d747a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     “I am the right word!”
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   It&#39;s sweet
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   This is a description of a merchant operating a sushi restaurant near Hongwon Port, which grew up in Seocheon. The spooky fish. We win the game with autumn delicacies.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Female crab in spring and crab in autumn. Steamed crab filled with meat - Seocheon-gun, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/170/66ede902-f1f2-4da4-b97c-2f57bed7f3f1.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Female crab in spring and crab in autumn. Steamed crab filled with meat
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The price varies depending on the amount of fish caught each year, which is around 35,000 won per kg this year.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sweet and sweet blue crab flesh - Seocheon-gun, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/170/72d67317-1607-4252-9bdb-4063e2588001.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sweet and sweet blue crab flesh
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you come to many or want to taste a variety of food, it is better to buy creatures such as fish, crabs, and lobsters to pay for in the restaurant.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Blue crab soup with cool soup - Seocheon-gun, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/170/e4ef2cad-93a8-4e20-809d-0919d8febcc4.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Blue crab soup with cool soup
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   I decided to taste the grilled fish and half the circuit with only 1kg. In order to feel the true taste of the fish, the radish passes boldly. Let&#39;s take a look at the blue crab and say, &#34;A crab in the spring and a crab in the autumn.&#34;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;15&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Autumn delicacies - Seocheon-gun, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/170/59a72257-21ae-4f4f-b2a1-a276764c5953.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Autumn delicacies
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Of course, I thought that the blue crab was the best egg crab. In autumn, crabs are in season. We also added living treats swimming hard.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;16&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Fall festivals, the main character of Daeha, are held - Seocheon-gun, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/170/c5721436-df1b-46e9-966b-8001e9f1dd20.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Fall festivals, the main character of Daeha, are held
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Once you&#39;ve tasted it all, it&#39;s time to meet the sunset of Maryangpogu. Maryangpo-gu, Hongwon Port, one of the most beautiful sunsets in the country I&#39;m here, but it&#39;s a pity to go back. There is nothing enviable in the world as you add yourself to the snow lake after you&#39;ve taken a good look with the delicious seasonal west coast delicacies.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;13&#34; id3=&#34;17&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A fun kick for those visiting the festival - Seocheon-gun, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/170/65093550-aa59-4712-ac96-75bc5d5a8ed6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A fun kick for those visiting the festival
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you are with your loved ones, a trip to the west coast of the city will be abundant. Something more savory than a roe, I hope everyone with you this fall! Indeed, even after the festival period, you can still enjoy the fish until the beginning of November.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;15&#34; id3=&#34;18&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Fun play for those who visit the festival - Seocheon-gun, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/170/b03fb6ca-f3d9-4804-ae76-591fcdc1aedf.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Fun play for those who visit the festival
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Seocheon Hongwon Port Natural Fish Crab Festival
     &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Period: 2019.9.21 ~ 10.6
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://tour.seocheon.go.kr/tour/sub04_01_04.do&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://tour.seocheon.go.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Muchangpo Mysterious Sea Road Festival
     &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Period: 2019.9.21 ~ 10.13
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.mbeach.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.mbeach.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Hongseong Namdang Port Daeha Festival
     &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Period: 2019.8.24 ~ 9.15
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://tour.hongseong.go.kr/tour/sub02_03_03.do&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://tour.hongseong.go.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Anmyeondo White Sand Beach Festival
     &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Period: 2019.9.29 ~ 10.14
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Restaurants near
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Restaurants cannot be introduced separately. The restaurant street starts from the beginning of the festival. If you want to taste only one or two types of raw fish sashimi for one or two people, the restaurant is cheap and if you plan on tasting multiple or various creatures, it is better to buy a creature from the fishing village and pay for it in the restaurant.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Rooms
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Seocheon Beachtel: Seoin-ro, Seomyeon-gun Seomyeon-ro (Maryang-ri) / 041-952-9566
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.seocheonbeachtel.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.seocheonbeachtel.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Adria Motel: Seosa-gun Seomyeon Busa-ro / 041-951-6699
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.adria.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.adria.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Beach Pension Motel: Seodun-gun Seomun Dodun-ri / 041-952-0737
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was updated in September 2019, and may be changed later, so please check before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seocheon-gun, Chungnam, Korea - From Hongseong to Seocheon, take the sea of Chungnam! Sea bathing and tidal flat experience at once!</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/from-hongseong-to-seocheon-take-the-sea-of-chungnam-sea-bathing-and-tidal-flat-experience-at-once-72/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 18:38:06 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/from-hongseong-to-seocheon-take-the-sea-of-chungnam-sea-bathing-and-tidal-flat-experience-at-once-72/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Seocheon-gun, Chungnam, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;from-hongseong-to-seocheon-take-the-sea-of-chungnam-sea-bathing-and-tidal-flat-experience-at-once--72&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Boryeong Muchangpo Beach Low Tide Shellfish - Seocheon-gun, Chungnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/72/178d0943-d83d-4910-8c61-6fa13f1b038f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Boryeong Muchangpo Beach Low Tide Shellfish
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   From Hongseong to Seocheon, take the sea of Chungnam! Sea bathing and tidal flat experience at once!
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Seocheon-gun, Chungnam, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   What is the west coast&#39;s greatest attraction? The West Sea is filled with charm that is different from the East Sea, which attracts street hands with clear and beautiful water. You can enjoy sea bathing on the boardwalk and enjoy the tidal-flat experience under the influence of high and low tide. So prepared. Along the coast of Chungnam, head to the gem-like beach and tidal-flat experience hotspots located in Hongseong, Boryeong, and Seocheon!
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Before starting the mudflat experience, let&#39;s know this!
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In order to enjoy the tidal-flat experience, some preparations are required. If you have comfortable shoes such as boots or sneakers, or a basket or a basket for fish and shellfish, you do not need to rent them. Some of the rental fees are included in the experience fee and some are separate. At low tide there are many beaches where you can enjoy clamming for free. Extra clothes are also required.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   The tidal-flat of Cheonsu Bay is caught with various foods, of which clams are the most common. Going south, the clams, the clams and the lilies are added. Familiar clams can be caught at all times except during the spawning season, from early July to mid-August. Don&#39;t worry about overlapping with summer vacation. Most experience centers manage and divide the experience zone, so visitors can collect their clams.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The most important thing in the tidal-flat experience is &#39;water time&#39;. National Maritime Research Institute
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.khoa.go.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;[새창열림]‘국립해양조사원’ 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
     http://www.khoa.go.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    If you enter, you can see the timetable of the area where you want to experience the tidal flats. Depending on the region and date, you can experience the tidal flat for two hours before and after “low tide”. This is directly related to safety, so be sure to check it out.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Basic experience of tidal flat - Seocheon-gun, Chungnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/72/f9153a96-ec0c-402a-9e55-abfb1740ecfe.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Basic experience of tidal flat
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   “Find a small hole in the tidal flat. The clam pores. The clams live just below the tidal flats, so scratching them with a pitchfork hurts them. Lightly press the rake and poke it, then lift the mud flat as it looks.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   I think if you scratch with a pitchfork, you will get clams in between, but if you scratch a tidal flat, you will get a cut on the surface of the clam that lives closest to the tidal flat. If you sit still and do it yourself, you can quickly get a feel for it. Thanks to the natural way of knowing how to collect. Here&#39;s a tip, a small chair that will help you focus more on clam collection. This is because the squat position is inconvenient. Most experience sites limit the amount to 1kg or basket per person.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Ice box to store the collected shellfish safely - Seocheon-gun, Chungnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/72/0d80943f-9763-46d5-b070-359a308138ca.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Ice box to store the collected shellfish safely
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Haesong and Moseom walk is a bonus, mixed tidal flat Hongseong Sokdong tidal village
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Let&#39;s look at Hongseong first. There is Sokdong Tidal Flat in Hongseong, which faces the Taean Peninsula, which stretches across Cheonsu Bay. In the middle of Sokdong Tidal Flat, Gungripo-gu is above and Namdang Port is below. In addition to the wide tidal flats, it boasts a beautiful scenery that includes the Sokdong Observatory, which belongs to the Hongseong Eight View.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sokdong Tidal-flat Village in Hongseong, South Chungcheong Province - Seocheon-gun, Chungnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/72/fe82c225-a99c-4e98-a96f-02deedff5407.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sokdong Tidal-flat Village in Hongseong, South Chungcheong Province
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It is easy to reach thanks to the road next to the big road (west coast seaside tourism road). At low tide, you can face the Sokdong Tidal Flats, which are not ashamed of the sea.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The pine trees greet you along the wooden deck that leads to Mosum. - Seocheon-gun, Chungnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/72/ddd2763d-6afc-4c7e-a605-ae9fca840978.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The pine trees greet you along the wooden deck that leads to Mosum.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   To experience Sokdong Tidal Flats, you should visit the Hongseong Sokdong Tidal Flat Village Village Information Center. If you pay the experience fee (Adult / Infant 7,000 won), you can borrow an experience tool such as boots and a rake to start digging clams. Even beginners can enjoy the taste of clams according to the guide&#39;s instructions.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Observatory - Seocheon-gun, Chungnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/72/462ede20-3a75-4fb2-ac69-ecc20e3f2232.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Observatory
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The most important thing is that you have to come in time. Sokdong Tidal Flat Village (070-7763-8450)
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://sokdong.invil.org/index.html&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;[새창열림]‘속동갯벌마을’ 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
     http://sokdong.invil.org/index.html
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Find the tide and book your experience at.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Cheonsu Bay from the Sokdong Observatory - Seocheon-gun, Chungnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/72/c8ebf45e-6a61-466c-b42e-b5785cc01e07.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Cheonsu Bay from the Sokdong Observatory
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you enjoyed catching clams, don&#39;t miss the Sokdong Observatory. Only wide open waters spread out at a glance. In front of it is Sokdong Tidal Flat Experience Center.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Beating of tidal flat - Seocheon-gun, Chungnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/72/45bc7874-3db1-47b9-a318-427976a8008e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Beating of tidal flat
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Go up to Mosum, which is located 100 meters away. As you climb the island through the wooden deck in Haisong Forest, another observatory awaits you. The fall here is also famous, so check it out.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Clam of fast-paced tidal flat - Seocheon-gun, Chungnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/72/5cb2d506-a597-488a-9883-5c6b92cc4f6d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Clam of fast-paced tidal flat
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Tidal Flats in the Sand, Boryeong Muchangpo &amp;amp; Seocheon Chunjangdae Beach
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It leaves the Sokdong tidal flat and heads to the coast of Boryeong. It passes through Namdang Port, which shakes with cockle in winter when it is winter, and reaches Daecheon Port. The Boryeong Mud Festival, beloved by the world, is held here. The beach is proud of the long sandy beaches of the West Coast. Thanks to the festival, there are plenty of accommodation facilities along the coast.
   &lt;br/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you want to enjoy swimming and shellfish more quietly and leisurely, go to Muchangpo. Muchangpo, which opened the first beach in the West Sea, is popular with family travelers thanks to its soft sandy beach and peaceful atmosphere.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Muchangpo Beach where the water falls out and reveals the flesh - Seocheon-gun, Chungnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/72/209ad799-dc22-49b7-8b6c-8e1d1857e36d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Muchangpo Beach where the water falls out and reveals the flesh
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   At low tide, you can catch shellfish in the sand for added fun.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Crab caught in Muchangpo Tidal Flat - Seocheon-gun, Chungnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/72/9004de06-489f-421b-abdd-94ef4533404d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Crab caught in Muchangpo Tidal Flat
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Not only that. Three or four times a month, “Moses&#39; Miracle” unfolds in front of Muchangpo.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Barnacles caught in Muchangpo Tidal Flat - Seocheon-gun, Chungnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/72/e5e0cfe8-9b66-4d62-bb70-e92055d0d14f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Barnacles caught in Muchangpo Tidal Flat
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   When the time comes, you can enjoy a mysterious and fun experience of catching sea cucumbers, seashells, and octopus along the sea path that leads to Seokdae-do, 1.5 km away.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Exciting tidal flat experience for both children and adults - Seocheon-gun, Chungnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/72/bfe1de24-6ac9-4c3d-8486-81da27751018.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Exciting tidal flat experience for both children and adults
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   This year, three days from August 14, the Muchangpo Mystery Sea Road Festival will be held.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Exciting tidal flat experience for both children and adults - Seocheon-gun, Chungnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/72/deb20167-044f-4d12-897c-37418975b261.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Exciting tidal flat experience for both children and adults
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If there is Muchangpo in Boryeong, there is Chunjangdae in Seocheon. Chunjangdae Beach, filled with lush pine trees and soft sand, can be used for fine sandy beaches, shellfish and camping.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Chunjangdae beach where you can enjoy tidal-flat experience - Seocheon-gun, Chungnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/72/6282477c-2a50-4a21-bfc5-36a7bd5bbace.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Chunjangdae beach where you can enjoy tidal-flat experience
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   At low tide, shellfish can be caught in the sand. The clam and the clam are caught. After the water has drained, you can gently step on the sand tidal flats to reveal the clams.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;14&#34; id3=&#34;15&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Chunjangdae beach, where you can enjoy bathing - Seocheon-gun, Chungnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/72/28455b2b-4c80-4a43-9b84-9e8f8bb4b724.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Chunjangdae beach, where you can enjoy bathing
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   You can enjoy fresh seafood at Hongwon Port and Maryangpo-gu, located near the coast of Chunjang Dae Beach.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;16&#34; id3=&#34;16&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Camping in Haesongrim which surrounds Chunjangdae Beach - Seocheon-gun, Chungnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/72/85f4b9c7-0e94-44b6-a6e4-472ffea8e3f0.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Camping in Haesongrim which surrounds Chunjangdae Beach
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Remember that Maryangpo-gu&#39;s fall is one of the best spots in the West Coast along with Muchangpo.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;18&#34; id3=&#34;17&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A shade curtain where you can relax looking at the sea from the sea - Seocheon-gun, Chungnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/72/8118ffa9-db76-4224-a5a1-687a3555dd73.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A shade curtain where you can relax looking at the sea from the sea
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Seocheon representative eco-travel! Wol-ha Castle &amp;amp; Sundori-ri Tidal Flat Experience
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The Wolheung Tidal Flat Village, famous for its “taste shellfish,” is crowded with people from all over the country during the holiday season. Unlike the quiet name of &#39;Castle under the Moonlight&#39;, visitors are filled with tidal flats.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;18&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;High Tide in the Wol-ha Castle Tidal Flat Village - Seocheon-gun, Chungnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/72/045abaf9-614d-468c-8a30-c21f6c281cec.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     High Tide in the Wol-ha Castle Tidal Flat Village
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Designated as a fishing village in 2002, an experience program for catching clams, lilies, donjuk, and clams began.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;19&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Low tide at Wolha Castle Tidal Flat Village - Seocheon-gun, Chungnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/72/f4be6a0b-099f-4929-8253-0b3cec6a9402.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Low tide at Wolha Castle Tidal Flat Village
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The long clam-like clam is very popular because of its unique appearance and unusual harvesting methods.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;20&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Experience visitors catching shellfish on the Tidal Flats - Seocheon-gun, Chungnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/72/11f05a07-4984-45a8-85f9-b48aba678eaa.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Experience visitors catching shellfish on the Tidal Flats
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   When the water runs out, you pay the entrance fee (5,000 won). Homina hooks, boots and other equipment are rented separately (1000 won each). If you have prepared in advance, just enter. The clams and donjuk are found throughout the wide tidal flats, and clams are found in pairs.
   &lt;br/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;21&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Entrance to Wolheseong Tidal Flat Village - Seocheon-gun, Chungnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/72/30e7e871-dce8-4df3-8cf5-f08f8b4e1d57.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Entrance to Wolheseong Tidal Flat Village
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Let&#39;s learn how to catch a clam for a while. Use a shovel to gently roll the mud flats and add salt to the eight-shaped hole. Then the clam will appear slightly out of the hole. If you are in a hurry, wait. After a while, you can take out the clam that has been soaked over the sand tidal flat and you&#39;re done!
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;22&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Dongjuk and Flavored Clams from Wolhaseong Tidal Flat Village - Seocheon-gun, Chungnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/72/3a71c8b7-7bdc-40d5-aef1-94de60a632e0.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Dongjuk and Flavored Clams from Wolhaseong Tidal Flat Village
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Here, Seocheon-ri&#39;s other tidal-flat experience village and Sunni-ri are also indispensable. Wolhaseong Tidal Flat Experience Village and Sundae-ri Tidal Flat Experience Village, about 3.4km away, are also representative of Seocheon.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;23&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The high tide of the Sundae-ri Tidal Flat Village - Seocheon-gun, Chungnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/72/0e6536e1-375e-4099-9d06-09339fce6edd.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The high tide of the Sundae-ri Tidal Flat Village
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   When you pay for the experience fee (5,000 won for adults and 3000 won for underage), a wide tidal flat spreads around the road leading to Ssangdo.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;14&#34; id3=&#34;24&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Low tide at Sundori Tidal Flat Village - Seocheon-gun, Chungnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/72/05b57008-930d-4cc8-bd20-c69c930ea6e1.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Low tide at Sundori Tidal Flat Village
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In Sundori, there are free buses that run to places where there is a lot of copper. However, more than 10 people must gather.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;16&#34; id3=&#34;25&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Visitors are harvesting clams from Sunshin-ri Tidal Flat - Seocheon-gun, Chungnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/72/ddb97574-24db-47d7-9610-8391ca8d73f8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Visitors are harvesting clams from Sunshin-ri Tidal Flat
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    As mentioned above, to properly enjoy the tidal flat experience, it is necessary to check the “watery time”. National Maritime Research Institute or Wolhaseong Tidal Flat Experience Village (041-952-7060)
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.westsea.net/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;[새창열림]‘월하성갯벌체험마을’ 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
     http://www.westsea.net/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Sundae-ri Tidal Flat Experience Village (041-952-5212)
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://cafe.daum.net/sundolri/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;[새창열림]‘선도리갯벌체험마을’ 정보 페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
     http://cafe.daum.net/sundolri/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    You can contact
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;18&#34; id3=&#34;26&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Visitors are harvesting clams from Sunshin-ri Tidal Flat - Seocheon-gun, Chungnam, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/72/f4b78d94-c439-4668-a44b-e7988d7c1068.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Visitors are harvesting clams from Sunshin-ri Tidal Flat
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel info
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Nearby restaurants
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Hongseong Deer Garden: Wolgye 2-gil, Hongseong-eup, Hongseong-gun / Korean Beef Ribs / 041-634-0100
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Boryeong Myeongga: Small Orat 4-gil, Boryeong-si / Hanwoo, Korean / 041-936-3338
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Seocheon Surawon: Jangsan-ro, Janghang-eup, Seocheon-gun / Hanwoo / 041-956-6250
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Seocheon Halmae Onset: Changseon 1-ri, Janghang-eup, Seocheon-gun / Agu Jjim / 041-956-4860
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.onjungjib.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.onjungjib.com/
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Seocheon Beach Sashimi Restaurant: Seochun-gun Seomyeon Chunjang-daero / Once, Kalguksu / 041-953-7000
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Accommodation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Hongseong Hot Spring Tourist Hotel: Naepo-ro, Hongseong-eup, Hongseong-gun, Chungnam / 041-633-7777
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.hongsungspa.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.hongsungspa.com/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Boryeong Muchangpovice Palace: Doksan-ri, Uncheon-eup, Boryeong-si / 041-939-5757
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.beachepalace.co.kr/bp/kor/index.do&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.beachepalace.co.kr/bp/kor/index.do
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Boryeong Hanwha Resort Daecheon Paros: Boryeong-si Beach 3-gil / 041-931-5500
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.hanwharesort.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.hanwharesort.co.kr
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Seocheon Beachtel: Seoin-ro, Seocheon-gun / 041-952-9566
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.seocheonbeachtel.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.seocheonbeachtel.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was updated in July 2016. It may change afterwards, so please check before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ The information such as text, photos and videos used in this article is copyrighted by Korea Tourism Organization, so unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>