<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Paju on Korea Tour</title>
    <link>https://codecorea.github.io/tags/paju/</link>
    <description>Korea Tour (Paju)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 11:23:18 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="https://codecorea.github.io/tags/paju/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Паджу, Кёнгидо, Корея - В лагере Гривз я потомок солнца!</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/in-camp-greaves-im-a-descendant-of-the-sun-63-ru/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 11:23:18 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/in-camp-greaves-im-a-descendant-of-the-sun-63-ru/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;in-camp-greaves-im-a-descendant-of-the-sun--63&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   В лагере Гривз я потомок солнца!
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Паджу, Кёнгидо, Корея
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   `` Потомки Солнца &#39;&#39;, драма, которая нагревает 2016 год. В то же время, пара Песни Песни забрала сердца людей, и место съемок также является горячей темой. Одним из них является лагерь Гривз, который расположен в ДМЗ, как военная драма. Поскольку это предсерийная драма, декорации сняты и остаются, но как насчет того, чтобы все еще? Если вы видите маленькое знакомое пятно, например, Дежа вю, на руке Сон Чжун Ги, вы можете сделать это где угодно!
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Лагерь Гривз, войска, которые спасли Райана
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Если вы фанат военных фильмов или драм, есть место, которое откроет вам глаза и заинтересует вас. 506-й полк был главным героем американской драматической группы «Братья» и героем Райана, героем фильма «Спасение рядового Райана», в котором рассказывалось о Второй мировой войне. Это лагерь Гривз, дислоцированный в Корее.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Camp Greaves Youth Hostel - Паджу, Кёнгидо, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/71648aa6-b64f-437d-8639-9ea454db4d94.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Camp Greaves Youth Hostel
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Знакомая база Урк, занимающая большую часть фона «потомков солнца», является одной из старейших военных баз США, куда в августе 2007 года вернулось подразделение 506-го пехотного батальона 2-й дивизии, оставшееся после Соглашения о перемирии в Корее. Появление вооруженных сил настолько велико, что это может стать работой для капитана Ю. Си-дзин.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Вход в лагерь Гривз - Паджу, Кёнгидо, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/74e54eda-73ad-42c0-b289-c7b474d114e3.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Вход в лагерь Гривз
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Лагерь Гривз находится всего в 2 км от южной границы демилитаризованной зоны (ДМЗ), демилитаризованной зоны, предназначенной для предотвращения столкновений между двумя Кореями. Военные были выведены в 2004 году, но след остается нетронутым и рассказывает историю. На земельном участке площадью более 200 000 квадратных метров различные объекты, такие как ремонтная мастерская, где Сонг Чжун Ги совершал великие действия на сцене боевых действий с американскими военными в «Потомках солнца», жилых помещениях офицеров, общежитиях и Гимназии сохранились как есть. Оно того стоит.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Единица марки с облегчением салюта. - Паджу, Кёнгидо, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/34c685c0-f4ea-4331-900a-2217ac5027f6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Единица марки с облегчением салюта.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Несмотря на достаточную культурную ценность, лагерь Гривз, который мог быть снесен, был преобразован в центр по обеспечению мира и безопасности для гражданского населения после усилий Паю, Кёнгидо. В дополнение к различным впечатлениям, таким как безопасный туризм и экологический опыт DMZ, к нам пришло первое молодежное общежитие, которое может провести ночь на гражданской линии контроля доступа (гражданская линия связи).
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Гимназии используются для различных мероприятий, таких как кинофестивали - Паджу, Кёнгидо, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/f65f6873-e6af-47dc-9a49-0f2f33e2e34a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Гимназии используются для различных мероприятий, таких как кинофестивали
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Армия? Молодежный хостел?
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Чтобы посетить лагерь Гривз, вы должны сначала обратиться к военным. Волнение перед открытым Мостом Объединения взволновано бесчисленными разновидностями баррикад и захваченными солдатами, которые тщательно проверяют свои удостоверения личности. Беззаботный разум падает перед входом в колючую проволоку Лагеря Гривз, которая похожа на военную часть со словами «Нет входа».
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Смущающе похож на воинские части - Паджу, Кёнгидо, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/07fef590-48f5-4fe6-93a8-517a4d31cff5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Смущающе похож на воинские части
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Молодежное общежитие, переоборудованное из четверти американских офицеров, рассчитано на 240 человек. На первом этаже расположены офисы и небольшие аудитории, на втором и третьем этажах - помещения, а на четвертом этаже - аудитории и рестораны для внутренних мероприятий. Если вы столкнетесь с тремя видами сетов, вы будете просветлены тем фактом, что вы можете увидеть военные кварталы, жилье, напоминающее армейские кварталы, еду, которую используют военные, и Nara Love Concert, музыкальный концерт, которым пользуются силовики 1-й дивизии.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Еда тоже! - Паджу, Кёнгидо, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/e165bf8d-d2a6-45f6-a9ff-c147a59f6390.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Еда тоже!
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Он не имеет учебных заведений, таких как физическая подготовка, но приветствует тех, кто ищет уникальный опыт безопасности, используя уникальность гражданской линии. DMZ 1129 - это обязательная программа полевых поездок на день, две ночи, две ночи и три ночи. В ней рассматриваются близлежащие достопримечательности, такие как 3-й тоннель, обсерватория Дора, станция Дорасан и парк мира Дорасан, для решения специальных задач в рабочей книге. способ. Программа, которая означает 1129 дней долгой войны, популярна, потому что она может естественно узнать о DMZ и реальности нынешнего разделения между Севером и Югом.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Ученики средней школы Daesung осматривают выставочный зал DMZ - Паджу, Кёнгидо, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/ef924961-f689-4851-9645-7b3421d2288f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Ученики средней школы Daesung осматривают выставочный зал DMZ
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Кроме того, чтобы удовлетворить вкусы различных участников, от учеников начальной школы до учеников старших классов, различные программы, такие как игры ОХ безопасности, объединение, мини-jangseung или создание сажи, экспресс-выбор воина, игровая площадка и сложные игры. DMZ Golden Bell готовы.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Ученики средней школы Daesung делают групповые фотографии - Паджу, Кёнгидо, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/d0296c2b-6a4e-426a-a41b-41763df090c0.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Ученики средней школы Daesung делают групповые фотографии
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   В конце мероприятия, «Молитва о мире», написанная молодым студентом, была написана в одном письме.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Студенты в программе «Стратегическое домино» - Паджу, Кёнгидо, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/133d6af9-9f83-439e-bd04-18f903f39b2f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Студенты в программе «Стратегическое домино»
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   В дополнение к программе опыта, Кэмп Гривз также встретится с посторонними различными способами, включая использование тренажерного зала в качестве места проведения церемонии открытия Международного фестиваля документальных фильмов DMZ. Это более ценно и значимо только потому, что вы можете испытать единственный сайт DMZ, который содержит боль разделения. Разве не время, чтобы поднять желание объединения через Лагерь Гривз, является ключом к нашему объединению?
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Пожелания участников, которые настаивали на «объединении двух Корей», передаются в их сердцах. - Паджу, Кёнгидо, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/f0dcf781-f4cd-4a1c-976b-ce2f831be1c5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Пожелания участников, которые настаивали на «объединении двух Корей», передаются в их сердцах.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Информация о путешествии
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Лагерные наголенники
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Адрес: 137, Красный Крест, Гунна-Мён, Паджу-Си, Кёнгидо
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Контакт: 031-953-6970
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://dmzcamp131.or.kr/common/include/site_main.php&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://dmzcamp131.or.kr/common/include/site_main.php
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Рестораны рядом
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    - Деревня Тонгил Деревня Джангконг: 64 Тонгилчон-гил, Гунна-Мён, Паю-си, Кёнгидо / Еда Джангданконг / 031-954-3443
    &lt;br/&gt;
    - Деревня Тонгил Донгсан Тофу: 480, Пилсеунг-ро, Танхён-Мён, Паю-си, Кёнгидо / Чхонгукьянгсик, Тофу Боссам, тушеное мясо с грибами тофу / 031-945-2114
    &lt;br/&gt;
    - Дом ивы: 881 Юлгок-ро, Папёнг-Мён, Паджу-си, Кёнгидо / Угорь на гриле, Монтан / 031-952-8285
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Близлежащие достопримечательности
     &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    3-й туннель: 210-358, 3-х туннельный туннель, Гунна-Мьен, Паджу-си, Кёнгидо, Корея / 3-й туннельный туристический информационный центр, 031-940-8526
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    - Обсерватория Дора: 310, 3Эонгул-ро, Чангдан-Мён, Паю-си, Кёнгидо / Туристический офис DMZ 031-954-0303
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Дорасан: 307, Хоуп-ро, Джангдан-Мён, Паджу-си, Кёнгидо / 031-953-3334
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ Приведенная выше информация была написана в марте 2016 года. Впоследствии она может измениться, поэтому, пожалуйста, проверьте это перед поездкой.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Информация, такая как текст, фотографии и видео, используемые в этой статье, защищены авторским правом Корейской туристической организации, поэтому несанкционированное использование статьи запрещено.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Corée - Au Camp Greaves, je suis un descendant du soleil!</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/in-camp-greaves-im-a-descendant-of-the-sun-63-fr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 11:21:04 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/in-camp-greaves-im-a-descendant-of-the-sun-63-fr/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;in-camp-greaves-im-a-descendant-of-the-sun--63&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Au Camp Greaves, je suis un descendant du soleil!
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Corée
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   `` The Descendants of the Sun &#39;&#39;, un drame qui se réchauffe en 2016. Dans le même temps, Songsong Couple a emporté le cœur des gens, et le lieu de tournage est également un sujet brûlant. L&#39;un d&#39;eux est Camp Greaves, qui est situé dans la DMZ comme un drame militaire. Comme il s&#39;agit d&#39;un drame de pré-production, le décor est démoli et reste, mais qu&#39;en est-il encore? Si vous voyez un petit endroit familier comme Deja vu le long de la main de Song Joong-gi, vous pouvez le faire n&#39;importe où!
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Camp Greaves, des troupes qui ont sauvé Ryan
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Si vous êtes un fan de films ou de drames de guerre, il y a un endroit qui vous ouvrira les yeux et vous intéressera. Le 506th Regiment était le personnage principal du drame américain Band of Brothers et le héros de Ryan, le héros du film &#34;Saving Private Ryan&#34;, qui mettait en vedette la Seconde Guerre mondiale. Ce sont des Camp Greaves stationnés en Corée.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Auberge de jeunesse Camp Greaves - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/71648aa6-b64f-437d-8639-9ea454db4d94.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Auberge de jeunesse Camp Greaves
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   La base familière d&#39;Urk, qui occupe la majeure partie des origines des «descendants du soleil», est l&#39;une des plus anciennes bases militaires américaines où la 2e division du 506e bataillon d&#39;infanterie, restée après l&#39;accord d&#39;armistice de la guerre de Corée, y est retournée en août 2007. Actuellement , l&#39;apparence des forces militaires est si élevée que cela pourrait être un travail pour le capitaine Yu Si-jin.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Entrée au camp Greaves - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/74e54eda-73ad-42c0-b289-c7b474d114e3.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Entrée au camp Greaves
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Le camp Greaves est situé à seulement 2 km de la limite sud de la zone démilitarisée (DMZ), une zone démilitarisée conçue pour éviter les affrontements entre les deux Corées. L&#39;armée s&#39;est retirée en 2004, mais la trace reste intacte et raconte l&#39;histoire. Sur un terrain de plus de 200 000 mètres carrés, diverses installations telles que l&#39;atelier de réparation où Song Joong-gi a effectué une grande action sur la scène des combats avec l&#39;armée américaine dans les `` Descendants du soleil &#39;&#39;, les logements des officiers, les dortoirs et les gymnases sont conservés tels quels. Ça vaut le coup.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Marque d&#39;unité avec relief de salut. - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/34c685c0-f4ea-4331-900a-2217ac5027f6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Marque d&#39;unité avec relief de salut.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Malgré une valeur culturelle suffisante, le camp Greaves, qui risquait d&#39;être démoli, a été transformé en un centre d&#39;expériences de paix et de sécurité pour les civils après les efforts de Paju, Gyeonggi-do. En plus de diverses expériences telles que le tourisme de sécurité et l&#39;expérience écologique DMZ, la première auberge de jeunesse qui peut passer la nuit dans la ligne de contrôle d&#39;accès civile (ligne de communication civile) nous est venue.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Gymnases utilisés pour divers événements tels que les festivals de films - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/f65f6873-e6af-47dc-9a49-0f2f33e2e34a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Gymnases utilisés pour divers événements tels que les festivals de films
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Armée? Auberge de jeunesse?
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Pour visiter Camp Greaves, vous devez d&#39;abord faire une demande auprès des militaires. L&#39;excitation devant le pont d&#39;unification ouvert est ravie des innombrables variétés de barricades et des soldats capturés qui vérifient soigneusement leurs pièces d&#39;identité. L&#39;esprit au cœur nu tombe devant l&#39;entrée du fil de fer barbelé de Camp Greaves, qui est comme une unité militaire avec les mots «Aucune entrée».
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Similairement confus avec les unités militaires - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/07fef590-48f5-4fe6-93a8-517a4d31cff5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Similairement confus avec les unités militaires
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   L&#39;auberge de jeunesse, rénovée à partir d&#39;un quart des quartiers des officiers militaires américains, est conçue pour accueillir jusqu&#39;à 240 personnes. Il y a des bureaux et des petits auditoriums au premier étage, des quartiers aux deuxième et troisième étages, et des auditoriums et des restaurants pour les activités intérieures au quatrième étage. Si vous rencontrez trois types de décors, vous serez éclairé par le fait que vous pouvez voir les quartiers militaires, des logements qui rappellent les quartiers de l&#39;armée, les repas utilisés par les militaires et le Nara Love Concert, un concert de musique apprécié par officiers de sécurité de la 1re division.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Repas aussi! - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/e165bf8d-d2a6-45f6-a9ff-c147a59f6390.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Repas aussi!
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Il ne dispose pas d&#39;installations de formation telles que la formation physique, mais accueille ceux qui recherchent des expériences de sécurité uniques en utilisant le caractère unique de la ligne civile. DMZ 1129 est un programme obligatoire d&#39;excursions pour la journée, deux nuits, deux nuits et trois nuits qui explore les attractions à proximité telles que le 3e tunnel, l&#39;observatoire de Dora, la station Dorasan et le parc Dorasan Peace Park pour résoudre des tâches spéciales dans le classeur le chemin. Le programme, qui signifie 1129 jours de longue guerre, est populaire car il peut naturellement en apprendre davantage sur la DMZ et la réalité de la division actuelle entre le Nord et le Sud.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Des lycéens de Daesung visitant le hall d&#39;exposition DMZ - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/ef924961-f689-4851-9645-7b3421d2288f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Des lycéens de Daesung visitant le hall d&#39;exposition DMZ
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   De plus, afin de satisfaire les goûts de divers participants, des élèves du primaire aux élèves du secondaire, divers programmes tels que les jeux de sécurité OX, l&#39;unification, le mini-jangseung ou la fabrication de suie, la sélection de guerriers express, la cour de jeu du camp et les défis La DMZ Golden Bell est préparée.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Les élèves du lycée de Daesung prennent des photos de groupe - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/d0296c2b-6a4e-426a-a41b-41763df090c0.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Les élèves du lycée de Daesung prennent des photos de groupe
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   À la fin de l&#39;événement, le ruban de prière pour la paix, rédigé par un jeune étudiant, a été rédigé en une seule lettre.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Étudiants du programme stratégique Domino - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/133d6af9-9f83-439e-bd04-18f903f39b2f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Étudiants du programme stratégique Domino
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   En plus du programme d&#39;expérience, Camp Greaves rencontrera également des étrangers de diverses manières, notamment en utilisant le gymnase comme lieu de l&#39;événement pour la cérémonie d&#39;ouverture du DMZ International Documentary Film Festival. Il est plus précieux et significatif que parce que vous pouvez découvrir le seul site DMZ qui contient la douleur de la division. N&#39;est-il pas temps d&#39;élever le désir d&#39;unification à travers Camp Greaves comme la clé de notre unification?
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Les souhaits des participants qui ont poussé à «l&#39;unification des deux Corées» sont transmis dans leur cœur. - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/f0dcf781-f4cd-4a1c-976b-ce2f831be1c5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Les souhaits des participants qui ont poussé à «l&#39;unification des deux Corées» sont transmis dans leur cœur.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Info voyage
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Grèves de camp
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Adresse: 137, Croix-Rouge, Gunnae-myeon, Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Contact: 031-953-6970
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://dmzcamp131.or.kr/common/include/site_main.php&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://dmzcamp131.or.kr/common/include/site_main.php
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Restaurants près de
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Tongil Village Jangkong Village: 64 Tongilchon-gil, Gunnae-myeon, Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do / Jangdankong Meal / 031-954-3443
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Tongil Dongsan Tofu Village: 480, Pilseung-ro, Tanhyeon-myeon, Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do / Cheonggukjangsik, Tofu Bossam, Potée de champignons au tofu / 031-945-2114
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Willow House: 881 Yulgok-ro, Papyeong-myeon, Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do / Anguille grillée, Maeuntang / 031-952-8285
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Attractions à proximité
     &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    -3e Tunnel: 210-358, 3 Tunnel Tunnel, Gunnae-myeon, Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea / 3rd Tunnel Tourist Information Center, 031-940-8526
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Observatoire de Dora: 310, 3Deongul-ro, Jangdan-myeon, Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do / DMZ Office du tourisme 031-954-0303
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Station Dorasan: 307, Hope-ro, Jangdan-myeon, Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do / 031-953-3334
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ Les informations ci-dessus ont été écrites en mars 2016. Elles peuvent changer par la suite, veuillez donc vérifier avant de voyager.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Les informations telles que le texte, les photos et les vidéos utilisées dans cet article sont protégées par les droits d&#39;auteur de l&#39;Organisation coréenne du tourisme, de sorte que l&#39;utilisation non autorisée de l&#39;article est interdite.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Corea - ¡En Camp Greaves, soy descendiente del sol!</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/in-camp-greaves-im-a-descendant-of-the-sun-63-es/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 11:18:52 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/in-camp-greaves-im-a-descendant-of-the-sun-63-es/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;in-camp-greaves-im-a-descendant-of-the-sun--63&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   ¡En Camp Greaves, soy descendiente del sol!
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Corea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   `` The Descendants of the Sun &#39;&#39;, un drama que calienta el 2016. Al mismo tiempo, Songsong Couple se ha llevado los corazones de las personas, y el lugar de rodaje también es un tema candente. Uno de ellos es Camp Greaves, que se encuentra en la DMZ como un drama militar. Como es un drama de preproducción, el set es demolido y permanece, pero ¿qué tal todavía? Si ves un pequeño lugar familiar como Deja vu a lo largo de la mano de Song Joong-gi, ¡puedes hacerlo en cualquier lugar!
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Camp Greaves, tropas que salvaron a Ryan
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Si eres fanático de las películas o dramas de guerra, hay un lugar que te abrirá los ojos y te interesará. El Regimiento 506 fue el personaje principal del drama estadounidense Band of Brothers, y el héroe de Ryan, el héroe de la película &#34;Salvando al soldado Ryan&#34;, que contó con la Segunda Guerra Mundial. Son Camp Greaves estacionados en Corea.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Albergue Juvenil Camp Greaves - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/71648aa6-b64f-437d-8639-9ea454db4d94.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Albergue Juvenil Camp Greaves
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   La conocida base Urk, que ocupa la mayor parte de los antecedentes de los &#34;descendientes del sol&#34;, es una de las bases militares más antiguas de los EE. UU. Donde el 506 ° Batallón de Infantería de la Segunda División, que permaneció después del Acuerdo de Armisticio de la Guerra de Corea, regresó a ella en agosto de 2007. En la actualidad , la apariencia de las fuerzas militares es tan alta que podría ser un trabajo para el Capitán Yu Si-jin.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Entrada al campamento Grebas - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/74e54eda-73ad-42c0-b289-c7b474d114e3.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Entrada al campamento Grebas
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Camp Greaves está a solo 2 km del límite sur de la zona desmilitarizada (DMZ), una zona desmilitarizada diseñada para evitar enfrentamientos entre las dos Coreas. Los militares se retiraron en 2004, pero el rastro permanece intacto y cuenta la historia. En una tierra de más de 200,000 metros cuadrados, varias instalaciones como el taller de reparación donde Song Joong-gi realizó una gran acción a través de la escena de lucha con el ejército de los EE. UU. En los `` Descendientes del Sol &#39;&#39;, alojamientos de oficiales, dormitorios y los gimnasios se conservan tal como están. Vale la pena.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Marca de la unidad con alivio de saludo. - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/34c685c0-f4ea-4331-900a-2217ac5027f6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Marca de la unidad con alivio de saludo.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   A pesar del valor cultural suficiente, Camp Greaves, que estaba en peligro de ser demolido, se transformó en una instalación de experiencia de paz y seguridad para civiles después de los esfuerzos de Paju, Gyeonggi-do. Además de varias experiencias como el turismo de seguridad y la experiencia ecológica de DMZ, se nos presentó el primer albergue juvenil que puede pasar la noche en la línea de control de acceso civil (línea de comunicación civil).
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Gimnasios utilizados para diversos eventos, como festivales de cine. - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/f65f6873-e6af-47dc-9a49-0f2f33e2e34a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Gimnasios utilizados para diversos eventos, como festivales de cine.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   ¿Ejército? ¿Albergue juvenil?
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Para visitar Camp Greaves, primero debe solicitar el servicio militar. La emoción frente al abierto Puente de Unificación está encantada con las innumerables variedades de barricadas y los soldados capturados que verifican minuciosamente sus identificaciones. La mente descorazonada se cae frente a la entrada del alambre de púas de Camp Greaves, que es como una unidad militar con las palabras &#39;Sin entrada&#39;.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Confusamente similar a las unidades militares - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/07fef590-48f5-4fe6-93a8-517a4d31cff5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Confusamente similar a las unidades militares
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   El albergue juvenil, remodelado de una cuarta parte de las dependencias de los oficiales militares de EE. UU., Está diseñado para albergar hasta 240 personas. Hay oficinas y auditorios pequeños en el primer piso, cuartos en el segundo y tercer piso, y auditorios y restaurantes para actividades en el interior en el cuarto piso. Si te encuentras con tres tipos de set, te iluminarás por el hecho de que puedes ver los barrios militares, el alojamiento que recuerda a los barrios del ejército, las comidas que usan los militares y Nara Love Concert, un concierto de música que disfrutan oficiales de seguridad de la 1ra división.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Comida también! - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/e165bf8d-d2a6-45f6-a9ff-c147a59f6390.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Comida también!
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   No cuenta con instalaciones de entrenamiento como el entrenamiento físico, pero da la bienvenida a aquellos que buscan experiencias de seguridad únicas utilizando la singularidad de la línea civil. DMZ 1129 es un programa obligatorio de excursiones para el día, dos noches, dos noches y tres noches. Explora atracciones cercanas como el 3er Túnel, el Observatorio Dora, la Estación Dorasan y el Parque de la Paz Dorasan para resolver tareas especiales en el libro de trabajo. la manera. El programa, que significa 1129 días de larga guerra, es popular porque naturalmente puede aprender sobre la DMZ y la realidad de la división actual entre el Norte y el Sur.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Estudiantes de la escuela secundaria Daesung que visitan la sala de exposiciones DMZ - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/ef924961-f689-4851-9645-7b3421d2288f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Estudiantes de la escuela secundaria Daesung que visitan la sala de exposiciones DMZ
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Además, para satisfacer los gustos de varios participantes, desde estudiantes de primaria hasta estudiantes de secundaria, diversos programas como juegos de seguridad OX, unificación, mini-jangseung o fabricación de hollín, selección de guerrero expreso, patio de juegos y desafíos. DMZ Golden Bell están preparados.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Los estudiantes de Daesung High School están tomando fotos grupales - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/d0296c2b-6a4e-426a-a41b-41763df090c0.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Los estudiantes de Daesung High School están tomando fotos grupales
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Al final del evento, la Cinta de Oración de la Paz, que fue escrita por un joven estudiante, fue escrita en una sola letra.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Alumnos en el programa de dominó estratégico(남성) - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/133d6af9-9f83-439e-bd04-18f903f39b2f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Alumnos en el programa de dominó estratégico(남성)
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Además del programa de experiencia, Camp Greaves también se reunirá con extraños de varias maneras, incluido el uso del gimnasio como sede del evento para la ceremonia de apertura del Festival Internacional de Cine Documental DMZ. Es más valioso y significativo solo porque puede experimentar el único sitio DMZ que contiene el dolor de la división. ¿No es el momento de aumentar el deseo de unificación a través de Camp Greaves ser la clave de nuestra unificación?
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Los deseos de los participantes que impulsaron la &#39;unificación de las dos Coreas&#39; se transmiten en sus corazones. - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/f0dcf781-f4cd-4a1c-976b-ce2f831be1c5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Los deseos de los participantes que impulsaron la &#39;unificación de las dos Coreas&#39; se transmiten en sus corazones.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Información de viaje
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Chicharrones
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Dirección: 137, Cruz Roja, Gunnae-myeon, Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Contacto: 031-953-6970
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://dmzcamp131.or.kr/common/include/site_main.php&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://dmzcamp131.or.kr/common/include/site_main.php
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Restaurantes cerca de
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Tongil Village Jangkong Village: 64 Tongilchon-gil, Gunnae-myeon, Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do / Jangdankong Meal / 031-954-3443
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Tongil Dongsan Tofu Village: 480, Pilseung-ro, Tanhyeon-myeon, Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do / Cheonggukjangsik, Tofu Bossam, Tofu hongo / 031-945-2114
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Willow House: 881 Yulgok-ro, Papyeong-myeon, Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do / Anguila asada, Maeuntang / 031-952-8285
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Atracciones cercanas
     &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    -3er túnel: 210-358, 3 túnel túnel, Gunnae-myeon, Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Corea / 3er túnel Centro de información turística, 031-940-8526
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Dora Observatory: 310, 3Deongul-ro, Jangdan-myeon, Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do / DMZ Oficina de Turismo 031-954-0303
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Estación Dorasan: 307, Hope-ro, Jangdan-myeon, Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do / 031-953-3334
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ La información anterior se escribió en marzo de 2016. Puede cambiar después, así que verifíquela antes de viajar.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ La información como texto, fotos y videos utilizados en este artículo tiene copyright de la Organización de Turismo de Corea, por lo que está prohibido el uso no autorizado del artículo.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea - In Camp Greaves bin ich ein Nachkomme der Sonne!</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/in-camp-greaves-im-a-descendant-of-the-sun-63-de/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 11:16:31 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/in-camp-greaves-im-a-descendant-of-the-sun-63-de/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;in-camp-greaves-im-a-descendant-of-the-sun--63&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   In Camp Greaves bin ich ein Nachkomme der Sonne!
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &#34;The Descendants of the Sun&#34;, ein Drama, das sich 2016 erwärmt. Gleichzeitig hat Songsong Couple den Menschen das Herz genommen, und der Drehort ist auch ein heißes Thema. Eines davon ist Camp Greaves, das sich wie ein Militärdrama in der DMZ befindet. Da es sich um ein Vorproduktionsdrama handelt, wird das Set abgerissen und bleibt erhalten, aber wie wäre es noch? Wenn Sie einen kleinen vertrauten Ort wie Deja vu an Song Joong-gis Hand sehen, können Sie es überall tun!
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Camp Greaves, Truppen, die Ryan gerettet haben
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Wenn Sie ein Fan von Kriegsfilmen oder Dramen sind, gibt es einen Ort, der Ihre Augen öffnet und Sie interessiert. Das 506. Regiment war die Hauptfigur des amerikanischen Dramas Band of Brothers und der Held von Ryan, dem Helden des Films &#34;Saving Private Ryan&#34; mit dem Zweiten Weltkrieg. Es sind Camp Greaves, die in Korea stationiert sind.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Camp Greaves Jugendherberge - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/71648aa6-b64f-437d-8639-9ea454db4d94.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Camp Greaves Jugendherberge
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Die bekannte Urk-Basis, die den größten Teil des Hintergrunds der &#34;Sonnennachkommen&#34; einnimmt, ist eine der ältesten US-Militärbasen, in die das 506. Infanteriebataillon der 2. Division, das nach dem Waffenstillstandsabkommen über den Koreakrieg verblieben war, im August 2007 zurückgekehrt ist Das Auftreten der Streitkräfte ist so hoch, dass es für Kapitän Yu Si-jin eine Aufgabe sein könnte.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Eingang zu Camp Greaves - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/74e54eda-73ad-42c0-b289-c7b474d114e3.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Eingang zu Camp Greaves
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Camp Greaves liegt nur 2 km von der südlichen Grenze der entmilitarisierten Zone (DMZ) entfernt, einer entmilitarisierten Zone, die Zusammenstöße zwischen den beiden Koreas verhindern soll. Das Militär zog sich 2004 zurück, aber die Spur bleibt intakt und erzählt die Geschichte. Auf dem mehr als 200.000 Quadratmeter großen Land wurden verschiedene Einrichtungen wie die Reparaturwerkstatt, in der Song Joong-gi mit dem US-Militär in den &#34;Nachkommen der Sonne&#34;, Offiziersunterkünften, Schlafsälen und Turnhallen bleiben so wie sie sind erhalten. Es lohnt sich.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Einheitsmarke mit Grußrelief. - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/34c685c0-f4ea-4331-900a-2217ac5027f6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Einheitsmarke mit Grußrelief.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Trotz des ausreichenden kulturellen Wertes wurde Camp Greaves, das vom Abriss bedroht war, nach den Bemühungen von Paju, Gyeonggi-do, in eine Einrichtung für Friedens- und Sicherheitserfahrungen für Zivilisten umgewandelt. Neben verschiedenen Erfahrungen wie Sicherheitstourismus und ökologischen Erfahrungen der DMZ kam die erste Jugendherberge zu uns, die die Nacht in der zivilen Zugangskontrolllinie (zivile Kommunikationslinie) verbringen kann.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Turnhallen für verschiedene Veranstaltungen wie Filmfestivals - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/f65f6873-e6af-47dc-9a49-0f2f33e2e34a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Turnhallen für verschiedene Veranstaltungen wie Filmfestivals
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Heer? Jugendherberge?
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Um Camp Greaves zu besuchen, müssen Sie sich zuerst beim Militär bewerben. Die Aufregung vor der offenen Vereinigungsbrücke ist begeistert von den unzähligen Barrikaden und den gefangenen Soldaten, die ihre Ausweise gründlich überprüfen. Der nackte Geist fällt vor dem Eingang zum Stacheldraht von Camp Greaves nieder, der wie eine Militäreinheit mit den Worten &#34;Kein Eintritt&#34; ist.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Verwirrend ähnlich wie Militäreinheiten - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/07fef590-48f5-4fe6-93a8-517a4d31cff5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Verwirrend ähnlich wie Militäreinheiten
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Die Jugendherberge, die aus einem Viertel des Quartiers der US-Militäroffiziere umgebaut wurde, bietet Platz für bis zu 240 Personen. Im ersten Stock befinden sich Büros und kleine Auditorien, im zweiten und dritten Stock Quartiere sowie im vierten Stock Auditorien und Restaurants für Indoor-Aktivitäten. Wenn Sie auf drei Arten von Sets stoßen, werden Sie von der Tatsache erleuchtet sein, dass Sie die Militärquartiere sehen können, Unterkünfte, die an die Armeequartiere erinnern, Mahlzeiten, die vom Militär verwendet werden, und Nara Love Concert, ein Musikkonzert, das von genossen wird Sicherheitsbeamte der 1. Division.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Essen auch! - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/e165bf8d-d2a6-45f6-a9ff-c147a59f6390.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Essen auch!
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Es gibt keine Trainingseinrichtungen wie körperliches Training, aber es begrüßt diejenigen, die einzigartige Sicherheitserfahrungen mit der Einzigartigkeit der zivilen Linie suchen. DMZ 1129 ist ein obligatorisches Exkursionsprogramm für den Tag, zwei Nächte, zwei Nächte und drei Nächte. Es erkundet nahe gelegene Sehenswürdigkeiten wie den 3. Tunnel, das Dora-Observatorium, die Dorasan-Station und den Dorasan-Friedenspark, um spezielle Aufgaben im Arbeitsbuch Das zu lösen der Weg. Das Programm, das 1129 Tage langen Krieges bedeutet, ist beliebt, weil es natürlich etwas über die DMZ und die Realität der gegenwärtigen Trennung zwischen Nord und Süd lernen kann.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Schüler der Daesung High School besuchen die DMZ-Ausstellungshalle - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/ef924961-f689-4851-9645-7b3421d2288f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Schüler der Daesung High School besuchen die DMZ-Ausstellungshalle
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Um den Geschmack verschiedener Teilnehmer, von Grundschülern bis zu Schülern, zu befriedigen, werden verschiedene Programme wie Sicherheits-OX-Spiele, Vereinigung, Mini-Jangseung oder Rußherstellung, Express-Kriegerauswahl, Camp-Spielplatz und Herausforderung angeboten DMZ Golden Bell sind vorbereitet.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Schüler der Daesung High School machen Gruppenfotos - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/d0296c2b-6a4e-426a-a41b-41763df090c0.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Schüler der Daesung High School machen Gruppenfotos
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Am Ende der Veranstaltung wurde das Friedensgebetsband, das von einem jungen Studenten geschrieben wurde, in einem einzigen Brief geschrieben.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Studenten im Strategic Domino Program - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/133d6af9-9f83-439e-bd04-18f903f39b2f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Studenten im Strategic Domino Program
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Neben dem Erlebnisprogramm wird Camp Greaves auch auf verschiedene Weise mit Außenstehenden zusammentreffen, unter anderem im Fitnessstudio als Veranstaltungsort für die Eröffnungsfeier des DMZ International Documentary Film Festival. Es ist nur deshalb wertvoller und aussagekräftiger, weil Sie die einzige Site-DMZ erleben können, die den Schmerz der Teilung enthält. Ist nicht die Zeit, den Wunsch nach Vereinigung durch Camp Greaves zu wecken, der Schlüssel zu unserer Vereinigung?
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#39;Die Wünsche der Teilnehmer, die die &#34;Vereinigung der beiden Koreas&#34; vorangetrieben haben, werden in ihren Herzen vermittelt. - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#39; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/f0dcf781-f4cd-4a1c-976b-ce2f831be1c5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Die Wünsche der Teilnehmer, die die &#34;Vereinigung der beiden Koreas&#34; vorangetrieben haben, werden in ihren Herzen vermittelt.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Reiseinformationen
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Lager Beinschienen
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Adresse: 137, Rotes Kreuz, Gunnae-myeon, Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Kontakt: 031-953-6970
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://dmzcamp131.or.kr/common/include/site_main.php&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://dmzcamp131.or.kr/common/include/site_main.php
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Restaurants in der Nähe
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Tongil Village Jangkong Village: 64 Tongilchon-Gil, Gunnae-Myeon, Paju-Si, Gyeonggi-Do / Jangdankong-Mahlzeit / 031-954-3443
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Tongil Dongsan Tofu Village: 480, Pilseung-ro, Tanhyeon-myeon, Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do / Cheonggukjangsik, Tofu Bossam, Tofu-Pilz-Hotpot / 031-945-2114
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Willow House: 881 Yulgok-ro, Papyeong-myeon, Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do / Gegrillter Aal, Maeuntang / 031-952-8285
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     In der Nähe Sehenswürdigkeiten
     &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    -3. Tunnel: 210-358, 3-Tunnel-Tunnel, Gunnae-myeon, Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea / 3. Tunnel Touristeninformationszentrum, 031-940-8526
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Dora-Observatorium: 310, 3Deongul-ro, Jangdan-myeon, Paju-si, Tourismusbüro Gyeonggi-do / DMZ 031-954-0303
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Dorasan Station: 307, Hope-ro, Jangdan-myeon, Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do / 031-953-3334
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ Die oben genannten Informationen wurden im März 2016 verfasst. Sie können sich später ändern. Bitte überprüfen Sie dies, bevor Sie reisen.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Die in diesem Artikel verwendeten Informationen wie Text, Fotos und Videos sind von der Korea Tourism Organization urheberrechtlich geschützt. Daher ist die unbefugte Verwendung des Artikels untersagt.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>韩国京畿道坡州市 - 在格里夫斯营，我是太阳的后裔！</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/in-camp-greaves-im-a-descendant-of-the-sun-63-zh-cn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 11:14:18 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/in-camp-greaves-im-a-descendant-of-the-sun-63-zh-cn/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;in-camp-greaves-im-a-descendant-of-the-sun--63&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   在格里夫斯营，我是太阳的后裔！
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    韩国京畿道坡州市
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   太阳的后裔，这是一部在2016年升温的戏剧。与此同时，松松夫妇也打动了人们的心灵，拍摄地点也是一个热门话题。 其中之一是格里夫斯营，它像军事戏剧一样位于非军事区。 因为是前期制作的话剧，所以场景被拆毁了，但是仍然怎么样？ 如果您在Song Joong-gi的手上看到一个像Deja vu一样熟悉的地方，则可以在任何地方进行！
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   格里夫斯营，挽救莱恩的部队
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   如果您是战争电影或戏剧的爱好者，那么有个地方可以让您大开眼界并引起您的兴趣。 第506团是美国戏剧《兄弟乐队》的主角，也是瑞恩的英雄，而瑞恩的英雄则是电影《拯救大兵瑞恩》（Saving Private Ryan）。 他们是驻扎在韩国的营地营。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;营格雷夫斯青年旅舍 - 韩国京畿道坡州市 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/71648aa6-b64f-437d-8639-9ea454db4d94.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     营格雷夫斯青年旅舍
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   熟悉的Urk基地占据了大多数“太阳后裔”背景，是美国最古老的军事基地之一，第2师第506步兵营在朝鲜战争停战协议之后仍在2007年8月重返该基地。 ，军队的外表如此之高，以至于上司金可能是一项工作。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;格里夫营地入口 - 韩国京畿道坡州市 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/74e54eda-73ad-42c0-b289-c7b474d114e3.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     格里夫营地入口
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   格里夫斯营地距离非军事区（DMZ）的南端仅2公里，该非军事区旨在防止两个朝鲜之间发生冲突。 军队于2004年撤退，但踪迹保持原样并讲述了故事。 在占地200,000平方米的土地上，有各种设施，例如维修车间，宋重基在美军在``太阳的后裔&#39;&#39;的战斗现场通过战斗场面表现出色，军官的住宿，宿舍和 体育馆保持原样。 这是值得的。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;带有敬礼救济的单位标记。 - 韩国京畿道坡州市 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/34c685c0-f4ea-4331-900a-2217ac5027f6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     带有敬礼救济的单位标记。
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   尽管具有足够的文化价值，但在京畿道坡州市的努力下，处于被拆除危险的格里夫斯营地已转变为平民的和平与安全体验设施。 除了诸如安全旅游和DMZ生态体验之类的各种体验外，第一家可以在民用出入控制线（民用通讯线）过夜的青年旅馆也来到了我们这里。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;用于电影节等各种活动的体育馆 - 韩国京畿道坡州市 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/f65f6873-e6af-47dc-9a49-0f2f33e2e34a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     用于电影节等各种活动的体育馆
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   军队？ 青年旅馆？
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   要访问格里夫斯营，您必须先向军队申请。 敞开的统一桥前的兴奋令无数种类繁多的路障和被俘的士兵彻底检查自己的身份证而激动不已。 赤手空拳落在营地铁丝网的入口前，就像一个军事单位，上面写着“禁止进入”。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;令人迷惑的类似于军事单位 - 韩国京畿道坡州市 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/07fef590-48f5-4fe6-93a8-517a4d31cff5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     令人迷惑的类似于军事单位
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   这家青年旅馆是从美国四分之一军官宿舍改建而成，可容纳多达240人。 一楼有办公室和小型礼堂，二楼和三楼有宿舍，四楼有用于室内活动的礼堂和餐厅。 如果您遇到三种场景，您会发现一个事实，那就是军事宿舍，让人联想起军队宿舍的住宿，军队所用的饭菜以及由奈良之恋举办的音乐音乐会Nara Love Concert 第一师保安官
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;吃饭呢！ - 韩国京畿道坡州市 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/e165bf8d-d2a6-45f6-a9ff-c147a59f6390.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     吃饭呢！
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   它没有诸如体育锻炼之类的培训设施，但是欢迎那些使用民用线路的独特性寻求独特安全经验的人。 DMZ 1129是一天，两个晚上，两个晚上和三个晚上的强制性实地考察计划，它探索了附近的景点，例如第三隧道，多拉天文台，多拉桑站和多拉桑和平公园，以解决工作簿中的特殊任务 方式。 该程序意味着1129天的漫长战争，之所以受欢迎，是因为它可以自然地了解DMZ以及当前南北分歧的实际情况。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;大成高中生参观DMZ展厅 - 韩国京畿道坡州市 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/ef924961-f689-4851-9645-7b3421d2288f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     大成高中生参观DMZ展厅
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   此外，为了满足从小学生到高中生的各种参与者的口味，各种程序，例如安全OX游戏，统一，迷你长城或烟灰制作，特选战士，营地游戏场和挑战赛 DMZ金钟已准备就绪。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;大成高中生合影 - 韩国京畿道坡州市 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/d0296c2b-6a4e-426a-a41b-41763df090c0.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     大成高中生合影
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   活动结束时，由一位年轻学生写的和平祈祷丝带写在一封信中。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;战略多米诺骨计划的学生 - 韩国京畿道坡州市 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/133d6af9-9f83-439e-bd04-18f903f39b2f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     战略多米诺骨计划的学生
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   除体验计划外，格里夫斯营还将以各种方式与局外人会面，包括将体育馆用作DMZ国际纪录片电影节开幕式的活动场地。 仅因为您可以体验到唯一包含分裂痛苦的站点DMZ，所以它更加珍贵和有意义。 通过格里夫斯营提高对统一的渴望的时间不是我们统一的关键吗？
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;推动“两国统一”的参与者的愿望在他们心中传达。 - 韩国京畿道坡州市 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/f0dcf781-f4cd-4a1c-976b-ce2f831be1c5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     推动“两国统一”的参与者的愿望在他们心中传达。
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   旅游信息
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     阵营胫甲
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -地址：京畿道坡州市群内面红十字会137
    &lt;br/&gt;
    联络电话：031-953-6970
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://dmzcamp131.or.kr/common/include/site_main.php&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://dmzcamp131.or.kr/common/include/site_main.php
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     附近的餐厅
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -桐乡村江岗村：京畿道坡州市市江面面桐村街64号/江丹岗粉/ 031-954-3443
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -同仁东山豆腐村：京畿道坡州市比贤路，延贤面面480 /庆州将军，豆腐老板，豆腐蘑菇火锅/ 031-945-2114
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Willow House：京畿道坡州市八平面裕国路881 /湄东当烤鳗鱼/ 031-952-8285
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     附近景点
     &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    -3号隧道：韩国京畿道坡州市群内面3号隧道210-358，/ 3号隧道游客咨询中心，031-940-8526
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -多拉天文台：京畿道坡州市长丹面延陵路3号310 / DMZ旅游局031-954-0303
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -斗山站：京畿道坡州市长丹面希望路307 / 031-953-3334
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※以上信息为2016年3月的内容。之后可能会发生变更，因此请在旅行前确认。
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※本文中使用的文字，照片和视频等信息受韩国旅游组织版权保护，因此禁止未经授权使用本文。
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea - In Camp Greaves, I&#39;m a descendant of the sun!</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/in-camp-greaves-im-a-descendant-of-the-sun-63/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 11:11:56 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/in-camp-greaves-im-a-descendant-of-the-sun-63/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;in-camp-greaves-im-a-descendant-of-the-sun--63&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   In Camp Greaves, I&#39;m a descendant of the sun!
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   `` The Descendants of the Sun, &#39;&#39; a drama that heats up 2016. At the same time, Songsong Couple has taken away people&#39;s hearts, and the filming location is also a hot topic. One of them is Camp Greaves, which is located in the DMZ like a military drama. As it is pre-production drama, set is demolished and remains, but how about still? If you see a little familiar spot like Deja vu along Song Joong-gi&#39;s hand, you can do it anywhere!
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Camp Greaves, troops that saved Ryan
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you are a fan of war movies or dramas, there is a place that will open your eyes and interest you. The 506th Regiment was the main character of the American drama Band of Brothers, and the hero of Ryan, the hero of the movie &#34;Saving Private Ryan,&#34; which featured World War II. They are Camp Greaves stationed in Korea.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Camp Greaves Youth Hostel - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/71648aa6-b64f-437d-8639-9ea454db4d94.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Camp Greaves Youth Hostel
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The familiar Urk base, which occupies most of the &#39;sun descendants&#39; background, is one of the oldest US military bases where the 2nd Division 506th Infantry Battalion, which remained after the Korean War Armistice Agreement, returned to it in August 2007. At present, the appearance of the military forces is so high that it might be a job for Captain Yu Si-jin.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Entrance to Camp Greaves - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/74e54eda-73ad-42c0-b289-c7b474d114e3.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Entrance to Camp Greaves
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Camp Greaves is just 2 km from the southern limit of the demilitarized zone (DMZ), a demilitarized zone designed to prevent clashes between the two Koreas. The military withdrew in 2004, but the trace remains intact and tells the story. On the land of more than 200,000 square meters, various facilities such as the repair shop where Song Joong-gi performed great action through the fighting scene with the US military in the `` Descendants of the Sun &#39;&#39;, officers&#39; accommodations, dormitories and gymnasiums are preserved as they are. It is worth it.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Unit mark with salute relief. - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/34c685c0-f4ea-4331-900a-2217ac5027f6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Unit mark with salute relief.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Despite sufficient cultural value, Camp Greaves, which was in danger of being demolished, was transformed into a peace and security experience facility for civilians after the efforts of Paju, Gyeonggi-do. In addition to various experiences such as security tourism and DMZ ecological experience, the first youth hostel that can spend the night in the civilian access control line (civil communication line) came to us.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Gymnasiums used for various events such as film festivals - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/f65f6873-e6af-47dc-9a49-0f2f33e2e34a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Gymnasiums used for various events such as film festivals
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Army? Youth hostel?
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   To visit Camp Greaves, you must first apply to the military. The excitement in front of the open Unification Bridge is thrilled with the countless varieties of barricades and the captured soldiers who thoroughly check their IDs. The bare-hearted mind falls down in front of the entrance to the Camp Greaves barbed wire, which is like a military unit with the words &#39;No entry&#39;.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Confusingly similar to military units - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/07fef590-48f5-4fe6-93a8-517a4d31cff5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Confusingly similar to military units
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The youth hostel, remodeled from a quarter of US military officers&#39; quarters, is designed to accommodate up to 240 people. There are offices and small auditoriums on the first floor, quarters on the second and third floors, and auditoriums and restaurants for indoor activities on the fourth floor. If you encounter three kinds of set, you will be enlightened by the fact that you can see the military quarters, lodging that is reminiscent of the army quarters, meals that are used by the military, and Nara Love Concert, a music concert enjoyed by security officers of the 1st Division.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Meal too! - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/e165bf8d-d2a6-45f6-a9ff-c147a59f6390.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Meal too!
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It does not have training facilities such as physical training, but welcomes those who seek unique security experiences using the uniqueness of the civilian line. DMZ 1129 is a mandatory field trip program for the day, two nights, two nights, and three nights.It explores nearby attractions such as the 3rd Tunnel, Dora Observatory, Dorasan Station, and Dorasan Peace Park to solve special tasks in the workbook That&#39;s the way. The program, which means 1129 days of long war, is popular because it can naturally learn about the DMZ and the reality of the current division between North and South.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Daesung High School students visiting the DMZ exhibition hall - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/ef924961-f689-4851-9645-7b3421d2288f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Daesung High School students visiting the DMZ exhibition hall
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In addition, in order to satisfy the tastes of various participants from elementary school students to high school students, various programs such as security OX games, unification, mini-jangseung, or soot-making, express warrior selection, camp play yard, and challenging DMZ Golden Bell are prepared.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Daesung High School students are taking group photos - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/d0296c2b-6a4e-426a-a41b-41763df090c0.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Daesung High School students are taking group photos
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   At the end of the event, the Peace Prayer Ribbon, which was written by a young student, was written in a single letter.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Students in the Strategic Domino Program - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/133d6af9-9f83-439e-bd04-18f903f39b2f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Students in the Strategic Domino Program
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In addition to the experience program, Camp Greaves will also meet with outsiders in various ways, including using the gym as an event venue for the opening ceremony of the DMZ International Documentary Film Festival. It is more precious and meaningful only because you can experience the only site DMZ that contains the pain of division. Isn&#39;t the time to raise the desire for unification through Camp Greaves be the key to our unification?
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The wishes of the participants who pushed on &#39;unification of the two Koreas&#39; are conveyed in their hearts. - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/63/f0dcf781-f4cd-4a1c-976b-ce2f831be1c5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The wishes of the participants who pushed on &#39;unification of the two Koreas&#39; are conveyed in their hearts.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel info
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Camp greaves
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Address: 137, Red Cross, Gunnae-myeon, Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Contact: 031-953-6970
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://dmzcamp131.or.kr/common/include/site_main.php&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://dmzcamp131.or.kr/common/include/site_main.php
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Restaurants near
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Tongil Village Jangkong Village: 64 Tongilchon-gil, Gunnae-myeon, Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do / Jangdankong Meal / 031-954-3443
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Tongil Dongsan Tofu Village: 480, Pilseung-ro, Tanhyeon-myeon, Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do / Cheonggukjangsik, Tofu Bossam, Tofu mushroom hotpot / 031-945-2114
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Willow House: 881 Yulgok-ro, Papyeong-myeon, Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do / Grilled Eel, Maeuntang / 031-952-8285
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Nearby attractions
     &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    -3rd Tunnel: 210-358, 3 Tunnel Tunnel, Gunnae-myeon, Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea / 3rd Tunnel Tourist Information Center, 031-940-8526
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Dora Observatory: 310, 3Deongul-ro, Jangdan-myeon, Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do / DMZ Tourist Office 031-954-0303
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Dorasan Station: 307, Hope-ro, Jangdan-myeon, Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do / 031-953-3334
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was written in March 2016. It may change afterwards, so please check before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ The information such as text, photos and videos used in this article is copyrighted by Korea Tourism Organization, so unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Паджу, Кёнгидо, Корея - Место съемки тоже потрясающее! Место, где была загружена грустная любовь первой любви, драма «Она была хорошенькой»</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/the-shooting-location-is-also-awesome-the-place-where-the-sad-love-of-first-love-was-loaded-the-drama-she-was-pretty-25-ru/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 22:33:37 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/the-shooting-location-is-also-awesome-the-place-where-the-sad-love-of-first-love-was-loaded-the-drama-she-was-pretty-25-ru/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-title=&#34;the-shooting-location-is-also-awesome-the-place-where-the-sad-love-of-first-love-was-loaded-the-drama-she-was-pretty--25&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Пляжная скамейка Гангмун, где сидели Сончжун и Хэджин - Паджу, Кёнгидо, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/fee90e25-8741-47d9-bc46-2ec5979dc669.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Пляжная скамейка Гангмун, где сидели Сончжун и Хэджин
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Место съемки тоже потрясающее! Место, где была загружена грустная любовь первой любви, драма «Она была хорошенькой»
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Паджу, Кёнгидо, Корея
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Этой осенью замечательная романтическая драма «Она была хорошенькой», отбросившая сердца женщин, попрощалась со зрителями. Хэджин, которого превратили в «бомбардировщика», и сладкий роман Сон Джуна, который превратился в «лотерею с супер-лазанием», также растопили их сердца. Давай найдем роман, который может встретить твою первую любовь.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Где ее рука коснулась его, Лес Мудрости
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Хеджин (Хванг Юнг-Юм) и Сунг Джун (Пак Сео-джун), герои мужских и женских персонажей в драме, похоже, не проходят. Тем не менее, есть место, которое предлагает их связи через книгу, найденную вместе с разницей во времени.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Вход в Лес Мудрости - Паджу, Кёнгидо, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/2c03cbc1-a19e-4fd2-afa0-46221a88f9fe.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Вход в Лес Мудрости
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Представленная как внутренняя библиотека во время спектакля, она часто появлялась как место встречи Сон Джуна, что повышало интерес зрителей. Это Лес Мудрости, расположенный в Издательском Городе Паджу.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Состояние посетителя, читающего свободно - Паджу, Кёнгидо, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/3b2f75f4-b3a2-4d65-aa7a-cd29f2f94968.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Состояние посетителя, читающего свободно
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Как только вы открываете дверь невысокого и своеобразного здания, вы, кажется, вошли в большой лес с книжными полками. Это около 8 м в высоту, и это о вихре. Однако, если вы идете по запаху бумаги, который согревает ваше сердце, вы можете найти более привлекательную библиотеку.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Пространство, предназначенное для комфорта посетителей в течение дня - Паджу, Кёнгидо, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/655c4568-4b8e-43e1-8f9b-1662f7e9c8df.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Пространство, предназначенное для комфорта посетителей в течение дня
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Это отличается от других библиотек, хвастающихся тяжелой тишиной. Потока свободы для матери, чтобы прочитать сборник рассказов своего ребенка. Если вы собираетесь перекусить, вы также можете насладиться легкими закусками в кафе. Для тех, кто хочет правильно питаться, в одном из трех павильонов, входящих в Лес Мудрости, есть ресторан Glow. В течение недели мы предлагаем выбор привлекательных обеденных наборов по хорошим ценам.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#39;Обеденный набор ресторана &#34;Glow&#34;, который удовлетворяет как вкус, так и цену - Паджу, Кёнгидо, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#39; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/dd5e5340-968b-43a9-add0-78152faa171e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Обеденный набор ресторана &#34;Glow&#34;, который удовлетворяет как вкус, так и цену
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Если вы хотите провести ленивую одну ночь и две ночи с книгой, вы можете воспользоваться поддержкой гостевого дома. Есть три здания, открытых 24 часа в сутки, поэтому идеально провести долгую ночь в море.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Гостевой дом Jijihyang Lounge - Паджу, Кёнгидо, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/574c96ec-456f-4e0e-8037-a23065a8fd07.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Гостевой дом Jijihyang Lounge
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Где он узнал ее, пляж Гангмун
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Ослабьте одинокий якорь лодки и заберитесь на сперму. Я буду.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Из песни Кан Чжон Чхоль, Канто Стар Сонг
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Пляж Гангмун с красивыми сооружениями для фотографирования - Паджу, Кёнгидо, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/c46c83ba-15af-47b2-ac46-79b3e48a8ceb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Пляж Гангмун с красивыми сооружениями для фотографирования
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Сон Кан Чхунчхол выразил, насколько прекрасным он был в Квандонге, с выражением «Все вокруг Каннына» - Гангмунгё (в настоящее время мост) в 16 веке. Море индиго за вывеской с этой фразой - то, где Сунг Джун впервые начал испытывать сладкие эмоции к Хеджину. Пляж Гангмун, расположенный к югу от моста Гангмун, является пляжем, который наполнял сердца многих людей, таких как она, улыбающихся в кадре камеры, снятом для фотосессии журнала.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Gangmun пляж с красивым индиго - Паджу, Кёнгидо, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/16e34049-4cb5-49f2-b4ec-e7cd59d6750f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Gangmun пляж с красивым индиго
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Расположенное рядом с пляжем Кёнпо, это маленькое и тихое место в отличие от пляжа Кёнпо, поэтому это лучшее место, чтобы думать в одиночестве. Это место идеально подходит для путешествий в одиночку. «Прекрасные структуры, которые я видел в драме, также редки, поэтому хорошо сфотографироваться с любимым или другом и оставить воспоминания. Если вы планируете остаться на ночь, обратите внимание на ночной пляж Гангмун. Отличный ночной вид на мостовой, соединяющий пляж Гангмун и пляж Кёнпо.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Каждый миг свет меняется, и ночной вид на более красивую башню - Паджу, Кёнгидо, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/d77e0c29-80c7-4365-8a13-43526fbd4fb4.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Каждый миг свет меняется, и ночной вид на более красивую башню
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Для тех, кто просто хочет встретиться с пляжем Гангмун, я рекомендую поесть в Paul &amp;amp; Mary, домашнем бургере, расположенном в самом начале. Пляж и домашние гамбургеры. Это странная комбинация, которую невозможно представить, но, по слухам, она уже в очереди.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Состояние экзотического магазина - Паджу, Кёнгидо, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/508bd58a-f3cd-4767-acef-8383b959ac5c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Состояние экзотического магазина
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Главное меню - бургер с беконом и моцареллой, где сыр моцарелла течет как водопад. Не удивляйтесь, увидев, как модификатор «визуальный головорез» совмещается. Сочные пирожки, жевательный и богатый сыр моцарелла и свежие овощи объединяются, чтобы создать более фантастическую комбинацию.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Типичный бургер с моцареллой и беконом - Паджу, Кёнгидо, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/9f14f46a-807a-453f-b5d2-62c315e74819.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Типичный бургер с моцареллой и беконом
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Место, где он и ее дрожат
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Он был очарован теплыми обедами, приготовленными для любимых, которые работают по выходным, и громким предложением. Это Dumulhead, место, которое зрители выбирают как лучшую сцену, и лучший выбор для любителей фотографии.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Dumulmul, ранее называвшийся «головой», относится к области Яншу-ри, Янсео-Мион, где встречаются и сливаются стебли реки Намхан и реки Бухан. До 1973 года плотина Палданг оставалась в Канвондо на водном пути. Однако вместо переулка лодка была заблокирована, как и его жизнь как морда.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Фантастический взгляд на голову Дюмюльде - Паджу, Кёнгидо, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/95990819-8bdd-4bad-a7ef-b1b0e3879bcb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Фантастический взгляд на голову Дюмюльде
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Но многие все еще посещают здесь. Чтобы увидеть фантастические пейзажи, вы не можете найти больше нигде. Синий свет, который встречает небо, единственная в Корее верфь Ким Хюэ-сун и 400-летнее дерево Зелкова, которое может похвастаться высотой 30 метров и окружностью 8 метров, в сочетании создают уникальный и редкий пейзаж. Благодаря этому, он популярен не только для драмы, но и для различных съемочных мест, таких как фильмы, реклама и свадьбы.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Лучшее место для фотографирования на Думулдеу - Паджу, Кёнгидо, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/31d3d96f-fe56-4236-ad53-25461e6c66f7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Лучшее место для фотографирования на Думулдеу
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   На рассвете фотографы со всей страны собираются, чтобы запечатлеть восхитительный восход головы Думула. Трудно выразить, как водяной туман, который расцветает комом, создает мечтательную атмосферу. Надпись на скале говорит нам: «Вы видели водяной туман, который таинственным образом поднимается на рассветном небе?» Если вам интересно узнать о чудесном рассвете водяного тумана, почему бы вам не пойти на раннее свидание в эти выходные?
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Художник рисует голову - Паджу, Кёнгидо, Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/c1b921be-b766-483d-900b-2ab7db4222bc.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Художник рисует голову
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Информация о путешествии
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Лес Мудрости
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Адрес: 145 Hoedong-gil, Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Контакт / Бронирование: 031-955-0082
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Пляж Гангмун
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Адрес: 352, Чанхэ-ро, Каннын-си, Канвондо
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Справки / Информация: Центр общей туристической информации 033-640-4414
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Янпхён Думул голова
      &lt;br/&gt;
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     Адрес: Yangsu 1-ri, Yangseo-myeon, Yangpyeong-gun, Кёнгидо
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Контакт / информация: Yangpyeong Культура и туризм 031-773-5101
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Близлежащие рестораны
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Столовое свечение: 145 Hoedong-gil, Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do / стейк, паста, ризотто / 031-955-0070
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://blog.naver.com/noeulms&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://blog.naver.com/noeulms
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Paul &amp;amp; Mary Burger: 33, Чанхэ-ро 350beon-gil, Каннын-си, Канвондо / Домашний бургер / 033-653-2354
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Wangui Champon: 305-2, Yongmun-ro, Yongmun-myeon, Yangpyeong-gun, Gyeonggi-do / Champon / 031-774-0091
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Размещение
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Yvestel: 446, Pilseung-ro, Tanhyeon-myeon, Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea / 031-944-0335
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Benikea Gyungpo Beach Hotel: 303-4 Кангмун-дон, Каннын-си, Канвондо / 033-643-6699
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Пансионат Ария: 33, Dojanggye-gil, Seojong-myeon, Yangpyeong-gun, Gyeonggi-do / 031-771-0030
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ Приведенная выше информация была написана в ноябре 2015 года и может впоследствии измениться. Пожалуйста, проверьте перед путешествием.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Информация, такая как текст, фотографии и видео, используемые в этой статье, защищены авторским правом Корейской туристической организации, поэтому несанкционированное использование статьи запрещено.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Corée - Le lieu de tournage est également génial! L&#39;endroit où le triste amour du premier amour a été chargé, le drame «Elle était jolie»</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/the-shooting-location-is-also-awesome-the-place-where-the-sad-love-of-first-love-was-loaded-the-drama-she-was-pretty-25-fr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 22:30:44 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/the-shooting-location-is-also-awesome-the-place-where-the-sad-love-of-first-love-was-loaded-the-drama-she-was-pretty-25-fr/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-title=&#34;the-shooting-location-is-also-awesome-the-place-where-the-sad-love-of-first-love-was-loaded-the-drama-she-was-pretty--25&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Banc de plage Gangmun où Seongjun et Hyejin étaient assis ensemble - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/fee90e25-8741-47d9-bc46-2ec5979dc669.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Banc de plage Gangmun où Seongjun et Hyejin étaient assis ensemble
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Le lieu de tournage est également génial! L&#39;endroit où le triste amour du premier amour a été chargé, le drame «Elle était jolie»
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Corée
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Cet automne, un drame romantique remarquable &amp;lt;Elle était jolie&amp;gt;, qui a jeté le cœur des femmes, adieu aux téléspectateurs. Hyejin, qui a été transformé en «bombardier-bombardier», et la douce romance de Seong-joon, qui est transformée en «homme de loterie super-montée», ont également fait fondre leur cœur. Allons trouver la romance qui pourrait rencontrer votre premier amour.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Là où sa main l&#39;a touché, la forêt de la sagesse
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Hyejin (Hwang Jung-eum) et Sung Joon (Park Seo-jun), les héros des personnages masculins et féminins du drame, ne semblent pas passer. Cependant, il y a un espace qui suggère leurs liens à travers un livre trouvé avec le décalage horaire.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Entrée dans la forêt de la sagesse - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/2c03cbc1-a19e-4fd2-afa0-46221a88f9fe.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Entrée dans la forêt de la sagesse
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Présenté comme une bibliothèque interne pendant la pièce, il est souvent apparu comme un lieu de rencontre pour Sung Jun, stimulant l&#39;intérêt des téléspectateurs. Il s&#39;agit de la forêt de la sagesse située dans la ville d&#39;édition de Paju.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;État du visiteur lisant librement - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/3b2f75f4-b3a2-4d65-aa7a-cd29f2f94968.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     État du visiteur lisant librement
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Dès que vous ouvrez la porte d&#39;un bâtiment bas et distinctif, vous semblez être entré dans une grande forêt de bibliothèque. Il fait environ 8 mètres de haut et il s&#39;agit d&#39;un tourbillon. Cependant, si vous marchez le long du parfum du papier qui réchauffe votre cœur, vous pourriez trouver une bibliothèque plus attrayante.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Un espace conçu pour garder les visiteurs à l&#39;aise tout au long de la journée - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/655c4568-4b8e-43e1-8f9b-1662f7e9c8df.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Un espace conçu pour garder les visiteurs à l&#39;aise tout au long de la journée
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Il est différent des autres bibliothèques au silence lourd. La liberté coule pour une mère de lire un livre de contes de son enfant. Si vous voulez prendre une bouchée, vous pouvez également déguster des plats légers au café. Pour ceux qui veulent manger correctement, l&#39;un des trois pavillons qui composent la forêt de la sagesse a un restaurant appelé Glow. Pendant la semaine, nous vous proposons une sélection de jolis sets à déjeuner à bon prix.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#39;Ensemble déjeuner du restaurant &#34;Glow&#34; qui satisfait à la fois le goût et le prix - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#39; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/dd5e5340-968b-43a9-add0-78152faa171e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Ensemble déjeuner du restaurant &#34;Glow&#34; qui satisfait à la fois le goût et le prix
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Si vous souhaitez passer une nuit paresseuse et deux nuits avec un livre, vous pouvez utiliser le support de la maison d&#39;hôtes. Il y a trois bâtiments ouverts 24h / 24, c&#39;est donc parfait pour passer une longue nuit dans la mer.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Guest House Jijihyang Lounge - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/574c96ec-456f-4e0e-8037-a23065a8fd07.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Guest House Jijihyang Lounge
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Où il l&#39;a reconnue, Gangmun Beach
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Desserrez l&#39;ancre du bateau solitaire et grimpez sur le sperme. Je vais.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -De Song Kang Jeong-cheol, Kanto Star Song
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Gangmun Beach avec de belles structures pour prendre des photos - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/c46c83ba-15af-47b2-ac46-79b3e48a8ceb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Gangmun Beach avec de belles structures pour prendre des photos
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Song Kang Chungcheol a exprimé à quel point il était beau dans le Kwandong Byeonggok avec l&#39;expression `` Tout est autour du Gangneung &#39;Gangmungyo&#39; (actuellement le pont) au 16ème siècle. La mer indigo derrière l&#39;enseigne avec cette phrase est l&#39;endroit où Sung Joon a commencé à ressentir des émotions douces pour Hyejin pour la première fois. La plage de Gangmun, située au sud du pont de Gangmun, est la plage qui a rempli le cœur de nombreuses personnes comme elle souriant dans le cadre de la caméra prise pour la séance photo du magazine.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Plage de Gangmun avec un bel indigo - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/16e34049-4cb5-49f2-b4ec-e7cd59d6750f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Plage de Gangmun avec un bel indigo
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Situé à côté de la plage de Gyeongpo, cet endroit est petit et calme contrairement à la plage de Gyeongpo, c&#39;est donc le meilleur endroit pour penser seul. Cet endroit est parfait pour `` voyager seul. `` Les belles structures que j&#39;ai vues dans le drame sont également rares, il est donc bon de prendre une photo avec votre amoureux ou un ami et de laisser des souvenirs. Si vous prévoyez de passer la nuit, consultez la nuit Gangmun Beach. La vue de nuit du pont sodaire reliant la plage de Gangmun et la plage de Gyeongpo est excellente.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;La lumière change à chaque instant et la vue nocturne de la plus belle tour - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/d77e0c29-80c7-4365-8a13-43526fbd4fb4.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     La lumière change à chaque instant et la vue nocturne de la plus belle tour
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Pour ceux qui veulent juste rencontrer la plage de Gangmun, je recommande un repas au Paul &amp;amp; Mary, un hamburger fait maison situé au début. Plage et hamburgers maison. C&#39;est une étrange combinaison qui ne peut être imaginée, mais la rumeur dit qu&#39;elle est déjà en ligne.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Etat de la boutique exotique - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/508bd58a-f3cd-4767-acef-8383b959ac5c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Etat de la boutique exotique
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Le menu principal est le burger de bacon mozzarella, où le fromage mozzarella coule comme une cascade. Ne soyez pas surpris de voir comment le modificateur «voyou visuel» s&#39;emboîte. Des galettes juteuses, du mozzarella moelleux et riche et des légumes frais se combinent pour créer une combinaison plus fantastique.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Burger typique à la mozzarella au bacon - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/9f14f46a-807a-453f-b5d2-62c315e74819.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Burger typique à la mozzarella au bacon
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   L&#39;endroit où lui et elle tremblent sont gardés
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Il a été fasciné par les déjeuners chauds préparés pour les proches qui travaillent le week-end et la visibilité des propositions. C&#39;est Dumulhead, un endroit que les téléspectateurs choisissent comme la meilleure scène et le meilleur choix pour les amateurs de photo.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Dumulmul, anciennement appelé «tête», fait référence à la région de Yangshu-ri, Yangseo-myeon où les tiges de la rivière Namhan et de la rivière Bukhan se rencontrent et fusionnent. Jusqu&#39;en 1973, le barrage de Paldang était un peuple résidant à Gangwon-do sur la voie navigable. Cependant, au lieu d&#39;une voie, le bateau était bloqué, tout comme sa vie de museau.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Look fantastique de la tête de Dumulde - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/95990819-8bdd-4bad-a7ef-b1b0e3879bcb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Look fantastique de la tête de Dumulde
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Mais beaucoup visitent toujours ici. Pour voir les paysages fantastiques que vous ne trouverez nulle part ailleurs. La lumière bleue qui rencontre le ciel, Kim Hue-sung, le seul chantier naval en Corée, et l&#39;arbre zelkova vieux de 400 ans, qui possède une hauteur de 30m et une circonférence de 8m, se combinent pour créer un paysage unique et rare. Grâce à cela, il est populaire non seulement pour le théâtre mais aussi pour divers lieux de tournage tels que les films, les publicités et les mariages.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Le meilleur endroit pour prendre des photos sur Dumuldeu - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/31d3d96f-fe56-4236-ad53-25461e6c66f7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Le meilleur endroit pour prendre des photos sur Dumuldeu
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   À l&#39;aube, des photographes de tout le pays se rassemblent pour capturer le fascinant lever de soleil de la tête de Dumul. Il est difficile d&#39;exprimer comment la brume d&#39;eau qui fleurit s&#39;unit pour créer une atmosphère de rêve. L&#39;inscription sur le rocher nous dit: «Avez-vous vu le brouillard d&#39;eau qui monte mystérieusement dans le ciel de l&#39;aube? Si vous êtes curieux de connaître la merveilleuse aube du brouillard d&#39;eau, pourquoi ne partez-vous pas tôt ce week-end?
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Tête de croquis de peintre - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/c1b921be-b766-483d-900b-2ab7db4222bc.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Tête de croquis de peintre
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Info voyage
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Forêt de la sagesse
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Adresse: 145 Hoedong-gil, Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Contact / Réservation: 031-955-0082
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Plage de Gangmun
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Adresse: 352, Changhae-ro, Gangneung-si, Gangwon-do
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Renseignements / renseignements: Centre d&#39;information touristique générale 033-640-4414
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Tête de Yangpyeong Dumul
      &lt;br/&gt;
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     Adresse: Yangsu 1-ri, Yangseo-myeon, Yangpyeong-gun, Gyeonggi-do
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Contact / Informations: Culture et tourisme de Yangpyeong 031-773-5101
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Restaurants à proximité
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Éclat de salle à manger: 145 Hoedong-gil, Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do / Steak, Pâtes, Risotto / 031-955-0070
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://blog.naver.com/noeulms&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://blog.naver.com/noeulms
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Paul &amp;amp; Mary Burger: 33, Changhae-ro 350beon-gil, Gangneung-si, Gangwon-do / Homemade Burger / 033-653-2354
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Wangui Champon: 305-2, Yongmun-ro, Yongmun-myeon, Yangpyeong-gun, Gyeonggi-do / Champon / 031-774-0091
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Hébergement
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Yvestel: 446, Pilseung-ro, Tanhyeon-myeon, Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Corée / 031-944-0335
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Hôtel Benikea Gyungpo Beach: 303-4 Gangmun-dong, Gangneung-si, Gangwon-si / 033-643-6699
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Pension Aria: 33, Dojanggye-gil, Seojong-myeon, Yangpyeong-gun, Gyeonggi-do / 031-771-0030
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ Les informations ci-dessus ont été rédigées en novembre 2015 et peuvent changer par la suite. Veuillez vérifier avant de voyager.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Les informations telles que le texte, les photos et les vidéos utilisées dans cet article sont protégées par les droits d&#39;auteur de l&#39;Organisation coréenne du tourisme, de sorte que l&#39;utilisation non autorisée de l&#39;article est interdite.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Corea - ¡El lugar de rodaje también es increíble! El lugar donde se cargó el triste amor del primer amor, el drama &#39;Ella era bonita&#39;</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/the-shooting-location-is-also-awesome-the-place-where-the-sad-love-of-first-love-was-loaded-the-drama-she-was-pretty-25-es/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 22:28:03 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/the-shooting-location-is-also-awesome-the-place-where-the-sad-love-of-first-love-was-loaded-the-drama-she-was-pretty-25-es/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-title=&#34;the-shooting-location-is-also-awesome-the-place-where-the-sad-love-of-first-love-was-loaded-the-drama-she-was-pretty--25&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Banco de la playa de Gangmun donde Seongjun y Hyejin se sentaron juntos - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/fee90e25-8741-47d9-bc46-2ec5979dc669.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Banco de la playa de Gangmun donde Seongjun y Hyejin se sentaron juntos
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   ¡El lugar de rodaje también es increíble! El lugar donde se cargó el triste amor del primer amor, el drama &#39;Ella era bonita&#39;
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Corea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Este otoño, un notable drama romántico &amp;lt;Ella era bonita&amp;gt;, que arrojó los corazones de las mujeres, adiós a los espectadores. Hyejin, que se ha transformado en un &#34;bombardero&#34;, y el dulce romance de Seong-joon, que se transforma en un &#34;hombre de lotería súper escalada&#34;, también ha derretido sus corazones. Vamos a buscar el romance que pueda encontrar tu primer amor.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Donde su mano lo tocó, el Bosque de la Sabiduría
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Hyejin (Hwang Jung-eum) y Sung Joon (Park Seo-jun), los héroes de los personajes masculinos y femeninos en el drama, no parecen pasar. Sin embargo, hay un espacio que sugiere sus vínculos a través de un libro que se encuentra junto con la diferencia horaria.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Entrada al bosque de la sabiduría - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/2c03cbc1-a19e-4fd2-afa0-46221a88f9fe.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Entrada al bosque de la sabiduría
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Introducido como una biblioteca interna durante la obra, a menudo apareció como un lugar de encuentro para Sung Jun, lo que aumentó el interés de los espectadores. Es el Bosque de la Sabiduría ubicado en la ciudad editorial de Paju.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Estado del visitante que lee libremente - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/3b2f75f4-b3a2-4d65-aa7a-cd29f2f94968.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Estado del visitante que lee libremente
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Tan pronto como abres la puerta de un edificio bajo y distintivo, pareces haber entrado en un gran bosque de estanterías. Tiene unos 8 m de altura y se trata de un torbellino. Sin embargo, si camina por el aroma de papel que calienta su corazón, puede encontrar una biblioteca más atractiva.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Un espacio diseñado para mantener a los visitantes cómodos durante todo el día. - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/655c4568-4b8e-43e1-8f9b-1662f7e9c8df.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Un espacio diseñado para mantener a los visitantes cómodos durante todo el día.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Es diferente de otras bibliotecas que cuentan con un silencio pesado. La libertad fluye para que una madre lea un libro de cuentos de su hijo. Si va a tomar un bocado, también puede disfrutar de algo de comida ligera en la cafetería. Para aquellos que desean comer adecuadamente, uno de los tres pabellones que conforman el Bosque de la Sabiduría tiene un restaurante llamado Glow. Durante la semana, ofrecemos una selección de atractivos almuerzos a buenos precios.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#39;Almuerzo del restaurante &#34;Glow&#34; que satisface tanto el sabor como el precio. - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#39; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/dd5e5340-968b-43a9-add0-78152faa171e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Almuerzo del restaurante &#34;Glow&#34; que satisface tanto el sabor como el precio.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Si desea pasar una perezosa una noche y dos noches con un libro, puede utilizar el soporte de la casa de huéspedes. Hay tres edificios abiertos las 24 horas del día, por lo que es perfecto para pasar una larga noche en el mar.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Guest House Jijihyang Lounge - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/574c96ec-456f-4e0e-8037-a23065a8fd07.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Guest House Jijihyang Lounge
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Donde la reconoció, la playa de Gangmun
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Afloje el ancla solitaria del bote y suba al esperma. Voy a.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -De Song Kang Jeong-cheol, Kanto Star Song
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Playa de Gangmun con hermosas estructuras para tomar fotos - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/c46c83ba-15af-47b2-ac46-79b3e48a8ceb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Playa de Gangmun con hermosas estructuras para tomar fotos
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Song Kang Chungcheol expresó lo hermoso que era en el Kwandong Byeonggok con la expresión &#39;Todo está alrededor del Gangneung&#39; Gangmungyo &#39;(actualmente el puente) en el siglo XVI. El mar índigo detrás del letrero con esta frase es donde Sung Joon comenzó a sentir dulces emociones por Hyejin por primera vez. La playa de Gangmun, ubicada al sur del puente de Gangmun, es la playa que llenó los corazones de muchas personas como ella sonriendo en el marco de la cámara tomada para la sesión fotográfica de la revista.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Playa de Gangmun con hermoso índigo - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/16e34049-4cb5-49f2-b4ec-e7cd59d6750f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Playa de Gangmun con hermoso índigo
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Ubicado junto a la playa de Gyeongpo, este lugar es pequeño y tranquilo a diferencia de la playa de Gyeongpo, por lo que es el mejor lugar para pensar solo. Este lugar es perfecto para `` viajar solo. &#39;&#39; Las hermosas estructuras que vi en el drama también son escasas, por lo que es bueno tomar una foto con tu amante o un amigo y dejar recuerdos. Si planeas pasar la noche, echa un vistazo a la playa de Gangmun. La vista nocturna del puente sodary que conecta la playa de Gangmun y la playa de Gyeongpo es excelente.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;La luz cambia cada momento y la vista nocturna de la torre más hermosa. - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/d77e0c29-80c7-4365-8a13-43526fbd4fb4.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     La luz cambia cada momento y la vista nocturna de la torre más hermosa.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Para aquellos que solo quieren conocer la playa de Gangmun, les recomiendo una comida en Paul &amp;amp; Mary, una hamburguesería casera ubicada al principio. Playa y hamburguesas caseras. Es una combinación extraña que no se puede imaginar, pero se rumorea que ya está en línea.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Estado de tienda exótica - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/508bd58a-f3cd-4767-acef-8383b959ac5c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Estado de tienda exótica
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   El menú principal es la hamburguesa de mozzarella con tocino, donde el queso mozzarella fluye como una cascada. No se sorprenda al ver cómo el modificador, &#39;matón visual&#39; encaja. Empanadas jugosas, queso de mozzarella masticable y rico, y verduras frescas se combinan para crear una combinación más fantástica.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Hamburguesa típica de mozzarella con tocino - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/9f14f46a-807a-453f-b5d2-62c315e74819.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Hamburguesa típica de mozzarella con tocino
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   El lugar donde él y su temblor se mantienen
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Le fascinaron los almuerzos cálidos preparados para los seres queridos que trabajan los fines de semana y el alto perfil de las propuestas. Es Dumulhead, un lugar que los espectadores eligen como la mejor escena, y la mejor opción para los aficionados a la fotografía.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Dumulmul, anteriormente llamado &#39;cabeza&#39;, se refiere al área de Yangshu-ri, Yangseo-myeon, donde los tallos del río Namhan y el río Bukhan se encuentran y se fusionan. Hasta 1973, la presa de Paldang era un pueblo que se quedaba en Gangwon-do en la vía fluvial. Sin embargo, en lugar de un carril, el bote estaba bloqueado, y también su vida como un bozal.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Fantástica apariencia de la cabeza Dumulde - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/95990819-8bdd-4bad-a7ef-b1b0e3879bcb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Fantástica apariencia de la cabeza Dumulde
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Pero muchos todavía visitan aquí. Para ver el fantástico paisaje que no puedes encontrar en ningún otro lugar. La luz azul que se encuentra con el cielo, Kim Hue-sung, el único astillero de Corea, y el árbol zelkova de 400 años de antigüedad, que cuenta con una altura de 30 my una circunferencia de 8 m, se combinan para crear un paisaje único y raro. Gracias a esto, es popular no solo para el drama sino también para varios lugares de rodaje, como películas, anuncios y bodas.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;El mejor lugar para tomar fotos en Dumuldeu - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/31d3d96f-fe56-4236-ad53-25461e6c66f7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     El mejor lugar para tomar fotos en Dumuldeu
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Al amanecer, los fotógrafos de todo el país se reúnen para capturar el fascinante amanecer de la cabeza de Dumul. Es difícil expresar cómo la niebla de agua que florece se acumula creando una atmósfera de ensueño. La inscripción en la roca nos dice: &#34;¿Vieron la niebla de agua que se levanta misteriosamente en el cielo del amanecer?&#34; Si tiene curiosidad sobre el maravilloso amanecer de la niebla de agua, ¿por qué no tiene una cita temprana este fin de semana?
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Pintor dibujando cabeza - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/c1b921be-b766-483d-900b-2ab7db4222bc.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Pintor dibujando cabeza
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Información de viaje
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Bosque de la sabiduría
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Dirección: 145 Hoedong-gil, Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Contacto / Reserva: 031-955-0082
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Playa Gangmun
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Dirección: 352, Changhae-ro, Gangneung-si, Gangwon-do
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Consultas / información: Centro de información turística general 033-640-4414
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Cabeza de Yangpyeong Dumul
      &lt;br/&gt;
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     Dirección: Yangsu 1-ri, Yangseo-myeon, Yangpyeong-gun, Gyeonggi-do
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Contacto / Información: Yangpyeong Culture &amp;amp; Tourism 031-773-5101
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Restaurantes cercanos
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Resplandor de cena: 145 Hoedong-gil, Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do / Steak, Pasta, Risotto / 031-955-0070
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://blog.naver.com/noeulms&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://blog.naver.com/noeulms
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Paul &amp;amp; Mary Burger: 33, Changhae-ro 350beon-gil, Gangneung-si, Gangwon-do / Homemade Burger / 033-653-2354
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Wangui Champon: 305-2, Yongmun-ro, Yongmun-myeon, Yangpyeong-gun, Gyeonggi-do / Champon / 031-774-0091
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Alojamiento
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Yvestel: 446, Pilseung-ro, Tanhyeon-myeon, Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Corea / 031-944-0335
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Benikea Gyungpo Beach Hotel: 303-4 Gangmun-dong, Gangneung-si, Gangwon-si / 033-643-6699
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Pensión Aria: 33, Dojanggye-gil, Seojong-myeon, Yangpyeong-gun, Gyeonggi-do / 031-771-0030
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ La información anterior se escribió en noviembre de 2015 y puede cambiar después. Por favor verifique antes de viajar.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ La información como texto, fotos y videos utilizados en este artículo tiene copyright de la Organización de Turismo de Corea, por lo que está prohibido el uso no autorizado del artículo.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea - Der Drehort ist auch super! Der Ort, an dem die traurige Liebe der ersten Liebe geladen wurde, das Drama &#39;Sie war hübsch&#39;</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/the-shooting-location-is-also-awesome-the-place-where-the-sad-love-of-first-love-was-loaded-the-drama-she-was-pretty-25-de/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 22:25:30 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/the-shooting-location-is-also-awesome-the-place-where-the-sad-love-of-first-love-was-loaded-the-drama-she-was-pretty-25-de/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-title=&#34;the-shooting-location-is-also-awesome-the-place-where-the-sad-love-of-first-love-was-loaded-the-drama-she-was-pretty--25&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Gangmun Strandbank, auf der Seongjun und Hyejin zusammen saßen - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/fee90e25-8741-47d9-bc46-2ec5979dc669.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Gangmun Strandbank, auf der Seongjun und Hyejin zusammen saßen
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Der Drehort ist auch super! Der Ort, an dem die traurige Liebe der ersten Liebe geladen wurde, das Drama &#39;Sie war hübsch&#39;
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In diesem Herbst ein bemerkenswertes romantisches Drama &amp;lt;Sie war hübsch&amp;gt;, das die Herzen der Frauen wegwarf und sich von den Zuschauern verabschiedete. Hyejin, der sich in einen „Bombenbomber“ verwandelt hat, und Seong-joons süße Romanze, die sich in einen „Super-Climb-Lotteriemann“ verwandelt hat, haben ebenfalls ihre Herzen zum Schmelzen gebracht. Lass uns die Romantik finden, die deine erste Liebe treffen könnte.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Wo ihre Hand ihn berührte, der Wald der Weisheit
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Hyejin (Hwang Jung-eum) und Sung Joon (Park Seo-jun), die Helden der männlichen und weiblichen Charaktere im Drama, scheinen nicht zu vergehen. Es gibt jedoch einen Raum, der ihre Verbindungen durch ein Buch suggeriert, das zusammen mit dem Zeitunterschied gefunden wurde.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Eingang zum Wald der Weisheit - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/2c03cbc1-a19e-4fd2-afa0-46221a88f9fe.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Eingang zum Wald der Weisheit
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Während des Stücks als hauseigene Bibliothek eingeführt, erschien es oft als Treffpunkt für Sung Jun, was das Interesse der Zuschauer weckte. Es ist der Wald der Weisheit in Paju Publishing City.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Zustand des Besuchers, der frei liest - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/3b2f75f4-b3a2-4d65-aa7a-cd29f2f94968.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Zustand des Besuchers, der frei liest
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Sobald Sie die Tür eines niedrigen und markanten Gebäudes öffnen, scheinen Sie einen großen Bücherregalwald betreten zu haben. Es ist ungefähr 8 m hoch und es geht um einen Wirbelwind. Wenn Sie jedoch den Duft von Papier entlang gehen, der Ihr Herz erwärmt, finden Sie möglicherweise eine attraktivere Bibliothek.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Ein Raum, in dem sich die Besucher den ganzen Tag über wohl fühlen - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/655c4568-4b8e-43e1-8f9b-1662f7e9c8df.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Ein Raum, in dem sich die Besucher den ganzen Tag über wohl fühlen
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Es unterscheidet sich von anderen Bibliotheken mit starker Stille. Eine Mutter hat die Freiheit, ein Märchenbuch ihres Kindes zu lesen. Wenn Sie etwas essen möchten, können Sie im Café auch leichtes Essen genießen. Für diejenigen, die richtig essen möchten, hat einer der drei Pavillons, aus denen der Wald der Weisheit besteht, ein Restaurant namens Glow. Während der Woche bieten wir eine Auswahl an attraktiven Mittagssets zu guten Preisen.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#39;Mittagsset des Restaurants &#34;Glow&#34;, das sowohl Geschmack als auch Preis befriedigt - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#39; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/dd5e5340-968b-43a9-add0-78152faa171e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Mittagsset des Restaurants &#34;Glow&#34;, das sowohl Geschmack als auch Preis befriedigt
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Wenn Sie eine Nacht und zwei Nächte mit einem Buch verbringen möchten, können Sie die Unterstützung des Gästehauses nutzen. Es gibt drei Gebäude, die 24 Stunden am Tag geöffnet sind, sodass Sie eine lange Nacht im Meer verbringen können.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Gästehaus Jijihyang Lounge - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/574c96ec-456f-4e0e-8037-a23065a8fd07.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Gästehaus Jijihyang Lounge
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Wo er sie erkannte, Gangmun Beach
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Lösen Sie den einsamen Bootsanker und klettern Sie auf das Sperma. Ich werde.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    - Aus dem Lied Kang Jeong-cheol, Kanto Star Song
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Gangmun Beach mit schönen Strukturen zum Fotografieren - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/c46c83ba-15af-47b2-ac46-79b3e48a8ceb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Gangmun Beach mit schönen Strukturen zum Fotografieren
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Song Kang Chungcheol drückte aus, wie schön er im Kwandong Byeonggok war, mit dem Ausdruck &#34;Alles rund um die Gangneung&#34; Gangmungyo (derzeit die Brücke) im 16. Jahrhundert. Das Indigo-Meer hinter dem Schild mit diesem Satz ist der Ort, an dem Sung Joon zum ersten Mal süße Gefühle für Hyejin verspürte. Gangmun Beach, südlich der Gangmun Bridge gelegen, ist der Strand, der die Herzen vieler Menschen wie sie erfüllte, die im Kamerarahmen lächelten, der für das Fotoshooting des Magazins aufgenommen wurde.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Gangmun Strand mit schönem Indigo - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/16e34049-4cb5-49f2-b4ec-e7cd59d6750f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Gangmun Strand mit schönem Indigo
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Dieser Ort befindet sich neben dem Strand von Gyeongpo und ist im Gegensatz zum Strand von Gyeongpo klein und ruhig. Daher ist er der beste Ort, um alleine zu denken. Dieser Ort ist perfekt für Alleinreisende. &#39;&#39; Die schönen Strukturen, die ich in dem Drama gesehen habe, sind auch spärlich, also ist es gut, ein Foto mit Ihrem Geliebten oder einem Freund zu machen und Erinnerungen zu hinterlassen. Wenn Sie über Nacht bleiben möchten, schauen Sie sich den Gangmun Beach an. Die Nachtansicht der Sodalbrücke zwischen dem Strand von Gangmun und dem Strand von Gyeongpo ist ausgezeichnet.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Das Licht ändert sich jeden Moment und die Nachtansicht des schöneren Turms - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/d77e0c29-80c7-4365-8a13-43526fbd4fb4.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Das Licht ändert sich jeden Moment und die Nachtansicht des schöneren Turms
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Für diejenigen, die nur den Strand von Gangmun kennenlernen möchten, empfehle ich eine Mahlzeit im Paul &amp;amp; Mary, einem hausgemachten Burgerhaus am Anfang. Strand und hausgemachte Burger. Es ist eine seltsame Kombination, die man sich nicht vorstellen kann, aber es wird gemunkelt, dass sie bereits in der Schlange steht.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Zustand des exotischen Ladens - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/508bd58a-f3cd-4767-acef-8383b959ac5c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Zustand des exotischen Ladens
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Das Hauptmenü ist der Speck-Mozzarella-Burger, bei dem der Mozzarella-Käse wie ein Wasserfall fließt. Seien Sie nicht überrascht zu sehen, wie der Modifikator &#34;Visual Thug&#34; zusammenpasst. Saftige Pastetchen, zäher und reichhaltiger Mozzarella-Käse und frisches Gemüse ergeben zusammen eine fantastischere Kombination.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Typischer Speck-Mozzarella-Burger - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/9f14f46a-807a-453f-b5d2-62c315e74819.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Typischer Speck-Mozzarella-Burger
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Der Ort, an dem er und sie zittern
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Es war fasziniert von den warmen Mittagessen für die Angehörigen, die an den Wochenenden arbeiten, und dem hohen Bekanntheitsgrad der Vorschläge. Es ist Dumulhead, ein Ort, den die Zuschauer als beste Szene und als beste Wahl für Fotohobbyisten auswählen.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Dumulmul, früher &#34;Kopf&#34; genannt, bezieht sich auf das Gebiet von Yangshu-ri, Yangseo-myeon, wo sich die Stämme des Namhan-Flusses und des Bukhan-Flusses treffen und verschmelzen. Bis 1973 war der Paldang-Damm ein Volk, das in Gangwon-do an der Wasserstraße wohnte. Anstelle einer Fahrspur wurde jedoch das Boot blockiert, ebenso wie sein Leben als Mündung.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Fantastischer Blick von Dumulde Kopf - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/95990819-8bdd-4bad-a7ef-b1b0e3879bcb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Fantastischer Blick von Dumulde Kopf
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Aber viele besuchen immer noch hier. Um die fantastische Landschaft zu sehen, können Sie nirgendwo anders finden. Das blaue Licht, das auf den Himmel trifft, Kim Hue-sung, die einzige Werft in Korea, und der 400 Jahre alte Zelkova-Baum mit einer Höhe von 30 m und einem Umfang von 8 m bilden zusammen eine einzigartige und seltene Landschaft. Dank dessen ist es nicht nur für Dramen beliebt, sondern auch für verschiedene Drehorte wie Filme, Werbung und Hochzeiten.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Der beste Ort, um auf Dumuldeu zu fotografieren - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/31d3d96f-fe56-4236-ad53-25461e6c66f7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Der beste Ort, um auf Dumuldeu zu fotografieren
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Im Morgengrauen versammeln sich Fotografen aus dem ganzen Land, um den faszinierenden Sonnenaufgang von Dumul Head festzuhalten. Es ist schwer auszudrücken, wie der Wassernebel, der zusammenklumpt, eine verträumte Atmosphäre schafft. Die Inschrift auf dem Felsen sagt uns: &#34;Hast du den Wassernebel gesehen, der auf mysteriöse Weise am Morgenhimmel aufsteigt?&#34; Wenn Sie neugierig auf den wunderbaren Beginn des Wassernebels sind, warum gehen Sie dieses Wochenende nicht früh?
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Maler skizziert Kopf - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/c1b921be-b766-483d-900b-2ab7db4222bc.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Maler skizziert Kopf
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Reiseinformationen
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Wald der Weisheit
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Adresse: 145 Hoedong-gil, Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Kontakt / Reservierung: 031-955-0082
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Gangmun Beach
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Adresse: 352, Changhae-ro, Gangneung-si, Gangwon-do
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Anfragen / Informationen: Allgemeines Touristeninformationszentrum 033-640-4414
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Yangpyeong Dumul Kopf
      &lt;br/&gt;
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     Adresse: Yangsu 1-ri, Yangseo-myeon, Yangpyeong-gun, Gyeonggi-do
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Kontakt / Information: Yangpyeong Kultur &amp;amp; Tourismus 031-773-5101
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Restaurants in der Nähe
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Essensglühen: 145 Hoedong-Gil, Paju-Si, Gyeonggi-Do / Steak, Pasta, Risotto / 031-955-0070
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://blog.naver.com/noeulms&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://blog.naver.com/noeulms
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Paul &amp;amp; Mary Burger: 33, Changhae-ro 350 Beon-Gil, Gangneung-si, Gangwon-do / hausgemachter Burger / 033-653-2354
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Wangui Champon: 305-2, Yongmun-ro, Yongmun-myeon, Yangpyeong-gun, Gyeonggi-do / Champon / 031-774-0091
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Unterkunft
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Yvestel: 446, Pilseung-ro, Tanhyeon-myeon, Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea / 031-944-0335
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Benikea Gyungpo Beach Hotel: 303-4 Gangmun-dong, Gangneung-si, Gangwon-si / 033-643-6699
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Arienrente: 33, Dojanggye-Gil, Seojong-Myeon, Yangpyeong-Kanone, Gyeonggi-Do / 031-771-0030
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ Die oben genannten Informationen wurden im November 2015 verfasst und können sich später ändern. Bitte überprüfen Sie vor Reiseantritt.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Informationen wie Text, Fotos und Videos, die in diesem Artikel verwendet werden, sind von der Korea Tourism Organization urheberrechtlich geschützt. Daher ist die unbefugte Verwendung des Artikels verboten.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>韩国京畿道坡州市 - 拍摄地点也很棒！ 充满了初恋的悲伤之情的戏剧《她很漂亮》</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/the-shooting-location-is-also-awesome-the-place-where-the-sad-love-of-first-love-was-loaded-the-drama-she-was-pretty-25-zh-cn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 22:22:54 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/the-shooting-location-is-also-awesome-the-place-where-the-sad-love-of-first-love-was-loaded-the-drama-she-was-pretty-25-zh-cn/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-title=&#34;the-shooting-location-is-also-awesome-the-place-where-the-sad-love-of-first-love-was-loaded-the-drama-she-was-pretty--25&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;成俊和惠珍坐在一起的江门沙滩长椅 - 韩国京畿道坡州市 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/fee90e25-8741-47d9-bc46-2ec5979dc669.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    成俊和惠珍坐在一起的江门沙滩长椅
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   拍摄地点也很棒！ 充满了初恋的悲伤之情的戏剧《她很漂亮》
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    韩国京畿道坡州市
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   今年秋天，一部引人注目的浪漫戏剧《她很漂亮》，把女性的心灵抛诸脑后，告别了观众。 被转变为“炸弹轰炸机”的慧珍和成俊的甜美浪漫，被转变为“超级攀岩彩票人”，也使他们的心melt。 让我们去寻找可能会遇到您的初恋的恋情。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   她的手触碰到他的地方，智慧之林
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   剧中男女角色的主人公Hyejin（黄正恩）和Sung Joon（朴瑞俊）似乎并没有过去。 但是，有一个空间可以通过一本书和时差来暗示他们的联系。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;智慧森林入口 - 韩国京畿道坡州市 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/2c03cbc1-a19e-4fd2-afa0-46221a88f9fe.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     智慧森林入口
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   在剧本中作为内部图书馆引入，它经常作为成俊的聚会场所出现，从而激发了观众的兴趣。 这是位于坡州出版城的智慧森林。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;访客自由阅读的样子 - 韩国京畿道坡州市 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/3b2f75f4-b3a2-4d65-aa7a-cd29f2f94968.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     访客自由阅读的样子
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   当您打开一幢低矮而独特的建筑的门时，您似乎已经进入了一个大书架森林。 它大约是8m高，大约是旋风。 但是，如果沿着温暖的纸张气味走动，您可能会发现一个更具吸引力的图书馆。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;一个旨在让游客全天舒适的空间 - 韩国京畿道坡州市 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/655c4568-4b8e-43e1-8f9b-1662f7e9c8df.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     一个旨在让游客全天舒适的空间
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   它与其他拥有沉重沉默的图书馆不同。 母亲可以自由地阅读孩子的故事书。 如果您想吃点东西，还可以在咖啡厅享用便餐。 对于那些想要适当用餐的人来说，组成智慧森林的三个凉亭之一设有一家名为Glow的餐厅。 在一周中，我们以优惠的价格提供精选的诱人午餐套餐。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;满足口味和价格的餐厅“ Glow”的午餐套餐 - 韩国京畿道坡州市 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/dd5e5340-968b-43a9-add0-78152faa171e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     满足口味和价格的餐厅“ Glow”的午餐套餐
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   如果您想一本书消磨一晚和两晚，可以使用旅馆的支持。 三栋大楼每天24小时开放，因此在海里度过一个漫长的夜晚非常理想。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;吉吉阳酒廊旅馆 - 韩国京畿道坡州市 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/574c96ec-456f-4e0e-8037-a23065a8fd07.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     吉吉阳酒廊旅馆
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   他认识她的地方，江门海滩
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    松开孤独的船锚，爬上精子。 我会。
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -来自关东星之歌宋康正哲
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;江门海滩，美丽的建筑拍照 - 韩国京畿道坡州市 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/c46c83ba-15af-47b2-ac46-79b3e48a8ceb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     江门海滩，美丽的建筑拍照
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   宋康忠哲用“江陵周围的一切”（现在的桥）表达了他在关东平谷时的美丽。 标语牌后面的靛蓝海是成俊第一次开始对慧珍产生甜蜜的情感。 Gangmun海滩位于Gangmun桥以南，充满了很多人的心，就像她在为杂志照片拍摄的相机框架中微笑一样。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;江门海滩，美丽的靛蓝 - 韩国京畿道坡州市 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/16e34049-4cb5-49f2-b4ec-e7cd59d6750f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     江门海滩，美丽的靛蓝
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   毗邻景浦海水浴场的地方，与景浦海水浴场相比小而安静，是独自思考的最佳地方。 这个地方非常适合``独自旅行。 &#39;&#39;我在戏剧中看到的美丽结构也很稀疏，因此最好与爱人或朋友合影留念。 如果您打算过夜，请前往夜港门海滩。 连接江门海水浴场和京浦海水浴场的跳桥的夜景非常好。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;灯光每时每刻都在变化，更美丽的塔楼的夜景 - 韩国京畿道坡州市 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/d77e0c29-80c7-4365-8a13-43526fbd4fb4.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     灯光每时每刻都在变化，更美丽的塔楼的夜景
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   对于那些只想去江门海滩的人，我建议在Paul＆Mary用餐，这是一家刚开始的自制汉堡店。 海滩和自制汉堡。 这是一个无法想象的奇怪组合，但有传言说它已经符合要求。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;异国情调的商店的样子 - 韩国京畿道坡州市 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/508bd58a-f3cd-4767-acef-8383b959ac5c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     异国情调的商店的样子
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   主菜单是培根芝士汉堡，其中的芝士奶酪像瀑布一样流动。 看到修饰符“视觉暴徒”如何组合在一起就不会感到惊讶。 多汁的肉饼，耐嚼和丰富的马苏里拉奶酪，以及新鲜的蔬菜相结合，创造出更加奇妙的组合。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;典型的培根芝士汉堡 - 韩国京畿道坡州市 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/9f14f46a-807a-453f-b5d2-62c315e74819.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     典型的培根芝士汉堡
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   他和她发抖的地方
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   为在周末工作的亲人准备的热午餐和引人入胜的提案而着迷。 它是杜穆尔黑德（Dumulhead），观众可以将其选择为最佳场景，也是摄影爱好者的最佳选择。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Dumulmul，以前称为“头”，是指南汉河和北汉河的水流汇合处的阳西面阳树里地区。 直到1973年，帕当丹水坝都是在水道上停留在江原道的人们。 但是，这条船不是一条小路，而是被堵住了，他的口吻也被挡住了。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;杜默德头像的奇妙外观 - 韩国京畿道坡州市 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/95990819-8bdd-4bad-a7ef-b1b0e3879bcb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     杜默德头像的奇妙外观
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   但是许多人仍然访问这里。 要看到奇妙的风景，您在其他任何地方都找不到。 蔚蓝的天空，韩国唯一的造船厂金惠成和拥有400年历史的榉树，树高30m，周长8m，共同创造了独特而罕见的景观。 因此，它不仅在戏剧中很受欢迎，而且在电影，广告和婚礼等各种拍摄场所也很受欢迎。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;在杜穆尔德（Dumudeu）上拍照的最佳场所 - 韩国京畿道坡州市 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/31d3d96f-fe56-4236-ad53-25461e6c66f7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     在杜穆尔德（Dumudeu）上拍照的最佳场所
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   拂晓时分，来自全国各地的摄影师齐聚一堂，捕捉迷人的Dumul头日出。 很难表达出聚集在一起的水雾如何营造出梦幻般的气氛。 岩石上的铭文告诉我们：“您看到黎明的天空神秘升起的水雾了吗？” 如果您对水雾的奇妙曙光感到好奇，那么为什么不在这个周末提早约会呢？
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;画家素描头 - 韩国京畿道坡州市 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/c1b921be-b766-483d-900b-2ab7db4222bc.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     画家素描头
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   旅游信息
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      智慧森林
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     地址：京畿道坡州市厚东街145号
     &lt;br/&gt;
     联系/预订：031-955-0082
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      江门海滩
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     地址：江原道江陵市昌海路352
     &lt;br/&gt;
     查询/信息：综合游客咨询中心033-640-4414
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      杨平杜穆尔头
      &lt;br/&gt;
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     地址：京畿道仰平郡仰水面仰苏1里
     &lt;br/&gt;
     联系方式：杨平文化观光031-773-5101
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1.附近的餐馆
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    用餐光晕：京畿道坡州市145号京东街/牛排，意大利面，烩饭/ 031-955-0070
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://blog.naver.com/noeulms&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://blog.naver.com/noeulms
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Paul＆Mary Burger：江原道江陵市昌海路350号街33号/自制汉堡/ 033-653-2354
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Wangui奖杯：京畿道杨平郡龙门面龙门路305-2 /奖杯/ 031-774-0091
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2.住宿
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Yvestel：韩国京畿道坡州市丹贤面皮尔胜路446 / 031-944-0335
    &lt;br/&gt;
    本昵客雅镜浦海滩酒店：江原市江陵市江门洞303-4 / 033-643-6699
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Aria Pension：京畿道杨平郡瑞钟面道延吉街33号/ 031-771-0030
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※以上信息为2015年11月撰写的内容，之后可能会有变更。 请在旅行前检查。
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※本文中使用的文字，照片和视频等信息均受韩国旅游组织版权保护，因此禁止未经授权使用本文。
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea - The shooting location is also awesome! The place where the sad love of first love was loaded, the drama &#39;She was pretty&#39;</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/the-shooting-location-is-also-awesome-the-place-where-the-sad-love-of-first-love-was-loaded-the-drama-she-was-pretty-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 19:04:34 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/the-shooting-location-is-also-awesome-the-place-where-the-sad-love-of-first-love-was-loaded-the-drama-she-was-pretty-25/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-title=&#34;the-shooting-location-is-also-awesome-the-place-where-the-sad-love-of-first-love-was-loaded-the-drama-she-was-pretty--25&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Gangmun beach bench where Seongjun and Hyejin sat together - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/fee90e25-8741-47d9-bc46-2ec5979dc669.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Gangmun beach bench where Seongjun and Hyejin sat together
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   The shooting location is also awesome! The place where the sad love of first love was loaded, the drama &#39;She was pretty&#39;
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   This fall, a remarkable romantic drama &amp;lt;She was pretty&amp;gt;, who threw away the hearts of women, farewell to viewers. Hyejin, who has been transformed into a “bomb bomber,” and Seong-joon&#39;s sweet romance, which is transformed into a “super-climb lottery man,” has also melted their hearts. Let&#39;s go find the romance that might meet your first love.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Where her hand touched him, the Forest of Wisdom
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Hyejin (Hwang Jung-eum) and Sung Joon (Park Seo-jun), the heroes of the male and female characters in the drama, do not seem to pass. However, there is a space that suggests their ties through a book found together with time difference.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Entrance to the Forest of Wisdom - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/2c03cbc1-a19e-4fd2-afa0-46221a88f9fe.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Entrance to the Forest of Wisdom
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Introduced as an in-house library during the play, it often appeared as a meeting place for Sung Jun, boosting viewers&#39; interest. It is the Forest of Wisdom located in Paju Publishing City.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;State of visitor reading freely - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/3b2f75f4-b3a2-4d65-aa7a-cd29f2f94968.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     State of visitor reading freely
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   As soon as you open the door of a low and distinctive building, you seem to have entered a large bookshelf forest. It&#39;s about 8m high, and it&#39;s about a whirlwind. However, if you walk along the scent of paper that warms your heart, you might find a more attractive library.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A space designed to keep visitors comfortable throughout the day - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/655c4568-4b8e-43e1-8f9b-1662f7e9c8df.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A space designed to keep visitors comfortable throughout the day
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It is different from other libraries boasting heavy silence. Freedom flows for a mother to read a storybook by her child. If you&#39;re going to take a bite, you can also enjoy some light food at the cafe. For those who want to eat a meal properly, one of the three pavilions that make up the Forest of Wisdom has a restaurant called Glow. During the week, we offer a selection of attractive lunch sets at good prices.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#39;Lunch set of restaurant &#34;Glow&#34; which satisfies both taste and price - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#39; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/dd5e5340-968b-43a9-add0-78152faa171e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Lunch set of restaurant &#34;Glow&#34; which satisfies both taste and price
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you want to spend a lazy one night and two nights with a book, you can use the guest house support. There are three buildings open 24 hours a day, so it&#39;s perfect to spend a long night in the sea.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Guest House Jijihyang Lounge - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/574c96ec-456f-4e0e-8037-a23065a8fd07.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Guest House Jijihyang Lounge
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Where he recognized her, Gangmun Beach
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Loosen the lone boat anchor and climb on the sperm. I will.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -From Song Kang Jeong-cheol, Kanto Star Song
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Gangmun Beach with beautiful structures to take pictures - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/c46c83ba-15af-47b2-ac46-79b3e48a8ceb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Gangmun Beach with beautiful structures to take pictures
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Song Kang Chungcheol expressed how beautiful he was in the Kwandong Byeonggok with the expression &#39;Everything&#39;s around the Gangneung&#39; Gangmungyo &#39;(currently the bridge) in the 16th century. The indigo sea behind the signboard with this phrase is where Sung Joon began to feel sweet emotions for Hyejin for the first time. Gangmun Beach, located south of Gangmun Bridge, is the beach that filled the hearts of many people like her smiling in the camera frame taken for the magazine photo shoot.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Gangmun beach with beautiful indigo - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/16e34049-4cb5-49f2-b4ec-e7cd59d6750f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Gangmun beach with beautiful indigo
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Located next to Gyeongpo Beach, this place is small and quiet unlike Gyeongpo Beach, so it is the best place to think alone. This place is perfect for `` traveling alone. &#39;&#39; The beautiful structures I saw in the drama are also sparse, so it&#39;s good to take a picture with your lover or a friend and leave memories. If you are planning to stay overnight, check out the night Gangmun Beach. The night view of the sodary bridge connecting Gangmun beach and Gyeongpo beach is excellent.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The light changes every moment and the night view of the more beautiful tower - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/d77e0c29-80c7-4365-8a13-43526fbd4fb4.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The light changes every moment and the night view of the more beautiful tower
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   For those who just want to meet Gangmun beach, I recommend a meal at Paul &amp;amp; Mary, a homemade burger house located at the beginning. Beach and homemade burgers. It&#39;s a strange combination that can&#39;t be imagined, but it&#39;s rumored to be already in line.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;State of exotic shop - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/508bd58a-f3cd-4767-acef-8383b959ac5c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     State of exotic shop
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The main menu is the bacon mozzarella burger, where the mozzarella cheese flows like a waterfall. Don&#39;t be surprised to see how the modifier, &#39;visual thug&#39; fits together. Juicy patties, chewy and rich mozzarella cheese, and fresh vegetables combine to create a more fantastic combination.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Typical bacon mozzarella burger - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/9f14f46a-807a-453f-b5d2-62c315e74819.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Typical bacon mozzarella burger
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   The place where he and her tremble are kept
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It was fascinated by the warm lunches prepared for loved ones who work on the weekends and the high-profile of the proposals. It&#39;s Dumulhead, a place that viewers choose as the best scene, and the best choice for photo hobbyists.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Dumulmul, formerly called &#39;head&#39;, refers to the area of Yangshu-ri, Yangseo-myeon where the stems of the Namhan River and the Bukhan River meet and merge. Until 1973, Paldang Dam was a people staying in Gangwon-do on the waterway. However, instead of a lane, the boat was blocked, and so did his life as a muzzle.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Fantastic look of Dumulde head - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/95990819-8bdd-4bad-a7ef-b1b0e3879bcb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Fantastic look of Dumulde head
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   But many still visit here. To see the fantastic scenery you can&#39;t find anywhere else. The blue light that meets the sky, Kim Hue-sung, the only shipyard in Korea, and the 400-year-old zelkova tree, which boasts a height of 30m and a circumference of 8m, combine to create a unique and rare landscape. Thanks to this, it is popular not only for drama but also for various shooting places such as movies, advertisements and weddings.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The best place to take pictures on Dumuldeu - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/31d3d96f-fe56-4236-ad53-25461e6c66f7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The best place to take pictures on Dumuldeu
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   At dawn, photographers from all over the country gather to capture the fascinating sunrise of Dumul head. It is hard to express how the water mist that blooms lump together creates a dreamy atmosphere. The inscription on the rock tells us, &#39;Did you see the water fog that mysteriously rises in the dawn sky?&#39; If you&#39;re curious about the wonderful dawn of the water fog, why don&#39;t you go on an early date this weekend?
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Painter sketching head - Paju, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/25/c1b921be-b766-483d-900b-2ab7db4222bc.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Painter sketching head
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel info
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Forest of Wisdom
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Address: 145 Hoedong-gil, Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Contact / Reservation: 031-955-0082
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Gangmun Beach
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Address: 352, Changhae-ro, Gangneung-si, Gangwon-do
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Inquiries / Information: General Tourist Information Center 033-640-4414
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Yangpyeong Dumul head
      &lt;br/&gt;
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     Address: Yangsu 1-ri, Yangseo-myeon, Yangpyeong-gun, Gyeonggi-do
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Contact / Information: Yangpyeong Culture &amp;amp; Tourism 031-773-5101
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Nearby restaurants
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Dining glow: 145 Hoedong-gil, Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do / Steak, Pasta, Risotto / 031-955-0070
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://blog.naver.com/noeulms&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://blog.naver.com/noeulms
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Paul &amp;amp; Mary Burger: 33, Changhae-ro 350beon-gil, Gangneung-si, Gangwon-do / Homemade Burger / 033-653-2354
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Wangui Champon: 305-2, Yongmun-ro, Yongmun-myeon, Yangpyeong-gun, Gyeonggi-do / Champon / 031-774-0091
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Accommodation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Yvestel: 446, Pilseung-ro, Tanhyeon-myeon, Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea / 031-944-0335
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Benikea Gyungpo Beach Hotel: 303-4 Gangmun-dong, Gangneung-si, Gangwon-si / 033-643-6699
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Aria Pension: 33, Dojanggye-gil, Seojong-myeon, Yangpyeong-gun, Gyeonggi-do / 031-771-0030
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was written in November 2015, and may change afterwards. Please check before traveling.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Information such as text, photos, and videos used in this article is copyrighted by Korea Tourism Organization, so unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>