<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chungbuk on Every Corner of Korea</title>
    <link>https://codecorea.github.io/tags/chungbuk/</link>
    <description>Every Corner of Korea (Chungbuk)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 03:21:03 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="https://codecorea.github.io/tags/chungbuk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Filming locations in Jecheon, from the movie &#39;Parkha Candy&#39; to the drama &#39;Shark&#39; - Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/filming-locations-in-jecheon-from-the-movie-parkha-candy-to-the-drama-shark-243/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 03:21:03 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/filming-locations-in-jecheon-from-the-movie-parkha-candy-to-the-drama-shark-243/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;filming-locations-in-jecheon-from-the-movie-parkha-candy-to-the-drama-shark--243&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;The sunset of Cheongpung Lake makes the inland sea feel real - Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/243/5e967bae-bca0-4a72-9905-60e7f5ee1779.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    The sunset of Cheongpung Lake makes the inland sea feel real
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Filming locations in Jecheon, from the movie &#39;Parkha Candy&#39; to the drama &#39;Shark&#39;
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Located in the central inland, Jecheon is a small town. It is perfect for quiet walking around. Recently, it has emerged as a city of movies and dramas. The police station set of the Visual Media Center, Cheongpungho and Uirimji area bring together the beauty and scenery of Jecheon and the memories of the movie.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Take the train to the movie location
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   “I want to go back!”
   &lt;br/&gt;
   The end of the film &amp;lt;Parkha Candy&amp;gt; was a scene that would remain in the movie history. It is not an exaggeration to say that the scene that made today&#39;s movie star Seol Kyung-goo. It is near Jinso village in Baekwoon-myeon, Jecheon-si. It is located above the elevated railroad in Chungbuk Line between Gongjeon Station and Samtan Station. There are two forked bridges, which are in front of the tunnel through the middle of the cliff. At the time of shooting, it was remote. After the movie was successful, the road opened and the number of vehicles increased. Pensions have also entered quite a few. The movie changed the village. Since it was a 1999 work, it was 14 years ago.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &amp;lt;Parkha Candy&amp;gt; was a flare. Since then, many movies and dramas have visited Jecheon. Local small towns&#39; unique feelings and moods sometimes exist as a set of movies. Several factors have also been added. The first is a train. Jecheon is the starting point of the Central Inland Circulation Train (O-Train). The central inland circulation train is a circular train that connects the three provinces of central inland. Departing from Jecheon, Chungbuk, passes Yeongju, Gyeongbuk, and Taebaek, Gangwon-do. You can feel the beauty of Baekdu-daegan. It&#39;s a movie-like train journey.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;New exhibition on the first floor of Jecheon Media Center - Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/243/4e9552b2-8081-4b9f-9335-a896f1bb03d6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     New exhibition on the first floor of Jecheon Media Center
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The second is the movie itself. It&#39;s not just a movie, it&#39;s a music movie. It is composed of music or music. Jecheon hosts international film festivals representing Korea, along with Busan, Bucheon, and Jeonju. Jecheon International Music Film Festival. This year, it opened on August 14th (Wed) and held six days until Monday (19th). Movie fans who simply visited to enjoy the music festival are immersed in the city&#39;s fascination around the end of the festival. So, I visit Jecheon once again. This is to meet Jecheon again as a travel destination, not a movie city of Jecheon. In that case, I recommend taking a trip to a filming or drama location filmed in Jecheon. Most of Jecheon&#39;s main filming locations are Jecheon&#39;s famous travel destinations.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Jecheon Film Media Center, a renovated old city council building - Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/243/45bbd879-ca44-4712-b736-5192402cce98.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Jecheon Film Media Center, a renovated old city council building
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Gathering of movie information, spring of Jecheon Media Center
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The first step in traveling to the Jecheon Filming Site is to start from the Jecheon Film Media Center in spring. It is a place that holds various information of the movie city Jecheon. The old Jecheon City Council building was remodeled and opened in 2008. In particular, the office of the Cheongpung Film Commission, which discovers and introduces the location of Jecheon, is located. It is often difficult to find the exact location of the filming location, but you can also get help such as the location and transportation of filming locations, movies, and dramas that are being released recently.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Traces of filming also exist within the center. This is the police station set inside. Many of the recent movies, such as &amp;lt;Howling&amp;gt;, &amp;lt;Broken Arrow&amp;gt;, and &amp;lt;Kan Ki Nam&amp;gt;, are set by the Jecheon Video Media Center. It is also released to the general public, but the detailed settings are not usually made, so you can only feel the atmosphere. At the entrance on the first floor, movies and drama posters taken in Jecheon have filled the inner walls. &amp;lt;Wagon&amp;gt;, &amp;lt;Gone with the Wind&amp;gt;, &amp;lt;Chosunyeong Detective&amp;gt;. In front of the stairs going up to the second floor, there is a new prop, the main prop of the movie &amp;lt;Shinkijeon&amp;gt;. &amp;lt;Shin Ki-jeon&amp;gt; by Jung Jae-young is a 2008 work. It dealt with the production process of Shinkijeon, a rocket propulsion arrow made during the Joseon Dynasty. A set was built in the mountains of Geumseong-myeon and photographed. At the time of filming, Dr. Chae Seok-yeon, a researcher at the Korea Aerospace Research Institute, restored a new mechanism and gathered attention. The new mechanism in the center was donated by the production company to Jecheon City. The production plan written in &amp;lt;Army Prayer&amp;gt; in &amp;lt;&amp;lt; National Ordinance of the Ordinance&amp;gt; is attached like a manual.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Muam Reservoir that Han Yi-soo and Cho Hae-woo met in &#39;Shark&#39; (Photo: Cheongpung video court) - Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/243/f51b51d2-4b97-425f-9ed3-c465892f5dad.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Muam Reservoir that Han Yi-soo and Cho Hae-woo met in &#39;Shark&#39; (Photo: Cheongpung video court)
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The Jecheon Media Center is useful when it comes to film festivals or location information rather than travel. You can also relax in the cafeteria on the first floor.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Muam Reservoir filming &#39;Gone with the Wind&#39; - Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/243/a15d0cf1-3670-4bcd-b4ac-126d85552659.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Muam Reservoir filming &#39;Gone with the Wind&#39;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   The Secret Lake of the Drama &amp;lt;Shark&amp;gt;
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Cheongpungho is the best place to travel in Jecheon. Cheongpung Lake is an artificial lake created by the construction of Chungju Dam. The same lake is called Chungjuho in Chungju and Cheongpungho in Jecheon. It is called the inland sea because it has the largest size after Soyang Lake. Bibongsan Mountain, Geumsusan Mountain, Insan Mountain, etc. are combined with the spectacular waterways of Namhan River to form a superb view.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;High price of Cheongpung Cultural Heritage Complex - Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/243/1d9f32e8-a4fe-47ad-a3d2-f9585775931a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     High price of Cheongpung Cultural Heritage Complex
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Cheongpung Lake is about a 30-minute drive from downtown Jecheon. It is only a lakeside when you get out of downtown and enter Geumseong-myeon. It is also suitable as a drive course. The Cheongpung Lake is carried whenever the recording path is curved. The first pass is the lakeside KBS shooting set. Filmed major historical dramas of KBS such as &amp;lt;Taejo Wang Geon&amp;gt;. Now closed. Cheongpungho was once a mecca for Korean historical dramas, but after rumors as a destination, its momentum diminished. Rather, the shooting of modern theater has increased than that of historical drama. Rather than building a new set, it captures the beautiful nature of Cheongpungho. The drama &amp;lt;Shark&amp;gt; starring Son Ye-jin and Kim Nam-gil is typical.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Geumnamru, used as a gate for Cheongpung Elementary School - Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/243/8c978a2d-ace8-4c84-9d68-6696d482b8eb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Geumnamru, used as a gate for Cheongpung Elementary School
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   After passing KBS filming location, it is the way to Muamsa Temple on the left. In the past, there was a &amp;lt;Shingijeon&amp;gt; set near Muamsa Temple. This also has lost functionality now. Before the Muam Valley and Muamsa Temple, they passed through the Muam Reservoir (Muam No. 1). As you move from the road toward the reservoir, you will find a small vacant lot on the waterside surrounded by mountains. There is a lonely tree towards the lake. The scenery of the tranquil lake catches the heart. In the drama &amp;lt;Shark&amp;gt;, this is the lakeside next to the villa where Han Yi-soo (Kim Nam-gil) and Jo Ha-woo (Sun Ye-jin) secretly encountered. It is a space suitable for expressing the secret feelings of love and hatred entangled between the two main characters.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Cheongpung Lake from the top of Cheongpung Cultural Foundation - Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/243/48afac3e-6cca-41e9-a1c6-8b945ac3f207.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Cheongpung Lake from the top of Cheongpung Cultural Foundation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   On the one side of the reservoir, the water path of the Muam Valley is also teeming. It is not a professional camping ground, but there are also a few people who enjoy camping with tents. Ahead of the release, starring Ha Ji-won&#39;s &amp;lt;Chosun Beauty Three Musketeers&amp;gt; and Cha Tae-hyun&#39;s &amp;lt;Gone with the Wind&amp;gt; were also filmed in Muamsa and Muam Reservoir. In terms of the scenery of the trip, Muamsa or Valley is better, but Muam Reservoir is a fascinating image of the movie.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;There are a lot of interesting trees, including annual trees. - Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/243/451683f8-1d2b-431a-9beb-09dfe9aa94d3.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     There are a lot of interesting trees, including annual trees.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Magnificent scenery of Cheongpung Lakeside
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   After exiting Muam Reservoir of &amp;lt;Shark&amp;gt;, go to Cheongpung Cultural Foundation and Cheongpung Monorail. It is a travel destination that retains the gorgeous scenery of Cheongpungho. On the way, there is also Cheongpung Land, and it is better to meet Cheongpung Cultural Foundation and Cheongpung Monorail at sunset.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   When you cross Cheongpung Bridge, Cheongpung Cultural Foundation emerges. The cultural assets of Cheongpung, which were in danger of sinking with the Chungju Dam, were collected and created. Climb the foot of the mountain while looking at the remains of the overpass, pavilion, and dolmen. From the top, the panoramic view of Cheongpungho is embraced as a 360-degree panorama. The red baekilhong on each way to climb makes the Cheongpung Cultural Foundation of this time stand out more. Interesting trees like the heart tree and the thinking tree are also interesting. The Cheongpung Cultural Foundation had a SBS historical drama set site just two years ago. I filmed &amp;lt;Awaiting&amp;gt;, &amp;lt;Iljimae&amp;gt;, and &amp;lt;Jang Gil-san&amp;gt;, but it was recently demolished. You can&#39;t look into the stage of an old historical drama directly, but the outstanding nature of Cheongpungho, which forms the background, is enough comfort.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Cheongpung Land where you can enjoy extreme sports - Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/243/430293be-0214-4d45-b06b-8749e2d584e5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Cheongpung Land where you can enjoy extreme sports
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Fortunately, a larger scale facility overlooking the Cheongpung Lake was created. It is Cheongpung Monorail that entered last year. Originally used for transporting paragliding equipment to the summit of Bibongsan, it was developed for tourism. It operates 7 cars and travels 3km away in 23 minutes one way. The monorail climbs to the top of Bibongsan Mountain at 531 meters above sea level. The view from the top is too undue to climb easily. Mt. Seollang, Seongbong, Guksabong, and Daedeoksan create a delightful landscape.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sunset of Cheongpung Land, filming &amp;lt;Radio Star&amp;gt; - Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/243/fb8d1679-71fe-46ae-a428-90d3cfc21c06.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sunset of Cheongpung Land, filming &amp;lt;Radio Star&amp;gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you have a leisurely time, Jardrock Road is also recommended. It is a path that walks through the mountainous village of Cheongpungho, and is made of 7 courses, including a small Dongsan-gil, Jeongbangsa-gil, and Ice Valley Ecological Road. There are many walks along the lake, creating a unique scenery. The short course takes 90 minutes and the long course takes 280 minutes. Then, visit Cheongpung Land at sunset.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Jardrock Road along the foothills of Cheongpung Lakeside - Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/243/134d31b1-9b68-4a31-8570-c32435983dfc.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Jardrock Road along the foothills of Cheongpung Lakeside
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   &amp;lt;Radio Star&amp;gt; at sunset
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   During sunset, go to Cheongpung Land (Resort) again. The parking lot filmed a scene from the movie Radio Star. Singer Choi Gon (Park Jung-hoon) and manager Park Min-soo (An Sung-ki) shared a cup of coffee and regained their righteousness. The lonely middle-aged life is exquisitely matched with the glow of the blue wind. The sunset in Cheongpung Land is the best. It is an unprecedented view from the inland sea. The shadows of the mountains formed by Bibongsan Mountain, Indeungsan Mountain, and Keimyung Mountain across the lake make you lose your words. It makes my heart beat like a romance in a movie. As you go down the lake, there are extreme leisure facilities next to the lakeside stage. The country&#39;s tallest 62m bungee jump, the country&#39;s first ejection seat, and the country&#39;s longest 1.4km cable coaster (zip line) bring exciting excitement.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;5&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Euirimji Promenade, one of the most beautiful night views - Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/243/a6e0ef3a-35f7-46b1-8549-bb369dfa6013.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Euirimji Promenade, one of the most beautiful night views
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   After watching the sunset in Cheongpung Land, head to Urimim not far from downtown Jecheon. Along with Cheongpungho, it is a must-see and travel destination in Jecheon. Uirimji is the oldest reservoir in Korea along with Gimje Byeokgolje and Miryang Fisheries. It is said to have been built for the first time during the King of Singa Jinheung. Currently, it is faithful to the role of an amusement park with parklands and trails. Around the pond, pine trees and weeping willows add luck. It is popular as a dating spot for lovers, like &amp;lt;The Secret Charm of Female Professors&amp;gt;. In the daytime, it is also worth visiting Solim Park in Uirimji, where you shot the scene of the gang&#39;s picnic. However, the late night reservoir walk is also indispensable. Uirimji is one of the most beautiful night views in Jecheon. It is not just a night view, but a night scenery that you can feel while walking slowly. Since it is held at the tiptoe, it captures Jecheon&#39;s travel to Sinab.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;5&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Night scenery of willow trees with willow trees - Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/243/241521d8-0894-43fe-8908-948bd2b63c4c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Night scenery of willow trees with willow trees
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Visual Media Center Spring
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    : 242, Uirim-daero, Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, 043-645-4995
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Cheongpung Land (Cheonpung Lakeside Stage)
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    : 26, Gyo-ri, Cheongpung-myeon, Jecheon-si, Chungbuk 043-648-4151
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Cheongpung Cultural Foundation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    : 6-20, Multae-ri, Cheongpung-myeon, Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, 043-641-5532
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Cheongpung Tourist Monorail
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    : 114, Dogok-ri, Cheongpung-myeon, Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, 043-642-3326
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Willim
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    : 241, Mosan-dong, Jecheon-si, Chungbuk 043-651-7101
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1.Nearby Restaurants
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Yechon: Gondrenamul Rice / 30 Cheongpung Myeongwol-ro, Cheongpung-myeon, Jecheon-si / 043-647-3707
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Ant Restaurant: Herbal Medicine Sundae / 114 Yongducheon-ro, Jecheon-si / 043-643-5093
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Taejeong: Herbal Bibimbap / 184 Jangrak-ro, Jecheon-si / 043-646-6565
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.태정.전문.kr&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;태정으로 이동&#34;&gt;
     http://www.태정.전문.kr
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2.Accommodation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Cheongpung Resort: 1763 Cheongpungho-ro, Cheongpung-myeon, Jecheon-si / 043-640-7000
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cheongpungresort.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;청풍리조트로 이동&#34;&gt;
     http://www.cheongpungresort.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Early morning lakeside pension: 53-15 Cheongpungho-ro 42-gil, Cheongpung-myeon, Jecheon-si / 070-8876-8677, 010-9049-8677
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.dreamlakepension.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;이른아침호숫가로 이동&#34;&gt;
     http://www.dreamlakepension.com/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Dream Lake Pension: 53-10 Cheongpungho-ro 42-gil, Cheongpung-myeon, Jecheon-si / 043-648-6380
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.dreamlake.co.kr&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     www.dreamlake.co.kr
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was created in September 2013, and may change later, so be sure to check it before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The world of junk art beyond imagination, &#39;Boeun Fun Park&#39; - Boeun-gun, Chungbuk, South Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/the-world-of-junk-art-beyond-imagination-boeun-fun-park-241/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 03:21:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/the-world-of-junk-art-beyond-imagination-boeun-fun-park-241/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Boeun-gun, Chungbuk, South Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;the-world-of-junk-art-beyond-imagination-boeun-fun-park--241&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Fun Park&#39;s Junk Art - Boeun-gun, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/241/4de0add6-4e79-4c7b-94ef-98618ac98b9a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Fun Park&#39;s Junk Art
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   The world of junk art beyond imagination, &#39;Boeun Fun Park&#39;
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Boeun-gun, Chungbuk, South Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    There was a boy who was very curious about machines as a child. A boy who liked the radio or sewing machine in his house more than a book turned into an eco-artist when he became an adult and made great works of art using abandoned tires, LPG gas cylinders, spark plugs, bolts and nuts. This is to remind children of the importance of nature by creating a second nature from wastes produced by the destruction of nature. This is the story of Oh Dae-ho, a sculptor who created a fun park based on junk art in Boeun, Chungbuk. Junk art is an art based on the scavengers and miscellaneous things that occur in everyday life.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Eco-friendly complex cultural play space using waste
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Fun Park (043-544-7702,
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.funpark.kr&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;펀파크 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
     www.funpark.kr
    &lt;/a&gt;
    )
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Is a unique playground that provides children with the opportunity and time to freely unfold their imagination. The material of the exhibition works is waste, but the completed works are interesting and friendly robots, animals, and dinosaurs.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   When arriving at the entrance, the first robot Taekwon V greets the children. After that, the dinosaurs appear through the trees. Robots and dinosaurs are the most favorite items for boys. Even if you don&#39;t go inside the fun park, the intuition of &#39;Your kids will love it&#39; comes.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Fun Park Ticket Office - Boeun-gun, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/241/556d809c-1179-4dc9-b9c9-28f08fbc3834.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Fun Park Ticket Office
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   At the ticket office, robots welcome visitors. The Transformers Voyager Starstream is visible, and the goblins are visible in the membrane. Boys who are sold by robots cannot enter easily. Only after taking a commemorative photo with the robot, the personality is released. Parents often wrestle with the children.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Transformer Voyager Starstream at the ticket office - Boeun-gun, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/241/115c4cef-3469-4246-98e1-f2aca26ee7b5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Transformer Voyager Starstream at the ticket office
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Even if you enter, the children rarely take a step. This is because animal friends in the fairy tale such as hippopotamus, wolf, raccoon, monkey, and rabbit give a welcome greeting. This time, the faces of the mother and daughter are full of smiles. Robots are exclusively owned by men, and girls are not interested. However, animals with funny and funny expressions are the characters that girls like.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Cute character doll - Boeun-gun, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/241/cd0a3870-5f75-448f-a4ea-142229223481.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Cute character doll
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The first place to visit is &#39;Art Gallery O&#39;. To go to the gallery, you have to go through the art park. The lawn is full of works using waste. A black dragon soaring up to the sky, King Kong with an angry look, a cow fighting head to head, and more.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Artwork Park in Fun Park - Boeun-gun, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/241/a09fef93-6fc8-4dea-917d-9da47ddaebff.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Artwork Park in Fun Park
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   King Kong is the most popular. There are many visitors who take pictures by imitating because they seem to be roaring because they are angry and they are dancing Psy&#39;s Gangnam Style.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;This is a work that embodies the fighting of Qingdao - Boeun-gun, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/241/f7000ec1-5102-4529-b32b-af5d9df2db73.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     This is a work that embodies the fighting of Qingdao
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   There are also fun amusement facilities packed with dolls. &#39;Yona Fish&#39; descending the slide through the belly of a whale, &#39;Nanta Drum&#39; tapping on the motorcycle and tapping on an angry rooster, &#39;Rooster Seesaw&#39;, and &#39;Orien-Bang Bang&#39; that rotates left and right when a pedal is rolled.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Children&#39;s favorite whale belly slide - Boeun-gun, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/241/89295b7e-bc12-4921-ba3e-1e64ef10e374.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Children&#39;s favorite whale belly slide
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It is not just about seeing, but touching, riding and tapping directly to get closer to the work. In the meantime, you are impressed by the artist&#39;s brilliant idea.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;14&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Tank with turret - Boeun-gun, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/241/fdeb3050-8c49-4020-90d9-6d27d175f6d8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Tank with turret
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   World of fairy tales and robots, art gallery O
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Art Gallery O was decorated with the works of Oh Dae-ho, who combined art and science with the theme of space and global environment. It has a fairy tale country and a robot land, and consists of eco art that emphasizes the importance of the environment, and media art that uses sound and video. It is a space reflecting the artist&#39;s philosophy of &#34;If not experienced, it is not art&#34;.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Fun Park&#39;s Junk Art - Boeun-gun, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/241/b2ce6367-ae5b-4fda-924f-dc83f5acd87e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Fun Park&#39;s Junk Art
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   There are tanks and spaceships at the entrance to the gallery. Tanks and spacecraft that were elaborately made from scraps were allowed to climb directly. What is curious is that the tank turret rotates and the spacecraft moves. It is a work tailored to the eye level of a little spectator who is not satisfied with just looking. Children on a moving tank like it without a hitch on an unexpected windfall. On the wall of the gallery, horses fly in the sky and colorful salmon dance. Next to it, a dove symbolizing peace is flying in line.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Fun Park&#39;s Junk Art - Boeun-gun, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/241/fbe00ec2-8e5a-4172-af4b-249fb3d056a5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Fun Park&#39;s Junk Art
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The fairy tale kingdom, not in the gallery, is a popular place for men and women of all ages. Works with motifs such as 《Girl River Travels》, 《Cinderella》, 《Snow White》, 《Shimcheongjeon》 attract attention. In order to enjoy watching the fairy tale country, you have to try to find a scene that is precisely expressed in the work.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Colorful objects and spaceships - Boeun-gun, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/241/3017039a-1d94-406f-acc2-1277d8c127ce.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Colorful objects and spaceships
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &#39;Gulver Travel Plane&#39; expresses Gulliver, which is tied to a rope by drifting to a small country, and has fun features hidden in each character. There are kings and queens of small countries, some who shoot bows, some who climb ladders. &#39;Snow White&#39; expressed the scene where she fell down after eating the apple given by Queen Witch. Abandoned apples are laid out in a bunch, while a witch is hiding behind a tree in the forest and watching. It is fun to find the fairy tale descriptions that are easy to pass by, as if looking for treasure.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#39;Gulliver&#39;s Travels&#39; in Fairy Tale - Boeun-gun, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/241/d905ef1e-3710-43ea-ae64-dfe1872bd604.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     &#39;Gulliver&#39;s Travels&#39; in Fairy Tale
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Upon further entry, the spaceship is under bright lighting. Star Wars spacecraft. It is amazing that it was made to respond to sound. If you clap loudly and clap, the colorful lights will flash. It&#39;s like taking a spaceship and traveling to a mysterious universe.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   Inside, there is a robot choir that sings, dances, and greets. Each character is amazing. The biggest robot is named Meron. It&#39;s cute to stick your tongue out.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Robot Choir - Boeun-gun, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/241/aca5c958-2f08-4806-b4d7-35557bfefc09.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Robot Choir
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In addition to this, there are color shadows that hung umbrellas on the ceiling to create a dreamy atmosphere, and a media art gallery where works with luminous paint in the dark radiate a mysterious light.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   Art Gallery O can be viewed in about 10 minutes by looking at it with a watermelon lick. But curious children need plenty of time. Parents should help them to watch slowly, increase their creativity, develop their imagination, and realize the value of their environment.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Color shadow to experience the art of light - Boeun-gun, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/241/db920a36-a403-46db-b061-8ecd7e11e203.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Color shadow to experience the art of light
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Math! It&#39;s not difficult, math experience center
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   A typical experience at Fun Park is math experience. This is an educational method that allows you to naturally interact with mathematics while touching and listening with a tool through mathematics play experience learning that combines amusement with math. The entrance to the mathematics experience center is paid, and you can watch it once a day three times a day (11:00, 14:00, 16:00) while listening to the curator&#39;s explanation.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Even if you don&#39;t have an experience center, you can enjoy a free math experience at the outdoor experience center. Leonardo Da Vinci&#39;s bridge is made without connecting parts such as nails. You will understand the spatial shape by touching and looking at how the wood is connected to each other.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A work that tells the abacus principle - Boeun-gun, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/241/d72b3f7c-4ae6-4b2c-b00a-7d6c7ce72820.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A work that tells the abacus principle
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &#39;What if the bicycle wheels are square?&#39; It breaks the stereotype that you can&#39;t ride a square wheeled bicycle and tells you that you can ride smoothly if you make the road convex. Convex roads where polygon wheels can run well are called &#39;suspension roads&#39; in mathematics. By installing a convex road, you can ride a square wheel bike and understand the flat shape.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;15&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Square wheel bike - Boeun-gun, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/241/fcf84f00-97a9-4219-bc54-25086c0f6a4e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Square wheel bike
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;topmr&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1.Access
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
     * Self-driving
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34; style=&#34;MARGIN-TOP: 0px&#34;&gt;
    Dangjin Sangju Expressway → Songnisan IC → Turn left toward Songnisan (National Road No. 25) → Jangnae Intersection → Agricultural Industrial Complex Intersection → GS Boeun Gas Station → Fun Park
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
     * public transport
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34; style=&#34;MARGIN-TOP: 0px&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Seoul → Boeun
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    : Operates 4 times a day (07:00, 10:30, 14:30, 17:30) from Central City Terminal (02-6282-0114), takes about 3 hours 10 minutes
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Operates 12 times a day (07: 30 ~ 18: 30) from East Seoul General Terminal (1688-5979), takes about 3 hours
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Daejeon → Boeun
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    : Operates 17 times a day (06: 50 ~ 20: 10) from Daejeon Complex Terminal (1577-2259), takes 1 hour 10 minutes
    &lt;br/&gt;
    ≫ Use the intra-city bus via Gwangi near Boeun Intercity Bus Terminal and get off at Boeun Fun Park. Operates every 30 minutes and takes about 20 minutes
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;topmr&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Restaurants around
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Kyunghee Restaurant:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Hanjeongsik / Songnisan-myeon, Sanae-ri / 043-543-7573
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Yonggung Restaurant:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Pork Bulgogi / Suhanmyeon Balsan-ri / 043-542-9288
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Mido dumplings:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Jujube Bread / Samsan-ri, Boeun-eup / 043-544-4097
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;topmr&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     3.Accommodation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Jung Yi Pum Motel:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Daeeun-ri, Boeun-eup / 043-543-9993
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Yasong Park:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Daeeun-ri, Boeun-eup / 043-542-7778
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Songnisan Youth Town:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Sangpang-ri, Songnisan-myeon / 043-540-7777
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.sokrisan.co.kr&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;속리산유스타운 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
     www.sokrisan.co.kr
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Songnisan Green Park Hotel:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Sarini-myeon, Songnisan-myeon / 043-543-3650
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://그린파크호텔.kr&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;속리산그린파크호텔 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
     http://그린파크호텔.kr
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    ※ The above information was updated in February 2014, and may change later, so be sure to check it before you travel.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A pleasant meeting between the mountain and the lake - Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/a-pleasant-meeting-between-the-mountain-and-the-lake-218/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 03:28:52 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/a-pleasant-meeting-between-the-mountain-and-the-lake-218/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;a-pleasant-meeting-between-the-mountain-and-the-lake--218&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Scenery of Gogok Castle Wall seen from Brothers&#39; Peak in Samusan (Photo courtesy of Jecheon City Hall) - Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/218/20beb6a5-55ec-425c-83b8-0c289786dcc2.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Scenery of Gogok Castle Wall seen from Brothers&#39; Peak in Samusan (Photo courtesy of Jecheon City Hall)
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   A pleasant meeting between the mountain and the lake
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The phrase &#39;Cheongpungho Jadrakgil&#39; is very pretty. It&#39;s also soft to pronounce, and it feels like ‘Sabujakjidada’, meaning that it acts lightly and effortlessly. I feel that it will be a trekking course that is easy to walk for some reason. Jadrak-gil refers to ‘a narrow path in a hilly country at the foot of a mountain.’ The name Cheongpungho is in front of it because the road runs around the mountain village surrounding Cheongpungho. It is a hiking trail, but it is difficult to walk. Of the 100 ridges in Cheongpungho in Jecheon, it is difficult to find a walking trail with such a great view point, as you walk along the beautiful scenery around the lake.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Cheongpungho Walk while looking at Cheongpungho
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In Cheongpungho Jardrock Road, 7 courses were developed. Among them, the 9.9km ‘Gokgok Wall Road’, starting from Oksunbong Rest Area in front of Oksundaegyo Bridge and passing through Gogok-ri and Dabul-ri to Gogogol in Jigok-ri, is the best course in harmony with a wonderful view and diverse flora.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   What is called Gogok Castle Wall Road is the place where the wall was formed in the past. The walls are not made of stone. The slopes of the slopes are named because they act as natural walls.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    jade
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Oksun Bridge, where the Gogok Wall Street begins - Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/218/fe52ce12-4356-48b8-929e-d7a5ddbe4bb4.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Oksun Bridge, where the Gogok Wall Street begins
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The hilly path at the foot of the mountain continues, and occasionally there is a place to breathe. It is good to keep the surrounding branches and weeds neatly organized. Occasionally, there is a shelter where you can see the scenery of Cheongpungho closely. Under the blue skies in May, the mountain streams colored by fresh green and the ripples of the lake with azure are spectacular.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Goegok Seongbyeok Trail - Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/218/9aceb191-e040-4ee7-90ba-b16e004c2962.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Goegok Seongbyeok Trail
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   From the start, I keep walking uphill, but it is not difficult. It is because the slope is gentle and comfortable. I&#39;m definitely hiking, but my steps are light. The white spring primrose and yellow yangji flower are greeted with bright light all over the place.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Goegok Seongbyeok Trail - Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/218/898fe378-dc26-4fbc-9465-b9d723ab7f9d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Goegok Seongbyeok Trail
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   this
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Great spot to take pictures - Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/218/4b9ceada-99fd-4224-a3f9-eb33a15db900.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Great spot to take pictures
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Turn around the road you came to and go to Dabuli, called &#39;the first town under the sky. If you follow the downhill path, the forest of trees will be cleared and you will see an open ridge, where there is the Baekbong Juk. This is a shelter created by the opening of Jardrock Road. For a moment, you can feel the emotion of a quiet and quiet mountain village filling thirst and hunger with rice wine and pancakes.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Dabuli called the first town under the sky - Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/218/e1afc1e3-ca1f-43b5-8f2c-42114a28a50e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Dabuli called the first town under the sky
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   From Baekbong Jukmak to the top of Dabuljae, a small village passes through a simple village. The road is paved with asphalt. The summit of Dabuljae is the middle point of Goebbulseongbyeokgil. From here, go round the foot of Samsan Mountain (478m) and go down to Gosugol. However, if you want to descend quickly because you feel limited by your physical strength or time, you can go down to where you first started through Gogok-ri.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Milestones informing Cheongpungho - Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/218/4d903782-4cfa-41c4-98b6-4bc5c92dfe8b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Milestones informing Cheongpungho
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   There are several roads where vehicles can be moved, and you can follow Imdo.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;14&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Milestones informing Cheongpungho - Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/218/a3f153ed-e7df-43f5-9af5-b7edc4150d78.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Milestones informing Cheongpungho
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   When you walk on a mountain path from Dabulam toward Gosugol, you pass through a dune field and thorny vines that exceed the height of your waist. The open ridge path is repeated and can be said to be a highlight section of the Goegokseong Wall Path while walking with Cheongpung Lake under your feet. If you walk for about an hour, you reach 403 bags, and if you walk another 15 minutes, Limdo comes out. The feeling of walking on Imdo is not just walking on a mountain path, but large and small fields spread out on the left and right sides of the road, allowing you to feel the freshness of green.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;16&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Hiker smelling herbal scents while hiking - Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/218/a1b0b75a-c47e-40f9-956b-b4879fdcb88c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Hiker smelling herbal scents while hiking
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Short but intense Jeongbangsagil
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;span&gt;
    &lt;span&gt;
     The advantage of Cheongpungho Jadrak Road is that it has a variety of courses. Even travelers who do not enjoy hiking or lack time can choose the course that suits their situation and enjoy the wonderful view of the mountain and lake.
    &lt;/span&gt;
   &lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Jeongbangsagil, a two-course course, is a short course of 1.6 km, but the nature in harmony with the temple makes an impressive impression. The way to climb from the entrance to the Neunggang Valley is quite Gapal sweat. Still, the forest is lush and the valley runs along the side of the road, so you can walk in the cool breeze. It is a pity that the road is paved, so it is not easy to drop the mountain.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Jeongbangsa scenery with a mountain on the back and a lake - Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/218/7b81d622-3861-47fe-9f48-9f0c7325443f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Jeongbangsa scenery with a mountain on the back and a lake
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The regret is rewarded with a wonderful scenery the moment you arrive at Jeongbangsa Temple. When you enter Jeolmadang, there are huge rocks that support the integrity of the cylinder, and in front, the Cheongpung Lake and the wavy ridge spread like a panorama. Sit in the yard chair and watch the scenery unfold before your eyes. This is a spectacular sight. Seokgansu, which rises out of the cliffs after the preservation of the cylinder, is an indispensable taste in Jeongbangsagil.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Jiak Jijang Bodhisattva statue carved in the rock wall - Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/218/4cb545fa-ccb7-44bc-94ac-31a34420b9df.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Jiak Jijang Bodhisattva statue carved in the rock wall
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Icygol Ecological Road where ice freezes in the middle of summer
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;span&gt;
    &lt;span&gt;
     The entrance to Neunggang Valley, where Jeongbangsaenggil begins, is also the starting point of the Ice Course, Ice Course, 3 courses. It is a 5.4km section that passes through the stone tower road along the valley and climbs Mandangam and Cheokdae to the ice valley. It is a mysterious natural phenomenon in which ice freezes even in the middle of summer.
    &lt;/span&gt;
   &lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Neunggang Valley at the entrance of Ice Valley (Photo provided by Jecheon City Hall) - Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/218/2c659a82-3441-4062-9c9c-7405b026e81e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Neunggang Valley at the entrance of Ice Valley (Photo provided by Jecheon City Hall)
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   When summer approaches, there are many people who open the valley next to the road and enjoy the Tak. It is because the cool time in the valley is more attractive than hiking. If the ice valley feels far away, it is recommended to walk to the stone tower road. A 20-minute round trip from the valley is enough. The stone tower built on the stone tower road is quite large. Hopefully, the monk of Kumbong Ambassador Geumsuam began to build one by one, and now hundreds of stone towers have been built. The stone tower was erected on a monotonous and boring mountain path, making it a new attraction.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A stone tower road constructed by carefully stacking stones one by one - Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/218/2ef995ed-fa6a-4192-a65f-223838eff706.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A stone tower road constructed by carefully stacking stones one by one
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Jecheon City Hall Tourism Division
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     043-641-6703
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1.Nearby Restaurants
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Geumsusan Trout Market: Trout society / 41 Cheongpungho-ro 39-gil, Geumseong-myeon, Jecheon-si / 043-652-8833
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Zelkova Sashimi House: Trout Bibimbap / 4, Bashiron-ro, Cheongpung-myeon, Jecheon-si / 043-647-0089
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Yechon: Yakchaejeongsik / 30 Cheongpung Myeongwol-ro, Cheongpung-myeon, Jecheon-si / 043-647-3707
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Hama Garden: Chicken Baeksuk / 214-9 Sindam-gil, Geumseong-myeon, Jecheon-si / 043-651-5613
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2.Accommodation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Cheongpung Resort: 1763 Cheongpungho-ro, Cheongpung-myeon, Jecheon-si / 043-640-7000
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cheongpungresort.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;청풍리조트로 이동&#34;&gt;
     http://www.cheongpungresort.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Lake Landscape Pension: 1595-58 Cheongpungho-ro, Geumseong-myeon, Jecheon-si / 043-642-8049
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.greenlake.kr&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     www.greenlake.kr
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Pongnep Pension: Cheongpungho-ro, Cheongpung-myeon, Jecheon-si 2019 / 043-653-5566
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.pontneuf.kr&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     www.pontneuf.kr
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Reed Pension: 439 Cheongpung Myeongwol-ro, Cheongpung-myeon, Jecheon-si / 043-646-6646
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.galipso.com&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     www.galipso.com
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Neunggang Song Pension: 1050, Oksunbong-ro, Susan-myeon, Jecheon-si / 043-651-0033
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was created in May 2013, and may change later, so be sure to check it before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Five markets together, Chungju traditional market outing - Chungju, Chungbuk, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/five-markets-together-chungju-traditional-market-outing-189/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 13:25:31 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/five-markets-together-chungju-traditional-market-outing-189/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Chungju, Chungbuk, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;five-markets-together-chungju-traditional-market-outing--189&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Chungju Free Market - Chungju, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/189/41f1fe28-4f36-49dc-a528-b703addddc64.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Chungju Free Market
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Five markets together, Chungju traditional market outing
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Chungju, Chungbuk, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Each city must have one or two markets to offer. So, when you travel to each city, you can&#39;t miss the fun of going around the traditional market. Another market is waiting for Chungju. Free market, Muhak market, public market, Chungui market, and Pungmul market are gathered in one place along Chungju stream. The fact that several markets are gathered in one place is one of the biggest characteristics of Chungju traditional markets. It&#39;s like a huge market, but five different markets work together to bring you special fun.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Unique free market with market cafes and theaters
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Let&#39;s go to the free market first. The free market is a market formed on the streets of Bukmun where the North Gate was, when Chungju-eupseong existed. Existing on the 5th day As the city was formed, it established itself as the current free market.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The free market tends to have more shops dealing with clothing, sandals, and fabrics than other places. In the past, there were many shops selling peppers, garlic, and rice, but it moved to the agricultural and fishery wholesale market in Chungju, opened in 1995, making it difficult to see the lively appearance as before.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Chungju Free Market - Chungju, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/189/09b665d5-16ef-4e89-85d0-5fafe19c67fb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Chungju Free Market
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   However, as the arcade was installed and registered as a recognized market in 2005, it is seeking change. The market has been cleaned up and new buildings such as customer support centers have been built.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Free cafe where customers visiting the market can rest - Chungju, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/189/ced61e58-f031-428c-934c-429f37de91ae.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Free cafe where customers visiting the market can rest
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The Free Market Customer Support Center building has a free cafe and a jjimjilbang. The free cafe was decorated with pictures showing the history of the market and a well-equipped resting area. There is also a DJ booth where you can subscribe and listen to music. Various drinks are also available, but the price is low, ranging from 500 won to 1,500 won. You can enjoy coffee at half price if you bring a receipt issued in the free market.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Free cafe where customers visiting the market can rest - Chungju, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/189/aff0c1ca-aadc-4c29-869e-09c2e37f177b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Free cafe where customers visiting the market can rest
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   As you look around the market, you can see a unique building called Freedom Theater. Opened in 2012, it recreates the theater atmosphere of the 1970s and 1980s.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Free theater in free market - Chungju, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/189/3726c1c8-35dd-49a7-8732-33023836cdb1.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Free theater in free market
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It is a special space in the market where you can watch old movies for free, but it is currently suspended due to management problems. Instead, movies are shown twice a day at the Free Cafe.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;13&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Free theater in free market - Chungju, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/189/36334e75-7c25-4b50-a976-98d6a40b0047.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Free theater in free market
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   The best spot in Chungju traditional market, Sundae dumpling alley
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you want to enjoy eating, go to Sundae Dumpling Alley. Located in the alley between Muhak Market and Public Market leading from the free market, Sundae Mandu Alley is a must-see for visitors to Chungju Market.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Entrance to Sundae Dumpling Alley at Muhak Market - Chungju, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/189/8b6c9651-ac54-4f68-afe7-f293f36de575.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Entrance to Sundae Dumpling Alley at Muhak Market
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   There are entrances to both Muhak Market and Public Market. The main character of this alley is Sundae and Mandu. Shops selling sundae and dumplings are lined up on either side of the street.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Delicious sundae - Chungju, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/189/ef373ba8-6f00-4d8b-9082-adb6138ca12d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Delicious sundae
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   When entering the Sundae Alley, the hand dumplings made by the grandmothers and aunts and the ripening Sundae stimulate the taste, smell, and vision. If you sit down at a favorite store and sit down, it will make food on the fly.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Delicious sundae - Chungju, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/189/355671c3-8d02-49c9-a323-f6ebd00d6a49.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Delicious sundae
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In particular, Sundaeguk in Soondae Alley has a different taste of broth with siraegi. On one side, pour the boiling broth of Siraegi in a pot, and then cut the warm sundae sliced into pieces. Since it is Siraegi broth, it has a lighter and deeper taste.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Hearty soup - Chungju, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/189/02eec967-df46-4c3c-9b33-f27e224fd191.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Hearty soup
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If the market is not as good as the market, it is often served with plenty of broth and tasted while waiting. The spaciousness, which is hard to find in ordinary restaurants, warms not only the stomach but also the heart.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Delicious hand dumplings - Chungju, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/189/3edaf584-bc50-4ef7-b0d2-c68d46319dc6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Delicious hand dumplings
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Some houses share sundae and dumplings, but most specialize in sundae or dumplings. You can also order dumplings at Sundaejip. Usually, there is a dumpling shop next to the sundae shop, so if you talk, the owner&#39;s mother will take care of the dumplings.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;13&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sundae Dumpling Alley - Chungju, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/189/a6146a0b-8f60-4db4-b67b-0053a7639e6e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sundae Dumpling Alley
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Delicious hand dumplings are also cheap. Meat dumplings are 5 1,000 won and kimchi dumplings are 7 1,000 won, so if you have a few thousand won, you can eat them abundantly.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;15&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Market-rich food - Chungju, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/189/afc1e8d4-9e3c-46c9-82d9-e033ed6ecd8d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Market-rich food
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Even around the alley, there are many shops selling dumplings, sundae, potato cakes, and snacks, so you can choose from a variety of menus to suit your taste.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;17&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Market-rich food - Chungju, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/189/02c0a7c6-4cbe-49df-a951-a4a28063d23f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Market-rich food
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Let&#39;s fully appreciate the attractiveness of the market at a reasonable price.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;19&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Market-rich food - Chungju, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/189/d2bcbb77-861f-4186-90f4-89ecc21b0f22.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Market-rich food
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   In the history of Mayor Chungju
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The history of Muhak Market, which is always visited by many people, such as Sundae Alley, has been around since 1978. When protests broke out in the process of cracking down on street vendors who had been in the position of the old gardening cooperative in Chung-in-dong, they settled in the current Muhak market by moving shopping malls in Munhwa-dong and Bongbang-dong. The Chungju Public Market leading to the Muhak Market was opened in 1964 in accordance with the government&#39;s market policy for small merchants.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;15&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Muhak market leading to free market - Chungju, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/189/a53ffb21-bef9-4373-9714-e96db542252c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Muhak market leading to free market
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The Sundae Alley connected with the Muhak Market is famous, and there have been several restaurants. Many stores sell foods such as vegetables, fish, and chicken.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;16&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Public market leading to free market - Chungju, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/189/069e0a3a-bff3-4433-beaa-f9a10d716b59.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Public market leading to free market
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   On the other hand, the small and quiet Chungui Market is a traditional market naturally formed in the place where 5 days of market continued from the free market.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;17&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;arcade - Chungju, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/189/c0257602-87fb-4482-8677-6d561ad8fc98.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     arcade
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The fruit and vegetable market and the alley alley were formed, and in the 1970s, there was a Chungju court market, so it was a commercial district. However, as the agricultural and fisheries wholesale market opened and the fruits and vegetables stores relocated, commercial districts are not the same now. Stores dealing with souvenir goods, pottery shops, and mills are mainly gathered, so people&#39;s feet are not frequent.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;18&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Seating area - Chungju, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/189/c3ff49c6-bf3d-4004-afc4-3ea155bab4cf.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Seating area
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Let&#39;s meet Chungju Poongmul Market along with Free Market, Muhak Market, Public Market, and Chungui Market. The Pungmul Market along Gyohyeoncheon is open on the 5th, 5th, 10th, 15th, 20th, 25th, and 30th each month.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;19&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Comfortable market atmosphere - Chungju, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/189/8feb3868-a211-4716-afc6-2056f6bc1df0.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Comfortable market atmosphere
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Originally, it was a naturally formed 5-day market around Yeseong Park, but moved to its current location in 2001. You can find a variety of products and food.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;13&#34; id3=&#34;20&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Chungju market map - Chungju, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/189/00307b9d-9814-4eea-aa3b-948cca9aa3c0.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Chungju market map
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   There is another spot you should not miss while looking around the market in Chungju. It is the Samhwa Forge in Nuri Market, not far from Muhak Market and Free Market. This is a meaningful place with the history of Mayor Chungin-dong. You can feel the past scenery of Chungil-dong scattered by blacksmiths.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;15&#34; id3=&#34;21&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Samhwa Grand Forge, which has the No. 13 night market in Chungbuk - Chungju, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/189/319da8b7-f0c6-496b-a1ad-34afc8a2ad04.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Samhwa Grand Forge, which has the No. 13 night market in Chungbuk
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The building itself is modern, but the traditional blacksmithing remains when you step inside. Kim Myung-il, designated as the 13th Intangible Cultural Property in Chungbuk, is still making iron tools by hand quenching and hammering.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;17&#34; id3=&#34;22&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Samhwa Grand Forge, which has the No. 13 night market in Chungbuk - Chungju, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/189/a6de954d-d32d-40ac-a2e7-4742fe7a78a9.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Samhwa Grand Forge, which has the No. 13 night market in Chungbuk
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   You can purchase high-quality and solid objects created by the intangible cultural property, and you can also experience forge. The well-established Samhwa Blacksmith owner Nobubu always welcomes guests who come to watch.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;19&#34; id3=&#34;23&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Samhwa Grand Forge, which has the No. 13 night market in Chungbuk - Chungju, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/189/d2a0f9e8-ce6a-4d86-8452-a06292201108.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Samhwa Grand Forge, which has the No. 13 night market in Chungbuk
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p style=&#34;COLOR: #7b1f42&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Free market
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Address: 30 Free Market Road, Chungju City, Chungbuk
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Contact: 043-848-3414
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p style=&#34;COLOR: #7b1f42&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Muhak Market
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Address: 15, Muhak 1-gil, Chungju-si, Chungbuk
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Contact: 043-848-2292
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p style=&#34;COLOR: #7b1f42&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Public market
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Address: 4-2, Chungin 8-gil, Chungju-si, Chungbuk
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Contact: 043-843-6138
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;topmr&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1.Access
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
     * Self-driving
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34; style=&#34;MARGIN-TOP: 0px&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Free Market:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Jungbu Inland Expressway Chungju IC → Jungwon-daero → Turn left at the 1st roundabout → Yeseong-ro → Free Market
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Muhak Market:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Jungbu Inland Expressway Chungju IC → Jungwon-daero → Turn left at Munhwa Intersection → Gukwon-daero → Turn right at Samwon Rotary → Tangeum-daero → Muhak Market
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Public market:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Jungbu Inland Expressway Chungju IC → Jungwon-daero → Public Market
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
     * public transport
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34; style=&#34;MARGIN-TOP: 0px&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     [train]
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Operated once a day from Seoul Station to Mugunghwa Lake to Chungju, takes 2 hours 33 minutes
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     [Bus]
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    From Central City Terminal to Chungju 35 times a day (06: 00-23: 00), takes 1 hour 50 minutes
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34; style=&#34;MARGIN-TOP: 0px&#34;&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34; style=&#34;MARGIN-TOP: 0px&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Restaurants around
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Unjeong Restaurant:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Allgang Haejangguk / 3432-1 Jungwon-daero, Chungju-si / 043-847-2820
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Boxer Haejangguk:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Haejangguk / 249-1 Seongnae-dong, Chungju-si / 043-842-0135
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Movie restaurant:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Sanchaejeongsik / 282-1 Oncheon-ri, Suanbo-myeon, Chungju-si / 043-846-2530, 043-846-4500
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Daejanggun Restaurant:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Traditional pheasant course dish / 105 Mireuksonggye-ro, Suanbo-myeon, Chungju-si / 043-846-1757, 043-846-6076
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Evergreen Restaurant:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Mushroom hotpot / 19, Jujeongsan-ro, Suanbo-myeon, Chungju-si / 043-846-0433
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;topmr&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     3.Accommodation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Chungju Grand Tourist Hotel:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    3496 Jungwon-daero, Chungju-si / 043-848-5554
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://cjgrand.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://cjgrand.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Film 37.2 Hotel:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    17 Yeonwon-ro, Chungju-si / 043-842-0515
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Hanwha Resort Suanbo:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    321-36 Suanbo-ro, Suanbo-myeon, Chungju-si / 043-846-8211
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.hanwharesort.co.kr/irsweb/resort3/resort/rs_room.asp?bp_cd=0600&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.hanwharesort.co.kr/irsweb/resort3/resort/rs_room.asp?bp_cd=0600
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Suanbo Xianglu Hotel:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    22, Jujeongsan-ro, Suanbo-myeon, Chungju-si / 043-845-3500
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.sangnokhotel.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.sangnokhotel.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;red&#34;&gt;
    ※ The above information was created in December 2013, and may change later, so be sure to check it before you travel.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chungju&#39;s delicious home, here it is ~ - Chungju, Chungbuk, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/chungjus-delicious-home-here-it-is-182/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 13:25:24 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/chungjus-delicious-home-here-it-is-182/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Chungju, Chungbuk, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;chungjus-delicious-home-here-it-is---182&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Freshly cooked rice - Chungju, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/182/0eb0e681-1845-4ad8-8aa9-4ceeb0d0fb41.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Freshly cooked rice
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Chungju&#39;s delicious home, here it is ~
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Chungju, Chungbuk, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Terms that describe good restaurants such as model restaurants, local restaurants, recommended restaurants, Daemulim restaurants, food restaurants, top restaurants, and TV broadcast restaurants vary by region. The expression I stumbled across the city of Chungju a while ago in Chungju was &#39;Good Rice House&#39;. Chungcheongbuk-do has been implemented since 2013. In Chungju City, a movie restaurant, Cheonnyeonhyang, Manna Rice House, and Sato Bonga were selected.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Sanchaejeongsik Indulge in its pure taste, Suanbo &#39;Movie Restaurant&#39;
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Even before the Maika boom in Korea, this restaurant was rumored to be delicious. Even now, he continues his reputation and has also been on the list of “Best Houses with Good Rice” selected by Chungcheongbuk-do Province.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Suanbo Movie Restaurant Exterior - Chungju, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/182/c9333d15-e1fe-4de0-958b-5180bacb5ad2.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Suanbo Movie Restaurant Exterior
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   When I visited the movie restaurant opened in 1980 and wondered about the process of cooking, I readily agree. As soon as the three-person family ordered a set meal, they put a stone pot on the gas fire and put the soaked rice. Pour water over it and add 3 more beans. This is a common sight. When the rice water starts to boil, the aunt in charge of cooking the rice takes a small amount of the rice and adjusts the amount. It is said to be the only method of movie restaurant. Rice is purchased from Suanbo Agricultural Cooperatives. Soybeans are used in the summer in a mixture of three types: hedge beans, frost tae, juwolyangdae, and peas. It takes about 15 minutes for delicious rice to be completed. Immediately after cooking, the miso soup is served on another gas fire. When it boils, rice is finished.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;3 beans in rice - Chungju, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/182/8a297f89-22ef-4bdb-9ddb-e189c3606f6a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     3 beans in rice
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   During this process, while the rice is being cooked, the side dish chef puts 30 herbs into a small dish. Each dish is labeled with herbs. Let&#39;s list the names of herbs you can taste at the movie restaurant. 쐬 dung (Wang-Wook-Wait), Shun-Wa-Hu, Shun-Bae-Hu-Jae, Castor, Goulgi, Bakgo-Ji, Darae-Soon, Eom-Ri, Shunnamul, Mountain Mulberry Leaf, Sesame Leaf, Seaweed Snack, Sari-Soon, Eom-Soon-Moon, Snack-Eat, Black Duck, Snake, Fern , Shiitake mushrooms, bento (simmer), etc. The herbs that rise on the guest statue depend on the season and the amount of herbs collected.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Soybean rice stimulates salivary glands - Chungju, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/182/7e020904-5e02-4eaf-8bba-17b8a139cdb2.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Soybean rice stimulates salivary glands
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The owner of the restaurant said, “We use herbs collected from Wolaksan or Sobaeksan. We endeavor to secure herbs from late March to early May. I take pride in the fact that I have never been. ”
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Guests who enjoy the mountain set meal in the movie restaurant - Chungju, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/182/afcaa42f-bacf-4405-8b49-b4c138354643.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Guests who enjoy the mountain set meal in the movie restaurant
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Regular customers often eat rice with various vegetables and rice in a large bowl after ordering a set meal (16,000 won). However, the way to eat really delicious is not to rub, but pick up each herb with chopsticks to feel the unique taste and aroma. If you want to eat it, it is said to eat rice, herbs, and sesame oil. Do not add red pepper paste or doenjang stew soup.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   Business hours from 8 am to 9 pm. Closed on New Year&#39;s Day and Chuseok.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The name of the herb is written on each bowl of herbs. - Chungju, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/182/b44126d5-d1d2-405e-b04a-f557ff69946b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The name of the herb is written on each bowl of herbs.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Medicinal constitutional rice is used to soothe Yeoksu, Yeonsu-dong &#39;Cheonnyanghyang&#39;
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &#39;Food and drug mobilization (食 藥 同 原)&#39;. Rice and medicine have the same roots, so if you meet good food on the road, you will feel tired. When you enter Cheonnyeonhyang, one of the ‘good-tasting homes’ in Chungju, the smell of medicinal herbs is soft. This restaurant is famous for its medicinal herb constitutional rice. It is run by Park Dong-soo, a holder of a health food prescription license. Above all, it is unique that customers can order and eat rice according to their constitution. Sitting in front of the sieve discriminator and recognizing the ten-finger print, it turns out that he is the owner of one of the constitutions: Taeinin, Taeumin, Soyangin, and Soumin.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Fingerprint recognition constitution discriminator at the entrance to Cheonnyeonhyang - Chungju, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/182/b6287f7d-cc30-420d-8f44-f8c74d721b2d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Fingerprint recognition constitution discriminator at the entrance to Cheonnyeonhyang
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Now customers can choose the type of food according to their constitution. In the dining room kitchen, cook rice cooked from a variety of grains and seeds. Rice water also uses herbal decoction water suitable for constitution. It is also fun to read the instructions on the back of the sieve while food is served.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Men&#39;s rice suitable for men - Chungju, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/182/0e7a6c45-ba0b-498c-a888-1695ab42f7d6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Men&#39;s rice suitable for men
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;font color=&#34;#367100&#34;&gt;
    -Good food for Taein people: rice, flour, barley, black sesame, glucose, Chinese cabbage, kale, cucumber, seaweed, shrimp, shellfish, crab, mugwort, persimmon, apricot, green tea, ogapi, shochu
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Good food for Taeeumin: Rice, brown rice, whole wheat flour, glutinous rice, chajo, sorghum, red beans, peanuts, yulmu, potato, bellflower, deodeok, lotus root, burdock, eggplant, pumpkin, seaweed, beef, watermelon, chestnut, walnut, pine nut , Bank, caring
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Good food for Soyangin: rice, mung bean, barley, black sesame, peanut, cabbage, spinach, radish, buttercup, radish, lotus root, burdock, pork, beef, egg, seafood, pear, persimmon, grape, strawberry, goji, beer
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Foods good for Soumin: Rice, brown rice, glutinous rice, sweet potato, Chinese cabbage, spinach, onion, ginger, garlic, red pepper, wild vegetables, seaweed, seaweed, chicken, apple, tangerine, orange, peach, jujube, ginseng, antler
   &lt;/font&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Women&#39;s rice suitable for women - Chungju, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/182/27a9e1b3-3f73-4e3d-92b0-e30cbd78bac0.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Women&#39;s rice suitable for women
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;strong&gt;
    If you order a meal for a thousand years, it is based on herbal idea constitutional rice.
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/strong&gt;
   In this restaurant, herbal medicine constitutional rice is called &#39;millennial rice cake&#39;. The Unam set meal (15,000 won) comes with medicinal rice porridge, 3 kinds of appetizers, Sasang constitutional rice with 17 dishes, seafood sundubu jjigae, and a herbal tea that fits the constitution. Poppy Daebotang comes up. Yakseonguibidaebotang is a food made from 16 kinds of herbs, boiled with shiitake, top, leek, leek, carrot, celery, ginseng, jujube, three roots, burdock, Angelica leaves, and beef.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Formal table top with herbal medicine soup - Chungju, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/182/89c44826-7f92-47de-9249-c1c1afd95b83.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Formal table top with herbal medicine soup
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In addition to the millennium class, there is also a medicine line yin and yang class. Different grains, seeds, and herbal decoctions are used to cook rice according to gender, such as Yin-in (female) and Yang-in (male). There are four types: Woosul Chosik (15,000 won), Yongdam Chosik (20,000 won), Sambaek Chosik (25,000 won), and Millennium Chosik (35,000 won).
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Hasuo black sesame skin - Chungju, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/182/db0828fb-d3c3-4849-9ad2-ce1e2166ad06.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Hasuo black sesame skin
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Even the herbal teas that come out as desserts are made differently according to gender. The man is provided with a lively train with Goji wolfberry, augusti, and hasoo, and a woman with Onbi aberration with baekchul, astragalus, dermis, and cinnamon. The sweet taste is preserved with licorice. I would have known about my constitution, which I didn&#39;t know so far. After eating a low-sodium diet made of fermentation enzymes and herbal powder, I even feel like I&#39;m taking a remedy.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   Business hours from 10 am to 10 pm. Closed on 2nd and 4th Sundays (September 1, 2015, except for the Lunar New Year and Chuseok holidays).
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;13&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sancho Salad - Chungju, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/182/544d6c3a-6fc1-4146-91b1-7b2ee41b7e56.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sancho Salad
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Morning breakfast with Hwangtae bean sprouts soup soup
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The restaurant&#39;s name is &#39;Manna Rice House&#39;, but many people are confused with &#39;Mana Rice House&#39;. The people of Chungju said that if they drank excessively the previous day or had no appetite, they would use a bowl of Haejangguk to loosen the bitter stomach and sweat. Restaurant owner Eun-sook Kim has been running Haejanggukjib for 23 years near the Chungju Courthouse and has moved on to its reputation five years ago.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Manna Rice House Entrance - Chungju, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/182/8d7b5745-19bd-4770-a7e5-3e2366e4a614.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Manna Rice House Entrance
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It&#39;s Haejanggukjip. In all cities, why was this restaurant selected as a “good rice house”? I&#39;m curious about how to cook the rice after eating the ingredients of Haejangguk. Once rice is grown in the Chungbuk region, it is supplied from the Agricultural Cooperatives in Chungju. Add a little bit of millet to make the rice taste better. And use a pressure cooker with 12 servings. If you use a larger rice cooker, it will be difficult to maintain the proper taste. That is the secret of delicious rice.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Information on the “Good Rice House” at the Manna Rice House - Chungju, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/182/d852cae0-0cc1-4b85-ac3a-8601ac3b2def.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Information on the “Good Rice House” at the Manna Rice House
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Haejangguk is cooked with yellow persimmon oil in perilla oil, and then cooks the broth for about 20 hours. Add boiled sprouts, eggs, and yellow beans to it, and add perilla powder. The soup is white and the taste is savory. Gangwon-do Hwangtae Haejangguk and Jeonju Bean Sprout Haejangguk are different flavors. Perilla oil and perilla powder met to create the flavor of Haejangguk, a unique restaurant. Seasoning with shrimp sauce and dipping green pepper in a side dish of kkakdugi makes it easier for the stomach to feel uncomfortable with a few drinks last night. You can also try barley rice and mungdu samgyetang (reserved 2 hours before summer).
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Hwangtae bean sprouts with soup - Chungju, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/182/3e3c521f-f9aa-438b-82af-f8cb8d635106.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Hwangtae bean sprouts with soup
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Business hours from 6:30 am to 9 pm. Closed on Sundays and New Year&#39;s Day and Chuseok.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;15&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Side dishes for customers ordering barley rice - Chungju, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/182/6b227634-c4b3-4242-a5b0-f8f2a51fb9a1.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Side dishes for customers ordering barley rice
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Bringing back the feeling of hometown with Cheonggukjang
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   From Sancheok-myeon Office, go to Jungwon Golf Course about 3km and you will find a restaurant called Sato Bonga. &#34;The three things are important to making rice well,&#34; said Park Hyup-gyu, CEO of the restaurant, which opened in 2003. The first good rice, the second rice time, the third steaming time. It uses rice produced in the Chungbuk region and cooks 20 servings of rice in a caster. When steaming, put a pot on top of the rice cooker lid to get the pressure cooker effect. The steaming time is about 30 minutes. Seasonal rice is mixed with chajo, millet, and black rice.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;16&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The appearance of Sato Bonga where Cheonggukjang is delicious - Chungju, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/182/28aefcb7-36e9-4b81-ae22-35f13adc9b01.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The appearance of Sato Bonga where Cheonggukjang is delicious
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   This carefully cooked rice meets the savory Cheonggukjang, which has little odor, and becomes a whole meal. Cheonggukjang floats two or three times a week, and the amount is about two horses (14kg) at a time. Soybeans are also farmed and used by local residents. Since no imported beans are used, one bowl of Cheonggukjang is 8,000 won, which is 1,000 to 2,000 won more expensive than the other. Boil tofu, radish, zucchini, old paper, green onion, cheonyang pepper, and onion in cheonggukjang. Neither anchovies nor pork. The taste of Cheonggukjang is still alive.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;17&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sato Bonga&#39;s Cheonggukjang - Chungju, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/182/319fea25-e32c-4400-a5df-e4150a53eeb7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sato Bonga&#39;s Cheonggukjang
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   As a dessert, Nurungji Sung-guk is served. I don&#39;t need any other dessert because I eat the salty paper that I made last fall as a side dish. In addition to the fresh cheonggukjang (4 pack 1kg 15,000 won), cheonggukjanghwan and cheonggukjang powder are also sold. We also prepared charcoal grilled meats for customers who like meat, and grilled yellow beans for customers who don&#39;t like Cheonggukjang.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;18&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Nurungji Soong-myeon - Chungju, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/182/f50c9baf-dfdf-4e28-a965-15e1dc79cefd.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Nurungji Soong-myeon
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Business hours from 9 am to 9 pm. No holidays (closed for a long period from early December to New Year&#39;s holidays).
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;19&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Cheonggukjang products sold in restaurants - Chungju, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/182/d385da9f-3a6f-4f9e-8c08-a1c5c698939d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Cheonggukjang products sold in restaurants
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Movie restaurant
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     : Sanchaejeongsik / 11, Multang 1-gil, Suanbo-myeon, Chungju-si, Chungbuk, Korea / 043-846-4500
     &lt;br/&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Millennium
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     : Herbal Sasang Constitutional Rice / 260 Beonyeong-daero, Chungju-si, Chungbuk / 043-844-1009
     &lt;br/&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Manna Rice House
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     : Hwangtae bean sprouts Haejangguk / 35 Dongsu 2-gil, Chungju-si, Chungbuk / 043-852-9590
     &lt;br/&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Sato Bonga
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     : Cheonggukjang / 229-8, Indeung-ro, Sancheok-myeon, Chungju-si, Chungcheongbuk-do / 043-854-7744
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://사또본가.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://사또본가.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Accommodation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Suanbo Royal Hotel: 26 Jangteo 1-gil, Suanbo-myeon, Chungju-si / 043-846-0190
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Gloria Motel: 12 Jangteo 2-gil, Suanbo-myeon, Chungju-si / 043-856-7008
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Film 37.2: 17 Yeonwon-ro, Chungju-si / 043-842-0515
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was created in July 2015, and may be changed later, so please check before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discover the mountain treasure chest! A small bookstore in the woods - Goesan-gun, Chungbuk, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/discover-the-mountain-treasure-chest-a-small-bookstore-in-the-woods-165/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 16:04:33 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/discover-the-mountain-treasure-chest-a-small-bookstore-in-the-woods-165/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Goesan-gun, Chungbuk, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;discover-the-mountain-treasure-chest-a-small-bookstore-in-the-woods--165&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;A small bookstore in the forest that nurtures people and their dreams together - Goesan-gun, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/165/1eaa2ab0-b28f-468a-9124-a1d98b908fb8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    A small bookstore in the forest that nurtures people and their dreams together
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Discover the mountain treasure chest! A small bookstore in the woods
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Goesan-gun, Chungbuk, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It is said that the season of reading is autumn. But think about it. There is no time to read a book other than futons. How about a break trip to prepare for a vibrant spring? So I prepared. It is a small bookstore hidden in the corner of a mountain, a small bookstore in the forest.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   A place where books are interesting, a small bookstore in the Miru Village Forest
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Miru Village located in Goesan Mountain Mountain, Chungbuk Province. In that small town, there is a small bookstore that Alice seems to be living in. If you are a bookworm, the place you want to visit once, even those who are not interested in books, are obsessed with the desire to read books. There are books that the owner made handmade papers with the contents of the books, and the old picture books turn into envelopes for books, a small bookstore in the woods.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Small bookstore in the forest - Goesan-gun, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/165/c4077f2d-45c7-4abd-98ee-0b126d2c7c28.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Small bookstore in the forest
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   This place, which is simply located in a family home, is also home to the wishes of a couple who operated a small children&#39;s library in Ilsan and Mapo. The first desire to build a library in a rural village and make it a place full of books and culture was paused for a number of difficulties, but instead brought their dreams into their homes without giving up.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Small library mailbox for those who take a break - Goesan-gun, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/165/08536b36-7033-49af-a661-3c67687cd1a8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Small library mailbox for those who take a break
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   This place is different from the entrance. When you push a small fence and step on one foot, your nose is creaky, so you can see the lush appearance of the book to the hut where a long Pinocchio greets, a hammock that you want to grab and grab a book in your hand, and a deck where you can taste the taste with your eyes. Also becomes a lucky person who has already found a treasure trove.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Inside the charming cabin on one side of the yard - Goesan-gun, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/165/9cef0871-00f1-4727-a953-e2821717af25.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Inside the charming cabin on one side of the yard
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The inside is also warm. From the moment you take off your shoes, the fairy tale books that are beautifully decorated seduce the concentricity that remains in one corner of your heart.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;It&#39;s perfect for falling into a book with a cup of hot tea. - Goesan-gun, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/165/baf78804-5acc-4ffa-bcdb-72b4bde71361.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     It&#39;s perfect for falling into a book with a cup of hot tea.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The central point of the bookstore is the living room. Books that seem to be indifferent in the warm sunshine are gathered together in accordance with their own order.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Section that sets a theme every two months and displays a book suitable for it - Goesan-gun, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/165/4ed16847-d649-4bea-af9d-cef8647fd7a4.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Section that sets a theme every two months and displays a book suitable for it
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Instead of being stuck with the back of the book, the signs made with great care make eye contact with visitors. The most powerful weapon that interests a book is the theory that it is a book cover.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;13&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A belt containing the contents of a book written by the owner. - Goesan-gun, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/165/08ec6d3b-9a6b-43a1-a2e9-51c6f7459ba1.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A belt containing the contents of a book written by the owner.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   A space to find dreams about books by making them want to come and read. That is the bookstore that the couple dreams of.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;15&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;As it is a small bookstore, it is a new display stand that is carefully selected and selected. - Goesan-gun, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/165/78adc17e-f934-4a73-8f28-237dc8b7a056.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     As it is a small bookstore, it is a new display stand that is carefully selected and selected.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   We hope to share a warm cup of tea with our guests, talk about the book, and sit in the most comfortable place of their choice and fall in love with the book for a long time.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;17&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Each accessory placed as if it were indifferent has a unique taste. - Goesan-gun, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/165/9f26a359-0ebd-4eeb-9369-0a8b58f96ea6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Each accessory placed as if it were indifferent has a unique taste.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   The fairy tale hidden behind the secret door and book stay
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   A small bookstore in the woods is a lovely day for just a visit, but there is a way to feel 120%. Attic, a hidden dream space in a small bookstore in the woods. On the second floor, there is an unexpected pleasure that you can&#39;t think of overnight.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   When the darkness falls and the bookstore&#39;s door closes, this place is completely my home. He stays on the second floor of the house where the owner stays and uses the bathroom and toilet together with the owner. As the sound of turning a book in silence keeps turning one, two, and more, the books I have read are piled up. The story that follows the consensus of a book with a drink or refreshment is more interesting and fresh than a book.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A loft in the woods that is simple yet cozy and wants to stay long - Goesan-gun, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/165/1a52ca18-3c75-4ccd-ad5e-95c5ae32d298.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A loft in the woods that is simple yet cozy and wants to stay long
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   This is not the only preference allowed in one night in the attic. If you open a bookshelf that is likely to come out of the Hogwarts School of Magic, open the hidden treasure chest. In the name of Alice&#39;s Attic. This is the name given to the idea that “Alice in Wonderland” is a strange place, like a strange country that I fell into a rabbit hole. In this room, more than 500 pop-up books, art books, and character dolls collected from all over the world are waiting for their hands to spend the night together.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The cozy look of a bookstore on the first floor overlooking the attic - Goesan-gun, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/165/8f706ad5-256a-4040-a085-d414d33a4fc9.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The cozy look of a bookstore on the first floor overlooking the attic
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It is a convenient world where books are delivered from home to home with just one click. But where can you compare the romance of a bookstore, shoulder-to-shoulder, and pick a book yourself, and sometimes sit down and fall in love with a book! A winter trip to a small bookstore in a forest full of culture, and a happy consumption in a book will make your winter warmer.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;You can meet rare pop-up books, art books and character dolls - Goesan-gun, Chungbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/165/bc45e86c-9dc1-4375-854d-68fe5a5c18d2.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     You can meet rare pop-up books, art books and character dolls
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Small bookstore in the forest
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Address: 90, Myeongtaejae-ro Miril-gil, Chilseong-myeon, Goesan-gun, Chungcheongbuk-do
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Inquiries: 043-834-7626
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://blog.naver.com/supsokiz&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://blog.naver.com/supsokiz
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Restaurants near
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Mat restaurant: 12 Goegang-ro, Goesan-eup, Goesan-gun, Chungcheongbuk-do / Olgangi-guk / 043-833-1580
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Parking restaurant: 282, Eupnae-ro, Goesan-eup, Goesan-gun, Chungcheongbuk-do / All-Gang-Guk / 043-832-2673
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Sancheon Restaurant: 162 Imkeokjeong-ro, Goesan-eup, Goesan-gun, Chungcheongbuk-do / Eoritang, Eolsulnungtang (Eotang) / 043-834-6474
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Rooms
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Hotel West of Canaan: 175-1 Suokjeong-gil, Yeonpung-myeon, Goesan-gun, Chungcheongbuk-do / 043-833-8814
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.westofcanaan.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.westofcanaan.com/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Hanhwa Resort Suanbo: 321-36 Suanbo-ro, Suanbo-myeon, Chungju-si, Chungcheongbuk-do / 043-846-8211
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was updated in February 2019, and may be changed later, so please check before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Autumn trip to Cheongju, from &#39;silk&#39; meat street market to &#39;Unbo&#39;s house&#39; and &#39;romantic&#39; Cheongnamdae - Cheongju, Chungbuk, South Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/autumn-trip-to-cheongju-from-silk-meat-street-market-to-unbos-house-and-romantic-cheongnamdae-113/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 09:54:38 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/autumn-trip-to-cheongju-from-silk-meat-street-market-to-unbos-house-and-romantic-cheongnamdae-113/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Cheongju, Chungbuk, South Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;autumn-trip-to-cheongju-from-silk-meat-street-market-to-unbos-house-and-romantic-cheongnamdae--113&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;The main entrance to the stylish meat market - Cheongju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/113/bad3f219-ec9a-4a74-9965-ab0a197e3380.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    The main entrance to the stylish meat market
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Autumn trip to Cheongju, from &#39;silk&#39; meat street market to &#39;Unbo&#39;s house&#39; and &#39;romantic&#39; Cheongnamdae
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Cheongju, Chungbuk, South Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Cheongju&#39;s autumn is more vibrant than ever. For the 2016 Fall Travel Week (October 24-November 6), various side events are being held in conjunction with the Korea Sale Festa at the General Street Market and major tourist attractions. If you set the schedule well, you can get cash gift vouchers. Cheongnam University Chrysanthemum Festival is in progress at this time. That&#39;s why we should leave for Cheongju right now.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   The best meat market in Cheongju market
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The six-way street market is a permanent market located in Sang-gu, Cheongju-si, which is the largest of the dozen Cheongju markets. In the past, the place was opened because of the name of the street, but now it is reduced to a range. Nevertheless, the front of the market gate with its huge tile roof is crowded like a street. Many people want to buy cheap goods. Don&#39;t panic if the front door is crowded. There are three public parking lots inside the market, so you only have to choose where to go.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The first thing you&#39;ll notice is the miniature trotters sold by the front door. Not long ago, it was introduced in TV shows and became popular. Unlike ordinary pork feet that have a lot of lumps, you can feel the chewing taste properly. A small alley behind the mini jogbal restaurant is the food alley at the meat street market. Tteok, Jeon, porridge, dumplings, and whole chicken are the main menus, and rumors of Sundae&#39;s popularity are overwhelming. Seemingly not so different from ordinary sundae, the taste becomes more curious.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Weekday afternoon, inside the market where guests are missing - Cheongju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/113/522518e0-3342-4024-8221-de38aca18148.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Weekday afternoon, inside the market where guests are missing
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Meat Street Market and Seongan-gil Shopping Street have opened the cooking process of Jjajangmyeon, fish gas and rice cake since last September, and share food with them. Bonus scales &#39;, &#39;80% sale event&#39; that sells up to 80% of seafood, agricultural products, and livestock products by date, &#39;Merchant experience&#39; to make cotton candy, and &#39;Movie Day&#39; to watch movies and animations in multi support center. The event has been going on.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Various foods sold at the food alley - Cheongju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/113/f485f276-df8d-40a1-9754-9c0411ebadac.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Various foods sold at the food alley
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Currently most of the events have ended, but some will last until this weekend (October 30). A concert featuring Hong Jin-young and Hwang In-sun will be held at the 2nd parking lot from 2 pm on the 27th, and the family cultural heritage tour will begin at 1 pm and 4 pm on the 29th and 30th. &#39;Travel of Family Culture Ruins&#39; is accompanied by a professional cultural commentator and tours Cheongju-eupseong, Jungang Park and Namseok Bridge.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Various foods sold at the food alley - Cheongju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/113/3ebd0f41-570b-4959-867d-97bf0400f810.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Various foods sold at the food alley
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The most popular money bag will be held on both the 29th and 30th of the last day. If you purchase more than 20,000 won at two stores and submit the receipt to the event headquarters on that day, you will receive a certain amount of Onnuri gift certificate (5,000 won) depending on the amount used.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Various foods sold at the food alley - Cheongju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/113/3e16a99b-a07a-4001-8a9f-a23cbece2192.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Various foods sold at the food alley
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you&#39;ve played well, worry about parking. Luckily, you can enjoy up to 30 days of free parking for up to 30 days if you show your receipts at three public markets in Seongan-gil and Seongan-gil shopping streets.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Various foods sold at the food alley - Cheongju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/113/e5269ed7-add4-4e9b-af93-09a34fc6bf62.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Various foods sold at the food alley
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Find hidden pictures in a fun way ~, Suamgol Mural Village
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Suamgol, which is not far from the meat market, has the nickname &#39;Cheongju&#39;s last moon.&#39; Several houses barely stood on the mountain slopes, and even the refugees settled here after the Korean War. The village, which was almost a gimmick, faced a completely different fate since 2008, when various murals were created as part of a public art project.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Suamgol Mural Village Scenery - Cheongju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/113/8aab419c-d846-4586-ad58-b1a609042490.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Suamgol Mural Village Scenery
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The stories in the murals are the lives of the elderly, as the artists completed their works by directly communicating with the local people. This is why pine trees and cranes that pray for disease-free life appear, as well as laundry scenes and briquette rear cars.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Briquettes buried in the ground - Cheongju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/113/8be48f0f-2708-4715-b62d-f91f7e90957c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Briquettes buried in the ground
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The unusual thing is that the mural doesn&#39;t just stay on the wall. The briquettes that played their part completely face each other. They have speech bubbles such as &#39;I love you when they are broken and broken!&#39;, &#39;I love you just as you are&#39; and &#39;Okay, spring is coming soon&#39;.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;There is a lot of briquette art in Suamgol - Cheongju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/113/19e16e58-bd5f-4278-b77a-03df5521db1a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     There is a lot of briquette art in Suamgol
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   There are also some pictures of amateur feeling. On the tiles that decorate the walls of someone&#39;s house, each person&#39;s face is drawn with a comment, &#34;anything coming back&#34;, &#34;anything ♡&#34;.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;There is a lot of briquette art in Suamgol - Cheongju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/113/efd76617-c288-405d-bbe8-a58006996ca4.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     There is a lot of briquette art in Suamgol
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Anyone can decorate their personality by participating in the shared wall painting experience held on October 30 and November 6 during the autumn travel week.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A diary on a wall - Cheongju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/113/60dedb94-8715-4086-b421-80947301b322.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A diary on a wall
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Another name of Suamgol is &#39;Kim Tak-gu Village&#39;. This is the actual location for the national drama `` Kim Tak-gu, &#39;&#39; which has the highest viewing rate of 49.3%.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;13&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Palbong Bakery, a symbol of Suamgol - Cheongju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/113/8f28d0fd-f757-4f33-994b-773bc0c74dda.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Palbong Bakery, a symbol of Suamgol
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Palbong bakery sells a variety of cafe menus, including the ones in the drama.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;15&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A loaf of bread - Cheongju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/113/dcb0cd59-8ede-4880-a811-9dd9318f9107.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A loaf of bread
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   After watching the drama script, the sign and poster of the cast on the first floor, enjoy the drinks and bread on the second floor.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;17&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#39;Baking King Kim Tak-gu&#39; Script - Cheongju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/113/d4c0a100-9c47-4e4b-b63d-6be592b69d1e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     &#39;Baking King Kim Tak-gu&#39; Script
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Unbo Kim Ki-chang
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In Hungdong-ri, Naesu-eup, Cheongwon-gu, Cheongju, there is Unbo Kim&#39;s house, the sister and artist of Kim Ki-chang. In 1976, after his wife and painter Park Rae-hyang passed away, Kim Ki-chang built his home in his mother&#39;s hometown and spent the rest of his life working there. Due to the rainy weather, the clouds and misty landscapes of the mountains were quite strangely matched with his hounbo. Engraved on the pillar of the entrance, &#39;I did not think it was unfortunate that I could not hear. . (Omitted) I think it was fortunate that I was able to concentrate on my art in quiet… Rainwater flowed vigorously over the writing.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;View of Unbo&#39;s house - Cheongju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/113/ebd2b27f-c3c3-44fb-ab08-9a01b5c45d12.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     View of Unbo&#39;s house
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   There was no one in Unbo&#39;s house except the caretaker. Thanks to this, the space of 50,000 pyeong ranging from Anchae, Art Museum, Sculpture Park, Bonsai Park, and Senior Park seemed to be my home. It was huge but it was cozy because everything was in place. A lot of small courtyard roses bloomed in Sarangchae, and the bonsai and the chiefs who expressed his taste around the well-organized inner house revealed their presence here and there. The texture of the old hanok was elegant and elegant. Sitting on Daecheong floor and watching the rainy garden was so precious that I didn&#39;t want to change anything. Artistic souls of artists who painted masterpieces such as Fool&#39;s Water, King Sejong&#39;s portrait of 10,000 won bills, Blue Green Water, and Gunmado were everywhere.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;15&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sitting at Daecheong and looking at the rain landscape - Cheongju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/113/83c045d7-52b7-4efc-8d19-fc74c7892e54.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sitting at Daecheong and looking at the rain landscape
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   After seeing the museum, the rain stopped and the sun started to glow. The cost of painting is as beautiful as painting wherever you can see it. Delicates that will never get tired even after dozens of times have attracted people. In particular, elephants, lady statues, Baekkyung, and meditation stones are among the nation&#39;s top ten gemstones.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;16&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;I preserved Unbo&#39;s studio - Cheongju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/113/181eda20-5d57-455c-9eeb-d703480e21e2.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     I preserved Unbo&#39;s studio
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Cheongnam University Chrysanthemum Festival
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   I can&#39;t come back to Cheongju without seeing Cheongnamdae. It is already famous for the presidential villas, but at the time of the chrysanthemum festival, you will be able to enjoy the visually near perfection. This year&#39;s chrysanthemum festival begins on October 22 and runs until November 13.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;17&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Cheongnam University Entrance with Falling Leaves - Cheongju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/113/b4e57518-fbce-4520-a1c5-84a8b06fca98.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Cheongnam University Entrance with Falling Leaves
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   At this time of year, Cheongnamdae is filled with colorful leaves and the waves of Daecheong Lake.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;18&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Chrysanthemum Festival full of flowers - Cheongju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/113/841f0443-60b9-44a0-be89-75778f1c59b3.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Chrysanthemum Festival full of flowers
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you follow the direction of viewing with the smell of soil, grass, and water at the same time, you will naturally enter the chrysanthemum festival. You pick up the camera.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;19&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Beautiful chrysanthemum - Cheongju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/113/f48aa186-c979-4325-9585-27df3b20a157.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Beautiful chrysanthemum
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   On one side of the courtyard, there is an experience booth that supports tasting chrysanthemum tea, calligraphy of fallen leaves, and bonsai powdering.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;20&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Beautiful chrysanthemum - Cheongju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/113/8c1774a8-4a6a-41d7-a2f1-0cdab7bac025.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Beautiful chrysanthemum
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If time permits, I recommend you pick one of the six trails named after the president. It takes as long as 1 hour and 30 minutes and as little as 20 minutes, but each has their own unique features.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;21&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The fish farm in front of the Presidential Memorial was used as a skating rink. - Cheongju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/113/dac062ae-e441-4f6d-9150-5cb27f5acf96.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The fish farm in front of the Presidential Memorial was used as a skating rink.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It&#39;s important to note that you can&#39;t use your car to look around. Private cars cannot be driven without prior approval. Since 500 cars are booked a day, people who want to use their car must park before paying a fee.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;13&#34; id3=&#34;22&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Daecheongho from the front of Ohgakjeong - Cheongju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/113/42bc99d4-ef98-4026-adb9-59052b24cfe8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Daecheongho from the front of Ohgakjeong
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   You can also take a city bus from the bottom of the mountain.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;15&#34; id3=&#34;23&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Metasequoia Road in Cheongnam University - Cheongju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/113/e143a083-7547-490c-9eff-bc40a5325937.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Metasequoia Road in Cheongnam University
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel info
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Cheongju Meat Street Market
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Address: 46, Cheongnam-ro 2197beon-gil, Daesang-gu, Cheongju-si, Chungcheongbuk-do
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Hours: 09:00 ~ 22:00 (varies by store)
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Inquiries: 043-223-6696
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Suamgol Mural Village
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Address: 58, Suam-ro, Daesang-gu, Cheongju-si, Chungcheongbuk-do
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Hours: Always (except residential area since 21:00 since it is residential area)
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Inquiries: 043-201-2043
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Cheongnam University
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Address: 646, Cheongnamdae-gil, Munji-myeon, Cheongju-si, Chungcheongbuk-do
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Opening hours: Summer season (February to November) 09: 00 ~ 18: 00 / Winter season (December to January) 09: 00 ~ 17: 00
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Closed every Monday, January 1, Lunar New Year, Chuseok
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Inquiries: 043-257-5080
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://chnam.chungbuk.go.kr&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;청남대 사이트로 이동&#34;&gt;
     http://chnam.chungbuk.go.kr
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Restaurants near
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Cheongsong Whole Chicken: Samgyetang, Whole Chicken / 116 Namsa-ro, Sangsang-gu, Cheongju-si, Chungcheongbuk-do
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Hwanghalma Galbi stew: steamed ribs, galbi stew / 30, Namsa-ro 140beon-gil, Daegu-gu, Cheongju-si, Chungcheongbuk-do / 043-222-9292
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Rooms
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Cheongju Gallery Tourist Hotel: 607 Jikji-daero, Heungdeok-gu, Cheongju-si, Chungcheongbuk-do / 043-267-1121
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://newgalleryhotel.com/kr/index/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://newgalleryhotel.com/kr/index/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Reho Tourist Hotel: 1175 Garosu-ro, Heungdeok-gu, Cheongju-si, Chungcheongbuk-do / 043-233-8800
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.hotelreeho.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.hotelreeho.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Article, photo
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0033&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was written in October 2016. It may change afterwards, so please check before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ The information such as text, photos and videos used in this article is copyrighted by Korea Tourism Organization, so unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Youngdong Shenzhen-ri Village, the hometown of the heart when we miss the countryside - Yeongdong-gun, Chungbuk, South Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/youngdong-shenzhenri-village-the-hometown-of-the-heart-when-we-miss-the-countryside-109/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 21:39:08 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/youngdong-shenzhenri-village-the-hometown-of-the-heart-when-we-miss-the-countryside-109/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Yeongdong-gun, Chungbuk, South Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;youngdong-shenzhenri-village-the-hometown-of-the-heart-when-we-miss-the-countryside--109&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Small station with impressive green roof, Shenzhen Station - Yeongdong-gun, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/109/4bb94e05-0298-4031-8f3f-6a1bc8f06be1.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Small station with impressive green roof, Shenzhen Station
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Youngdong Shenzhen-ri Village, the hometown of the heart when we miss the countryside
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Yeongdong-gun, Chungbuk, South Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &#34;I want to go back!&#34; There are times when anyone wants to go somewhere, like the lines in a movie. At any point in the past, or anywhere in the past, there are times when you will be reminded of your memories. Especially when a big holiday is over. When the word family and home come to mind, busy hands are slowly turning upside down.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   A simple station where memories live and the town scenery spread out like a black and white photo
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   But going back in time is not easy. As time goes by, the appearance of hometown is changing. In the meantime, there are some places that retain their former appearances as if they were passing away. If you want to go back to a moment in the past, take a slow train to Shenzhen station in Yeongdong, Chungbuk.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Shenzhen Station is a small convenience station. The station was opened as a regular station in 1905. The station has been newly built and moved to Gyeongbu Line double track construction in 1934. The history of the 1930s was preserved in the original form of the gable roof and was designated as Registered Cultural Property No. 297 in 2006. When you get off at the small station, you can see the green roof and the words &#39;the station where the old memories stay&#39;. There are not many people getting on the train and getting off. The scent of dull feelings abounds in history and railroad tracks. The waiting room is small too.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34; - Yeongdong-gun, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/109/ac2b7eab-b159-43c7-b78f-fdec4bcdaebd.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &#34;Once there were a lot of passengers and bustling times. The market was activated and many people gathered, but now it&#39;s a very quiet station.&#34; The station worker looks at the empty waiting room and explains the old look of Shenzhen Station.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Simple Shenzhen Station Waiting Room - Yeongdong-gun, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/109/46b058b3-e3ec-4db2-acad-71d1238aff3c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Simple Shenzhen Station Waiting Room
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Exiting the waiting room leads to the station square. The square is quite wide compared to the small train station. It is not only the station that Shenzhen has gone through.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Old drugstore centered on the station square - Yeongdong-gun, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/109/f509be1e-53d0-4558-9810-a992ecbb7b3c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Old drugstore centered on the station square
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Right in front of the train station is an old pharmacy called Supergang Pharmacy, and at the entrance to the plaza there are two stores that have annual rings instead of common convenience stores. It&#39;s like a movie set set in the 1970s.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Old commercial center centered on the station square - Yeongdong-gun, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/109/f937ad31-bd8c-4268-abda-87bb6b89b390.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Old commercial center centered on the station square
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The view inside the drugstore is also nice. Bacchus boxes are lined up. Even if there is no sore place, I want to make a ping pong and cross the threshold once.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;13&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A video store that brings memories - Yeongdong-gun, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/109/2e65dcf8-a0a8-452b-abc7-67b2915f5932.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A video store that brings memories
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In front of &#39;Brother&#39;s Club&#39; and &#39;Reverse Chamber of Commerce&#39; there are beautiful trees. Underneath, a few of my grandmothers are chatting together. It is the scenery of a rural village that I remembered when I was young. Miraculous. Is time passing by here at a different speed?
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;15&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Membrane Mill - Yeongdong-gun, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/109/66a63ec6-2b29-4006-889a-ba962e062ed4.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Membrane Mill
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   There are shops and houses along the two-lane road along the Brotherhood. There is a cotton office, a restaurant, a pesticide shop and a mill. The neighborhood where Shenzhen Station is located is Shenzhen-li, Shenzhen-myeon, Yeongdong-gun, Chungbuk. It was hard to imagine the bustle of the past without the guidance of a station worker in Shenzhen, who once said that it was a busy and noisy neighborhood. The neighborhood was quiet.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;17&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;An iron gate is also a medium for memories - Yeongdong-gun, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/109/7dc6db46-69ea-4e7c-9211-a03066869ce3.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     An iron gate is also a medium for memories
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &#34;Oh, is this store closed today? You have to open the doors on Saturdays to help the farmers with their farming.&#34; This conversation is coming and going. The voices of the uncles on the road can be heard across the street. When someone passes by, they pretend to know and talk with each other.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;19&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;An iron gate is also a medium for memories - Yeongdong-gun, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/109/c572106a-0de1-4969-ac97-c918b512d981.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     An iron gate is also a medium for memories
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Take a picture of a rusty fence in front of a farm machinery store. A faded video store signage is also pictured. Lack of scenery seems to be warming somewhere. &#34;What do you use to write it?&#34; The uncle who passes by throws a horse. I&#39;m glanced at doing something really useless. Yeah. The scenes were common 20-20 years ago, but now it&#39;s amazing that I&#39;m trying to capture every single camera.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;21&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The friendly scenery you encounter as you walk slowly through the town - Yeongdong-gun, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/109/89d2a77e-3f16-4fce-9fde-4e1879eb4c28.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The friendly scenery you encounter as you walk slowly through the town
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Sometimes the bus, sometimes a car, and the words &#39;slowly&#39; written on a quiet road are noticeable. Yes, sometimes it&#39;s good to go slowly in either side of the world.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;23&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The word &#39;slowly&#39; written on the road sticks to my heart - Yeongdong-gun, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/109/902f2a54-0314-4425-9ee8-e25d655e0b94.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The word &#39;slowly&#39; written on the road sticks to my heart
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Add beautiful sound to your memories trip, Yeongdong Gugak Village
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It doesn&#39;t take long to get around the neighborhood around Shenzhen Station. If you want to spend more time here, take a bike hire from Shenzhen station. It is also known as &#39;blue bike&#39;. Passengers traveling to Shenzhen on a train can travel for free. You can ride a bicycle along the nearby river or explore the nearby attractions.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;If you visit Shenzhen by train, you can use the bicycle for free. - Yeongdong-gun, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/109/e0ad1ba2-5fdd-43e7-a3ea-a477008c90db.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     If you visit Shenzhen by train, you can use the bicycle for free.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   One course (8.1km) to Okgye Falls, two courses (9.4km) to Iwon Bridge, and three courses (5.8km) to Yeongdong Gugak Village.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Yeongdong Shenzhen-myeon, North Chungcheong Province is famous for the hometown of Nanji Park. - Yeongdong-gun, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/109/89cd285d-5f87-4dd3-a0ee-320039b5c149.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Yeongdong Shenzhen-myeon, North Chungcheong Province is famous for the hometown of Nanji Park.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Now that we came to Shenzhen-myeon, Yeong-dong, Chungbuk, which is the hometown of the Nangye Park Yeon, one of the three malice in Korea, let&#39;s head to the Yeongdong Gugak Village. Yeongdong Gugak Village has Cheongogak along with facilities such as performance halls and experience rooms. The Cheongogak is the largest drum in the world, and is the space where the Cheongo is registered. The ceiling is 7 tons in weight, with a diameter of 5.54m, a diameter of 6.4m and a width of 5.96m.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Yeongdong Gugak Village, a free performance of Korean traditional music every Saturday - Yeongdong-gun, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/109/4dc67167-7d6a-4694-911f-b7216b1fb780.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Yeongdong Gugak Village, a free performance of Korean traditional music every Saturday
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you want to make full use of Yeongdong Gugak Village, visit on Saturday. This is because the permanent performance of Nanji Gugak Orchestra is held every Saturday. You can enjoy a variety of genres, from authentic Korean traditional music to fusion. During the performance, a description of Korean musical instruments may be given. There is also a space where you can touch the lyre, gayageum, and janggu at the entrance. After listening to the Korean traditional music performances, we will deal with musical instruments. The Korean traditional music, which felt difficult and far away, is approaching intimately.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;You can play lyre, gayageum, and janggu yourself. - Yeongdong-gun, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/109/1c3991db-a8b7-409c-9a52-93190010875e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     You can play lyre, gayageum, and janggu yourself.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Near the Yeongdong Gugak Village, Nangye Gugak Museum, where materials about Korean traditional music and egg-based yeon are displayed, Nangye Family House, which is the place where Nangye Park Yeon was born. have. The journey started at Shenzhen Station, where &#39;old memories stay&#39;, leads to the Youngdong Gugak Village where &#39;old sounds stay&#39; on a blue bicycle. Nostalgic sound is added to the nostalgic memories. Stimulates travel sensibility in autumn.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;15&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Let&#39;s visit Nangye Gugak Museum with Yeongdong Gugak Village - Yeongdong-gun, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/109/963060dd-1afe-4de9-b1b9-d0ab1808fe7c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Let&#39;s visit Nangye Gugak Museum with Yeongdong Gugak Village
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel info
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Shenzhen Station
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Address: 5-1 Shenzhen-ro 5-gil, Shenzhen-myeon, Yeongdong-gun, Chungcheongbuk-do
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Contact: 1544-7788
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Yeongdong Gugak Experience Center
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Address: 33, Gugak-ro 1-gil, Shenzhen-myeon, Yeongdong-gun, Chungcheongbuk-do
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Inquiries: 043-740-3891
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://gugak.yd21.go.kr/home/main.php&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://gugak.yd21.go.kr/home/main.php
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Restaurants near
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Elephant Dumpling: Snack / 35, Jungang-ro, Yeongdong-eup / 043-743-4165
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Songcheon Garden: Trout Sashimi, Freshwater Maetang / 793, Nam-ro, Yongsan-myeon / 043-742-8300
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Rooms
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Beomyeong-ru: 57, Mulhan 4-gil, Sangchon-myeon / 043-745-2628
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://blog.naver.com/bumyoungru&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://blog.naver.com/bumyoungru
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Standal Motel: 24, Gyesan-ro 1-gil, Yeongdong-eup / 043-744-7228
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Dubai Motel: 7-1, Gyesan-ro 6-gil, Yeongdong-eup / 043-744-2235
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0033&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was updated in January 2019 and may change afterwards. Please check before traveling.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ The information such as text, photos and videos used in this article is copyrighted by Korea Tourism Organization, so unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harmony of the red fish cake and sweet glutinous rice cake - Jecheon, Chungbuk, South Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/harmony-of-the-red-fish-cake-and-sweet-glutinous-rice-cake-108/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 21:39:07 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/harmony-of-the-red-fish-cake-and-sweet-glutinous-rice-cake-108/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Jecheon, Chungbuk, South Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;harmony-of-the-red-fish-cake-and-sweet-glutinous-rice-cake--108&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Jecheon&#39;s specialty “red fish cake” - Jecheon, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/108/eb4d9af4-660d-4191-b2af-ca32f43111e2.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Jecheon&#39;s specialty “red fish cake”
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Harmony of the red fish cake and sweet glutinous rice cake
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Jecheon, Chungbuk, South Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Fish paste is one of the popular street foods when the weather gets colder. A glass of broth and a glass of broth will withstand the cold energy. Fish cake is Busan, but &#39;red fish cake&#39; makes Jecheon come to mind. Eat a few skewers of spicy and warm red fish cakes and taste glutinous rice cakes made with decades of care. In addition, you can enjoy healthy and delicious delicacies in Jecheon, including yokan made from herbs, steamed buns, and donuts.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   The taste goes hand in hand, red fish cake
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you go to downtown Jecheon, you will see many shops named `` red oden. &#39;&#39; Red fish paste is a food seasoned with red fish paste. Although there is no accurate record of how and when red fish cake began in Jecheon, it has been popular as a snack of Jecheon for decades.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;In Jecheon, there are many snack shops named `` red oden &#39;&#39;. - Jecheon, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/108/8d19df0e-a5c4-4d89-af6e-9393c83e9337.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     In Jecheon, there are many snack shops named `` red oden &#39;&#39;.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Fish paste is usually one kind in other local snack houses, but it is divided into red fish paste and bite fish paste in Jecheon. The fish paste is the fish paste we usually eat in soup, and the red fish cake is accompanied by spicy chili sauce. There are two kinds of bitter breadth and round one, but red fish cake usually uses only wide bread.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;In Jecheon, there are many snack shops named `` red oden &#39;&#39;. - Jecheon, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/108/26a35503-6fa5-4046-85e5-3ee425b5d66d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     In Jecheon, there are many snack shops named `` red oden &#39;&#39;.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Fold the fish cakes in a twisted shape, put them in wooden chopsticks, and put them in the broth. And the red sauce transfers it to a sizzling wide plate. At this time, align the fish cakes to the sides. Top it with seasoning and sprinkle with chopped green onions.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Warm bite - Jecheon, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/108/4bbca3d4-9a98-4743-a6f2-e12fa42dad97.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Warm bite
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In some stores, long rice cakes are placed in chopsticks and seasoned like red fish cakes.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Spicy red fish cake - Jecheon, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/108/68f4e1ca-fc53-401b-8286-c8200444941f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Spicy red fish cake
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The recipes and appearances do not vary greatly from shop to shop. There are only slightly different sauce tips for each shop. Some are spicy and some are less spicy. You can choose according to your taste. Generally, they are served with tempura and gimbap, and some places offer other foods. Red fish paste is strangely addictive. If you eat one, you will eat two or three. The price is good so you can eat more than one. It is 1,000 won for 4 red fish cakes.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;How to make it is the same - Jecheon, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/108/28a55e78-51eb-4c70-95b6-b6b69d0026c2.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     How to make it is the same
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The red fish cake, which was loved by Jecheon locals, became widely known to foreigners through the Jecheon International Music Film Festival. So now more people are coming to Jecheon to eat red fish cake.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   There are many red fish shops around Jecheon Central Market, Nato Traditional Market, and Dongmun Market. The Jecheon Red Oden near the Central Market is one of the oldest, and the Red Oden House at the entrance to the Nato Traditional Market and the Oatgad House in the Nato Traditional Market are popular among locals. Note that some shops are closed on the first and third Sundays of each month.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;14&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;How to make it is the same - Jecheon, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/108/c991b024-c6f8-44a4-8520-52e6ea3755a1.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     How to make it is the same
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Take a bite, Dengsil Dunk ~, &#39;Dunksil&#39; glutinous rice cake and donuts
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   A must-try snack in Jecheon with red fish paste is glutinous rice cake of &#39;dunkilssik&#39;. I&#39;m so excited about the name of the store. The name &#34;Dengshil&#34; means &#34;to everyone in the world,&#34; and &#34;to taste deliciously.&#34; In front of the shop, there is a small signboard with a friendly greeting. The signs that change every day bring little fun. The rustic store facade reflects decades of history. Following his mother-in-law, daughter-in-law has been handed down for the second generation. So many old regular customers. If you want to taste glutinous rice cakes and donuts on the weekend, hurry up a little. It&#39;s because it&#39;s so popular that it&#39;s too early to be a full version. Remember that Sunday is closed.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;‘Dunsil&#39;s meal’ shows signs of time - Jecheon, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/108/03f8e8a4-6d0d-4934-a943-f2b58afa5fff.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     ‘Dunsil&#39;s meal’ shows signs of time
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Dengsil Bun makes both glutinous rice cakes and donuts by hand. It&#39;s fun to see how red bean paste is put into chewy glutinous rice dough to make crunchy rice cake. Seeing glutinous rice cakes filled on a large tray makes mouthwatering. Even in chilly weather, a fan runs to cool the glutinous rice cake on one side. When the hot seaweed of glutinous rice cake falls out, put it in a box.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Glutinous rice cake made by hand - Jecheon, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/108/b1c65883-6cc0-4f23-8ffe-0c0161fa0c7e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Glutinous rice cake made by hand
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   One large glutinous rice cake is just 700 won. Glutinous rice cake made with domestic glutinous rice and domestic red beans is very affordable. Try a bite of glutinous rice cake. Rather than a board draws, chewy chewy lives. Red bean is filled in immaculate glutinous rice cake. Bean jam is not sweet. The color and taste are very different from those of ordinary glutinous rice cake. This is because not only red-red beans in dunsil&#39;s meal, but also dark green gray beans are used to make red bean paste. Boil red beans usually twice a day.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Glutinous rice cake made by hand - Jecheon, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/108/d5548561-aaa2-4b15-b258-1063fd089cc9.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Glutinous rice cake made by hand
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Dungsil is not only glutinous rice cake but also donuts. Unlike regular donuts, it has a chewy texture. It is chewy like glutinous rice cake. In Dungsil, ferment the dough with rice wine and rice water instead of yeast. Donuts are sold hot as soon as they are fried. There are two kinds of donuts. Dongle adzuki bean donuts with red beans inside, and dungling donuts without beef. On weekends, you can only taste Dungling Donuts. In response to a customer question, &#34;What&#39;s in this?&#34; Dangling donuts are chewy and sweet even if nothing is in them.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Glutinous rice cake of Jecheon &#39;Dunkilssik&#39; with decades of history - Jecheon, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/108/c5db0f5a-77e3-481d-96ba-19c59dfadc91.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Glutinous rice cake of Jecheon &#39;Dunkilssik&#39; with decades of history
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Donuts are best eaten when they&#39;re fresh, and glutinous rice cakes can be left at room temperature for a day or two. If you leave the glutinous rice cake for a long time, you can store it in the freezer.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Freshly fried chewy donuts - Jecheon, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/108/9f57a849-8292-4b82-b8b0-a489b32d6382.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Freshly fried chewy donuts
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Acorn King Songpyeon, Herbal Yokan, and Hwangdogi Nuts
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   There are many healthy snacks in Jecheon. First, let&#39;s go to Jecheon station square heart market in front of Jecheon station. If you go to the &#39;Taechang Tteok Mill&#39; located in Hanmaeum Market, you can taste the acorn Wangsongpyeon. Its size is almost the size of an adult fist, and its name is Wang Peng.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Large Acorn King Songpyeon - Jecheon, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/108/17b59c09-5160-4332-8ff1-3741d251864b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Large Acorn King Songpyeon
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The rice cake kneaded with acorn powder is filled with beef powder and nuts. Chewy taste and chewy taste go well together. It&#39;s also big and it&#39;s full of cows. It&#39;s light and sweet, so everyone loves it.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Large Acorn King Songpyeon - Jecheon, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/108/05fd784d-b006-4ca9-9810-8190ebca9494.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Large Acorn King Songpyeon
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In the Hanmaeum Market, the high-speed rice cake mill sells yokan made with mulberry leaves, longan meat, and donkeys. The smell of herbs is not strong, sweet children eat well. Try one by color or one by one.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sweet yokan made with herbs - Jecheon, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/108/017cf2a2-65d6-4e1e-adfa-071fd99351f4.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sweet yokan made with herbs
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   As a breakdown of herbs, the jeonjuburi using herbs was also noticeable. In Hanmaeum Market, you can taste herbal donuts in addition to yokan containing herbs. Medicinal donuts are made by kneading flour and mixing Angelica powder with Jecheon-san Astragalus and Jujube. Use canola oil for frying donuts. Blow freshly fried donuts and bite a bite.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;15&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sweet yokan made with herbs - Jecheon, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/108/490c9fa0-cb3d-4d6e-9172-800d754e770d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sweet yokan made with herbs
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In addition, you can also taste steamed buns made with Astragalus delicacies in Nato Traditional Market and Dongmun Market.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;16&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Steamed Bread Kneaded with Astragalus Water - Jecheon, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/108/57c3507c-7ebd-49a6-84ee-507106197f88.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Steamed Bread Kneaded with Astragalus Water
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel info
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;b&gt;
     Jecheon Red Oden
    &lt;/b&gt;
    / 2, Euiyeong-daero 18-gil, Jecheon-si, Chungbuk, Korea / 011-459-0605
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;b&gt;
     Red oden
    &lt;/b&gt;
    / 2 Pungyang-ro 15-gil, Jecheon-si, Chungbuk
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;b&gt;
     Vine
    &lt;/b&gt;
    / 5 Doksun-ro 6-gil, Jecheon-si, Chungbuk / 043-643-2133
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;b&gt;
     Jecheon station square heart market
    &lt;/b&gt;
    / 12 Natoro 28-gil, Jecheon-si, Chungbuk / 043-645-2729
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;b&gt;
     Nearby attractions
    &lt;/b&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Uilim Area: 241, Mosan-dong, Jecheon-si / 043-651-7101
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Cheongpung Cultural Foundation: 2048 Cheongpungho-ro, Cheongpung-myeon, Jecheon-si / 043-641-5532
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Baron Shrine: 296, Balonseongji-gil, Bongyang-eup, Jecheon-si / 043-651-4527
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.baeron.or.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.baeron.or.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Rooms
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Cheongpung Resort: 1798 Cheongpungho-ro, Cheongpung-myeon, Jecheon-si / 043-640-7000
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cheongpungresort.co.kr/web/kor/asp/index/index.asp&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     https://www.cheongpungresort.co.kr/web/kor/asp/index/index.asp
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Resom Forest: 365, Geumbong-ro, Baegun-myeon, Jecheon-si / 043-649-6000
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://resom.co.kr/forest/main/main.asp&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://resom.co.kr/forest/main/main.asp
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Cheongpung Guesthouse: 5, Eulim-daero 6-gil, Jecheon-si / 070-8621-5886
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.jecheonguesthouse.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;[새창열림]‘청풍게스트하우스’정보 페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
     http://www.jecheonguesthouse.com/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was updated in February 2019 and may change afterwards, so please check before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ The information such as text, photos and videos used in this article is copyrighted by Korea Tourism Organization, so unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet the History of Chungju Blooming along the Namhan River - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/meet-the-history-of-chungju-blooming-along-the-namhan-river-47/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 08:12:11 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/meet-the-history-of-chungju-blooming-along-the-namhan-river-47/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;meet-the-history-of-chungju-blooming-along-the-namhan-river--47&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Jodong-ri History Museum - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/47/a491d9bd-999f-40e5-ba3e-db7dbc388e08.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Jodong-ri History Museum
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Meet the History of Chungju Blooming along the Namhan River
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Chungju Chungju is the hometown of Jungwon culture. Prehistoric remains remain around the Namhan River, and in the Three Kingdoms era, it was a fierce battlefield to occupy Jungwon. It is also the place where Jungwongyeong was made among the 5 blind spots since the Three Kingdoms period. In January, a large amount of bronze artifacts from the early Iron Age were excavated in Hoam-dong, Chungju. In the early Iron Age tomb 19 artifacts were excavated all at once, including the Sejong bronze sword. Let&#39;s meet Chungju&#39;s history from prehistoric times to Goryeo dynasty along the Namhan River, which is dotted with intense historical traces and various ruins.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Meet the Bronze Artist&#39;s Life 3000 Years ago
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Since ancient times, the place where there is water has always been a place of people&#39;s living. Even now, prehistoric people who lived and settled in have chosen a place with water to live. The prehistoric ruins of Jodong-ri, located in Dongyang-myeon, Chungju-si, are large village ruins from the Neolithic Age to the Bronze Age, based on the Namhan River. The large river called Namhan River and the alluvial plains created by the flooding were suitable for people to live. Prehistoric ruins date back to approximately 7000 years. Since the Neolithic began to live for the first time, the Bronze activists continued their agricultural life 3000 years ago.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Excavation and ruins of Jodong-ri History Museum - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/47/53aa1535-c891-4c7e-8837-2bb586f2515f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Excavation and ruins of Jodong-ri History Museum
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Jodong-ri History Museum is located adjacent to the entrance of Dongyang-myeon and Namhan River. It is a place where you can see the discovery process of Jo Dong-ri and various relics. It is composed of Jodong-ri History and Culture Center on the 1st floor, Jodong-ri Farming Room on the 2nd floor, and Memorial Hall for Huh Mun-hoe, agronomist.
   &lt;br/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Bronzeman&#39;s Whirlwind - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/47/5e702f52-cf88-4eb4-9ec2-a74f0f6575f3.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Bronzeman&#39;s Whirlwind
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The prehistoric ruins of Jo Dong-ri became known to the world as the ruins were exposed in 1990 due to heavy rain. Over the next ten years, some of the ruins of the Neolithic era, as well as the ruins of the Bronze Age, as well as the burning seats and huts were excavated. The ruins reveal that prehistoric people lived on a large scale in villages and active farming.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Diorama showing the bronze life - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/47/3ac9b291-b1a2-48e0-92eb-4c78c08b1574.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Diorama showing the bronze life
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   When you cross the bridge made of tempered glass that reproduces the scene of the excavation, you will meet the dioramas that tell the life of the time based on the ruins of the excavated house, umyu-gu, and the seat of burning, earthenware and grains. It is a place where you can spread your imagination through the excavated artifacts. A huge diorama of the bronze fighter who lived in a large village based on the topography of Jodong-ri. The life of the Bronze Age unfolds like a panorama of catching fish or farming by the river, raising livestock, harvesting fruit, and burning pots and baking earthenware.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Diorama showing the bronze life - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/47/18416aa1-36dd-44aa-bd65-27dc6fe5e014.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Diorama showing the bronze life
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   You can also see the bronze life of the bronze fighter. This is a reconstruction of the 7th house found at Jo Dong-ri Prehistoric Site. The figure shows a man who trims the net, a child who grinds grains and shreds, and a woman who bakes fish on fire.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Diorama showing the bronze life - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/47/819d3580-c451-4563-a48a-bcb09e717450.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Diorama showing the bronze life
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Unification Rice with Green Revolution Found in Prehistoric Ruins
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Jodong-ri Agricultural Room on the 2nd floor of the museum is a place where you can examine the use of agricultural artifacts discovered in Jodong-ri and the grains of the time. You can see the picture of the moisturizer used to plow the ground, the vandal knife and scythe used to cut the grain, and the use of the reeds and reed used to peel the fruit or grind grain. Among them, care was not only used to plow the land, but also a multifunctional tool that played a role as a shovel and a hoe. Wouldn&#39;t it be MacGyver knife these days? In the ruins of Jo Dong-ri, various traces of grain were excavated. Wheat was the largest with 723 eggs, and barley and rice, rice, rice, and park and peach seeds were also found. Most of them are carbonized, but it&#39;s easy to see the grain from 3000 years ago.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Bronze Engineer Farm Equipment Moisturizing Restoration - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/47/da35a9e4-05f6-424b-9b3c-fe8f5616f33f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Bronze Engineer Farm Equipment Moisturizing Restoration
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Next to the farm room is a place in commemoration of Dr. Huh Mun-hui, a farmer from Chungju. Dr. Huh, who has made great contributions to Korean agricultural history, has developed a unified rice that opened the rice self-sufficiency era. In Korea, there were four springs, often called “barley hills,” until the 1970s. It was a country that mainly produces rice, but most people did not have a warm meal.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Carbonized barley found in Jodong-ri prehistoric ruins - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/47/c393fd04-c0b0-413a-8219-5490577527ab.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Carbonized barley found in Jodong-ri prehistoric ruins
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Unification rice is a hybrid of Japanese and Taiwanese rice varieties, and is a cultivar developed by three-way breeding of IR8, which was nurtured by the International Rice Research Institute. Rice grown in Korea was weak against wind and pests, and the yield was very low a year. Since the unification of rice since 1972, rice self-sufficiency rate has surpassed 100% with increasing production.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Unification rice developed by Dr. Huh Moon Hoe - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/47/e1ffef0e-46be-41ed-8ff4-182bc9717f27.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Unification rice developed by Dr. Huh Moon Hoe
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Considering the time when we worried about meals 40 years ago, is our life too undeserved? Nowadays, when rice consumption remains unprecedented, it&#39;s a good idea to reflect on Barley Hill&#39;s days. In that sense, the commemoration room for the agronomist Humunmun teacher is a meaningful place.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Agronomist - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/47/79e35059-e3dd-4cf1-b89d-783c6ce31d7d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Agronomist
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Rustic stones that meet at the central tower flowing through the Namhan River
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Various traces from the Three Kingdoms Period to the Goryeo Dynasty remain around the Namhan River, which flows through the Chungju Jungang Pagoda to Yeoju. Crossing Tangeum Bridge is Changdong-ri, the first town in the middle of Pagoda. In Changdong-ri, there are simple, majestic stone towers of the Koryo Dynasty, stone Buddhas, and Mae Buddha.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Chungju Changdong-ri Maaebul View - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/47/0636ba71-5b5d-4484-ab5f-acf869d952ec.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Chungju Changdong-ri Maaebul View
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you cross the Tangeum Bridge for about 1km, you will meet Maebul, Changdong-ri, Chungju to the right. It&#39;s a magic fire carved on a rock wall facing the Namhan River over a small hill. As you climb the hill past the entrance, you will see a steep staircase leading down the river. He unintentionally descends the stairs and is amazed by the appearance of a huge 4 meter tall Buddha. A friendly and stern expression and harsh expression are typical of the Buddha&#39;s love. It seems to be a Buddhist image that wishes for the well-being of those who cross the boat by the Mae Fire, which is seen from the Namhan River flowing toward Yeoju.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Changae-ri Maaebul overlooking the Namhan River - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/47/aad87770-dea1-464e-a40a-dcc14f0bd457.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Changae-ri Maaebul overlooking the Namhan River
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The five-story stone pagoda in Changdong-ri and the stone statue of a stone pharmacist are standing side by side within 200m from Changae-ri Maaebul. It is easy to find the Jungwon Party that makes Cheong Myeongju designated as Chungbuk Intangible Cultural Property No.2.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Five-storied pagoda and Changjo pharmacy - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/47/b885cea6-bdbf-46f5-a059-41b3972166e2.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Five-storied pagoda and Changjo pharmacy
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Changdong-ri Five Storeyed Stone Pagoda and Stone Carved Buddha Statue are also known for the Goryeo Dynasty. The stone statue of the stone pharmacist is carved from the pharmacist&#39;s standing standing on the big stone. If Chang Dong-ri&#39;s Ma-a-bul has a blunt look, the pharmacist&#39;s statue is a cute figure with a gentle smile on his vivid face.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Gentle smile of stone statue - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/47/46802480-fff4-46d2-b06f-c5e885b13541.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Gentle smile of stone statue
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The five-storied pagoda has a slim pagoda on a thick two-story podium, as if two other stones were placed on it. The stone pagoda is from a nearby abandoned site, and the pharmacist statue was taken from a nearby abandoned mine. Standing side by side in a narrow open space, it offers simple yet splendid scenery.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Chungju Changdong-ri Five-story Stone Tower - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/47/a6bad3e0-eaeb-47fb-9c8f-7116dd469dd2.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Chungju Changdong-ri Five-story Stone Tower
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Along the way from the Chungju-guguryeo Vision Exhibition Center to the Chungju-gugur Astronomical Science Museum, if you cross the hill, you will reach Bongwang-ri. On the way up the iron rod that runs along the Hanpocheon flowing into the Namhan River, there is Mae Buddha statue in Bongwangri, Chungju designated as treasure 1401.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;13&#34; id3=&#34;15&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Bonghuangri Maae Buddha Statue - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/47/e9d744e0-1a84-436d-96f5-72e8e1ad1391.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Bonghuangri Maae Buddha Statue
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Climbing steep stone staircase and iron staircase leads to the first rock climbing with 8 hearts. Various Buddha statues are engraved, including chants, offerings, and bodhisattva statues.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;15&#34; id3=&#34;16&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Travelers looking at Penghuangri Maae Buddha Statue - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/47/6b6b5e35-555a-4247-9f81-22977a57c07d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Travelers looking at Penghuangri Maae Buddha Statue
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It was difficult to find all eight Buddha statues because it was built in the Three Kingdoms period and endured a long time. As if you are searching for hidden pictures, you can find them by looking at them one by one.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;17&#34; id3=&#34;17&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Statues and chants of the Phoenix Buddha - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/47/0b8197e6-77c7-44ff-9d42-622423b461a1.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Statues and chants of the Phoenix Buddha
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you climb a little higher than the Buddha statue, there is a statue of the Buddha. Five fires which put the cross seat on the Buddha&#39;s widespread eye attract attention. If you turn your view in front of the Maae Buddha statue, you will come to the scenery of Hanpocheon, which is merged into the Namhan River, and the high mountain.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;19&#34; id3=&#34;18&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Fireworks carved on the giant boat on Ma&#39;ae - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/47/0ad2e8c3-886a-4337-afc8-dba67a601ea7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Fireworks carved on the giant boat on Ma&#39;ae
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel info
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Jodong-ri Prehistoric Museum
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Address: 15, Jodong 1-gil, Dongyang-myeon, Chungju-si, Chungbuk
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Contact: 043-850-3992
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Nearby destinations
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Madang Garden: Freshwater Maeuntang / 441, Jideung-ro, Dongyang-myeon, Chungju-si / 043-851-4077
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.마당가든.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.마당가든.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Unjeong Restaurant: Olgang Haejangguk / 3432-1, Jungwon-daero, Chungju-si / 043-847-2820
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Ahn Sungwoo Hanwoo: Hanwoo / 1512 Gagok-ro, Angseong-myeon, Chungju-si / 043-855-5808
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Accommodation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Bonghuang Natural Recreation Forest: 540, Suryongbonghwang-gil, Gaeum-myeon, Chungju-si / 043-850-7315
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Filim 37.2 Hotel: 17, Yeonwon-ro, Yeonsu-dong, Chungju-si / 043-842-0515
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Beautiful house: 268 Jideung-ro, Dongyang-myeon, Chungju-si / 043-851-4022
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was made in February 2015. It may change afterwards, so please check before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Information such as text, photos, and videos used in this article is copyrighted by Korea Tourism Organization, so unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jecheon, Chungbuk, South Korea - One-Day Trip to the Jecheon Scenic Tour Village, a City of Natural Healing</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/oneday-trip-to-the-jecheon-scenic-tour-village-a-city-of-natural-healing-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 22:03:34 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/oneday-trip-to-the-jecheon-scenic-tour-village-a-city-of-natural-healing-15/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-title=&#34;oneday-trip-to-the-jecheon-scenic-tour-village-a-city-of-natural-healing--15&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Wood Train Remodeled - Jecheon, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/15/5f3829c8-7773-40ce-9e63-c7812c95decb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Wood Train Remodeled
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   One-Day Trip to the Jecheon Scenic Tour Village, a City of Natural Healing
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Jecheon, Chungbuk, South Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Tourism Tour is a new type of community-led tourism management community project where local residents become owners and voluntarily run tourism projects to create jobs and profits. In 2013, five areas including Yangpyeong, Gyeonggi-do, Yang-gu, Gangwon-do, Jecheon, Chungbuk, Cheongsong, and Jeonbuk, Buan were selected for the pilot project and supported by the Ministry of Culture, Tourism and Sports. Of these five, we will visit the “Tourism Village” in Jecheon, Chungbuk, which is actively operated due to the characteristics of the region.
   &lt;br/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The Jecheon Sightseeing Tour Village Tour Course consists of three tour village projects and a program that combines tourist attractions located nearby. In order to transform Jecheon&#39;s hidden treasures, Gyodong folk painting villages and republic villages into tourist destinations, the “Own Culture and Arts Cooperative” was launched. The Folk Painting Institute in Minhwa Village has developed a variety of murals, experiences, and souvenirs based on folk paintings. The former school, Gongjeon School, offers a variety of enzyme experiences and enzyme meals that are responsible for family health. &#39;History of History&#39;, which is not used at present, is being revived as a &#39;woodtrain&#39; woodcarving workshop.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Gyodong Folk Painting Village, where we meet beautiful and humorous folk paintings through murals
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Gyo-dong, where Gyo-dong Folk Painting Village is located, was a dwelling complex in the form of urban and rural complexes since the 1960s, when Korea&#39;s industrialization began.However, empty houses have begun to increase in recent years. From the beginning of drawing folk paintings, it is transformed into a folk painting village.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Jangseung Mural in Gyodong Folk Painting Village - Jecheon, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/15/6a809fc2-9367-4b49-9b45-698f6e1f7636.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Jangseung Mural in Gyodong Folk Painting Village
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Most of the single-storey houses have folk paintings such as tigers and deer, as well as innocent children, who have begun to decorate the walls of Kyodong.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Dragonfly and flower mural - Jecheon, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/15/a6b1ad39-0b36-4144-a83f-46953496ef56.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Dragonfly and flower mural
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The mural of Kyodong Folk Painting Village is different from the murals of other regions, and the theme of the mural is ‘어변성룡’.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Tiger mural - Jecheon, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/15/0b40d151-4fb2-4d09-bc14-4012fb47c547.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Tiger mural
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   This word, which means “fish turns into a dragon,” symbolizes passing or success, so I think it&#39;s a good place for parents with children.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Fantastic harmony of flowers and murals - Jecheon, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/15/268f7514-f3d7-4d2e-9542-e144af544f80.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Fantastic harmony of flowers and murals
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Jieun-soon Minhwa Research Institute, which serves as the starting point for Gyodong Folk Painting Village, runs various experience-based event programs, such as drawing folk paintings, making “Eomseong Sungryong” lucky bags using folk paintings, and making folk painting fan. In addition, you can listen to various stories related to folk paintings, and drawing folk paintings using traditional paints provides fun memories for both children and adults.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Eun-Soon Ji Minhwa Debt - Jecheon, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/15/36df427c-a2fa-46fa-825b-e4309dc1306a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Eun-Soon Ji Minhwa Debt
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    In Gyodong Folk Village there is Gyodong Hyanggyo. Gyodong Hyanggyo was established in the year of King Gongyang, the last king of Goryeo, and was designated as Local Tangible Cultural Property 105. It is also a demonstration yangkyo designated by miners of cultural gymnasium.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Abyssal Dragon Lucky Bag - Jecheon, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/15/25d22e5e-8929-4b2f-a207-b8c38f827aec.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Abyssal Dragon Lucky Bag
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Public electronic junior high school, a place to experience and learn about nature
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The “Own Art and Culture Cooperative” is a kind of collaboration made by 15 artists from Jecheon. Other majors, such as literature, photography, ceramics, woodwork, and art, are being utilized and the ones that are lacking are working together to prepare a foundation for independence in various fields such as culture, tourism and hands-on education.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The closed school &#39;Gongjeon Elementary School&#39; and the closed area &#39;Gongjeon Station&#39; have been refurbished to operate the &#39;Gongjeon Elementary School&#39; centered on enzymes, and the &#39;Woodtrain&#39; where you can experience woodworking with cypress wood. &#39;Gong-jeon Institute&#39; is famous for various enzyme experiences such as Omija, Ogapi fruit plum, and herbal medicine, and natural enzyme dishes with side dishes.
   &lt;br/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;GongYeon School Cafe - Jecheon, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/15/fc4b1af7-191a-45d9-b996-b7a7a56b0f9a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     GongYeon School Cafe
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &#39;Gongjeon Junior High School&#39; is located in Gongjeon Elementary School, Gongjeon-ri, Bongyang-eup, Jecheon-si. Gongjeon Elementary School, once a large school with more than 2,000 students, was closed in 1999 due to the agricultural phenomenon.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Public electronics school signs - Jecheon, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/15/6154fc2e-046f-4f26-ab8a-397b62e100bf.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Public electronics school signs
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In recognition of this, Ahn Myung-sook has been rented from Jecheon Office of Education and Support since 2013, and has opened a new door to the “Public Electron School”.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Herbal tea tasting - Jecheon, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/15/0935e862-db9b-484f-86bd-93f08567f7ba.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Herbal tea tasting
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   One of the most popular programs of the public engineering school is the enzyme making experience using seasonal fruits.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Apple enzyme making - Jecheon, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/15/947e9462-fa0f-4b90-bb37-27d394216183.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Apple enzyme making
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Green apples grown organically on the farm are used to make enzymes. Four apples are cut into 18 pieces, seeded well, put in a gourd, put sugar on top and mixed together for a long time. Mix until the sugar has melted and mixed in the apple juice. After tossing it, put it in a glass jar and pour sugar back to the top to cover the apples.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Completed Apple Enzyme - Jecheon, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/15/ba3fb53e-1530-49ec-84eb-f6d392211590.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Completed Apple Enzyme
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The real attraction here is the natural enzyme meal table. We carefully prepare freshly grown vegetables and enzyme natural meal using enzyme. More than a dozen side dishes add boiled pork. The most important part of a natural enzyme meal is that it comes with a colander of organic vegetables grown by hand. The clear insect streaks on the leaves of the vegetables are proof that they are organic, free of pesticides.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Enzyme side dish - Jecheon, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/15/7d36e0ac-cadf-41c5-9b07-148b598b8490.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Enzyme side dish
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The rice is not mixed with white rice, but with brown rice, chew more than 30 times, and the sweetness comes out on its own. Like all natural enzymes, the salinity of all side dishes is low. So you eat more side dishes than rice. Flour brown rice with organic rice and a spoonful of organic ssamjang with a spoonful of honey.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;14&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Grain rice - Jecheon, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/15/ca40f208-a6d3-413b-8a21-6b6ea6b4a687.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Grain rice
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Wood-Train Wood Works, where you can make everything you need for everyday life
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    In &#39;Gongjeon Station&#39;, there is a &#39;Wood Train&#39; run by Kim Kwang-ki. It is a space that produces and displays props that can be used in real life such as props, toys, name initials, pencil holders, etc.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Woodtrain Signs - Jecheon, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/15/47537ad0-f418-44fa-b2a6-0fc33c6d2019.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Woodtrain Signs
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The café displays a variety of woodwork and jigsaw art pieces that can be used in real life. The most eye-catching is a portrait of a former president made of jigsaw craft on a birch drawing board, hanging over the main entrance of the station. The outdoor carpentry experience room has a space where up to 50 people can experience woodworking. The representative experience program is to make pencil case and letter case using cypress. Pencil cases and letterboxes made from sandpaper, nailed, and carpentry glued to the sticky parts of the cypress cut into various shapes are popular experience programs that preschool children can complete in an hour.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;15&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Woodtrain Cafe Exhibit - Jecheon, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/15/360ec3f8-882c-409b-b5f7-948cbcba787d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Woodtrain Cafe Exhibit
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The station was opened in 1959 and was used by more than 100,000 passengers per year by the end of the 1970s. However, since late 2008, there were no vehicles left without passengers. However, in 2012, Kwang-gi Kim, a woodworking artist, rented history from the Korean Railroad and was reborn as a woodcraft experience space called &#39;Woodtrain&#39;. The station waiting room, the space where people waited to come and go, was made into a cafe space where you can experience woodworking and drink tea.
   &lt;br/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;16&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Presidential Jigsaw Craft - Jecheon, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/15/291b7cfa-0783-4472-948e-81b65727ecfa.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Presidential Jigsaw Craft
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   There are many things to see around the station. Yoo In-seok, a teacher of Sungjae Yoo-jung, raised a medical school to save his country and saved the country. There is Jinso Cheon Railway, famous for the filming of the starring Mint Candy. Woodtrain recently aired as a filming location for its popular program, &#34;1 Night and 2 Days.&#34;
   &lt;br/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;17&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Cypress pencil case made by participants of the experience program - Jecheon, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/15/750e254f-1520-488b-a1cf-3c3cc357d0c6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Cypress pencil case made by participants of the experience program
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel info
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Jieun Sun Folk Research Institute
      &lt;br/&gt;
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     Address: 16 Myeongnyun-ro 19-gil, Jecheon-si, Chungbuk
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Contact: 043-651-3440
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Public Electronics School
      &lt;br/&gt;
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     Address: 345, Euiam-ro-gil, Bongyang-eup, Jecheon-si, Chungbuk
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Contact: 043-645-6758
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Woodtrain
      &lt;br/&gt;
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     Address: 698, Euiam-ro, Bongyang-eup, Jecheon-si, Chungcheongbuk-do
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Contact: 070-4418-5120
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;a href=&#34;http://cafe.daum.net/wood1&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
      http://cafe.daum.net/wood1
     &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Nearby restaurants
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Muk Village
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    : Acorn Chameokbap / 3-1 Jupo-ro, Bongyang-eup, Jecheon-si / 043-645-6758
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Dongwon Garden
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    : Native charcoal grilled chicken / 294-1, Haksan-ri, Bongyang-eup, Jecheon-si / 043-651-8100
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Trang Road
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    : Dolgotsanchaejeong / 49-21, Baronseongji-gil, Bongyang-eup, Jecheon-si / 043-651-2121
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was updated in July 2015. It may change afterwards, so please check before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Information such as text, photos, and videos used in this article is copyrighted by Korea Tourism Organization, so unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Take the train, Chungju Samtan Amusement Park &amp; Indeungsan</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/take-the-train-chungju-samtan-amusement-park-indeungsan-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2020 16:47:42 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/take-the-train-chungju-samtan-amusement-park-indeungsan-7/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-title=&#34;take-the-train-chungju-samtan-amusement-park-indeungsan--7&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Samtan Station and Chungbuk Line Train - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/7/dd2d3621-407a-44a5-a92d-85491648882b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Samtan Station and Chungbuk Line Train
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Take the train, Chungju Samtan Amusement Park &amp;amp; Indeungsan
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Water play that reminds me of summer and water play in scenic nature is a fresh play. With the romantic romance of the train, the pleasure of traveling multiplies, regardless of time.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In front of the train station, Samtan Amusement Park where water, forest and mountains are combined. Camping is easy to leave, and it is easy to use the accommodations that are located next to the amusement park. It is also a good idea to have a regular mountain climbing mountain. On the way back, enjoy sightseeing near Chungju Station, and your trip will be more enriching. Let&#39;s leave by train, Chungju!
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Jupocheon from the Samtan Bridge - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/7/3457c21d-7a59-4b99-a0a6-5098890c3892.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Jupocheon from the Samtan Bridge
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Samtan Amusement Park by train track
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Samtan Amusement Park is located at Sancheok-myeon, Chungju-si, Chungbuk. The train to Samtan Amusement Park is good. This is because there is an amusement park about 500 meters from Samtan Station. Pass the Samtan Bridge right in front of the station and follow the road to Myeongdol Village. Samtan means three streams, such as government office, pine and barnacle. Jupocheon, which leads to the Namhan River, flows around the amusement park.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Myeongdol Village Entrance Seats and Sports Park - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/7/1055277e-1c3b-4948-be1f-b551560680f3.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Myeongdol Village Entrance Seats and Sports Park
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In the past, the people were rare enough to stay with them, but in 1958 trains passing through Samtan Station were extended to form villages and amusement parks. In June 2000, a sports park was created next to the amusement park. Recently, a natural grass soccer field has been set up in the center of the park. Most of the facilities in the amusement park can be used free of charge, but lawn parks require a maintenance fee after booking.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Athletic Park - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/7/89f15461-67ed-430b-8e1a-e73f8f84aff7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Athletic Park
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In addition to the turf field, the vacant lot can also be used as a camping ground. The large campsite makes it easy to find a place to go. There are also facilities such as toilet, drinking fountain and parking lot.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Jopocheon and amusement park gravel under the train tracks - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/7/a32e9c70-1b31-48ef-be36-24b10fa5271d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Jopocheon and amusement park gravel under the train tracks
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The malls along the funfair ramp combine restaurants, canteens and bed and breakfasts. You can rent or buy some fishing gear as well as some simple fishing gear. Every summer, residents work together to improve the environment around the park. This year, from July 16th to August 15th, an environmental information center and Saemaul Library will be run by 200 residents. The Environmental Information Center is a voluntary activity that creates a clean environment for vacationers by removing garbage and collecting recyclables around the amusement park. Saemaul Library has over 2,000 books available for free rental and leads a healthy holiday culture. Residents in charge of the river reside in preparation for safety accidents.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Midsummer Willow - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/7/4eddd09e-695f-4feb-8ec8-5d8832e23218.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Midsummer Willow
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The amusement park is surrounded by mountains, and the odd rock cliffs are superbly located across the main stream. The river is wide and the water level is varied, so it is good for children to adults. Gravel fields spread out next to the sports park. There is a lush forest on top of it, and rich trees such as willows make the shade.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Amusement park next to sports park - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/7/fd0c5b13-3333-4f3a-882b-2189ec1ef132.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Amusement park next to sports park
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Receive the energy of three
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Indeungsan is a 667m high mountain located just behind the amusement park. It belongs to Cheondeungsan (807m) in the north and Jideungsan (535m) in the south, and belongs to Samdeungsan which means Cheon, Ji, and Injae. Sandeungsan is known for being sheltered from the mountains and deep in valleys. In addition, the legend is said that if one crosses all three mountains, one wish will be fulfilled.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Train passing railroad crossing by the amusement park - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/7/38c59bea-d86c-494f-b814-2f9e9751aab8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Train passing railroad crossing by the amusement park
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Cheondeungsan Mountain is named after the top of the mountain. The trail is not easy. Along with Bakdaljae, he became famous as a popular song &amp;lt;Crying Bakdaljae&amp;gt;, but in fact, about 9km away from Cheondeungsan and Wonseocheon, it belongs to Mt.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Samtan Amusement Park from the Beginning of the Trail - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/7/ea50c910-9362-406c-ab51-93e03d8f3d65.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Samtan Amusement Park from the Beginning of the Trail
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Jideung Mountain is a mountain that is connected to Indeung Mountain. In climbing is a mountain that can be climbed without difficulty. While walking to the summit, the scenery is beautiful, and on a good day, you can look down to Chungju Lake.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Forest road heading to the observatory - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/7/cff814b1-5bce-4e6d-b443-818d2e4cc196.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Forest road heading to the observatory
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   When the weather is too hot, it&#39;s a good idea to walk along the forest road to the observation deck.
   &lt;br/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Hiking trail by the valley - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/7/93e21d10-1218-4bb6-b123-6b6285431876.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Hiking trail by the valley
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It is about 3km from Samtan Amusement Park to Observation Deck. Passing the mall opposite the amusement park leads you to the apple orchard. When you enter the road, you will be able to walk around the mountain. Do not enter the valley road, it is good to follow the road. There are no milestones on the mountain trail next to the valley, so you can wander around.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Observation Deck 700m - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/7/814ab089-28ea-49be-bc9a-0f1f14e92b55.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Observation Deck 700m
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you climb about 1.7km from the entrance, you will come to a three-way street. Follow the signs to the right for about 700m to reach the observatory. If you climb the observatory, you can see the Cheondeungsan Mountain opposite you and face the river flowing under the mountain.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The area of Jideungsan from the Cheonjiin Observatory - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/7/af0bc49d-f6ef-4237-93b7-38d7133b51e0.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The area of Jideungsan from the Cheonjiin Observatory
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The train tracks seen from the mountain are also superb views.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;14&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Village seen from the observation deck - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/7/03a5af3a-844c-4d26-9248-0c628cc3d810.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Village seen from the observation deck
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Chungju caliber on the way back
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Before heading home, let&#39;s go from Samtan Station to Chungju Station in time for the train. Jungang Top Park is located about 7km from Chungju Station. It is called the tower in the center of Korea. Its historical name is Joongwon Papyeong-ri Seven-storied pagoda. It is the largest stone pagoda in the Unified Shilla Era. It is currently designated as National Treasure No. 6. In 1992, a historic park was built around the pagoda, and in 2007, the park facility was built along with the reorganization and repair work around the central pagoda. Inside the park are Chungju Museum 1 and 2, an open-air museum and a music hall. A music fountain is installed on Tangeum Lake in front of the park.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Next to the park is the World Liquor Museum. Visit the Wine History and Culture Museum for information about wine. There is also an experience facility where you can listen to the whiskey ripening process and taste the whiskey in oak barrels. A collection of beers, spirits, and oriental alcohol from around the world. The liquor of our country attracts people&#39;s attention by displaying traditional and modern wine more carefully. In addition to the exhibition halls, a separate education center will be operated and mainstream culture and fermentation science experiences will be conducted. Anyone can join in advance.
   &lt;br/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Jungwon Tappyeong Seven-storied Pagoda in Jungang Pagoda Park - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/7/1815917a-14fb-4b55-a73e-1f0c5a1e4ff7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Jungwon Tappyeong Seven-storied Pagoda in Jungang Pagoda Park
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   There are many charming restaurants around the museum. Next door is Tangeumho International Rowing Center. Tangeum Lake was formed during the construction of Chungju Dam in 1985. Until 2004, the stadium was used as a water sports park for the general public and as a training ground for rowers. In summer, the Chungju Lake Festival is held in this area, and water sports activities are free for the general public.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;15&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Museum of World Liquor Culture - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/7/fd614432-3993-46f5-a130-a7937fa12feb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Museum of World Liquor Culture
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel info
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Samtan Amusement Park
      &lt;br/&gt;
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     Address: Myeongseo-ri, Sancheok-myeon, Chungju-si, Chungbuk
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Contact: 043-850-2400
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Nearby tourist spots
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Joongang Pagoda Historical Park
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    : 11, Toppyeong-ri, Gaeum-myeon, Chungju-si / 043-842-0531
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     World Liquor Culture Museum Liqueurium
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    : 12, Tapjeongan-gil, Gaeum-myeon, Chungju-si / 043-855-7333
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Tangeumho International Rowing Center
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    : 124, Jungangtap-gil, Gaeum-myeon, Chungju-si / 043-850-6670
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2.Nearby restaurants and accommodations
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Orange House
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    : 6-1, Samyeoul-gil, Sancheok-myeon, Chungju-si / 010-3290-2324
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Zelkova house
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    : Myeongdol, Myeongseori, Sancheok-myeon, Chungju-si / 426-852-7795
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Samtan Minbak
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    : 4, Samyeoul-gil, Sancheok-myeon, Chungju-si / 043-852-6639
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Solbat Cottage
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    : 510-3, Myeongseo-ri, Sancheok-myeon, Chungju-si / 043-852-8495
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Ilheung Guest House
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    : 484-4, Myeongseo-ri, Sancheok-myeon, Chungju-si / 043-852-6751
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was written in July 2014. It may change afterwards, so please check before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Information such as text, photos, and videos used in this article is copyrighted by Korea Tourism Organization, so unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>