<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mapo-gu on Every Corner of Korea</title>
    <link>https://codecorea.github.io/tags/mapo-gu/</link>
    <description>Every Corner of Korea (Mapo-gu)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 07:43:00 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="https://codecorea.github.io/tags/mapo-gu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Jinhon and Yeomwon&#39;s House, Seoul War and Women&#39;s Human Rights Museum - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/jinhon-and-yeomwons-house-seoul-war-and-womens-human-rights-museum-222/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 07:43:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/jinhon-and-yeomwons-house-seoul-war-and-womens-human-rights-museum-222/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;jinhon-and-yeomwons-house-seoul-war-and-womens-human-rights-museum--222&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;War and Women&#39;s Human Rights Museum - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/222/6a9371a5-06ec-474f-b297-8fa33364454d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    War and Women&#39;s Human Rights Museum
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Jinhon and Yeomwon&#39;s House, Seoul War and Women&#39;s Human Rights Museum
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    This museum is located in a residential area under Seongmi Mountain in Seongsan-dong, Mapo-gu. In 2012, he won the Grand Prize at the Seoul Architecture Awards. The museum records the painful history of the survivors of the Japanese comfort women. A building built with bricks is not overwhelmed by its scale and is not decorated with splendor.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   8-year-old museum
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Demand protests are held every Wednesday in front of the Japanese Embassy in Seoul. It is a place to urge the Japanese “comfort women” problem. Victims of the comfort women, members of the Korea Mental Problems Countermeasures Council (Jung Dae-hyup), citizens, and students participate. The protest, which began on January 8, 1992, reached its 1,000th on December 14, 2011. On that day, the Peace Monument (Girls&#39; Award) was established. The girl statue wears a raincoat on rainy days and a shawl in winter. The War and Women&#39;s Human Rights Museum opened on May 5, 2012, the following year. The spirit of space is an extension of demand demonstrations. It contains a willingness to remember the painful history of comfort women survivors and to solve the problem. Going one step further, we aim for a world without war and violence against women.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   The process of building the museum was not only smooth. In 1994, the Preparatory Committee for the Construction of Feed Museums was established. In 1999, a small educational center was established to inform the history of the Japanese comfort women near Seodaemun. It was in 2004 that discussions on building the museum took place in earnest. Chung Dae-hyup launched the War and Women Human Rights Museum Establishment Committee, and the government life support fund raised by 17 comfort women grandmothers became the cornerstone. Initially, it was planned to be built in Seodaemun Independence Park. However, in March 2009, the first shovel had to be stopped. Unexpectedly, the defamation of the Sunkuk Seonyeol was the reason for opposition. It wasn&#39;t until August 2011 that the site was purchased at the foot of Seongmi Mountain. The cost of construction was raised through donations and fundraising activities by citizens such as the “10,000 Won Donation Relay Campaign”. Japanese citizens also joined. It was a process that took 8 years to complete after the construction committee was established. Sometimes it is not easy to take for granted the fact that it is so natural.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The War and Women&#39;s Human Rights Museum is less than 1 km from Hongik University Station. It is a street corner of the residential area that entered the alley toward Seongmisan Mountain at the intersection of Gyeongseong High School. If you turn the wall of gray brown bricks, you will see the entrance. On the wall, there are letters written on yellow butterfly-shaped paper. It is the trace of citizens who visited the museum. A 23-year-old woman wrote, &#34;I hope that this will never happen again.&#34; It is mostly about cheering up comfort women and pledge themselves. The yellow butterfly is a symbol of Jeong Dae-hyup&#39;s activities, meaning hope and solidarity. As I turned around the corner along the wings of a butterfly, the building beyond the wall was a bit clearer. The color of the dark exterior walls surrounding the whole is solemn. In the alley, it was the part that was covered by fences and trees. The brick house is a little more realistic.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Yellow butterfly-shaped cheering notes on the wall - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/222/d60b431b-ddaf-4629-a68c-12a639fe01f5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Yellow butterfly-shaped cheering notes on the wall
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   A shuddering pace
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The War and Women&#39;s Human Rights Museum is the work of Wise Architects Young-cheol Jang and Jeon Suk-hee. They received the Young Architect Award from the Ministry of Culture, Sports and Tourism in 2010. Participated in projects such as ABC Office, Y House, and Lee Sang-Ho. The Museum of War and Women&#39;s Human Rights won the Grand Prize at the Seoul Architecture Awards. Their architecture is not a game of scale. It is also characterized by developing various architectural and cultural activities together.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   The museum has no historical connection with Seongmisan. This is a remodeling of a two-story house of about 344m2, which is the home of an ordinary person. The comfort women issue is a tremendous event that has shaken the lives of ordinary people. In that sense, the first impression of a dark gray-brown house and a house that sits at the end of a narrow alley makes the meaning reminiscent. It is a symbol of a space without a symbol.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Open the door and enter the room. Dark space, the beginning of the journey. Buy a ticket at the right side of the entrance. It is different from the existing admission ticket. By purchasing a ticket, you have a relationship with a woman who is a comfort woman. It is the process of going to see him, and through him, we look into the life of a comforting woman. First, we face the interaction video on the wall of the reception room. It is a butterfly that flies out of the frame. It is a wing that goes beyond the wall of violence and discrimination. The first step goes out there again. Rather than going straight into the exhibition room on the first floor, it is a movement that experiences an external space and goes up to the ground building through the basement.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Picture of a girl on the left wall of a crushed stone road - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/222/4727ea04-e241-4b77-b460-3b1abd948f35.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Picture of a girl on the left wall of a crushed stone road
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   When you open the door to the outside, you can hear the boots. The crushed stone road now opens. The narrow passageway at the edge of the building leads to the basement. The road about 1m wide was laid with crushed stone and artificial gravel. On the left is a picture of a black girl, and on the right is an old man&#39;s face and hand relief. Visitors walk through the gaps of time in the meantime. It is a history of war madness and violence that they had to go through. The pebble echo spreads in a narrow space, knocking on the door of the heart A few steps by the comfort women were drawn by the stairs going down the ground after passing through the crushed stone path. This is also awesome.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Face and hand relief are the comfort women&#39;s present. - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/222/0507a211-90a4-48af-9906-4210cf8ebdba.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Face and hand relief are the comfort women&#39;s present.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The underground exhibition hall reconstructed the comfort station with a yoke. It was originally used as a boiler room for a house. In the photo of the ticket received when entering, the grandmother interview is shown. This day is the testimony of Hong Kang-rim&#39;s grandmother. Born in Gimcheon, North Gyeongsang Province in 1922, he was taken to Bongcheon, China in 1938. She ended her life in China without stepping on her homeland. “I ca n’t go, I ca n’t come… . ” Following that lonely confession, she looks back on her life. In the middle of a cryptic underground room, hair shoes and shoes are placed neatly like a store.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Another room where the past and reality intersect - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/222/032af426-eac3-4019-b8c7-4583a8581a77.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Another room where the past and reality intersect
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   45,000 pieces All bricks with eager breeze
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Head to the 2nd floor from the underground exhibition hall. It is a copper line that goes down from the basement to the first floor after going through the second floor. The walls of the landing are concrete bricks. It is a smooth, unbroken deadline like the remains of a ruins. The skeleton revealed when the walls were torn to remodel the house into a museum was left untouched. It feels like a long history of fighting for comfort women. In the meantime, pictures and bricks of comfort women were placed. The core in the chest remained a text for each brick. A bloody voice echoes along the stairs. Nevertheless, the more you climb the stairs, the more hopeful it is. I hope that the same pain will not be repeated to someone else. It is a wish in the name of the Museum of War and Women&#39;s Human Rights. Before facing the exhibition space on the second floor, a work called &#34;Flowers Blooming in the Border&#34; by artist Jun-Hwa Ryu took. He wanted women not to be seen as simple victims. Think briefly about the life that will bloom across the border.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Comfort woman grandmother&#39;s words engraved on the stairs brick - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/222/9e2a906b-e4b6-4201-b4e1-ae3fc4a9241c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Comfort woman grandmother&#39;s words engraved on the stairs brick
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The exhibition room on the second floor is a little clearer. The ceiling on the first floor is open to the second floor. On the left and right, the list of donors remained as a donor wall. Around the perimeter, there are exhibition spaces, such as a history hall, a sports hall, and a life hall. The History Museum displays Japanese military documents and related materials. The first sentence is the term ‘comfort women’. It was written from the point of view of the perpetrated man, but it was written in quotation marks to reveal the historical concept. Beneath it was a comfort card and a condom named “Assault No. 1”, which was given to soldiers, and a diary describing the contents of the Japanese troops going to the comfort station. The exercise academy looks at the footsteps of efforts to resolve the comfort women problem. The scene of demand demonstrations that continue every Wednesday is also reproduced. The Peace Monument girl statue was also present. The Life Hall displays the remains of victims. Now go to the memorial hall connected to the balcony on the second floor.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Ryu Jun-hwa&#39;s &amp;lt;Flowers Blooming in the Border&amp;gt; - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/222/4023dec6-3a47-4d96-b1f2-d9a2d41e95cd.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Ryu Jun-hwa&#39;s &amp;lt;Flowers Blooming in the Border&amp;gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The memorial hall is a striking exterior of the museum when viewed from the outside. Bricks were piled up intentionally and carefully to allow light and wind to pass. For each brick, the faces, names, and date of death of the grandmothers who were victims of 170 women were recorded. Victims who failed to leave their names and faces are honored with black bricks. In the gap between the bricks, flowers of memorial were placed. Next to the entrance, there was a donation box. The donation will be used for the next visitor&#39;s wreath. Then he goes back to the first floor.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;An athletic academy that reproduces the scene of demand demonstrations - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/222/28ac43b8-6c0d-4e2d-a453-7c7d67433492.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     An athletic academy that reproduces the scene of demand demonstrations
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The first floor is close to the exhibition hall. There is a permanent exhibition on the theme of world conflict and violence against women. A space for participation was also prepared. You can also go out to the museum front yard. In the yard, the exterior of the museum is clearer. A total of 45,000 bricks are piled up to form a complete body. It is the sum of some winds. Which brick to treat easily? Which death will pass easily? Even if you don&#39;t try to interpret it, the hidden meaning is clear.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;History museum exhibiting Japanese military documents and materials - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/222/6cf77cd6-7daf-4ff7-873e-8a99ce0b4c9c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     History museum exhibiting Japanese military documents and materials
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Eight years is an hour of hard work. It is a sincere and solidarity that has been piled up one by one with donations and donations. It is an earnest desire and a wish. Above all, it is a footprint of pain and suffering that cannot be expressed in words. It is a message of architecture that is revealed at once.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Memorial flowers in the crevices - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/222/bc1c9aeb-38c5-426f-a17b-ddbf9c65592a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Memorial flowers in the crevices
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      War and Women&#39;s Human Rights Museum
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Address: 20 World Cup Buk-ro 11-gil, Mapo-gu, Seoul
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Contact: 02-365-4016
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.womenandwar.net&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     www.womenandwar.net
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1.Nearby Restaurants
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Retre Campane: Pizza and Pasta / 46 Hongik-ro 5-gil, Mapo-gu / 02-336-3378
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Santi: Curry and Tandoori Chicken / 9, Wausan-ro 23-gil, Mapo-gu / 02-325-1779
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2.Accommodation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Hotel Seogyo: 130, Yanghwa-ro, Mapo-gu / 02-330-7777
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.hotelseokyo.co.kr/asp/view/main/main.asp&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;호텔 서교로 이동&#34;&gt;
     http://www.hotelseokyo.co.kr/asp/view/main/main.asp
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Stay Korea: 60-5 Donggyo-ro 27-gil, Mapo-gu / 02-336-9026
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.staykorea.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;스테이코리아로 이동&#34;&gt;
     http://www.staykorea.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was created in June 2013, and may be changed later, so be sure to check it before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alleyway taste trip to another world, Yeonnam-dong alley food and coffee shop - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/alleyway-taste-trip-to-another-world-yeonnamdong-alley-food-and-coffee-shop-180/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 00:55:01 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/alleyway-taste-trip-to-another-world-yeonnamdong-alley-food-and-coffee-shop-180/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;alleyway-taste-trip-to-another-world-yeonnamdong-alley-food-and-coffee-shop--180&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Taco and Quesadilla of Bemucho Cantina, Mexican family meal - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/180/96654e33-abf9-475e-b2d5-df54a3cc04e2.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Taco and Quesadilla of Bemucho Cantina, Mexican family meal
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Alleyway taste trip to another world, Yeonnam-dong alley food and coffee shop
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   When you cross a crossing in Hongdae Street, crowded with crowds all day, you meet Yeonnam-dong, which leads to an old and alley. Narrow alleys, Yeonnam-dong Alleys, filled with analogue sensibility and vintage charm, are filled with strange and fresh taste and aroma.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Except for more than 50 m, an exotic day at the Thai restaurant &#39;Tuk Tuk Noodle Thai&#39;, &#39;Coffee Shop Issim&#39;, &#39;Coffee Breve&#39;, Mexican restaurant &#39;Bemucho Cantina&#39;, and curry restaurant &#39;Himeji&#39; Is simple, comfortable, fragrant and plain.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Tuk Tuk Noodle Thai Appetizer, Fried Shrimp Pork - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/180/30294346-e9db-4769-a5bf-549080754c77.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Tuk Tuk Noodle Thai Appetizer, Fried Shrimp Pork
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Nice place to walk slowly alone, Yeonnam-dong alleyway
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   There are such people. An alley that only I know, a gourmet that only goes to me. The small desire to keep everyone&#39;s own space without wanting to inform anyone seems to be selfish and timid, but the inner heart of saving that space is more affectionate and passionate than anyone else. This is the heart of people who love the alleys of Yeonnam-dong.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   After walking off the bustling street at the intersection of Exit 3 of Hongik University Subway Station and walking for about 10 minutes on the left side of the street, you will see a small alley going down the side of the Kimbab House. This is a small alley leading to Yeonhui-dong, the old address of Yeonnam-dong, located at 227. Gallery, bookstore, coffee shop, and restaurant representing Yeonnam-dong are gathered in the alleyway overlooking the neighborhood at a glance.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Gallery Barracks opened in the alley of Dongjin Market - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/180/f38d5bde-70c6-49d1-b51a-d23483f11e04.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Gallery Barracks opened in the alley of Dongjin Market
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Influencing the wind of culture and art in the alleys of Yeonnam-dong, known as Chinatown and Knights Restaurant, is a complex cultural space called &#39;Place Mak&#39;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.placemak.com&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     www.placemak.com
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    to be. It opened in 2010 and re-lighted the old alleys of the old town by collecting and displaying chairs containing the memories of residents of Yeonnam-dong. More than 30㎡, this is a non-profit space that begins as an artistic shelter for residents of Yeonnam-dong, where free and innovative exhibitions of young artists such as installation, sculpture, furniture, and paintings can be freely continued. As a small tree in front of the gallery, the gallery is like a love room in the neighborhood where anyone can look back and relax.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Gallery, Place of Culture and Art in Yeonnam-dong Alley - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/180/f33288f4-d379-4171-8c4e-abe3ece1e2c7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Gallery, Place of Culture and Art in Yeonnam-dong Alley
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   As you walk through the alleys of Yeonnam-dong, you&#39;ll find a bookstore that has disappeared into a faint memory due to the cafes and pubs. It is the bookstore Pinocchio (070-4025-9186), which sells picture books as the first graphic novelty store in Korea that opened a year ago.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Picture book, bookstore Pinocchio that adult and child see together - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/180/e3bfd37d-45fa-47db-80a3-0933aa0127f2.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Picture book, bookstore Pinocchio that adult and child see together
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In a 20㎡ space, looking through essays, illustration books, and handmade fairy tales full of beautiful paintings, you will be moist. There are also valuable books imported from overseas in the bookshelf, where the picture books seen by adults and children are packed together.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A space full of essays and fairy tales with pretty pictures - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/180/93e6ab47-729d-47d3-b599-7be35df22c74.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A space full of essays and fairy tales with pretty pictures
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Tuk Tuk Noodle Thai
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    If you&#39;ve entered the alley in search of a hot place in Yeonnam-dong, you may be disappointed at the plain atmosphere of the entrance to the alley and the simple entrance down to “Tuk-tuk Noodle Thai”. A small alley that runs smoothly is beautiful after long viewing. Tuk Tuk Noodle Thai&#39;s food is also a taste that falls out once you taste it.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Tuk Tuk Noodle Thai&#39;s representative menu, Yang Yang and Yang Tam Kai - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/180/c8120416-2798-4499-b66b-4d1fa42084a8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Tuk Tuk Noodle Thai&#39;s representative menu, Yang Yang and Yang Tam Kai
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Chefs from Issan, northeast of Thailand, say the food is exceptional. That&#39;s why Tuk Tuk Noodle Thai&#39;s food is delicious. The Thai food produced by local chefs from Issan is generous and local style compared to other places, making it especially satisfying for local food lovers. When you enter the dining room, the hammock ceiling, elephant painted walls, and exotic wooden tables create an exotic atmosphere with a unique herbal scent.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Stir-fried noodles with plenty of pork and vegetables, Pad Thai - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/180/2149d30a-7100-4a13-9535-5e69178723c9.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Stir-fried noodles with plenty of pork and vegetables, Pad Thai
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Chicken and papaya salad with curry powder and spices added to the dish, and Yom Tam Khai Yang is a signature menu of Tuktuk Noodle Thai. The crispy fried chicken and sweet and sour sweaty salad are fresh enough to fit any dish.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Crispy fried chicken and papaya salad - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/180/87b4e7cf-a674-4826-a0fe-4928a2af0db8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Crispy fried chicken and papaya salad
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   똠 Yang-Yang, a dish with rich broth, is a taste that combines the sour taste of tomato, lime, and lemongrass, the sweet taste of coconut milk, and the juicy texture of crayfish.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Iced tea enjoyed by Thais - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/180/755d17d2-e2f9-4729-ab07-0224a4f5600a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Iced tea enjoyed by Thais
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In addition, you can taste over 50 different Thai dishes, such as Pad Thai, Punim Pat Pong Curry, and Chek Man Yum.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Entrance to Tuk Tuk Noodle Thai - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/180/86c25a0f-7265-4b19-8aeb-540539e8ea2b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Entrance to Tuk Tuk Noodle Thai
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It is also famous as a regular home for foreigners living in Korea, so reservation is required. In some cases, your reservation may be over a week ago.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;13&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Interior decorated with local Thai ornaments - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/180/d5c50b85-c8d0-42c1-b10b-04d4f6bc1333.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Interior decorated with local Thai ornaments
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Bemucho Cantina&#39;s Mexican Homestyle
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Most restaurants in Yeonnam-dong are open until noon. It is a small store run by one or two people, so there are many things to prepare. “Bemucho Cantina”, with five tables, is decorated with ornaments from Mexico, the owner&#39;s hometown, and is like a pub in Mexico.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The Bemucho Cantina, shortened to the “Besame Mucho Tavern,” is a place where Mexican men and women from Yeonnam-dong meet and cook Mexican home-cooked meals. The owner, who has a strong sense of cooking experience in Mexico, offers fresh and hearty Mexican cuisine by picking local ingredients. It is basic to use fresh lettuce and tomatoes. By making use of the taste of the hometown, they produce exotic and delicious Mexican food.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Bemucho Cantina Spinach Quesadilla and Fried Chicken Tacos - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/180/7b22d3ee-5724-458f-af4d-aa8d78dbc2e4.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Bemucho Cantina Spinach Quesadilla and Fried Chicken Tacos
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Popular menu items include chicken bria, lettuce, corn, onion, paprika, sour cream, and tomato salsa sauce. Fry Chicken Taco, which is perfect for Koreans, tastes delicious with tomato salsa salad by frying the taco with chicken.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Fry Chicken Taco, the main menu of Bemucho Cantina - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/180/e5e6f4a1-20f5-4455-abfa-8186ccde4a98.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Fry Chicken Taco, the main menu of Bemucho Cantina
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The husband takes care of the dishes, and the wife devotes himself to traditional Mexican drinks. Orchata, a traditional rice drink that is seasoned with sugar and cinnamon by grinding rice flour every three or four times, is often sweet and savory. There are many customers on the weekend and there are few tables, so if you make a reservation 30 minutes in advance, the table will be empty.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Cooking is more delicious with traditional Mexican beverages - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/180/75ef2070-dc3c-467c-8bdb-5ffb88cb9195.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Cooking is more delicious with traditional Mexican beverages
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Slow food, Himeji curry rice
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    During lunchtime, a long line of curry pours along the smell of the sweet curry. The representative menu of Himeji is curry rice. The old bicycle shop reminds me of a small home in a Japanese residential area. It is a cozy and comfortable atmosphere where the curry rice is good for indoors.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Curry rice, cooked in a Japanese style with only vegetables such as potatoes, carrots, and broccoli, is familiar to us. The popular curry udon, which is eaten with curry, is also popular. The soy sauce noodles with plenty of ginger aren&#39;t Japanese soba, but the noodles that the owner used to boil with Haejang. The soft noodle goes well with the taste of the soup that opens up inside.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;15&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Himeji reminds me of a small Japanese family home - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/180/7abde3cc-ab28-462f-910a-141ef09b4ba3.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Himeji reminds me of a small Japanese family home
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Curry rice is topped with curry sauce that is boiled and boiled in yellow and wrinkly cooked rice with turmeric. The pieces of bell peppers sprinkled like a decoration are chewed crisp and give a pleasant taste. The scent of pepper goes very well, so I eat a lot of rice by scratching it. I have never learned cooking, no restaurant experience, and no secrets, but like the taste of a mother&#39;s hand, Himeji&#39;s curry boiled for a long time without feeling spared the essence of slow food.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;16&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34; - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/180/47ff4aa8-9e8a-4cd8-97fd-b890c86422a7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Coffee full of heart, coffee shop Lee Sim and coffee libre
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    An alley that is familiar to those visiting Yeonnam-dong is a road park path from Himeji to Bookstore Pinocchio, the back street of Dongjin Market and the next big road and Yeonnam-dong Community Service Center. There is a coffee shop that hopes to stay in Yeonnam-dong for a long time, even if a new cultural space enters the Dongjin Market, where only traces remain, and there are three or four cafes a month.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;5&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;17&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Yeonnam-dong has a coffee shop where you can drink the best coffee - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/180/09db181b-f8ae-4e6c-afe0-490b2988a456.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Yeonnam-dong has a coffee shop where you can drink the best coffee
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   There are two coffee shops in Yeonnam-dong that attract coffee enthusiasts: &#39;Coffee Store Lee Sim&#39; and &#39;Coffee Brivre&#39;. &#39;Issim&#39;, famous for its Turkish coffee, grinds coffee in a traditional way with a tool called &#39;Ibrick&#39;.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;5&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;18&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Coffee shop Lee Sim is crowded with coffee lovers - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/180/581ba8f2-76aa-4ddc-ba71-0c69b48e7658.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Coffee shop Lee Sim is crowded with coffee lovers
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   For the regulars who come to buy long beans, the coffee beans piled up by Subuk and a thick roasting machine make you feel proud of good coffee.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;5&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;19&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Papua New Guinea Kimmel from drip - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/180/af5b7a44-eb82-4fb8-9ae4-3574b24a7f6e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Papua New Guinea Kimmel from drip
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Coffee Libre&#39;s coffee menu that made Yeonnam-dong trouble while on the air with &#39;Good Coffee&#39; is more straightforward than I thought.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;5&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;20&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Drip coffee with owner&#39;s sincerity is more fragrant - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/180/bc64802e-a157-4b3f-bb1e-b7decf864ddc.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Drip coffee with owner&#39;s sincerity is more fragrant
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Four types of brewed coffee, espresso, americano, aeropress or french press.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;5&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;21&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Coffee Libre exterior showing the virtues of simplicity - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/180/4c88c380-23e0-43ae-9d9e-f9575dece156.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Coffee Libre exterior showing the virtues of simplicity
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you buy coffee beans, a cup of coffee is free. Roasting green beans and brewing coffee all day is busy.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;5&#34; id2=&#34;13&#34; id3=&#34;22&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The medicine cabinet Kankan is full of fresh beans. - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/180/9cdcd6a5-57c9-4e0b-b896-95fa5e822ed8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The medicine cabinet Kankan is full of fresh beans.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   We bring in and sell the best green beans selected from the “Cup of Excellence”, which ranks the best among the beans harvested each year.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;5&#34; id2=&#34;15&#34; id3=&#34;23&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Complimentary takeaway coffee with purchase of coffee beans - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/180/8f3e1207-e7d5-4fe0-a304-3b8ade4e0530.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Complimentary takeaway coffee with purchase of coffee beans
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1.Access
     &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    -Go up about 200m on the left hill road from the intersection of Exit 3 of Hongik University Subway Station, turn left at the Gimbap World, and go downhill to the alleyway of Yeonnam-dong.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Restaurants around
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Tuk Tuk Noodle Thai:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Thai food / 37 Yeonhui-ro, Mapo-gu
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://blog.naver.com/tuktuknoodle&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://blog.naver.com/tuktuknoodle
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Bemucho Cantina:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Mexican food / 40 Donggyo-ro 46-gil, Mapo-gu
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.facebook.com/bmuchocantina&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     https://www.facebook.com/bmuchocantina
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Himeji:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Japanese home meal / 198 Seongmisan-ro, Yeonnam-dong, Mapo-gu
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Coffee shop Lee Shim:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Turkish Coffee / 42 Donggyo-ro 46-gil, Mapo-gu
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Coffee Libre:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Drip coffee / 198 Seongmisan-ro, Yeonnam-dong, Mapo-gu
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.coffeelibre.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.coffeelibre.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     3.Accommodation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Just Stay:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    3, Euljiro 40-gil, Jung-gu / 02-2271-2287
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Hotel Manu:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    19 Toegye-ro, Jung-gu / 02-777-0100
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.hotelmanu.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.hotelmanu.com/
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Adrige Hotel:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    3-6, Teheran-ro 28-gil, Gangnam-gu / 02-552-9711
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;red&#34;&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was updated in March 2017, and may be changed later, so please check before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Gyeongui Precinct Street where the train disappeared - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/the-gyeongui-precinct-street-where-the-train-disappeared-166/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 20:16:49 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/the-gyeongui-precinct-street-where-the-train-disappeared-166/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;the-gyeongui-precinct-street-where-the-train-disappeared--166&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Near the exit 6 of Hongik University Station - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/166/75e14d4e-6f45-4cca-a597-053155e8dbde.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Near the exit 6 of Hongik University Station
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   The Gyeongui Precinct Street where the train disappeared
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   There is a way to enjoy a book while walking outside the stuffy interior. It refers to &#39;Gyeongui Seonseo Street&#39;, which is a book-themed theme around Hongik University Station, renowned for its music, art and youth. It&#39;s a good way to sit on a bench and read a book on the upcoming spring day. This is a road where you can enter the booth installed at the Gyeongui Precinct Street and enjoy the good luck of sharing your eyes with the artist you stumbled upon while reading a book. Let&#39;s go on a picnic in the early spring as a book street ..
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Books made in the city of publishing around Hongdae
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The start is exit 6 of Hongik University Station. If you come out of the basement and go back, you will see a sculpture written as Gyeongui Precinct Street. Starting from here, the road leading to the lower section of the Wo Wago Expressway is a respectable street.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   On the road that leads to about 250m, there are bookstores and cultural spaces that display and sell books on various topics. Various events organized by bookstores are held at Gyeongui Seonseo Street. As you walk along the road, you can easily access works representing books and book information. There is a bicycle parking space next to the operation office, so anyone can use it. Toilets are available in the office building on the day of the event. On the other day, you should use the toilet at Hongik University Station.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;There is a bicycle parking space next to the operation office - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/166/7ec84546-24e1-43ae-bcd8-045818c989e8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     There is a bicycle parking space next to the operation office
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Right next to the sculpture of Gyeongui Precinct Street, there is an inscription that briefly introduces this place. Above, you can see an installation that depicts a woman reading and a man playing guitar. It is a work symbolizing the surrounding area of Hongdae, Gyeongui Precinct Street and Music Street. Please note that there is an outdoor publicity bulletin board that informs you of the events and books you are planning at Gyeongui Precinct Street.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A woman reading a book at the entrance of Gyeongui Seonseo Street - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/166/932fcb2e-fdcd-4f7a-a7dd-0f2f09903f34.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A woman reading a book at the entrance of Gyeongui Seonseo Street
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Gyeongui Line refers to the railroad linking Yongsan and Sinuiju in 1906. Even during the Japanese colonial era, it was a major means of transportation between North and South Korea. The train stopped operating for many years in the midst of war and division, but after the 2000 North-South summit, the Gyeongui Line restoration project began, and in 2009, a wide area train from Seoul Station to Munsan Station was opened. At this time, the Yongsan Line section of 6.3km connecting &#39;Yongsan ~ Gajwa&#39; was made underground and made the Gyeongui Line Forest Road on the ground. It was natural for publishers to make books around Hongik University.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Gyeongui Seonseo Street Bookstore where you can meet various books - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/166/a1267f03-1507-4e1c-bb80-84f3edaf75e4.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Gyeongui Seonseo Street Bookstore where you can meet various books
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Books and cultural life at 10 booths
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   There are 10 booths that display, sell, or hold books at Gyeongui Precinct Street. In the booth&#39;s name, all the words &#39;walking&#39; are combined to make this place a place that you can enjoy while walking. In &#39;Space Walk&#39;, meetings with authors, book concerts, and lectures are held. Exhibitions, small gatherings, and workshop experience programs are held at &#39;Future Walk&#39;, &#39;Creative Walk&#39;, and &#39;Cultural Walk&#39;. Some bookstores are run by publishers. You can read or purchase books related to the name of the booth in &#39;Tourism Walk&#39;, &#39;Art Walk&#39;, &#39;Children&#39;s Walk&#39;, &#39;Humanities Walk&#39;, &#39;Literature Walk&#39;, and &#39;Theme Walk&#39;.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Children&#39;s walk is exhibiting &#39;wild animal traces&#39; - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/166/72f74348-e40a-4791-8d77-bdc1ac4452fb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Children&#39;s walk is exhibiting &#39;wild animal traces&#39;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Each bookstore exhibits a variety of things to see or conducts experience programs.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Citizen in love with reading books - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/166/a858cda4-d14a-4401-be31-44049b909309.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Citizen in love with reading books
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Gyeongui Preliminary Street where you can meet authors and books for 312 days
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In space walks, future walks, creative walks, and cultural walks, the concept of &#39;where you can meet the author for 312 days&#39; is held from Tuesday to Sunday except Mondays, which are closed.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Book sculptures on the road
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In addition to the booth, various exhibits on the theme of books are installed outdoors in the Gyeongui Line. After the cultural walk, a book sculpture resembling the shape of a book stuck in a bookshelf is attached to a wall on an outdoor seat. If you are looking at sculptures engraved with the titles of books such as &amp;lt;Considerations from Prison&amp;gt;, &amp;lt;What is History&amp;gt;, and &amp;lt;My Cultural Heritage Interpreter&amp;gt;, I would like to take out a book and read it. There is also a girl statue at the end climbing a ladder to take out a book.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Book sculptures resemble the shape of a book in a bookshelf - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/166/e3345cee-2a6a-4f31-b1e7-755beaba254d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Book sculptures resemble the shape of a book in a bookshelf
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Next is &#39;Text Forest&#39;. This is an area where you can enjoy a short walk by making the letters into a forest shape.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The lights are on in the dark text forest. - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/166/ad82b83f-dcc3-455b-8b8d-5cad7416f423.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The lights are on in the dark text forest.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you go through the forest of text and go down to the Wow Gogga Expressway, it is the famous &#39;Book Street Station&#39;. When the train was on the Gyeongui Line, it was located between Sekyori Station and Sogang Station, making it a book street station. At the bottom, traces of Gyeongui Line railroad tracks and crushed stone are visible. There are a lot of people taking photos to leave memories in the vicinity of Book Street Station, which has been stylishly decorated in mint colors.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;It is the best book street station to take pictures at Gyeongui Seonseo Street - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/166/383da232-7ad0-4afe-8ab6-45df78371de7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     It is the best book street station to take pictures at Gyeongui Seonseo Street
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Opposite Book Street Station is &#39;Wow School Bulletin Board&#39;. Wow Gogachado, the question, &#34;What book do you want to share with you today?&#34; Stops people coming and going. The bulletin board displays a list of books and promotional posters recommended to citizens every month.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;What book do you have with you today? - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/166/81b9cd75-a6a2-483b-aba4-3a7b0bc468ac.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     What book do you have with you today?
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   There are many places to visit while walking around the Gyeongui Precinct Street. After the Wow Gogado Expressway, it is a dash. This is the name given when the train crossing the railroad crossing made the sound of a “click” as the railroad crossing went down.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Observation Street of Darkness - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/166/89a5b84e-3cda-42cf-8fe9-a8c64b82c988.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Observation Street of Darkness
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   At the entrance to Ding Ding Street, there are statues of station officials in front of the breakers and families trying to cross the railroad tracks.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;13&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A statue representing a station attendant and a family trying to cross the street - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/166/ff4eda48-89bc-49e8-b047-195942091d8b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A statue representing a station attendant and a family trying to cross the street
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you turn your feet again and go up to the Wago Garage Road, you will see a wide range of Gyeongui Preemptive Streets. Like a book made on a railroad track, the cultural walk booth seen from above looks like a train. The night view of Gyeongui Seoncheok Street is so beautiful that many people who go out on a date visit it.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;15&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;You can enter the Gyeongui Precinct Street from the side of the road. - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/166/f35b5644-e900-45a5-bff0-5cbab909210d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     You can enter the Gyeongui Precinct Street from the side of the road.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Gyeongui Preemptive Street
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Address: 50-4, Wausan-ro 35-gil, Mapo-gu, Seoul
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Inquiries: 02-324-6200
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Operating hours: 11 am to 8 pm
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Closed: Every Monday
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://gbookst.or.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://gbookst.or.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Restaurants near
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Outside: raw ribs, Anchangsal / 13 Seongmisan-ro, Mapo-gu, Seoul / 02-334-7942
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Tuk-tuk Noodle Thai: Yangyang-myeon / 161-8 Seongmisan-ro, Mapo-gu, Seoul / 070-4407-5130
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://blog.naver.com/tuktuknoodle&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://blog.naver.com/tuktuknoodle
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Coffee and people: Hand drip coffee / 74 Hongik-ro 6-gil, Mapo-gu, Seoul / 02-333-6809
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Rooms
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Petercat Hotel: 21 Baekbeom-ro 2-gil, Mapo-gu, Seoul / 02-717-0722
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Hotel M: 14 Baekbeom-ro 4-gil, Mapo-gu, Seoul / 02-703-8801
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Junhee Bin Hotel: 16 Yanghwa-ro, Mapo-gu, Seoul / 02-332-7771
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://junibinhotel.blog.me/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://junibinhotel.blog.me/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;span style=&#34;color: rgb(213, 0, 0);&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was updated in February 2019, and may be changed later, so please check before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/span&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea - The unique bookstore exhibition where culture blooms in a book</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/the-unique-bookstore-exhibition-where-culture-blooms-in-a-book-65/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 11:44:57 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/the-unique-bookstore-exhibition-where-culture-blooms-in-a-book-65/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;the-unique-bookstore-exhibition-where-culture-blooms-in-a-book--65&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Independent publication beef stew in pamphlet form - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/65/e7794479-5649-4a56-84cd-41abcb2dbd14.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Independent publication beef stew in pamphlet form
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   The unique bookstore exhibition where culture blooms in a book
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   With the development of internet bookstores, it is hard to find bookstores around the house, as it is necessary to go to large bookstores to serve books. However, bookstores that can smell books and taste more than that are attracting people&#39;s attention little by little. Let&#39;s meet a unique bookstore that pursues a different direction than others.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   ‘Bookbook’, have you heard of it? Book by Book
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Sangam-dong Media City Building With forest in front of the road, there is a bar, the alley where rice cakes boil together, and the old bookstore “Bukbaibook” is run by the sister and brother. Although it is bewildering to have a bookstore, it is always captivated by the charms of the Book By Book.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;When you enter the entrance, you meet - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/65/309959bb-9514-4caf-8fdc-cba6faab44eb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     When you enter the entrance, you meet
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Book-bookers are usually regulars when they love books. You can feel it as a space filled with hearts for the owners&#39; books. First of all, I applied vinyl full of analog sensibility to one book so that the book did not wear out like the textbooks wrapped in vinyl in elementary school.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;I have categorized it with interesting naming names, such as ‘The author Holic Jung’. - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/65/f4946433-21ad-4b72-99ee-cca5b6d28902.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     I have categorized it with interesting naming names, such as ‘The author Holic Jung’.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Books on display are beautifully coated with the tails of customers or authors who leave a story or recommendation about the book. There is also a customer reading card that allows you to record the books you read, so you can&#39;t erase the feeling of space for me.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Booktails packed with customers&#39; attention - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/65/b9ac89cd-5003-42b6-9c94-e504ac3f2c4c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Booktails packed with customers&#39; attention
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The reason for the popularity of this place is &#39;book mac&#39;. Only the person who has experienced the comfort of reading typefaces with a glass of cold beer leans on the sofa on one side can know. Not only that. The owner&#39;s seal is also generous. Present free coffee coupons to customers in various ways, including writing a booktail, selling a book, and posting it on social media. Points that can be earned in a variety of ways can be used like cash, from buying coffee to purchasing books to special lectures.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Office workers relax after work - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/65/3f78b636-4682-4a88-b6f7-2cb359ab19aa.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Office workers relax after work
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Bookstores are often transformed into different clothes. First, there is a pop-up store on one side of the bookstore. &#39;SUNDAYJAM&#39;, famous for homemade jam, is now in the store with a cute phrase that &#39;people will buy bread to eat jam&#39;.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sweet SUNDAYJAM - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/65/e4654992-e6c3-4bc2-b9fe-14abadad1d46.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sweet SUNDAYJAM
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In addition, small but well-known concerts and lectures are often held, including “writer lightning” where writers and readers meet and talk. If you&#39;re curious about the schedule, visit the host&#39;s sns. In addition to blogs, Kakao Story, Instagram, and other channels through a variety of information, such as news and schedule information.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sweet SUNDAYJAM - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/65/880cb51f-c0a3-4e4b-b524-6d9eb9e59659.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sweet SUNDAYJAM
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Red bookstore
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you&#39;re a bookworm, you might have heard the podcast ‘Red Bookstore’. In May 2012, Lee Dong-jin, a film critic, started as the main MC, and now has overwhelming No. 1 in the book category. Not only that. Thanks to its popularity, a cafe called &#39;red bookstore&#39; was opened in front of the mecca of young people, Hongdae.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A mailbox that connects with critic Lee Dong-jin - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/65/7020758b-eecc-43a1-ad4b-7250789d7e70.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A mailbox that connects with critic Lee Dong-jin
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Unlike the nose, which responds to the scent of coffee when you open a large, thick door like a hardcover, your eyes respond to a large, red bookshelf. Bookstores are located in the cafe area where you can enjoy coffee and chat, or spend a quiet day reading books.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Small exhibitions are held throughout the cafe - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/65/a328724a-4891-4936-a005-f9d844d2642a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Small exhibitions are held throughout the cafe
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Most of the books in the bookshelves are new books and bestsellers recommended by critic Lee Dong-jin. In addition, there is a bookshelf full of books introduced in the podcast, and red bookstore enthusiasts are tempted to buy and read every book.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Don&#39;t miss out on coffee and desserts - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/65/f64d7f83-2774-48ab-b52e-9dcbcfaa3548.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Don&#39;t miss out on coffee and desserts
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you want to see the critic&#39;s recording of the red bookstore, you can visit the red bookstore. There is a recording booth on the 3rd floor for podcasts on open radio.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Podcast “Red Bookstore” with listeners - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/65/02ce4ea2-d57d-47ac-ab52-71d132f5a0d3.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Podcast “Red Bookstore” with listeners
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Put a story in the red mailbox labeled Dear.DJ on the 2nd and 3rd floors to win the luck read by Lee Dong-jin. The schedule can be found on the official Red Bookstore blog.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;‘이동진, a book I wrote’ - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/65/3d089dbd-1ee2-4ea5-adf1-b51394bb5e27.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     ‘이동진, a book I wrote’
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Only sell limited edition! Your mind
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Independent Publishing. This may be unfamiliar but good for people who like writing and for those who are thirsty for new books. Independent publications are books that are held in someone&#39;s arms through the help of one person from content creation to publication and distribution. Most of them are published at their own expense and do not have many copies. Instead, the preciousness doubles because it is a hard-to-find book. There are some books that aren&#39;t released, so it&#39;s like a limited edition.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Your Mind mascot cat, Morro, sitting on a stand - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/65/761af448-caf0-40cd-820c-b09eec647464.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Your Mind mascot cat, Morro, sitting on a stand
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Your Mind is a bookstore that distributes these independent publications. Unlike other bookstores on the first floor, it is unique because it is easily accessible to people. Even without an elevator, you have to go through hard times. Instead, you will be lucky to meet a book full of author&#39;s devotion.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Your mind feels like attic - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/65/7711f7c2-1300-4329-8b43-f71662a152e0.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Your mind feels like attic
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The height of the floor is quite high, but the interior, which is designed like an attic, a bookshelf, a small stand, and a desk, is warm like my library. It&#39;s warmer because there are cats sitting on the cushions in front of the bar, picking their hairs and nodding them. Independent bookstores are as different from their uniform counterparts as their production. From handbook-sized pamphlets to thin magazines that are published occasionally, their shapes, designs, and content vary. So the fun is more diverse.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Books are placed around like a desk at home - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/65/4cf83e14-e3b0-4f03-9596-4c98f6510e10.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Books are placed around like a desk at home
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The owner is a couple addicted to independent publications. Before becoming a bookstore owner, he is a veteran producer who publishes writing, photographs, and designs by himself, including the award-winning magazine &#34;M&#34;. Various workshops are held to lower entry barriers for those who like to write their own books.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;15&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Visitors looking at books for a long time - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/65/2f447c49-ac84-4e0d-9bfb-616a9d66f0c4.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Visitors looking at books for a long time
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you want to know more about independent publications, you can participate in the annual Unlimited Edition. You can meet independent publishers and producers who have a sense of distance from general promotion through the &#39;Direct Sales Booth&#39;.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;16&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Grooming cutie cat - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/65/63116876-74f3-41dd-bbb2-0320b2f3c13b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Grooming cutie cat
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel info
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Book by Book
     &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    -Address: 26-2 World Cup Buk-ro 44-gil, Mapo-gu, Seoul
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Inquiries: 02-308-0831
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Red bookstore
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Address: 27, Dokmak-ro, Mapo-gu, Seoul
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Inquiries: 02-332-1995
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://redbookcafe.blog.me/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://redbookcafe.blog.me/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Your mind
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Address: 7, Wausan-ro 35-gil, Mapo-gu, Seoul
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Contact: 070-8821-8990
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.your-mind.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.your-mind.com/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Restaurants near
     &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    -Agly Stove: 19, Hongik-ro, Mapo-gu, Seoul / Ricotta Cheese Salad, Steak, Pasta, Pilaf / 02-334-1110
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Tuk Tuk Noodle Thai: 37, Yeonhee-ro, Mapo-gu, Seoul
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://blog.naver.com/tuktuknoodle&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://blog.naver.com/tuktuknoodle
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Simstapas: 48-14 Wausan-ro 29-gil, Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea / Tapas / 02-3141-2386
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Rooms
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Mary Gold Hotel: 112, Yanghwa-ro, Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea 02-332-5656
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.hotelmarigold.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.hotelmarigold.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -24 Guesthouse Sinchon: 9 Sinchon-ro 18-gil, Mapo-gu, Seoul / 02-334-0900
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://sinchon.24guesthouse.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://sinchon.24guesthouse.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Lotte City Hotel Mapo: 109, Mapo-daero, Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea / 02-6009-1000
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was updated in July 2017. It may change afterwards, so please check before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ The information such as text, photos and videos used in this article is copyrighted by Korea Tourism Organization, so unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea - The main character on TV is me, I do it! MBC WORLD Broadcast Theme Park [My Home Trip_Seoul]</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/the-main-character-on-tv-is-me-i-do-it-mbc-world-broadcast-theme-park-my-home-tripseoul-49/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 09:49:18 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/the-main-character-on-tv-is-me-i-do-it-mbc-world-broadcast-theme-park-my-home-tripseoul-49/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;the-main-character-on-tv-is-me-i-do-it-mbc-world-broadcast-theme-park-my-home-tripseoul--49&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;MBC WORLD Broadcast Theme Park Hall of Fame - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/49/008fc096-2806-4111-8c6c-35665f30d835.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    MBC WORLD Broadcast Theme Park Hall of Fame
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   The main character on TV is me, I do it! MBC WORLD Broadcast Theme Park [My Home Trip_Seoul]
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It is a warm Chinese New Year where at least two generations and as many as four generations gather together to multiply happiness. Why don&#39;t you go out on your way home with your family? Seoul prepared for those who are home. Let&#39;s have fun at MBC WORLD broadcasting theme park where the space inside the TV spreads out right in front of you.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Infinite Challenge is in front of my eyes!
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The station I thought only as a vague world becomes my world! MBC WORLD Broadcast Theme Park where you can meet the stars on TV and experience the shooting scene. Everyone who is interested in the broadcasting system and overseas tourists who have visited our country on the Korean wave are experiencing this place.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A place where you can see the history of MBC and broadcasting equipment - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/49/bcc64af7-5517-4a34-a8e5-17898717ba65.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A place where you can see the history of MBC and broadcasting equipment
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   M
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Props used by reporters at the Seoul Olympics - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/49/e0dec737-af9c-4d7c-a2dd-fd2d80366386.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Props used by reporters at the Seoul Olympics
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The best gift for tourists who visited K-Pop stars is the hologram concert. Hallyu stars such as Big Bang and Psy will be captivated when they reach out. You can enjoy a stage that is more dynamic with the effects of directing and effects that are difficult to realize on the general stage.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Children in virtual experiences playing roles in news experience studios - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/49/3b2ab5b2-e934-427a-bfe5-a6b2b0a2b0d7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Children in virtual experiences playing roles in news experience studios
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   How about becoming a member of the 7th infinite challenge? In order to fulfill the mission received at MBC Yeouido&#39;s underground parking lot, he meets a horror special, Creepy Broadcasting Station, in his 360-degree virtual reality. Unexpected tricks lurking everywhere invite you into a creepy horror. In addition, you can go through the corner of the station with an announcer and walk the DMZ with Henry to experience the real experience.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;VR experience to meet 360 degree virtual reality - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/49/0e6733e5-67ef-4426-9fa0-e47037a6e1fe.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     VR experience to meet 360 degree virtual reality
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   There is also a news experience studio that solves the mystery of children dreaming of being broadcasters. Made in a reduced size, you can broadcast yourself as a PD, announcer or weathercaster. There is also an exciting corner where you can learn how to dance to popular singers or receive autographs with greetings from the stars.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;I can receive an autograph by an email with the greeting of the star - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/49/a4ed6ec7-93f9-420d-857f-9d9c6b8a763f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     I can receive an autograph by an email with the greeting of the star
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   GD and I are virtual couples!
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   C zone where G-Dragon can take pictures in the desired pose and make memories of singing with Kim Bum-soo. Located in the lobby of the first floor of the Media Center, it is a lively attraction space where you can join the stars in line with MBC&#39;s hot programs.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Posing with the virtual husband G-Dragon and one, two, three! - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/49/35cc49cc-aa0f-4ffa-8bae-ddd40ba42c1a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Posing with the virtual husband G-Dragon and one, two, three!
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In the augmented reality recording studio of &amp;lt;I am a singer&amp;gt;, the stars of &amp;lt;I am a singer&amp;gt; such as Kim Bum-soo, Yoon Min-su, and Yoon-ha sing and sing with me. On the other hand, in our booth, you can go out with your favorite star and take photos of couples. In addition, King of Mask Singer, I Live Alone, and My Little Television are waiting for visitors.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#39;House alone&#39; Cut with Gangnam! - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/49/70adcfcc-a9ca-4a67-84ac-c753231d105e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     &#39;House alone&#39; Cut with Gangnam!
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Camera B is essential in Building B. The trick art that makes the experience vivid through three-dimensional drawing is made up of popular dramas such as &amp;lt;Infinite Challenge&amp;gt;, &amp;lt;The King of Mask Singers&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;Coffee Prince&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;The Moon of the Sun&amp;gt;.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Augmented Reality recording studio recording duet of “I miss you” - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/49/dd536901-5088-4554-bc15-dfe1be7391d5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Augmented Reality recording studio recording duet of “I miss you”
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   MBC WORLD Broadcast Theme Park where you can experience various aspects of the station with your family. On New Year&#39;s Day, let&#39;s have a good time here instead of chatting with rice cake soup at home. Young nieces will be filled with heart-feeling emotions, and adults will be given a memorable gift.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Zone B with various trick art - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/49/c6b42adb-ebe8-40d1-ad72-93e8d6c56935.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Zone B with various trick art
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   MBC WORLD broadcast theme park is open from 10:00 to 18:00. Admission is available 2 hours before closing. It is closed on New Year&#39;s Day, and online reservation is possible.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Zone B with various trick art - Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/49/77743028-8d5d-4e6c-bacb-90e861f50ad2.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Zone B with various trick art
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel info
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     MBC WORLD Broadcast Theme Park
     &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    -Address: 267 Seongam-ro, Mapo-gu, Seoul
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Inquiries: 02-789-3705
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://mbcworld.imbc.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://mbcworld.imbc.com/
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Restaurants near
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Weiching China: 2F, 402 KGIT, World Cup Buk-ro, Mapo-gu, Seoul / Seafood Nurungjitang, Champon, Crab meat fried rice, Yuringi / 02-6393-1900
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Brotherhood: 396 World Cup Buk-ro, Mapo-gu, Seoul
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Rooms
     &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    -Namkyung Jang Hotel: 11 Yanghwa-ro, Mapo-gu, Seoul 02-333-0071
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Petercat Hotel: 21, Baekbeom-ro 2-gil, Mapo-gu, Seoul, Korea / 02-717-0722
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Junhee Hotel: 16 Yanghwa-ro, Mapo-gu, Seoul 02-332-7771
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://junibinhotel.blog.me/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://junibinhotel.blog.me/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was updated in January 2017 and may change afterwards, so please check before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ The information such as text, photos and videos used in this article is copyrighted by Korea Tourism Organization, so unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>