<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>english on the Korea Tour</title>
    <link>https://codecorea.github.io/tags/english/</link>
    <description>the Korea Tour (english)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2020 01:41:09 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="https://codecorea.github.io/tags/english/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>4.5 billion Asian festivals! Compete for over 3000 medals in 36 events</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/45-billion-asian-festivals-compete-for-over-3000-medals-in-36-events-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2020 01:41:09 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/45-billion-asian-festivals-compete-for-over-3000-medals-in-36-events-3/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-title=&#34;45-billion-asian-festivals-compete-for-over-3000-medals-in-36-events--3&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   4.5 billion Asian festivals! Compete for over 3000 medals in 36 events
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Seo-gu, Incheon, South Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    On September 19, the 17th Incheon Asian Games started with the opening ceremony of Incheon Asiad Main Stadium in Incheon, Korea. 45 Asian countries, including Korea, China, and Japan, compete for over 3000 medals in 36 sports (28 Olympics and 8 Olympics) including basketball, rugby, archery, weightlifting, swimming, canoeing and boxing. The event, which includes all members of the Asian Olympic Council (OCA), including North Korea, will be held for 16 days until October 4. The third Asian Games to be held in Korea is the third after Seoul in 1986 and Busan in 2002. As of 2014, only Thailand (4) and South Korea have hosted more than three Asian Games.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/3/f51aa74f-88fd-4fca-bde2-33eb2ce884be.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Opening ceremony of the 17th Incheon Asian Games
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Departure begins at the opening ceremony of Incheon Asiad Main Stadium on September 19, 2014
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Before looking at the full schedule, let&#39;s take a look at the Incheon Asiad Main Stadium, which was completed for the Incheon Asian Games. It boasts a floor area of 11,620m2 (approximately 34,000 pyeong) and five floors and more than 60,000 seats. The competition started with the opening ceremony of Incheon Asiad Main Stadium. It is held in Incheon and Suwon Gymnasium (Handball), Munhak Park Tae-hwan Swimming Pool (Swimming). If you&#39;re a sports fan, it&#39;s a good idea to check the location of the stadium to create a line.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/3/c9e581e8-e4f6-41dd-a8fb-ef62110ec80d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Opening Ceremony of 2014 Incheon Asian Games
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   A game of over 3000 medals. How should we look? Since we cannot introduce all the schedules, we arranged the schedules focusing on handball, swimming, archery, and gymnastics games loved by Koreans, mainly soccer, baseball, and basketball.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/3/1b3dc930-bf0c-4846-83a5-7d41b46ea238.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Opening Torch Light
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    First of all, the soccer became fun until the 2002 Korea-Japan World Cup. The final will take place at the Literature Stadium on October 2. In the soccer qualifiers held on September 21st, the Korean men&#39;s team beat Laos 2-0 and the women&#39;s team beat Maldives 13-0. Baseball, which started on the 22nd, won 15-0 against Thailand. The semi-finals and finals will take place on the 27th and 28th after the match against Hong Kong on the 24th. All take place at the Literary Baseball Stadium. Basketball is scheduled to play against Jordan at the Samsan World Gymnasium on the 25th. On the 28th, the quarter finals will be held at the Hwaseong Stadium.
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/3/eb17ea63-1dc9-4688-a388-c133d0208a55.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Kim Young-Soo Chairman, Organizing Committee, Asian Games
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Match schedule? It&#39;s not difficult!
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Marine Boy Park Tae-hwan&#39;s swimming game is not to be missed. On the 21st, they won bronze medals in the men&#39;s freestyle 200m final and the men&#39;s freestyle 400m final on the 23rd. The freestyle 100m preliminaries are scheduled for 9 am on the 25th.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Gymnastics Fairy Son Yeon-jae will compete in the rhythmic gymnastics individual qualifiers on October 1 at Namdong Gymnasium. The rhythmic gymnastics consists of four events: ribbon, ball, club and hoop. There was a medal in gymnastics. On the 23rd, Lee Sang-wook won the bronze medal in the Men&#39;s Gymnastics Men&#39;s Final, and Yun Na-rae added another bronze medal in the Women&#39;s Individual Final. On the 24th, Yang Hak-sun will play in the final match of the gymnastics men&#39;s floor exercise, and will play against Li Segwang of North Korea. Gymnastics is the exercise of postponing body movements using machines. Express stability, difficulty, elegance and originality. Men&#39;s sports are Maru, Cheolbong, Parallel Bar, Massage, Ring, Chopping Board, and Women&#39;s Floor, Average Bar, Double Parallel Bar, Chopping Board.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   Traditional medallion archery. The Republic of Korea breathes on a single arrow that cuts off the target. Archery won eight gold medals, including the 2014 Incheon Asian Games and the newly added compound. In the men&#39;s group qualification round (compound) held on the 23rd, Choi Yong-hee (2nd) and Yang Young-ho (5th) played in the men&#39;s individual qualification round. The women&#39;s team also took first place in the Compound Women&#39;s Qualifying Round and Choi Bo-min (1st) and Seok Ji-hyun (2nd) in the individual qualification round. The game is played every day until the 28th.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   Wait here! There are two types of archery: a recurve bow and a compound bow. All archery we have seen in the meantime is recurve. Compound archery hasn&#39;t been an Olympic or Asian competition. However, attention has been increasing as it was adopted as a regular sport since the Incheon Asian Games. What is the difference between the two? As the name implies, the bow structure is different. If the recurve is a traditional bow, the compound is a mechanical bow. The recurve is heavy and sensitive, so the player&#39;s concentration is important. Thinking of the archery field in the meantime makes it easier to understand. Compounds, on the other hand, are lighter and smaller than mechanical arrowhead recurve arrows that are easy to learn for beginners with pulleys and sights.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   In the finals of the badminton men&#39;s team where the opposition hero Lee Yong-dae played on the 23rd, he added a gold medal. The men&#39;s and women&#39;s mixed singles and doubles games will be held until the 29th. In addition, medal competitions will be held in 36 events including judo, shooting, cycling, and land. As of September 24, 2014, South Korea is ranked second overall with 61 medals, including 20 gold, 19 silver and 22 bronze.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/3/ebdd8512-73eb-4cf7-8947-6129feefa004.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Judo Qualification
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Indeed, don&#39;t forget the seal of three children, Vichuon, Barame, and Chumyeon, the mascots of the Incheon Asian Games. The mascot of the convention has influenced the image of the competition. As the name suggests, the eldest son of the Incheon Asian Games, Bichuon, is, as the name suggests, &#39;the messenger of light shining hope on the whole world&#39;. Was taken from. Why don&#39;t you enjoy the festival of autumn, wind, light and wind?
   &lt;br/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/3/2a2aa3f5-899a-41f2-a87a-18c34c533368.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Panoramic view of Literary Park Tae Hwan Swimming Pool
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel info
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Incheon Asiad Main Stadium
      &lt;br/&gt;
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     Address: 806, Bongsu-daero, Seo-gu, Incheon (Yeonhee-dong)
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Contact: 032-458-2014
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.incheon2014ag.org/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.incheon2014ag.org/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Nearby restaurants
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Legend of Noodles Strongest Seafood Jjambbong: 240 Toyoji-ro, Seo-gu / 032-564-7775
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Hamheung Naengmyeon, Seoknam-dong: 87, Seoknam-ro, Seo-gu / 032-583-8445
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    One Chicken Chicken: 11, Wanjeong-ro 202beonan-gil, Seo-gu / 032-564-1151
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://blog.naver.com/10004okdak&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://blog.naver.com/10004okdak
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Accommodation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    SG Tourist Hotel: 13-9, Takok-ro 51beon-gil, Seo-gu / 032-562-0511
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Matte Motel: 33, Sinseok-ro 122beon-gil, Seo-gu / 032-579-9464
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Clio Motel: 42 Wanjeong-ro 117beon-gil, Seo-gu / 032-562-2303
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Written by Lee So-won, Reporter, Korea Smart Tourism Team, Korea Tourism Organization
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was written in September 2014. It may change afterwards, so please check before traveling.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Information such as text, photos, and videos used in this article is copyrighted by Korea Tourism Organization, so unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Incheon Metropolitan City Interpretation Secretary app download link
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=kr.co.csli.asiangameinterpreter&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=kr.co.csli.asiangameinterpreter
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/3/eeac2b92-4178-42f9-ab73-bf104855ac3f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hannam-dong Back Alley Tour</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/hannamdong-back-alley-tour-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2020 01:13:53 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/hannamdong-back-alley-tour-2/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-title=&#34;hannamdong-back-alley-tour--2&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Hannam-dong Back Alley Tour
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Yongsan-gu, Seoul, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &#39;Usadan-ro 10-gil&#39;, once located in Itaewon, once called the Liberation Village, has once again attracted the attention of the world. On the last Saturday of every month, we will visit the 10th Usadan-ro, Hannam-dong, a “warm town” in Seoul, which is being transformed into a forward base for small-business start-up as well as a space for artistic creation for young people.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/2/db8d8fb1-9b2b-4736-8dd1-03416cb1047e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Hannam-dong Back Alley Travel Map
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Hansa-dong&#39;s Usadan-ro 10-gil, a young base for convergence and convergence of youth
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Hansa-dong&#39;s Usadan-ro is less than 900 meters from Bogwang Elementary School to Cheongseok Super. Exit No. 3 of Itaewon Station (Line 6) and go up 100 meters to the &#39;119 Safety Center&#39; alley. Looking up from here, you can see two towers towering towards the sky. &#39;Seoul Central Masjid&#39;. In front of the main entrance to the Islamic Masjid, the road that stretches in the direction of the Han River is Usadan.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/2/92d301ab-faaa-44fc-85a2-22402d18d0d4.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Daytime in the Islamic Central Member of Seoul
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If there were a lot of pear trees and it was called &#39;Itaewon (梨 泰 院)&#39;, &#39;Usadan-ro&#39; came from the record that the altar &#39;Usadan&#39; was built here for the rain festival during Taejong, Joseon Dynasty. Usadan-ro 10-gil is a favorite place for photographers because of the interruption of the redevelopment project. Let&#39;s take a look at what&#39;s going on.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/2/91c8b8c7-1993-4e75-a7f1-f6b2e0faff1a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Seoul Islamic Central Masquerade Night
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It&#39;s hard to find an alley where Shingu is harmonious, like Usadan-ro 10-gil from Seoul.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/2/2fd1ac70-0517-457a-9d4e-fcc534fab798.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Hanjin Barber Shop
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   From old-fashioned barbershops that use firewood as fuel, to radio stations, rice cakes, Pakistani and Turkish restaurants, the traditional market blends together, and the guest house, as well as a jewelry design shop using the latest technology.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/2/87a747bd-03dc-4fcd-82cb-3be73c7eeb49.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     50-year-old Barber Chair at Hanjin Barber Shop
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Walking along this road, there are so many foreigners that I wonder if there are more foreigners than Koreans.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/2/73331760-50c3-4c51-a383-00dc384873b4.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Kebab restaurant transformed in mutt PC room
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Not only the geographical features of Itaewon and Islam mosques, but also because of the old houses, the rent is cheap and the language and living environment are convenient.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/2/66648753-2288-4f52-af40-fc03ce593013.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Kebab restaurant transformed in mutt PC room
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Itaewon&#39;s famous staircase and “Come in store”
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Here is a community that drives young desires and change. The young cultural artists &#39;Usadandan (雩 祀 壇 團)&#39; combines interesting cultural contents and business with the young people traders. Since 2012, young people who live in the area and have business spaces such as workshops have been working together to create local culture and revitalize their business.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/2/89074631-2cd9-4873-a78e-d82c64b2ae56.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Stairs next to the central Islamic mosque where the staircase was held
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The most representative business is the free market called &#39;stair leader&#39;. The staircase, which started on 63 steps next to a mosque last spring, has only 30 to 40 participants, but now it has become one of the representative flea markets in Seoul.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/2/fe6e2a49-6b04-4651-aabd-0d120edb92b0.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Stairs next to the central Islamic mosque where the staircase was held
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The stairs are open from 12 am to 6 am on the last Saturday of every month.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/2/26f24793-2ef4-4e46-b2b1-83ad1528de4e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Street scene of Usadan-ro, where the staircases come in
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It was originally held on 63 steps, less than 3 meters wide. Sellers can be assigned three stairs to sell.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/2/e2f64071-7048-492e-8bc8-c4c8aa4158c0.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Street scene of Usadan-ro, where the staircases come in
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   However, for the safety and convenience of many visitors to the stairs, the place is moved to &#39;Usadan-ro 10-gil&#39;.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/2/f31daf63-65d3-4379-ba6b-a1fd03c5618b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Street scene of Usadan-ro, where the staircases come in
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The &#39;coming shops&#39; with the catch phrase &#39;Come in because it&#39;s hot&#39; on both sides of the street, and the temporary seller table installed in front of it, replace the stairs.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/2/f305ec00-6265-439c-8c77-e9ee79bfc03c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Street scene of Usadan-ro, where the staircases come in
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   One of the popular programs of &#39;Staircase-In Come&#39; is &#39;Tongtong Tour&#39;, which explores local culture.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;14&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/2/1e72010c-a391-4411-a875-f6b4dae030ef.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Plump Tour
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   You will wander through the alley for two hours and hear interesting stories about the history and culture of the area.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;16&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/2/82c1bc0e-a13f-4ac7-9652-67ac103daecd.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Tattoo drawing
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The tour program, which starts at the central mosque and ends at the supermarket, is conducted by young local residents.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;18&#34; id3=&#34;15&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/2/378cd8d8-6ce3-465d-967f-84767d17b873.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Seller&#39;s homemade basil pesto
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   As with any flea market, the most popular places are the gourmet foods, tattoo houses, and portrait shops, where you can draw a portrait in 10 seconds for 10 won.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;20&#34; id3=&#34;16&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/2/3bccc32f-3ad5-4535-9683-ad162c2c5629.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Portrait that draws in 10 seconds for 10 won
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Usadan-ro 10-gil, Itaewon, transforming into an artist studio and cultural spot
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   There are a growing number of shops on Usadan-gil, with unique attractions run by young Soho entrepreneurs and artists.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;17&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/2/778fabd6-e29c-4409-901f-7f2a3e132080.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Suine&#39;s Snack Store Famous for Spicy Chicken Feet
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In particular, the Potato House, which is run by youth traders, sells the popular concept of Potato and Beer.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;18&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/2/143f9e20-441a-4982-92e7-f3c4c89c72e4.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A young merchant who is good at Sabah
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In addition to trendy foods such as meals and snacks for lunch and dinner in the evenings, Sooky&#39;s Snack Shop, a spicy chicken restaurant popular with famous celebrities, is whether it&#39;s a snack bar or a bar. It&#39;s weird.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;19&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/2/4eec62a1-511e-4ac9-9d55-338eb15f279c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sophisticated Yukgaejang
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Chicken shops such as Song Elim Chicken, which are commonly found in the traditional world of &#39;Eating My World&#39;, offer chefs&#39; menus that change every day.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;20&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/2/5fa5bbe3-d449-4399-bfa1-bf08c17daf60.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Deep-fried brown chicken
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   There are a variety of cafes on Usadan-gil.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;21&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/2/94b78112-763f-4d87-82ef-8f9198a9ff69.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     coffee
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   There are cafes in various forms, ranging from “today&#39;s opening” to “entropy” reminiscent of the laws of physics and “champs” reminiscent of boxing films.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;22&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/2/66007a39-cd6e-475e-9c9a-72fa45b8a5e1.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Entropy
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Champ is a roasting café operated by three brothers and made freshly roasted coffee beans to become a favorite coffee shop not only for the elderly, but also for young people. Down. 10 minutes patiently wait.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;14&#34; id3=&#34;23&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/2/8fe2ccd7-1ed0-4aa4-bd5a-c6a7a748621c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Champ Coffee
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &#39;It would have opened today&#39; is a free-spirited cafe that the owner wants to open, but now it is open every day except Sundays.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;16&#34; id3=&#34;24&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/2/09e462ec-1ba5-4599-bb99-9593f3a9805d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     I would have opened today
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   There are designer jewelery shops on both sides of the street, opened by young people with both dexterity and sense.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;18&#34; id3=&#34;25&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/2/2bd2ce59-3bea-49ac-91e3-efaaec60010b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Designer Jewelry Products on Usadan-ro 10-gil
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Young designers and makers work together to produce and display jewelry, bags, and accessories, which are made by giving off artistic artists.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;20&#34; id3=&#34;26&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/2/cd2336dd-d4f5-43c3-b344-b28a4dfdaba9.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Designer Jewelry Products on Usadan-ro 10-gil
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Typical shops include MK Leather Work (handmade leather bracelet), &#39;World I live&#39; (handmade metal workshop), &#39;Mind Mine&#39; (design jewelry), &#39;Luciente&#39; (homemade jewelry), Ampersand (classic leather accessory), &#39; Thy &#39;(leather wallet, wooden glasses, watch),&#39; The 7th Heaven &#39;(silverwork),&#39; J &amp;amp; J Works&#39; (jeans recycling accessory), and Xia&#39;s emotional doll.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;22&#34; id3=&#34;27&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/2/1d245822-f702-4ab7-a9df-d5824122b26d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Designer Jewelry Products on Usadan-ro 10-gil
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   They create beautiful props that bring youth and run experience classes.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;24&#34; id3=&#34;28&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/2/7a6da566-38fc-4702-bad6-435dc47d85d2.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Designer Jewelry Products on Usadan-ro 10-gil
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In addition, &#39;WORKS&#39;, which commissions and sells works produced by independent designers, &#39;Soul Ink&#39;, which combines an art tattoo shop and a graffiti exhibition hall, &#39;Kiss Gallery&#39; with three works and a bench for viewing outside the window, Don&#39;t forget &#39;Art Recipe&#39;.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;26&#34; id3=&#34;29&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/2/812ba1c5-9e77-4a4e-9201-9743dce729ed.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Kiss pics
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   HAUS, a guest house for travelers, not only accepts guests in three rooms with bunk beds, but also serves as a local tourist information center and love room.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;28&#34; id3=&#34;30&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/2/eb9f9725-82c0-45d3-9091-9eda9033a492.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Guest House Haus
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Tiger House has a well-viewed guest house famous for its bare tacos and polar beer.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;30&#34; id3=&#34;31&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/2/c727db53-bb65-4c4f-9166-47ebdf301ac3.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Tiger House
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Usadan-ro 10-gil ending at Dokkaebi Market and Supermarket
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Entering the &#39;Dokkaebi Market&#39;, the road is divided into two parts. On the right side is the &#39;Cheongseok Super&#39;, the end of 10 roads in Usadan-ro. Follow the road on your left to &#39;Supermarket&#39;. &#39;Supermarket&#39; is a three-story building that is used as a café, small gatherings, parties, and dining venues by renovating an existing building.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;32&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/2/3ccd3f11-7392-4210-8ee7-b3c557b84b58.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Supermarket cafe
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &#39;Dokkaebi market&#39; is a traditional market. When the crackdown of the ward office comes, it avoids it like a goblin.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;33&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/2/4fe5ab8a-3166-4cc4-8147-8526216b9f07.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Han River catches a glance at rooftop table
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The characteristic of the shops that entered Usadanro is the creative space that made the old buildings with minimal remodeling. So some shops use old signs to confuse visitors. Nevertheless, due to the affection and passion of young artists and entrepreneurs, Usadan Street, which can turn into an unsafe crime alley, is transformed into an art creative street, and the streets of young people representing Seoul following Hongdae, Garosu-gil, etc. It is transformed into.
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;34&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/2/f23f8b0a-4553-435a-8299-3ad5bb874e86.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Dokebi Market
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   P.S.
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    On the late evening of Wednesday, four days after the staircase-incoming ceremony was held, I went back to the street. It&#39;s nine o&#39;clock, and people are cut off and most shops are closed. English phrases written on the glass window reflecting the appearance of a few young people busy preparing to open a design office called “P.S.” touch the chest. “People all have names. Sometimes, things name people. We name things that already have names. Now, this could be the only name. ” “A person has a name, and sometimes things name a person. Even when there is a name for things, people call it again. ” In addition, I remember the title of poet Lee Kyung-ok&#39;s collection of poetry `` Road makes a way by walking. &#39;&#39; I wonder if we should walk on Usadan Road and call out its name to create the Usadan Street that young people dream of. And wishes.
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel info
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Usadan-ro 10-gil
      &lt;br/&gt;
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     Location: Usadan-ro 10-gil, Yongsan-gu, Seoul-From Islamic Temple (39) to Hannam-dong Dokkebi Market
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Stairway Information: March to October, Last Saturday of every month from 12:00 to 6:00 pm
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Facebook :
    &lt;/font&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.facebook.com/wosadan&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
      https://www.facebook.com/wosadan
     &lt;/font&gt;
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Nearby restaurants
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The Baker&#39;s Table: 244-1, Noksapyeong-daero, Yongsan-gu / 070-7717-3501
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Don Charley: 34, Hoemok-ro, Yongsan-gu / 070-8154-4475
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    El Grecos: 23, Noksapyeong-daero 54-gil, Yongsan-gu / 070-8263-8678
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Accommodation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Hotel Crown Itaewon: 138, Noksapyeong-daero, Yongsan-gu / 02-797-4111
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.hotelcrown.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.hotelcrown.com/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Hamilton Hotel: 179, Itaewon-ro, Yongsan-gu / 02-794-0171
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.hamilton.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.hamilton.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Capital Hotel: 23, Jangmun-ro, Yongsan-gu / 02-6399-2000
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.hotelcapital.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.hotelcapital.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Written and Photographed by Korea Tourism Organization, Korea Smart Tourism Team
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was written in August 2014. It may change afterwards, so please check before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Information such as text, photos, and videos used in this article is copyrighted by Korea Tourism Organization, so unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The main hub of maritime traffic between Japan and China in the Silla era</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/the-main-hub-of-maritime-traffic-between-japan-and-china-in-the-silla-era-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2020 00:47:31 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/the-main-hub-of-maritime-traffic-between-japan-and-china-in-the-silla-era-1/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-title=&#34;the-main-hub-of-maritime-traffic-between-japan-and-china-in-the-silla-era--1&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   The main hub of maritime traffic between Japan and China in the Silla era
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Wando-gun, Jeonnam, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Wando-gun. Is it because the island contains ‘島’. Wando is more popular with his islands than the main island itself. It&#39;s easy to think of Slow City&#39;s Cheongsan-do and Bogil-do, which bears alpine Yun Sun-do. To enter these two islands, you have to board a boat from Wando or the neighboring town of Haenam. As a result, even though they traveled to Wando, it is not uncommon for them to travel to the main island of Wando. That doesn&#39;t mean there&#39;s nothing to see on Wando Island. So today I prepared a round trip to Wando main island.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Crossing Wando Bridge from Haenam and entering Wando land, it is Wando-eup. The Shinji Bridge, which connects Wando-eup and Sinjido, can be reached by road to Sinjido. Aiming to be completed in 2015, all islands including Gogeum, where the construction of the landing bridge is in full swing, as well as birthdays and weekdays, are all islands within the island. In addition to the main island of Wando, I also visited Myeongsasimni Beach, which Shinjido, which was connected by a landing bridge. Myeongsasimni Beach, which is a popular summer vacation destination, boasted a beautiful coast as its name.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/1/392499aa-f98a-490d-8ccd-e149193b486d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     View from Wando Chunghae Ruins (Jangdo)
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Blueprinted ruins of General Jang Bogo
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Let&#39;s look at the map of Wando first. Go straight across the intersection and cross the Wando Bridge to reach the Chungcheong ruins, then turn clockwise in order from Mongdol Beach, Cheonghae Pogu Shooting Site, and Wando Arboretum.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/1/2b321f0c-aa3a-480d-b79e-8fe86ea86159.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Chungcheong ruins with traces of Silla
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Turn right at the three-way street and turn in the reverse order. Of course, it&#39;s free to choose only your favorite.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/1/d18ab737-5b7a-4213-a5a9-cf0d40608a9c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Chungcheong ruins with traces of Silla
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It runs about 10km along the 13th national road from Wando Bridge to reach Jangdo (Janggun Island) where the cleared ruins of Jangbogo, the sea king of Silla era, were found. Now, the wooden bridge can be placed at any time of the day, but in the past it was time to meet the water. Entering Jangdo Cheonghaeji (Historic No. 308), you can see the appearance of Cheonghae at that time by restoring the outer gate and introspection gate.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/1/e96d99b9-1662-4b98-b9c7-8b259d13db53.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Statue of Jang Bo-go at the site of Chung-Jeong&#39;s Ruins
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The Haesin Bulmok-ri Set site, which is located not far from Chungcheong&#39;s ruins, was closed on August 5, 2014 to prevent safety accidents due to the risk of deterioration of facilities.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/1/ca5cd2c6-a9f0-4cb8-9d90-cd3f300a9531.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Jangbogo Memorial Hall
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Here are a few things you need to know to enrich your trip to Wando. Born in Wando, it is a general named Jang Bogo. One thousand years ago, Cheonghae, which seized the East Asian maritime rights from Silla, China, Japan, and Southwest Asia, was located in Wando, and Jangbogo was at the center.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/1/e270b2a6-0ccc-427f-9ab1-d6ca5abb5b8e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Cheonghae Pogu Shooting Site
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Jang Bogo planted a camp in Jangdo to slay pirates and seize the maritime rights. Born of a humble status, but with excellent martial arts, he went to the Tang Dynasty and saw the Tang pirates kidnap and sell the new lines to Nobi.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/1/6511adbd-2ec3-44d7-93a6-021caffd6e9e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Cheonghae Pogu Shooting Site
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   And it will start the trade trade between Japan and Tang. Jang Bogo contributed to Silla&#39;s leadership in maritime trade between Silla, Japan and Tang.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;14&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/1/98aa0d88-4bbc-4093-ab15-03a83db79832.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Cheonghae Pogu Shooting Site
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The traces can be found in the Jangja-ri Daejari area, centered on Jangdo, a cleared historical site. This is because there are ship docks, Saturn and wells. It is the trace of the best international trade port of the 9th century.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;16&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/1/6a956ab4-d8ed-4edd-a6b3-fa0fa3b8a21e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Cheonghaepo-gu Shooting Range
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   How many boats were carried by this waterway that contained a jewel-like island? Leaving behind, she crosses Shinji Bridge and heads for Myeongsasimni.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;18&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/1/21ae06e0-39d0-47f6-bbc6-021bd806bb1c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Cheonghaepo-gu Shooting Range
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Myeongsasimni Beach Fine Sand VS. To mondol including the old quarter
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Myeongsasimni Beach, which means &#39;the sound of sand crying across the streets.&#39; Fine sand shines in the light. With its fine sand and shallow water, it is a popular space for family vacationers. Children dressed in short sleeves are playing in the water. There are plenty of places to take care of accommodation, including pensions, campsites and restaurants. There is also a convenience store near the parking lot, so there is no difficulty to have a neck or snack.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/1/683a07c1-c64b-46af-92dd-98c05fe390ce.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Shinji Myeongsasimni Beach
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    After returning to the main island of Wando again, run south to reach Mongdol Beach Gugyeung (Scenic Spot No. 3). &#39;The stones form nine steps&#39; are filled with mondols of various sizes, ranging from small chestnuts to dinosaurs. It is a viewpoint that is considered a sunset point. Occasionally there are tourists trying to take them against Mondol, which is difficult. A &#39;place in place&#39; campaign is underway.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/1/e5a8b4f4-0702-4760-917d-6e63d03a87ca.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Shinji Myeongsasimni Beach
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    If you have seen the old seasons, head to the Cheonghaepo-gu shooting site. Cheonghae Pogu filming site in the small pogu is a place where the drama &#39;Haesin&#39; and &#39;Jeongjeon&#39;, as well as the recently released &amp;lt;Myeongnyang&amp;gt; were filmed. Buildings such as pier, muzzles, ships and other objectives, buildings, dungeons, military barracks, and watchtowers are located. It is also considered a sunset point. It takes about 40 minutes to see it. If you like movies and dramas, you can add fun to the shooting location. There is also a shop where you can have light food and snacks inside. There is no General Bogo, who may have been here someday, but the waterway he looked at still holds its place.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/1/7ff4c75d-0eb2-491f-810f-007e92cdb573.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Old stone beach
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel info
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Nearby restaurants
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Cheongsil Sashimi Restaurant: Seaside Park-ro, Wando-eup / 061-552-4559
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Miwon Sashimi Restaurant: Seaside Park-ro, Wando-eup / 061-554-2506
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Sora Sashimi Restaurant: Myeongsasimni-gil, Shin-ji, Wando-gun / 061-552-7874
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Accommodation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Benikea Wando Tourist Hotel: Beach Park-ro, Wando-eup / 061-552-3005
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Grand Motel: Gaepo-ri, Wando-eup / 061-554-4965
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Rivera Motel: Wando Park-ro, Wando-eup / 061-554-4455
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Wando XYM Motel: Gunna-ri, Wando-eup / 061-554-5448
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was written in August 2014. It may change afterwards, so please check before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Information such as text, photos, and videos used in this article is copyrighted by Korea Tourism Organization, so unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>