<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Paju-si on Every Corner of Korea</title>
    <link>https://codecorea.github.io/tags/paju-si/</link>
    <description>Every Corner of Korea (Paju-si)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 14:43:51 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="https://codecorea.github.io/tags/paju-si/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A fairy tale day with a garden fairy, Paju First Garden - Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/a-fairy-tale-day-with-a-garden-fairy-paju-first-garden-368/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 14:43:51 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/a-fairy-tale-day-with-a-garden-fairy-paju-first-garden-368/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;a-fairy-tale-day-with-a-garden-fairy-paju-first-garden--368&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34; - Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/368/9bd25b7a-46af-43c7-a3aa-b0a7a8519889.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   A fairy tale day with a garden fairy, Paju First Garden
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you are a busy garden, and the arboretum is cool, pay attention to First Garden. First Garden, located in Paju City, consists of a garden with 23 themes of 5,800 square meters (16,000 pyeong), amusement facilities such as Ainori and the four seasons sledding area, cafes and restaurants, and an experiential learning and wedding hall. . Anyone can spend a day full of rich stories.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It was a city life that seemed to have driven only shallow breaths due to the continuous fine dust warning. As soon as you pass the ticket office, you breathe down into the spacious lawn park. Instead of the center where the colored flowers are planted, they move into a quiet forest. From the Tuscan fountain to the right, from the oak and cherry forest forests to the butterfly gardens where butterflies come from, to the white and mysterious white garden. Twenty-three gardens decorated with each concept create a different atmosphere.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34; - Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/368/252da765-a9cb-4a00-85dd-c5b7721fb7d3.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   When you walk through the alleys of a quiet forest and a small garden, you can see the face flowers that barely crossed your knees and knees. Holding a pair of ferns and ferns, and stretching fingers with the other hand, “Teacher, what is this?” A tumultuous flower that chatters without rest. First Garden is especially visited by children.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34; - Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/368/7775d090-6735-4b6f-9920-1cd14e7b634d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   This is because there are various amusement facilities including various gardens as well as an inori with playground equipment such as a carousel and a viking, a thrilling four-sled sledding range, and a challenge to jump over and balance and climb a lot. If you go around the Inori on a small train, you will be a friend who greets you with your neck and bows in the window. At Hesseng Cultural Center, there is an experience program that allows you to create your own art objects from plants such as wood crafts and plant crafts, so parents with children can spend a day with a good crossing between Ainori and Hessett.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34; - Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/368/de3da10d-ecab-44b5-8b02-53f8dc91f171.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   First Garden is a great destination for couples who want to get the right “life shot” in a romantic atmosphere. The embroidered flowerbed that takes a picture of the Zeus water fountain behind has a European atmosphere with statues of gods from Roman mythology such as Bacchus and Mars. This is a regular photo zone for prospective newlyweds who visit for self-wedding snapshots. If you want to take pictures of tropical forests, visit Green House. It presents a fairy-tale scenery that is so charming that the spirit of the forest pops out even soon. Bird Plaza, located at the edge of the Green House, has cute crosshairs and parrots waiting for tourists. Cross-sister is a name given to mean that if you put 10 birds, you will behave like a sister. If you put a little bit on your palm and wait a few seconds, it will come and tickle your palm.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34; - Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/368/5aea422a-513e-4f31-a886-b36c0c916c85.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Is there a good atmosphere and a delicious restaurant outing? Italian restaurant Piato Gome and Asian restaurant gaze are located at a location where you can see the embroidery flower bed and Ainori at a glance. In particular, Piato Gome, located on the 2nd floor, offers luxurious Italian cuisine prepared by 14 chefs at reasonable prices. The recommended menu is Seafood Tomato Pasta. Tender shrimp and sour sauce bring spring to taste.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34; - Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/368/c4a2a036-19bf-4fe5-bed8-2932ba7a9b9a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;br/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     First Garden
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Address: 260 Topsakgol-gil, Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Inquiries: 031-957-6861
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Fare: Adults 7,000 won on weekdays, 8,000 won on weekends, 6000 won on weekdays for children and local residents, 7000 won on weekends
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;https://korean.visitkorea.or.kr/detail/ms_detail.do?cotid=9290abf1-d7ca-4c1d-a4d1-352ec5693726&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     https://korean.visitkorea.or.kr/detail/ms_detail.do?cotid=9290abf1-d7ca-4c1d-a4d1-352ec5693726
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Restaurants near
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Piato Gomae: Pasta, Steak / 260 Topsakgol-gil, Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do / 031-957-6863
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;https://korean.visitkorea.or.kr/detail/ms_detail.do?cotid=06b1359a-f14c-4406-9cf5-ce571008115a&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     https://korean.visitkorea.or.kr/detail/ms_detail.do?cotid=06b1359a-f14c-4406-9cf5-ce571008115a
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Gaze: Asian fusion cuisine / 260 Topsakgol-gil, Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do / 031-957-6862
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;https://korean.visitkorea.or.kr/detail/ms_detail.do?cotid=80b084f6-66f0-4b6d-b877-a10bc91a644d&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     https://korean.visitkorea.or.kr/detail/ms_detail.do?cotid=80b084f6-66f0-4b6d-b877-a10bc91a644d
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34; style=&#34;font-weight: bold;&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was updated in April 2019, and may be changed later, so please check before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The bow was the final weapon of our nation, the Paju Yeongjipungsi Museum - Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/the-bow-was-the-final-weapon-of-our-nation-the-paju-yeongjipungsi-museum-300/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2020 03:16:37 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/the-bow-was-the-final-weapon-of-our-nation-the-paju-yeongjipungsi-museum-300/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;the-bow-was-the-final-weapon-of-our-nation-the-paju-yeongjipungsi-museum--300&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Yeongjip Palace Museum exterior - Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/300/713404e9-0eab-40c5-bb8d-e78578bb70e3.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Yeongjip Palace Museum exterior
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   The bow was the final weapon of our nation, the Paju Yeongjipungsi Museum
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &#34;It&#39;s a small weapon, but it has a long range, and it&#39;s also a weapon to be wary of.&#34;
   &lt;br/&gt;
   This is an article about our traditional bows expressed in an ancient Chinese book. The power of the palace was so great that one person was able to deal with dozens of people. The movie &amp;lt;The Final Weapon Bow&amp;gt; shows how well our people shot the bow and how frightening and powerful it was as a weapon.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   A bow that cannot be separated from our people. Paju&#39;s Yeongjipungsi Museum is where you can see and learn everything about the bow. Archery refers to arches and poetry, that is, bows and arrows. It is the first archery museum in Korea to show the traditional bows and arrows of Korea and Europe and Asia, as well as Korean traditional bows. Various archaeological artifacts are exhibited, including bows and arrows, crossbows, various tools for archery, and foreign bows.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Small but long range traditional bow
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The road to Yeongjipungsi Museum. My heart flutters. I was wondering what kind of bow was used by our ancestors who were famous for shooting well, and whether there was really an unusual arrow that Jushinta (Ryu Seung-ryong) from Qing Dynasty in the movie &amp;lt;The Final Weapon Bow&amp;gt;.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The Yeongjip Palace Museum, which arrived after the Heyri Art Village, is smaller than expected. There are few exhibits, and the conditions, such as facilities, are rather awkward. Even if it is a private museum, it is difficult to hide the disappointment if you see only the appearance. However, the museum&#39;s true value can only be seen by looking inside. He said, &#34;I can see as much as I know.&#34;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Shingijeon, a high-tech weapon of the Joseon Dynasty - Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/300/bf19477b-87cd-4716-b263-4601c46b9d7f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Shingijeon, a high-tech weapon of the Joseon Dynasty
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   At the Yeongjip Palace Museum, the narrator accompanies and explains in detail how and how to make traditional bows, and the differences from European or Asian bows at eye level. The narrator is full of pride in the traditional bow, and he feels good about his detailed description and sincerity. If you look at the exhibits while listening to explanations, you will be proud of our culture.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Yeongjipungsi Museum Exhibition Hall Landscape - Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/300/094f5050-ff1a-4345-acb3-4f3923c61dc0.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Yeongjipungsi Museum Exhibition Hall Landscape
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Bows are used around the world, but each has its own characteristics. The first European longbow that stands out in the museum is only plausible to see straight, but practical. The British longbow splits the resilient yew tree, which has a short range compared to the fact that it takes a lot of effort to pull the protest. The long bow makes it difficult to carry, making it difficult to shoot on a horse or in the woods. The same goes for the Japanese bow made of bamboo. Made from one material with low elasticity is called simple palace.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Traditional bow with strong elasticity - Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/300/503dbd62-a853-4775-a460-ebed7e1fc60a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Traditional bow with strong elasticity
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Our bow is a composite arch, which is a composite arch that combines various materials with short and resilient length. A buffalo horn was attached to a bamboo or mulberry tree, and the iron wire that acts as a spring was finely chopped, and then around and inside to add elasticity. The curled bow you can see in the exhibition room is our bow. When in use, bend the bow to the opposite side to protest. As a result, it is clearly different from the bow of other countries in resilience. Elasticity is proportional to the bow&#39;s penetration and range. Our bows send arrows from 300 to 400m, while the western bows only reach half of them.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Bows to hold protests and bows to keep normally - Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/300/15fe2796-30fb-43d8-a8ed-3f70113a2f15.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Bows to hold protests and bows to keep normally
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Among the exhibits, Shinkijeon, a gunpowder weapon, also stands out. It is a secret weapon of Joseon that was able to fire 100 arrows at a time. In the Annals of the Joseon Dynasty, it was recorded that Singijeon played a large role in the war to reclaim our land from the Yeojin of the Yalu River and sub-Tuman River in the early Joseon Dynasty. Unfortunately, Shingijeon, which was a cutting-edge science weapon in the 15th century, disappeared with the development of a cannon, a kind of cannon.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Straight western bow - Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/300/56bec2b0-ae12-4e7e-8151-b909c2cc599c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Straight western bow
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Arrowheads of various shapes
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Arrows also come in many varieties. The flesh is made of a straight, light and resilient material, with bamboo, willow or sage. Bamboo-made ones are made from bamboo shoots and willows or sage trees.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Baby flesh and infant - Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/300/02d3be5f-7971-4375-8357-c5d7f1813b20.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Baby flesh and infant
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The arrowheads have a variety of shapes than you think. Shapes can vary from the general shape of a triangle or lozenge to the shape of an axe or a hook. The arrow drawn on the hunting map of the Goguryeo Dance Gun is also unique in appearance.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Tools used to shoot a bow - Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/300/b17a8751-837f-4c1c-9b4c-7d90aef430df.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Tools used to shoot a bow
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   There is also a baby weapon (convenience), a secret weapon of the Joseon Dynasty. It is about 30cm, about half the size of an arrow, and shoots in a bucket called Tong-A, which is divided into half. It is said that even if the baby&#39;s flesh was blown away, Tong-ah remained intact, and even if the enemy tried to reuse the arrow, it did not fit the bow. The speed of the flight is also high, so you will not notice the arrow flying and die.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Various arrowheads - Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/300/92758c7d-3f1a-41e5-8b0d-c800d1c88b62.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Various arrowheads
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Baby flesh also appeared in the movie &amp;lt;The Final Weapon Bow&amp;gt;. A scene emerges when the Qing Dynasty soldiers, who considered Joseon&#39;s bow insignificant, are faced with the death of Nami (Park Hae-il) &#39;s baby.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Various arrowheads - Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/300/9ed08a21-c4cf-4343-87e8-c70dc1fcaa01.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Various arrowheads
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    If you learned about bows and arrows in the showroom, it&#39;s time to go out and pull the bow. You can learn how to shoot a bow and experience shooting a bow at the bow site provided at the Yeongjipung Palace Museum. Unlike archery, which draws protests with the index finger and middle finger, the archery holds the arrow with the thumb and holds it as if wrapped around it. The hand with the bow is also slightly tilted towards the body. The archery lesson is only 5 minutes. It&#39;s that easy and simple. Anyone can learn to shoot for a while and try to shoot.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A bow experience outdoors - Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/300/6add9c29-33a5-4d68-930e-f82dda6cc8c7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A bow experience outdoors
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Heyri Art Village where culture and art come together
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    On the way to and from Yeongjipungsi Museum, stop by Heyri Art Village and you will find a unique architecture that blends city, architecture, nature and life. More than 400 artists, including writers, artists, filmmakers, architects, and musicians, gathered to decorate museums, galleries, galleries, music rooms, cafes, restaurants, bookstores, small theaters, and studios. It is a special space where you can watch exhibits and relax while drinking a cup of tea in a beautifully decorated café.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Heyri Art Village Scenery - Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/300/1654c71a-69eb-4b48-8ea9-c4385542f998.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Heyri Art Village Scenery
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Yeongjip Palace Museum
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Address: 242-5 Beopheung-ri, Tanhyeon-myeon, Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do (168, Gukwonmal-gil)
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Contact: 031-944-6800
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Nearby restaurants
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Jangdan Bean Tofu Village: Seongdong-ri, Tanhyeon-myeon / Sundubu / 031-945-2114
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    500 years Nurungji Baeksuk: Seongdong-ri, Tanhyeon-myeon / Baeksuk chicken / 031-8071-6500
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Miso Art: Gyoha-dong / Miso-jjigae Set / 031-941-3628
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Imjindae House: Imjin-ri, Munsan-eup / Crab Crab, Hwangbok / 031-953-5174
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Rooms
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Hotel Whiz: Seongdong-ri, Tanhyeon-myeon / 031-949-9046
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Boutique Hotel M: Seongdong-ri, Tanhyeon-myeon / 031-949-4226
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Hotel Mirage: Yulgok-ri, Papyeong-myeon / 031-954-0021
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was created in February 2013, and may change later, so be sure to check it before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In search of Sansa, filled with the filial piety of Yeongjo, Bogwangsa Temple in Goryeongsan, Paju - Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/in-search-of-sansa-filled-with-the-filial-piety-of-yeongjo-bogwangsa-temple-in-goryeongsan-paju-199/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 07:26:54 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/in-search-of-sansa-filled-with-the-filial-piety-of-yeongjo-bogwangsa-temple-in-goryeongsan-paju-199/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;in-search-of-sansa-filled-with-the-filial-piety-of-yeongjo-bogwangsa-temple-in-goryeongsan-paju--199&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Bogwangsa Temple Daeungbojeon - Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/199/63407edd-1b46-45cb-a2cb-911a7459c310.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Bogwangsa Temple Daeungbojeon
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   In search of Sansa, filled with the filial piety of Yeongjo, Bogwangsa Temple in Goryeongsan, Paju
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Do not hesitate to select Jeongjo as the wage that Hyoshim was the most powerful among the kings of Joseon. In addition to Jeongjo, there was a person who conveyed his endless love for his mother throughout his reign, which is Yeongjo, his grandfather. Sukbin Choi, who went to the palace in Musuri and climbed to Sookbin, the first item in the list, is the mother of Yeongjo and the main character of the drama &amp;lt;Dongi&amp;gt;. Bogwangsa Temple is a large temple that was extended to the words obtained by the king of the royal family, as the patrol of the Soryeongwon where Sookbin Choi was asleep. Yeongjo&#39;s Hyosim and sights Visit Bogwangsa Temple.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   &#39;Dongyi&#39; Sookbin Choi&#39;s original review, Goryeongsan Bogwangsa Temple
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    There are exceptionally many cemeteries in Paju. It is a comfortable sanctuary for the dead and a place of longing for the living. It&#39;s ugly, but I think I can&#39;t help getting used to it for some reason. The road to Bokwangsa Temple, the original source of the Soryeongwon where Sookbin Choi is asleep, also goes through this path.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Goyang-dong Goyang-dong is bordered by Paju-si. In order to go to Bogwangsa Temple, you have to cross one of the rough heads called Jakbak Pass. The name of the head, which is named because it looks like a head, is quite steep enough to be called “the limit of Paju”.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    As soon as you cross the park, you pass right around Bogwangsa Temple. It is a quiet forest path leading to Bogwangsa Temple. Goryeong Mountain, inhabited by Bogwangsa Temple, is a mountain with a divine name. Bogwangsa Temple was originally called Goryeongsa Temple, but since then it has been changed to Bogwangsa Temple. Bogwangsa Temple is a millennium review that was established by Doseon Guksa in the Unified Silla period as a Buddhist temple. Although it burned during the Korean War and the Imjin War, there are still traces of the royal palace touches and cabinets for Daeungbojeon.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Sukbin Choi was originally Musuri, who served Queen Inhyun, the queen of King Sukjong. In 1689, a major incident occurred in which Queen Inhyeon was destroyed. When Hee-bin Jang became queen, she, who served Queen In-hyun, suffered a lot of trouble. Every day, I prayed for the reinstatement of Queen Inhyeon, but one day, after wearing Sukjong&#39;s Seung Eun, she went through a longing to reach the status of Vienna, the first item in the list. Her son Yeongjo later became King of the 21st Joseon Dynasty following King Sukjong and King Gyeongjong, but she did not become the queen. This is because Sukjong, who feared that Mr. Heebin Jang&#39;s tragedy would be repeated, forbade him to rise from court lady to queen. Was it because of that? During the long reign, Yeongjo tried to win his mother Sukbin Choi as a queen, and upgraded Sukbin&#39;s grave to a land palace and Sukbin grave to a major rank. It was from this time that Bogwangsa became involved with the royal family. Youngjo used Bogwangsa as the patrol of the Major General, and concentrated on Daeungbojeon and Manseru. And at the beginning of each month, I went over the park and met my mother. It seems that Yeongjo lowered his head and called it “the digging head” because it looks like this head is split.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Bogwangsa Temple Daewoongbojeon Dragon Head Horror Decoration - Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/199/6072febb-71fe-460d-a030-c1835948ca92.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Bogwangsa Temple Daewoongbojeon Dragon Head Horror Decoration
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Special things to see in Bogwangsa Temple
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Bogwangsa Temple is a temple filled with Yeongjo&#39;s extreme filial piety. Yeongjo&#39;s filial piety is conveyed by Eosilgak and the juniper tree standing in front of it. Eosilgak is a small cabinet that enshrines Sukbin Choi&#39;s Youngjeong and his status. On the front and side, the roof of the roof is placed in the middle of a square with a private roof.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sukbin Choi&#39;s spirit and spirit - Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/199/64391073-2c2f-4fd2-994b-b69f98955b74.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sukbin Choi&#39;s spirit and spirit
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   A bunch of juniper trees are quite standing in front of them. This juniper tree, which is more than 300 years old, is said to have been planted together when Yeongjo created Eosilgak. Would you have wanted to protect your mother on behalf of yourself in Hanyang? It is as if the general standing wearing a cloak is wearing a cloak.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A 300-year-old juniper tree that is said to have been planted by Yeongjo - Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/199/2ed3ab3f-6e5e-4654-a3f0-5a120f18786d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A 300-year-old juniper tree that is said to have been planted by Yeongjo
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In addition, traces of Yeongjo can be found all over Bogwangsa Temple. Yeongjo largely tackled Boungsa Temple&#39;s Daeungbojeon and Manseru, and engraved his writings on the Daeungbojeon plaque. The hanging signboard of Daeungbojeon is currently known as the handwriting of Yeongjo. Daewoongbojeon and Manseru are the special traces of Yeongjo&#39;s hand, since Yeongjo was in the middle of the Korean War and was not burning during the Korean War.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Daewoongbojeon signboard, known as the handwriting of Yeongjo - Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/199/7533f77c-a60d-4162-81ed-4f45039a9a30.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Daewoongbojeon signboard, known as the handwriting of Yeongjo
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Daewoongbojeon, which sits on a pile of stones, goes well with the mountains of Goryeong Mountain. Bogungsa Temple Daeungbojeon has a unique exterior wall that cannot be found in other temples. In other temples, most of the walls are lime-painted, except for the frontal gates. In Bogwangsa Temple, Daeungbojeon is surrounded by wooden panels that surround the left and right sides. In addition, murals on the 10 panel walls are a mixture of Buddhist paintings and folk paintings.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Banya Yongseon on the wall of Daeungbojeon in Bogwangsa Temple - Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/199/9a92fc14-cf01-4f77-a581-96ac04d5a668.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Banya Yongseon on the wall of Daeungbojeon in Bogwangsa Temple
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   There are three people carrying a large rock in which white dragons and white dragons are sitting, as well as a half-night boat that goes on a trip to the paradise. have. Also noticeable is the white tiger you can often meet in folk paintings. Looking around the mural is like watching a painting exhibition at an art museum.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Elephant painted on the wall of Daeungbojeon, Bogwangsa Temple - Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/199/487b33a7-6d77-4376-805d-6b3266fc4b60.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Elephant painted on the wall of Daeungbojeon, Bogwangsa Temple
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   You can&#39;t miss the wooden fish hanging on the mansuru. Along with Beomjong, Beopgo, and Unpan, the woodenfish is one of the objects used in Buddhist rituals.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;13&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Manseru panoramic view - Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/199/671b51bc-a912-4c33-8f88-0649f3bc3f1c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Manseru panoramic view
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Bokwangsa&#39;s neck is probably the closest one you can see. The head is dragon and the tail is fish. In a word, it seems to be ascending to become a spokesperson for Eoseongseongryong. The faded look is very impressive.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;15&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A long-necked octopus - Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/199/81bac410-23af-4f5a-9059-96be38cd0d17.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A long-necked octopus
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Looking at the garden of dead people
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    In addition to the road from Goyang-dong to Bogwang-sa, there is a road beyond Hyeum-ryeong to Yongmi-ri in Paju. Before the Hui Eum-ryeong, there was a place where Chinese envoys stayed for a day before entering Hanyang, and there was a wall hall where the soldiers of the Ming Dynasty longevity Yi Yeo-song defeated the Japanese army during the Imjin War. Paju Yongmi-ri Maaeui statue and conquering Yeojin and building the 9 northeastern provinces also met the tomb of General Yoon Kwan in the Goryeo period.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Paju Yongmi-ri Maae Fu Statue - Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/199/7936e2ad-c662-4f24-a74c-d35246fad90e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Paju Yongmi-ri Maae Fu Statue
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Standing at the foot of the eastern foot of Yongamsa Temple, the statue of Maae-i Buddha in Yongmi-ri, Paju, is a typical stone statue of the Goryeo Dynasty, which is designated as Treasure No. 93. It is a unique Buddha statue engraved on a huge natural rock wall with a magical technique and made with a separate neck, head, and shade. After moving a large stone and placing it on a natural rock wall, the Buddha&#39;s face was carved. The stone Buddha on the left is a godly figure wearing a round shade and holding a lotus flower. It is a stone Buddha that tells the story of the king&#39;s 13th king, King Seonjong&#39;s concubine, the original shrine of King Seongjong, who gave birth to Wang Yun after giving birth to the request of a high priest.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Neck, head and lampshade were raised on a natural rock - Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/199/31e9b546-73d1-4bd4-840f-ea5c6fa6b1ef.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Neck, head and lampshade were raised on a natural rock
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The two Buddhas close their eyes and look at the Yongmyiri Municipal Park Cemetery across the street. It is a place where the story of the birth of Seokbul is passed down, but now it is as if praying in prayer of the paradise of the dead.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Stone Buddha overlooking the Yongmyiri Municipal Park Cemetery - Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/199/8805be2c-2126-4c9c-ae1e-51d545f4250f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Stone Buddha overlooking the Yongmyiri Municipal Park Cemetery
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p style=&#34;COLOR: #7b1f42&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Bogwangsa Temple
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Address: 87, Bogwang-ro 474beon-gil, Gwangtan-myeon, Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Contact: 031-948-7700,
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.bokwangsa.net&#34; style=&#34;COLOR: #7b1f42&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;보광사 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
     www.bokwangsa.net
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1.Access
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
     * Self-driving
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34; style=&#34;MARGIN-TOP: 0px&#34;&gt;
    Outer Ring Road, Tongil-ro IC → toward Munsan → Turn right at Goyang-dong at Daeja 3-way intersection → Goyang 2nd Bridge → Goyang-dong → Turn right at Provincial Road No. 367 toward Bogwangsa Temple → Yeongbak Pass → Bogwangsa Temple
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34; style=&#34;MARGIN-TOP: 0px&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
     * public transport
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34; style=&#34;MARGIN-TOP: 0px&#34;&gt;
    Take bus 333 from Gupabal Station on Subway Line 3 and get off in front of Bogwangsa Temple
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34; style=&#34;MARGIN-TOP: 0px&#34;&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34; style=&#34;MARGIN-TOP: 0px&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Restaurants around
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Countryside Barley Rice House:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Sanchaejeongsik / 32-22, Bogwang-ro 471beon-gil, Gwangtan-myeon, Paju-si / 031-948-7169
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Barley head:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Barley Rice / 51 Yeongjang-ri, Gwangtan-myeon, Paju-si / 031-948-1012
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Eunjin Restaurant:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Baekban / 36, Gisan-ro, Gwangtan-myeon, Paju-si / 031-948-5241
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     3.Accommodation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Youleisure Town:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    877, Bogwang-ro, Gwangtan-myeon, Paju-si / 031-948-6161
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Palace of Dreams Hotel:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    48, Bogwang-ro 600beon-gil, Gwangtan-myeon, Paju-si / 031-949-5120
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Day Garden Pension:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    264, Jaunseowon-ro, Court-eup, Paju-si / 031-959-8853
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.haruhouse.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.haruhouse.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    ※ The above information was created in January 2014, and may change later, so be sure to check it before you travel.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can you hear me, the miracle of tomorrow ringing in Paju - Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/can-you-hear-me-the-miracle-of-tomorrow-ringing-in-paju-181/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 13:25:23 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/can-you-hear-me-the-miracle-of-tomorrow-ringing-in-paju-181/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;can-you-hear-me-the-miracle-of-tomorrow-ringing-in-paju--181&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;I look forward to the day when the bridge will run to the other side - Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/181/873e23a8-c46a-4258-8998-af88fcaa94be.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    I look forward to the day when the bridge will run to the other side
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Can you hear me, the miracle of tomorrow ringing in Paju
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In June 1950, the ground rang with a loud bombardment. Han River, Imjin River, Gongneung Stream, and Munsan Stream. Paju, which was called “the village on the bank,” had many roads in Oga. Today, 68 years later, Paju, arising from the pain of a dog-legged bridge, is a space that contains happiness, such as a museum and a garden cafe, touching people&#39;s wounds and dreaming of a miracle tomorrow.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Drawing a unification on the broken bridge, Skywalk
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   31 December 1950. The steam locomotive of Gyeongui Line, heading from North to South, was shot at 1020 rounds and stopped at Jangdan Station. The train, which had since been left in the DMZ, was not moved to Imjingak in 2006.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Steam locomotive at Jangdan Station on the Gyeongui Line, where it has been lost (Registered Cultural Property No. 78) - Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/181/7a673583-6f34-452a-b07d-c9d48e6b2a4c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Steam locomotive at Jangdan Station on the Gyeongui Line, where it has been lost (Registered Cultural Property No. 78)
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The Dokgae Bridge, an old railroad line connecting the old Gyeongui Line connecting Uncheon-ri, Munsan-eup, Paju-si and Nosang-ri, Jangdan-myeon, was also destroyed by bombing. From 1953 to 1998 when the Unification Bridge was opened from 1953, when the armistice was restored to allow the captives to return to the armistice, Dokgae Bridge, which was the only channel connecting the north of the civilian ship and Panmunjom, was a symbol of tragedy and pain. .
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Imjingak served as the embankment of South Korea during the Korean War. - Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/181/9ed5ac85-bf9c-46ca-9e3d-e048f61984cb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Imjingak served as the embankment of South Korea during the Korean War.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   How to soothe the wounds that Ching Ching has wound. In December 2016, the dog&#39;s legs were refurbished in hopes that the scab would sit on the wind and hope for the hope to come together. Using the remaining five piers, the skywalk “Tomorrow&#39;s Miracle Sound”, which is 105m long and 5m wide, reproduces the iron bridge before the war. The two-story structure consists of the past, present, and future sections. Anyone can stay on Skywalk located within the civilian access control line without restrictions during the viewing time.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;I hope the miracle will sound again at the Paju Dogak Bridge - Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/181/4055d33f-7da3-4121-bbe5-ca14ae956374.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     I hope the miracle will sound again at the Paju Dogak Bridge
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   As if starting a journey, the past section of the Gyeongui Line steam locomotive carriage can be imagined as an urgent and fierce scene sitting on a chair in a room while viewing a black and white photograph of the situation. At a train station in Seoul, where everything is ruined, is the brother and sister in a black and white photograph looking for food by waving empty cans?
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The past section that lets you start your time journey - Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/181/455a6c63-5d00-43dd-a8d2-8b4c60dec6d7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The past section that lets you start your time journey
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you step outside and step on the rail, you will see the current section of the wooden deck. You can observe the bottom of the bridge through a special glass on the floor.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Looking forward on the second floor of Skywalk, the end of the future section, North Korea can be seen through the red markers that indicate the bullet marks left during the Korean War on the pier and beyond.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The day before, even though the temperature was quite high, it snowed enough to accumulate overnight.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;13&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;I wish tomorrow a miracle will sound - Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/181/d625e224-c100-4416-b1e9-11f7ba572e07.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     I wish tomorrow a miracle will sound
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The sound of a train ringing a horn into the landscape across the river seems to be heard.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;15&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;People who have made many wishes until the tree, which was a seedling, grew - Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/181/5dc9bfee-16fd-4370-85db-94bacc3bbda3.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     People who have made many wishes until the tree, which was a seedling, grew
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Memories of the whole family, Korea Museum of Modern and Contemporary History
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   I visited the Museum of Modern and Contemporary History to learn more about Korea&#39;s modern and contemporary history by looking at the dog&#39;s legs.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Korea Museum of Modern and Contemporary History sent an invitation to time travel - Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/181/c8c5bd5f-3df2-4fd8-99cd-fff0a4f0b03b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Korea Museum of Modern and Contemporary History sent an invitation to time travel
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Korea&#39;s 20th-century culture has undergone exceptional fluctuations. From 1910 to the 40&#39;s when Japan lost control, the 1950s had a painful 6/25 war. &#39;Let&#39;s live well&#39; was from the 1970s to the 1980s, when people from all over the world joined together.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A museum that seems to have moved the entire village as it is. - Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/181/a0baf276-3d90-4e25-ad17-9caf1307a70a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A museum that seems to have moved the entire village as it is.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In hopes of not forgetting those days for a long time, I moved over 70,000 pieces of various visual artifacts collected in 30 years to Heyri Village in 2005.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Difficult times when it was a wish to eat three meals - Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/181/4287f88a-f3a7-4312-b6cf-62f9e3c4cc0a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Difficult times when it was a wish to eat three meals
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The Korean Museum of Modern and Contemporary History, which smells the smell of the past from the entrance, consists of one basement floor and three stories above the ground, and is the first museum of modern and contemporary history in Korea that reproduces a village of different eras for each floor.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Election posters that gathered the hardest - Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/181/4f090c26-2971-4d1b-9f6c-c27e32aca198.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Election posters that gathered the hardest
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   “I was hungry. Yesterday, the only thing I felt hungry the day before was that my only wish was to eat three full meals. ” The grandmother, who walked the streets of the 1960s at Pungmul Hall on the 1st basement floor, looks at the rice bowl and talks to her grandson.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Everyone has a memory that comes to mind - Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/181/5c0e5218-7269-4df8-a72c-af0050820735.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Everyone has a memory that comes to mind
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   One bowl of spicy soup and two bottles of soju in two bowls of Seolleongtang. Even when I summed it all up, it was 990 won. The grandson grabs the hands of a grandmother whose eyes are reddened by the thought of working late into the night and feeding the envelope again to feed her a bite.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;13&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Warmth that can be felt only when delivered by hand - Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/181/30f597ae-9ce2-4248-8f78-f878c0eef61d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Warmth that can be felt only when delivered by hand
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In the age of changing along the stairs, the dressmaker&#39;s dress, the mother&#39;s high school days, and the dad&#39;s school uniform pass. “Uh, I used to eat this often when I was in school! Wow, nice to meet you. ” Laughing flowers bloom on the faces of the Warr family in front of the grocery store. With a lighter mind, he steps toward the nearby 93 Museum.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;15&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Even hard times pass, it becomes a memory to laugh - Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/181/21f31fcf-9a87-40d1-9cbb-d3510f6de05e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Even hard times pass, it becomes a memory to laugh
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Laughing flowers in full bloom with portrait painting and trick art, 93 Museum
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The young man, who was eager to paint, divided his first salary of 3,000 won and bought a picture. The genre that was the cheapest at the time was portrait painting. After 15 years, the pictures were piled up, and there were several rare works that were rarely seen in Korea. The 93 Museum is a collection of over 1,000 pictures and the site of Paju.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Choi Je-woo, the founder of Donghak, learned from textbooks - Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/181/4bb24a3f-0344-4809-afe6-0604133bc909.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Choi Je-woo, the founder of Donghak, learned from textbooks
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The portraits that started to be collected are displayed on the 3rd floor under the theme of &#39;Kwannang&#39;, and the photographs of the famous Joseon parasites, including Choi Hae-woo, the founder of Donghak, greet with intense color as if restored.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;15&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Joseon ’s parasites who were idols - Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/181/49b44113-82f9-4d11-b34b-17317969b8b5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Joseon ’s parasites who were idols
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   You can see not only the past, but also portraits of celebrities such as modern politicians, and some art works of ex-president Chun Doo-hwan are exhibited.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;16&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Portrait of comfort women - Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/181/c3ee4a8d-c638-47f6-8878-c38a8b05b345.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Portrait of comfort women
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   On the 1st and 2nd floors, trick art and novel modern art are exhibited so that you can see them with your own eyes and become part of the painting yourself.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;17&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;It&#39;s only time to make people - Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/181/915f94e4-3fb1-44b1-8a0f-74edcd143c2b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     It&#39;s only time to make people
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Marilyn Monroe, which has a different body weight depending on the angle, and if you&#39;ve been interested in going around in front of the picture you&#39;re wearing and taking off, it&#39;s time to enter the submarine exploration room and enjoy the painting in earnest.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;18&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Mysterious trick art that is part of the picture - Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/181/14c11230-81ad-4d99-b012-4bab26f35d9d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Mysterious trick art that is part of the picture
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   On the breathtaking bridge, posing in the water overlooking the dark water, taking pictures of each other, I don&#39;t know how long it will take. If you have a commentator around you, be sure to hand over the camera. You can enjoy more realistic trick art from the skillful angles accumulated through numerous careers.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;13&#34; id3=&#34;19&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Depending on the angle, it can be expressed more realistically. - Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/181/19649a85-5c85-4f4f-83d6-c28321e838c1.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Depending on the angle, it can be expressed more realistically.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   A sip of coffee in a handsome tree-filled garden, Soulwon
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Time to finish the journey that has crossed the times and spaces. Let&#39;s settle down in a quiet garden café that sometimes filled our hearts. It takes about 10 minutes by car to reach Soulwon. Soulwon is made of bonsai, garden stones, and garden water collected for 20 years in hopes that the energy of purification given by plants will be transmitted and become a “garden full of laughter”.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;20&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Soulwon in a quiet landscape - Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/181/e05f961e-0a58-4279-9380-60f0c6a32a48.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Soulwon in a quiet landscape
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Before looking around the garden, you lay down your heart in the rough comfort of a stone tower built with basalt. It is still chilly. Even in the season when spring is hard to find its place, bonsai in the greenhouse will soothe the sadness. As the day unfolds, the artificial waterfall also emits a stream of water.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;21&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The water of an artificial waterfall marks the beginning of spring - Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/181/791d90de-1292-4374-84f9-594db867bc04.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The water of an artificial waterfall marks the beginning of spring
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you combine the garden trees and bonsai here, you will reach 25,000.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;22&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Inside a warm greenhouse full of green - Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/181/e5b26385-aa5f-48ee-8afd-b6fa4449d0a4.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Inside a warm greenhouse full of green
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Trees that have seen their history and countless people coming and going around them in the same place for a long time. Chop the whole heart into trouble and hang it at the end of the peacock leaves, filling the empty heart with oak leaves.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;23&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The integrity of the tree makes fruit - Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/181/0329c97b-4837-4b38-8094-dd5d4c6f2cb6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The integrity of the tree makes fruit
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   As he listens to the thoughts of finding himself, the tree absorbs all those tears and embraces secrets to wipe out young leaves every year.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;24&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;minute - Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/181/0cd01ec2-c840-4f76-991a-812abb9a0dab.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     minute
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Dog Bridge Skywalk
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Address: 1400-5, Majeong-ri, Munsan-eup, Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Inquiries: 031-956-8305
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Hours of use: November to February 09:00 to 17:00, March to October 09:00 to 18:00
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Recess day: Monday
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Admission: Adults 2000 won, children (under 12 years old) 1000 won
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;https://ggtour.or.kr/blog/tour_theme/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     https://ggtour.or.kr/blog/tour_theme/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Museum of Modern and Contemporary Korea
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Address: 59-85, Heyri Village-gil, Tanhyeon-myeon, Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Inquiries: 031-957-1125, 0240
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Use time: 09: 30 ~ 18: 00
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Closed: Mondays (no closing during summer vacation, normal if Monday is a national holiday or holiday)
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Admission: Adults 7,000 won, children 5000 won, national merit / military / disabled people / guardians 5000 won
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.kmhm.or.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.kmhm.or.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     93 Museum
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Address: G-31 Heyri Art Village, 59-58, Heyri Village-gil, Tanhyeon-myeon, Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Inquiries: 031-948-6677
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Hours of use: November to February 09:00 to 17:00, March to October 09:00 to 18:00
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Recess day: Monday
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Admission: Adults 8,000 won, youths 7000 won (may change depending on the period)
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.galleryfocus.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.galleryfocus.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Soulwon
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Address: 299-3, Chukhyeon-ri, Tanhyeon-myeon, Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Inquiries: 031-945-4261
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Hours: March 09: 30 ~ 18: 30, April ~ October 09: 30 ~ 19: 00, November 10: 00 ~ 17: 30, December ~ February 10: 00 ~ 17: 00
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Recess day: Monday
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Admission fee: 5000 won for adults, 3000 won for youths (8 to 18 years old)
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://soulone.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://soulone.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Restaurants near
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Unification Village Jangdan Kong Village: Jangdan Kong Restaurant / 64 Tongilchon-gil, Gunnae-myeon, Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do / 031-954-3443
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Cozy house: Pyongyang food, gondebap, soy sauce crab set meal / 82-112, Heyri village road, Tanhyeon-myeon, Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do / 031-948-3440
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Imjin Gangpokpojang: Trout society, sturgeon society / 550 Cheongsong-ro, Papyeong-myeon, Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do / 031-959-2222
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Rooms
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Hanok Experience Village Salimchae: 126-20, 327beon-gil, Sorajiro, Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do / 010-8747-9891
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://slc98.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://slc98.com/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Nostalja Hotel: 34 Seongdong-ro, Tanhyeon-myeon, Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do / 031-949-9525
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Hills Hotel: 20-41 Seongdong-ro, Tanhyeon-myeon, Paju-si, Gyeonggi-do / 031-945-9800
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.hillshotel.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.hillshotel.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was created in March 2018, and may be changed later, so please check before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>