<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bonghwa-gun on Every Corner of Korea</title>
    <link>https://codecorea.github.io/tags/bonghwa-gun/</link>
    <description>Every Corner of Korea (Bonghwa-gun)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2020 03:16:34 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="https://codecorea.github.io/tags/bonghwa-gun/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Bonghwa Gumadong Valley, a primitive valley that steals late heat - Bonghwa-gun, Gyeongbuk, South Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/bonghwa-gumadong-valley-a-primitive-valley-that-steals-late-heat-297/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2020 03:16:34 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/bonghwa-gumadong-valley-a-primitive-valley-that-steals-late-heat-297/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Bonghwa-gun, Gyeongbuk, South Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;bonghwa-gumadong-valley-a-primitive-valley-that-steals-late-heat--297&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;It is good to play when the water is clean after rain. - Bonghwa-gun, Gyeongbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/297/69e4a10c-6e24-40f4-b82f-01232e28989b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    It is good to play when the water is clean after rain.
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Bonghwa Gumadong Valley, a primitive valley that steals late heat
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Bonghwa-gun, Gyeongbuk, South Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The water flowing from the foot of Taebaek Mountain made the Guma-dong Valley. The valley extends for over 10 km between dense forests, and above it is a valley of birds and mountain beasts that cannot be carried by humans. When you walk with a stream of water next to you, you feel like jumping in quickly.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   From the beginning of the valley to the Kuma Red Lodging
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The valley is not unusual from the head. The path that a car can barely pass through, and the cross section of a carved mountain foot is as weird as the monster land in the movie The Lord of the Rings. The left side of the road is a cliff that goes directly to the valley. Water flows from the cut section of the mountain.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It is 7 to 8 km from Kuma Red Lodging Bed and Breakfast. So far, there is no way to go down the valley. From the end of the mountain, people smell. The houses that entered the valley did not form a village and sat down one or two sparsely. A house was laid in the middle of a sloped field.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The right side of the road is an incision and the left side is cliff - Bonghwa-gun, Gyeongbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/297/5e002a36-5c81-401a-80c8-5346c401b9de.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The right side of the road is an incision and the left side is cliff
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Aside from the cliffs that fall into the valley, they are all mountains and cliffs. The word ‘Chapguksan’ fits perfectly into this valley. As you go upstream, you become accustomed to the breath of the valley, from the eyes, ears, nose and pores. One cover seat I met on the road tells me that there was an elementary school here. The “Goseon National School”, which opened in 1962 in the valley, was closed on March 1, 1992. Over 30 years, 140 graduated from the school.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The Gumadong Valley flows between high mountain forests - Bonghwa-gun, Gyeongbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/297/a52cfd3e-d1b2-48ab-85ed-9c03383ff74a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The Gumadong Valley flows between high mountain forests
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The mountains are high and the valleys are deep, so darkness comes early. The place where the tree covered the sky is dim. The fresh scent of the forest and the refreshing energy of the valley full of negative ions surround the whole body. After walking while enjoying the feeling, I can see the way down to the valley. Soak your feet in the valley for a moment. My feet are sore because it is out of the sun.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   Cool off the sweat and walk again. When I arrive at the hostel, people are quite visible. Unload your luggage and rush to the valley where the darkness falls.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A rock cliff is hiding in the wooded forest next to the valley. - Bonghwa-gun, Gyeongbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/297/aae2af5d-9d55-4c68-9629-e4be1b3f51e2.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A rock cliff is hiding in the wooded forest next to the valley.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Gumadong Valley Night
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Even at the end of summer, it is hot during the day. In the midday heat, the raindrops that come and go are added, and the body is full of sweat and humid energy. I changed to the shorts I prepared and went straight into the valley.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The valley over 10km shows various shapes - Bonghwa-gun, Gyeongbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/297/f1b43f95-7989-4c0f-85b2-27b2134773d0.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The valley over 10km shows various shapes
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   There is a valley right in front of the guest house. Large and small pebbles formed a stone field. The stream flows creating a stream, and the sound is refreshing. It&#39;s cool just by listening. Go into the water, lay a stone pillow, and lie down. The whole body flutters in the water passing through the back stem. The sound of the water passing through the earlobe is clear. The wind that has passed through the forest touches the body, so the goosebumps rise. The heat does not go away, but it takes a chill. The heat of sweat and moisture blends with the heat, and the feeling of sticking to the body flies away. It is not long and comes out of the water.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   Since it is a deep mountain valley, darkness comes early. The lights are lit one by one in the guest house and the smell of cooking spreads over the valley.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The valley water breaks white over a small beam - Bonghwa-gun, Gyeongbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/297/4615becf-2183-4323-8763-17afe1654000.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The valley water breaks white over a small beam
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Prepare dinner with a clear and refreshing body and mind. Boil samgyetang with chicken from Hyundong. You have to cook for an hour, but during that time, you cheat the market with ramen.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   Suddenly the valley was full of darkness. It is the world of people until the light of the street light in front of the guest house. The valley and forest beyond the light is a world of beasts. Sometimes the sound of a beast is heard in the dark forest. As the wind gets stronger, the sound of wind passing through the forest is ugly. The sound of the valley water is also louder than during the day. At first, these sounds were strange and anxious, but as I got used to it, I felt comfortable.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Small stones gathered to form a stone field - Bonghwa-gun, Gyeongbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/297/21faadbb-0183-4a56-90d4-7db2c35810bc.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Small stones gathered to form a stone field
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The sound of nature embraces a guest house in the darkness of ebon. The light of rest comes out from the window of the guest house seen from the valley of the night. The night in the Gumadong Valley is getting so deep.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The cloud resembled a wave breaking in the creek. - Bonghwa-gun, Gyeongbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/297/3bb5d44b-6c09-483c-8136-8a56cc0eb663.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The cloud resembled a wave breaking in the creek.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Guma-dong Valley, which flourished as a gold mine
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    I eat late the next morning and go out. The lodging is in the middle of the valley, so I saw only half of the valley yesterday. Go further up the valley from the hostel.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Water flows over the small beams created to cross the valley. The water falling from the beam breaks white. The light color and bright sound shining in pale jade are cool.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   A tree that looks like a Christmas tree forms a forest, and water fogs bloom in the valley flowing between the forests. It is the best view of the Guma-dong Valley promenade from yesterday to today. I just can&#39;t pass, and I go into the landscape. Soak your feet in the valley and sit for a while.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   As you go up the water, you meet a wide field. It may be the widest land in the Gumadong Valley. A villager who met there tells an old story of the Gumadong Valley.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;There is a farmhouse right next to the valley and a field spreads out. - Bonghwa-gun, Gyeongbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/297/d12f44b3-10c7-4e1b-a544-7d9566ede4de.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     There is a farmhouse right next to the valley and a field spreads out.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It is said that during the Japanese colonial period, gold was mined from the gold mine and trees were cut from the dense forest. It was the site of resource looting. It is said that about 150 households lived along the valley in the height. There were one elementary school each downstream and upstream of the valley. Since there are a lot of people, there were three main curtains. It is said that the vicinity of the elementary school that became closed school and the site of Norumok Serumam were famous streets.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The sound of flowing water is good - Bonghwa-gun, Gyeongbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/297/f03fa43f-ff7b-4535-915b-bf84761e81fd.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The sound of flowing water is good
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   After walking through the old story of the Gumadong Valley, my step back to the hostel is slow. Small life in valleys and forests that were invisible when coming, comes into sight. Butterflies flutter in the grass, and bees fly on flowers that bloom on cliffs. Like a step, my mind is relaxed.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Mist rises from the valley - Bonghwa-gun, Gyeongbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/297/d7b73861-775c-426a-862e-083614a9b26b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Mist rises from the valley
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Guma-dong Valley
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Address: Goseon-ri, Socheon-myeon, Bonghwa-gun, Gyeongsangbuk-do
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Inquiries: 054-679-6312 (Bonghwa-gun Cultural Tourism Division)
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Restaurants near
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Bonghwa Korean Medicine Woo Plaza: Hanyakwoo (Hanwoo) / 47, Agriculture-in-gil, Bongseong-myeon, Bonghwa-gun, Gyeongsangbuk-do / 054-674-3400
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.bhhywoo.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.bhhywoo.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Yongdu Restaurant: Songi cuisine / 526-4, Dadeok-ro, Bongseong-myeon, Bonghwa-gun, Gyeongsangbuk-do / 054-673-3144
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Chogajip Restaurant: Chueotang / 843, Dadeok-ro, Bongseong-myeon, Bonghwa-gun, Gyeongsangbuk-do / 054-673-9981
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Rooms
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Kuma Hwangto Bed and Breakfast: 521-1 Gosun-ri, Socheon-myeon, Bonghwa-gun, Gyeongsangbuk-do / 054-672-7367
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Mujin Park: 220 Cheongok-ro, Socheon-myeon, Bonghwa-gun, Gyeongsangbuk-do / 054-673-9988
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Kwon Jin House (Seongam Old House): 39, Nakcheondang-gil, Chunyang-myeon, Bonghwa-gun, Gyeongsangbuk-do, 054-672-6118, 010-9016-3201
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://blog.naver.com/kwonjinsa&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://blog.naver.com/kwonjinsa
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was created in August 2013, and may change later, so be sure to check it before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The scent of pine needles ~ Bonghwa Bongseong Pork Charcoal Fire Complex - Bonghwa-gun, Gyeongbuk, South Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/the-scent-of-pine-needles-bonghwa-bongseong-pork-charcoal-fire-complex-270/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 13:25:44 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/the-scent-of-pine-needles-bonghwa-bongseong-pork-charcoal-fire-complex-270/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Bonghwa-gun, Gyeongbuk, South Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;the-scent-of-pine-needles-bonghwa-bongseong-pork-charcoal-fire-complex--270&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Charcoal-grilled Bongseong pork - Bonghwa-gun, Gyeongbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/270/d2f96e6e-57ca-4c06-9d53-bdd346c5bbe3.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Charcoal-grilled Bongseong pork
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   The scent of pine needles ~ Bonghwa Bongseong Pork Charcoal Fire Complex
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Bonghwa-gun, Gyeongbuk, South Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    There is a road to Cheongnyangsan Mountain, a place to stop and set foot. Bongseong Pork Charcoal Fire Complex is where the smell of fragrant bulgogi catches your feet. Unlike other regions, it is a place for roasting pork charcoal using pine charcoal and pine needles. A dish of pork charcoal grill with a long history is quite a bit airy! How about climbing to Cheongnyangsan Mountain with this energy? If you embrace the charcoal-grilled pork and even the autumn leaves of Cheongnyangsan Mountain, the fun of traveling to Bonghwa will double.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Bongseong&#39;s Taste of 1000 Years of History
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    From Bonghwa-eup to Cheongnyangsan Mountain, you must go through the locations of Bongseong-myeon and Myeongho-myeon. Around the Bongseong-myeon, the gentle fragrance stops the foot. In particular, by the time the navel clock makes a loud noise, white smoke rises from the chimneys of Bongseong-myeon, like smoke from Bonghwa-myeon, and the fragrant smell of mouth-watering punctures the nose. This is the scent of pork charcoal grilled from Bongseong Pork Charcoal Fire Complex.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Charcoal-grilled Bongseong pork has a long history. Looking at the history of Bongseong-myeon first, it was called Bongseong-hyeon during the Goryeo Dynasty and was renamed Bonghwa-hyeon during the Goryeo Dynasty. In the Bongseong Pork Charcoal Fire Complex, the old Bonghwahyeon Gwanah building, Bongseoru (Gyeongsangbuk-do Cultural Properties No. 418) remains, so you can see the old traces.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Charcoal-grilled Bongseong pork charcoal fire complex - Bonghwa-gun, Gyeongbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/270/8ce5b688-b029-4385-9777-ba878a8cb211.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Charcoal-grilled Bongseong pork charcoal fire complex
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   From the old days, there was a marketplace where people and products gathered in a major town. In Bongseong, there was also a long history of bon-growth since Goryeo Dynasty. In particular, the right market was large. The history of Bongseong Pork&#39;s charcoal-grilled fire begins with Bongseong. Pork charcoal grilled food is served as a meal or as a snack to people from all over the world. Since the Goryeo Dynasty, it has been passed down to the present, boasting a history of over a thousand years. It is known that the “Macchik” eaten by the people of the Mack people considered to be our ancestors, and “Seolya”, which is said to have come from Mongolia during the Goryeo Dynasty, is known as the origin of Korean bulgogi. Wasn&#39;t Bongseong Pork charcoal grilling a tradition or a shoulder-to-shoulder traditional food?
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Bongseong Pork Charcoal Fire Complex - Bonghwa-gun, Gyeongbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/270/8a35b0fd-5d21-44d9-bffa-70f4c0b68322.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Bongseong Pork Charcoal Fire Complex
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Charcoal-grilled pork with pine cone
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The restaurants specializing in charcoal-grilled pork located in Bongseong-myeon are designated as a local food complex in Bonghwa-gun. Cheongbong, Solbong, Duribong, and Bongseong Siksik Restaurant, as well as Hopejeong, which is known as the origin of pork charcoal grilling, are growing along the road connecting Bongseong-myeon and Myeongho-myeon.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Grilling pork on charcoal - Bonghwa-gun, Gyeongbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/270/6c9d7dd9-4509-459a-a942-6a665518f174.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Grilling pork on charcoal
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Now it&#39;s time to taste the charcoal-grilled Bongseong pork with a history of 1000 years. When you step into the restaurant following the fragrant and fragrant aroma that rises through the chimney, the busiest place is the charcoal fire in the kitchen that roasts pork. The dark aura of charcoal fire shines brightly in the dark charcoal kiln.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Pine needles used for roasting charcoal - Bonghwa-gun, Gyeongbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/270/d888e655-b0bf-40f4-becc-53cfd45fc882.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Pine needles used for roasting charcoal
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   When a grill with meat is placed on top of a charcoal fire, a full-scale dwarf spreads. When the charcoal fires with the sound of meat being grilled, it is like watching a fireworks display. Just looking at it makes me feel full and filled with hungry stomach.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Add pine needles and bake again - Bonghwa-gun, Gyeongbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/270/03063645-c356-4bed-8e12-cf99ec85a1db.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Add pine needles and bake again
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Charcoal fires use pine charcoal rather than oak. This is because the charcoal fire is not strong and soft, and it is well lit. Pork mainly uses sows that are less vulnerable. Put the thickly sliced meat on the grill, salt it and bake it over and over again.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Charcoal-grilled pork served on a plate with pine needles - Bonghwa-gun, Gyeongbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/270/0958d341-7717-47e5-a87d-7aad3bac259e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Charcoal-grilled pork served on a plate with pine needles
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It is important to grill the meat so that it does not burn. Although it seems to be flipped over by eyes, the skill of baking moderately is the master&#39;s skill derived from many years of experience. As the meat matures, the oil falls flat under the grill, and the white smoke that burns the oil goes out on a high chimney.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Charcoal-grilled pork served on a plate with pine needles - Bonghwa-gun, Gyeongbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/270/d620c6d9-8bc4-46af-a8d8-09b28e9c9b34.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Charcoal-grilled pork served on a plate with pine needles
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   When the meat is properly cooked, the unique recipe of Bongseong Pork Charcoal Grill is added. It is a pine needle. The scent of pine needles removes the smell of meat and makes the taste lighter. It is said that the terpene ingredient from pine needles is absorbed into meat and is also good for preventing adult diseases. Put the pine needles on the meat and bake it again, then put the pine needles on the plate again, put the meat on it, and immediately go out to the top. It&#39;s baked in the kitchen right away, so it tastes as good as it&#39;s grilled on a charcoal fire.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Char-grilled and seasoned - Bonghwa-gun, Gyeongbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/270/461951e0-a76c-457b-83c0-186f105aa1df.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Char-grilled and seasoned
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Charcoal-grilled Bongseong Pork is a food eaten with taste and aroma. It tastes good, but it combines charcoal and sol flavors to stimulate the mouth. It seems that you can feel the history of the millennium that has been passed since the Goryeo Dynasty.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;14&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Hey... - Bonghwa-gun, Gyeongbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/270/c7fcc10d-553a-463e-8a4d-4c8c1cb8b91a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Hey...
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Cheongnyang Mountain and sky bridge in autumn
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   From Bongseong Pork Charcoal Fire Complex, take Route 35 to Andong, passing Myeongho-myeon to reach Cheongnyangsan. It was the place where Kim Chi-won, who was superior to Choi Chi-won of the Silla language and Wang Hee-ji of China, did the capital and where King Kong Gongmin escaped the difficulties of Hong Geon-jeok. During the Joseon Dynasty, Toegye Lee Hwang studied at Cheongnyangjeongsa Temple. Mr. Se-Boo Joo toured Cheongnyang Mountain and named it &#39;Yukyukbong&#39;. It is a mountain that often contains 12 generations, 8 oysters, and 4 tablets. In autumn, the autumn leaves in harmony with the rock formations are the best part.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    There are several courses to climb to Cheongnyangsan Mountain. The course that climbs Cheongnyangsa Temple and the rear thread head and the course that climbs through Eungjinjeon and Gimsaenggul at the standing are the most. The course through Cheongnyangsa and the back thread can be reached the fastest, but the slope is steep. On the other hand, the standing course is a course where you can enjoy the autumn leaves of Cheongnyangsan Mountain and enjoy the hidden history. The standing course can be climbed almost effortlessly, except for the entrance to the entrance, the road to Eungjinjeon, and the road from Gimsaenggul to Jasobong.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    When you pass a steep dirt road, the fallen leaves quickly turn into a lush trail. It&#39;s a steep road with shortness of breath. The beauty of the yellow and red maple leaves seems to hold my breath once again. If you climb about 10 minutes, you will get a forked road. One side is the way to Cheongnyangsa Temple and the other to Eungjinjeon. The road to Eungjinjeon is also a difficult climb. However, if you take a step by step, you will be rewarded properly as it is difficult. Eungjinjeon, standing like hanging on Cheongnyangsan Mountain, is wrapped in autumn leaves.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    In particular, you can see the scenery of Cheongnyangsan Mountain near Eoungdae and Chongmyeongsu after passing Eungjinjeon. Cheongnyangsa Temple and Cheongnyangsan Mountain unfold like a watercolor in Eoungdae, and the three-story stone pagoda and Yeonhwabong Peak of Cheongnyangsa Temple protruding from the path of Gimsaenggul.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Feast of autumn leaves seen around Kim Saeng-gul - Bonghwa-gun, Gyeongbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/270/53280448-d4e6-4e21-847e-281db9f2c795.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Feast of autumn leaves seen around Kim Saeng-gul
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    It is the most difficult course from Kim Saeng-gul to Jasobong. If you climb the ridge in less than an hour, it is a long time to reach the sky bridge. The light green sky bridge is a 90m long bridge that connects the Jaranbong and Seonhakbong of Cheongnyangsan Mountain. It is made in the form of a suspension bridge, but it is a rigid bridge. People who cross this bridge experience heaven and hell. Because it is literally a sky bridge floating at 800m high.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    I didn&#39;t walk the moment I climbed the bridge, but I can feel a slight tremor. When you take a step, it starts to shake, and the movement of people crossing from the other side adds up, and it starts to slam. The feet are dark and the whole body shakes, so it is truly thrilling as if you are going between heaven and hell.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Cheongnyangsan Sky Bridge - Bonghwa-gun, Gyeongbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/270/c3f52452-d766-4c90-93b6-a36defe04982.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Cheongnyangsan Sky Bridge
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p style=&#34;COLOR: #7b1f42&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Bongseong Pork Charcoal Fire Complex
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Cheongbong Charcoal Grill: 565-1, Bongmyeong-ro, Bongseong-myeon, Bonghwa-gun, 054-672-1116
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Hopejeong: 564, Bongmyeong-ro, Bongseong-myeon, Bonghwa-gun, 054-672-9046
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Solbong Charcoal Grill: 2, Mireukgol-gil, Bongseong-myeon, Bonghwa-gun, 054-674-3989
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Bongseong Charcoal Fire Meat Restaurant: 578, Bongmyeong-ro, Bongseong-gun, Bonghwa-gun, 054-672-9130
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;topmr&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1.Access
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
     * Self-driving
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34; style=&#34;MARGIN-TOP: 0px&#34;&gt;
    Punggi IC on Jungang Expressway → National Road No. 5 toward Bonghwa from Bonghyeon Intersection → Turn left at Sinjeon Intersection → Turn right toward Bonghwa at Seocheon Intersection → National Road No. 36 toward Bonghwa at Sangman Intersection → Turn right at Geumbong Intersection → Bongseong Pork Charcoal Complex
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
     * public transport
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34; style=&#34;MARGIN-TOP: 0px&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Seoul → Bonghwa:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Operates 6 times a day (07: 40-18: 10) from East Seoul General Terminal, takes 2 hours and 40 minutes
    &lt;br/&gt;
    * From Bonghwa Bus Terminal (054-673-4400), use the bus bound for Bongseong, property, and nutrition
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34; style=&#34;MARGIN-TOP: 0px&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34; style=&#34;MARGIN-TOP: 0px&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Restaurants around
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Yongdu Restaurant:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Songi Cooking / 526-4, Dadeok-ro, Bongseong-myeon, Bonghwa-gun / 054-673-3144
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Bongseong Oriental Medicine Plaza:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Han Yak-woo / 47 Bongseong-myeon Agriculture-in-gil, Bonghwa-gun / 054-674-3400
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.bhhywoo.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.bhhywoo.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Sansuyu-gil Road:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Sansu Yoosik / 202-64 Sansuyu-gil, Bongseong-myeon, Bonghwa-gun / 054-673-5860
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Inhawon:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Songi Cooking / 20 Yurok-gil, Bonghwa-eup, Bonghwa-gun / 054-673-9881
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;topmr&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     3.Accommodation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Haheon Old House:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    20 Yangji Village-gil, Myeongho-myeon, Bonghwa-gun / 054-672-2339
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Mansan Old House:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    21-19 Seodong-gil, Chunyang-myeon, Bonghwa-gun / 054-672-3206
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Kwon Jin&#39;s house (Seongam old house):
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    43-3, Nakcheondang-gil, Chunyang-myeon, Bonghwa-gun / 054-672-6118
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    ※ The above information was created in October 2013, and may change later, so be sure to check it before you travel.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>