<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jeju on Every Corner of Korea</title>
    <link>https://codecorea.github.io/tags/jeju/</link>
    <description>Every Corner of Korea (Jeju)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 21:39:09 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="https://codecorea.github.io/tags/jeju/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Fun and sweet winter museums in Jeju - Jeju, South Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/fun-and-sweet-winter-museums-in-jeju-110/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 21:39:09 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/fun-and-sweet-winter-museums-in-jeju-110/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Jeju, South Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;fun-and-sweet-winter-museums-in-jeju--110&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Chocolate Museum - Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/110/294c34a1-00f2-4247-87b8-3f8ff34c68e8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Chocolate Museum
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Fun and sweet winter museums in Jeju
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Jeju, South Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   There are many fun museums in winter even on Jeju Island. Among them, the museum introduces an experience museum that can be used to educate children and also be enjoyed by adults.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Chocolate Museum
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The Chocolate Museum is amazing from the outside. Once the facade of the museum looks like the architecture of the South American Inca civilization, the birthplace of cacao. Also, as soon as you enter, you are welcomed by the coffee and it is more fun. The Chocolate Museum is a fun place to look at all the chocolates in each region, including the history of chocolate. The museum features chocolate statues and famous cultural works. Is it because it melts because many people touch it with their hands? Of course you should look only with your eyes.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The pavilion starts with a poster for the chocolate factory of the movie Charlie, which will be interesting to children. Also explain how to make chocolate from cacao. There is also a space that reproduces the chocolate of the ancient Aztec civilization, which is intrigued by the model train coming and going around. One side of the museum explains the types and benefits of cacao. I only know that chocolate can help me regenerate, but I first learned that there are so many different types of cacao.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    In the museum, there is a quiz game to convey knowledge of various chocolate cacao through not only exhibitions but also quizzes.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    It is not just an enumeration, but an exhibition that induces the interest and participation of visitors through various attempts such as chocolate quiz, chocolate misunderstanding and truth.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The second floor displays chocolates and tea cups, mostly from medieval Europe. Chocolate is now popular, but in the past it was only used by the upper classes in Europe as a premium drink. The spaces that explain the colorful and diverse look-and-feel exhibitions and related stories also attracted many people.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Chocolate Museum Experience Center - Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/110/a1dcea63-a7e0-4544-be67-96b0f9d0b0e4.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Chocolate Museum Experience Center
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   On the first floor of the museum, there is a space that shows the scene of making chocolate. Unfortunately this is not a place for visitors. For the unfortunate audiences, there is a Junior Experience Hall on the first basement floor where you can make chocolates with your children.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Chocolate Museum Production Room - Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/110/fbefec60-9b8c-41e3-a149-eb1f543f6e89.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Chocolate Museum Production Room
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Teddy Bear Museum
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Now let&#39;s go to the Teddy Bear Museum located in Jungmun, Jeju Island. Teddy Bear is a teddy bear that everyone knows. I&#39;ve made and constructed a museum and I&#39;m curious how to decorate it. First of all, it seems to be popular with children in terms of the theme of teddy bears.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Once inside the museum, it consists of various structures, such as a history hall decorated with teddy bear dolls, important events of modern history of humanity, and an art museum decorated with works of art in teddy bears, and exhibitions. Starting with the birth of the car, various events such as the moon landing of mankind and the return of Hong Kong to China are centered on teddy bear dolls. It is an educational museum for children and a cute and cute museum for adults.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The museum&#39;s interior art gallery draws Van Gogh&#39;s paintings as teddy bears and draws visitors with a variety of themes such as Teddy Bears decorated with Louis Vuitton. There is also a teddy bear souvenir shop in the basement. Parents who have been holding their children&#39;s hands can get out of here by buying teddy bear dolls.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Teddy Bear Museum Souvenir Shop - Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/110/e4a50e3d-17c5-4cba-815c-644e254d6f05.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Teddy Bear Museum Souvenir Shop
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Lastly, there is a hidden teddy bear performance, Elvis Presley. The show is not long, but Elvis Presley dances and music in Teddy Bear and is worth seeing. The venue is located a little far from the main exhibition hall, but don&#39;t forget to stop by.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The Teddy Bear Museum has outdoor gardens and outdoor stages as well. These days it&#39;s midwinter, so I couldn&#39;t go outdoors, but if it&#39;s a nice day in summer, the outdoor garden with grass plaza and walking trails will be a good gift for nature with cool sea breeze.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Teddy Bear Museum - Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/110/10dead87-d969-4304-a457-7f388a36a618.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Teddy Bear Museum
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Haenyeo Museum
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Now move to the Haenyeo Museum near Seongsanpo. Isn&#39;t it a haenyeo that can not be missed in Jeju Island? Haenyeo Museum is operated by Jeju Island and consists of three exhibition rooms with the theme of Jeju Island Haenyeo.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The dormitory of Haenyeo, the first exhibition room, shows the life of haenyeo in Jeju Island. A traditional house was recreated and the village of Jeju Island was modeled next to it. In addition, there are various exhibitions such as living utensils, food culture and customs.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Haenyeo Museum - Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/110/721afe92-8e23-4911-9eb3-e4a82bd66ba7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Haenyeo Museum
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The second exhibition room, Haenyeo&#39;s Workplace, is a showroom that maximizes the visual effect by decorating the dolls and showing them as images. You can also find out about the hierarchies of haenyeo and the daily life of haenyeo. There are also spaces that show the achievements of devoted women who have dedicated themselves to the nation, such as the Haenyeo Anti-Japanese Movement.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    In the third exhibition room, Haenyeo&#39;s life, she can become the first woman in her life and see her various hierarchies. There are also interesting exhibits, such as a video where you can listen to live experiences of divers.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Haenyeo Museum - Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/110/1a8edbc3-fa9b-4675-b46d-da429da2700d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Haenyeo Museum
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Lastly, there is the Children&#39;s Haenyeok, an experience hall for children. This is a place where only children and guardians can enter. Children can become more familiar with Haenyeo by playing with Jeju Haenyeo related rides.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Haenyeo Museum is proud of its outdoor park. The open-air large park is called Haenyeom Square, which also houses the Jeju Haenyeo Anti-Japanese Movement Memorial Monument.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Haenyeo Museum - Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/110/df590b50-1ee1-4178-a5bb-abf7328a7065.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Haenyeo Museum
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;div style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;
    &lt;span style=&#34;color: rgb(204, 0, 0);&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was updated in February 2019 and may change afterwards, so please check before you travel.
    &lt;/span&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;
     ※ The information such as text, photos and videos used in this article is copyrighted by Korea Tourism Organization, so unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wiesen Village, an oasis of body and mind that wants to relax life - Jeju, South Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/wiesen-village-an-oasis-of-body-and-mind-that-wants-to-relax-life-105/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 21:39:04 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/wiesen-village-an-oasis-of-body-and-mind-that-wants-to-relax-life-105/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Jeju, South Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;wiesen-village-an-oasis-of-body-and-mind-that-wants-to-relax-life--105&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Jade sea is the pride of Jeju Island - Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/105/cbc81b20-04ff-4bee-8287-69d338c6a4be.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Jade sea is the pride of Jeju Island
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Wiesen Village, an oasis of body and mind that wants to relax life
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Jeju, South Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &#39;Summer vacation is one year.&#39; How long have you been dreaming? Like the squirrel wheel and the freedom of the gold that leaves the fixed life frame and seeks a strange sun, it is the golden time that is allowed for us.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   I unfolded the map and pondered where to go. Tourists face the tropical mood, palm trees, the jade sea running over the white sand, and the hot sun. Jeju Island has already become a landscape by its name. There is also a resting place to quench my thirst like an oasis in my body and mind that wants to rest.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Bizen Village where various spaces coexist - Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/105/8ae6c32f-424a-4698-b3a9-0b2ae2696f5c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Bizen Village where various spaces coexist
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Bizen Village is in the middle of the Hadori Carrot Field on the east side of Jeju Island. Although it opened this year, it is already a cultural space with industrial design and vintage props among those seeking a trendy lifestyle. Travelers are sheltered with dormitories, penthouses and camping trailers, but they are not just places to sleep. It is a complex cultural space with various facilities for relaxation such as a restaurant hard table, an organic farm cafe beer round, a loft market selling vintage props and longboards, a gallery displaying lighting collections and an outdoor swimming pool.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;There is a large swimming pool in the middle of the yard. - Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/105/fcc24eb6-a027-4568-a65e-75b6c3b0b219.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     There is a large swimming pool in the middle of the yard.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   There is nothing urgent in Bizen Village. Move slowly and enjoy nature, and relax without doing anything. Above all, it is better to interact with travelers. The worries here are: &#39;Swim or read a book or a beer?&#39; I only do it. Therefore, Bizen Village is not called a hotel or a pension. It is said to be a hangout of stylish travelers.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Basketball court on one side of Bizen Village - Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/105/ad3f675e-d86c-4656-ba6c-8dd015d02bb0.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Basketball court on one side of Bizen Village
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Industrial Design meets Boutique Hotel Design
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It is just the first meeting with Bizen Village. Buildings and containers like warehouses say &#39;what is this?&#39; It makes you think. But when you look at the rooms that are stylish and vintage, you change your mind. It&#39;s like looking at a boutique hotel in Europe.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;6-Bed Dormitory &amp;lt;Photo courtesy of Bizen Village&amp;gt; - Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/105/1cda11bb-4ac7-4198-b449-8fa9ada4a2e8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     6-Bed Dormitory &amp;lt;Photo courtesy of Bizen Village&amp;gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Rooms vary in dormitory, couple room, penthouse and camping trailer. Considering the purpose and taste of travelers. If you are traveling alone, a dormitory, a couple&#39;s room for couples or couples, a penthouse is a good choice if you want to spend a luxurious night. If you want to have a special experience with the romance of your trip, we recommend camping trailers.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Utilizing the texture of wood, you can feel warm sensibility. - Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/105/0a8cf8c9-8a2a-480e-9a50-2ca451e59553.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Utilizing the texture of wood, you can feel warm sensibility.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Dormitory is the pride of Bizen Village. The name &#39;village&#39; is used because it stands for &#39;village inhabitants&#39;. Six and four rooms were set up in three buildings so that more than 100 people could relax.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Neatly decorated couple rooms - Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/105/be730a9d-2fc8-45dd-b9a4-ef886351e789.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Neatly decorated couple rooms
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you think &#39;the dormitory is there, what&#39;s wrong&#39;. The dormitories here are different from those of a typical guest house.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Penthouses in Bizen Village - Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/105/e0b2e6e0-9d90-4243-bd76-832c7da53c4f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Penthouses in Bizen Village
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Travelers who have used dormitories know. How hard it is to find a good bed. Bizen Village is a bed made of wood for the traveler to stay as comfortable as possible. You don&#39;t have to worry about sleeping. Classic joint lighting is used as an interior accessory to add a warm atmosphere.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Bathroom in a penthouse - Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/105/8b85cbc7-c3f4-450b-a243-78ec5b754b13.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Bathroom in a penthouse
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The composition of the three spaces is the same, and the color of the room and the material of the furniture have changed. It is a space where anyone can rest casually and form a consensus among travelers.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A lamp is both a light and an interior accessory - Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/105/31247269-7c8f-4248-8b6f-5c2e5a39d9ad.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A lamp is both a light and an interior accessory
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The penthouse can be thought of as a royal suite of a deluxe hotel. The exterior is a container, but the interior is finished with wood texture and filled with furniture collected by the owner, giving the 1970s vintage sensibility.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;14&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Gield&#39;s joint lighting reveals the traces of time - Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/105/1d65ab5a-6bc6-4a56-b6b5-b1a7c143c5b9.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Gield&#39;s joint lighting reveals the traces of time
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Vintage furniture and lights are Orissa chairs by Wim Rietveld, famous for their lighting and vintage furniture designs by Kaiser Idell, Louis Poulsen and Gielde All.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;16&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;There is no ordinary lighting in Bizen Village - Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/105/2eea2823-2249-4e40-88b3-a81e711b3844.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     There is no ordinary lighting in Bizen Village
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   None is inadvertently placed. Under thorough calculations, it is properly positioned to feel the analog sensitivity. The stylish interior space meets the analog sensibility and is born as a place where present and past coexist. The same design concept was applied to the Avion camping trailers obtained from the United States.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;18&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Unique furniture and arrangement avoided the monotony of the room - Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/105/c318c489-9122-43b2-a7e8-3c203b0708d8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Unique furniture and arrangement avoided the monotony of the room
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The special lighting in each room is related to the history of the owner Choi Jung-hoon. He ran the interior company dot-to-design and vintage lighting &amp;amp; furniture shop loft market in Seoul. Then I came to Jeju with the idea of creating a boutique hotel where old and modern emotions coexist.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;20&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Stylish rooms with simplicity - Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/105/93cf9c1d-6087-4d89-91a1-b335ab8f3b22.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Stylish rooms with simplicity
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   I found a landscape full of carrot fields in Hadori and built a Bizen Village. Then he brought a selection of precious vintage lights, furniture, and speakers. This allows visitors to and from Bizen Village to encounter original vintage props that can only be seen in museums, rather than beautifully imitated interior props.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;22&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Bizen Village Night View - Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/105/798b7993-6507-44ff-99d3-1c453c3ae903.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Bizen Village Night View
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Vintage and chic but modern
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Bizen Village&#39;s cafés, restaurants, editorial shops and galleries have a strong industrial feel. Exposed concrete, crunchy design, old props… . The vintage, chic but modern atmosphere makes you feel like you are in a foreign country.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;15&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Industrial Café Beer Round - Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/105/3cfba2cb-6c5e-4793-a3bf-1ffd5f8e88c5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Industrial Café Beer Round
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The editor&#39;s shop Loft Market sells longboards and high-low furniture as well as outdoor goods and clothing. It is a selection of things that the owner likes.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;16&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Loft market selling items collected by the owner - Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/105/043c690c-83b7-49e1-822d-874b8279f343.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Loft market selling items collected by the owner
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Restaurant Hado Table is a great place to enjoy brunch dishes made with organic vegetables grown directly in the garden. It is a restaurant during the day, but at night it is transformed into a pub &amp;amp; club where you can drink beer and dance.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;17&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Breakfast made with organic ingredients - Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/105/d8c64fd5-c3a0-49c9-9109-fe282cdf9b26.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Breakfast made with organic ingredients
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Organic Farm Cafe Beer Round is Jeju&#39;s favorite spot for women. There are many cute accessories to take pictures in unique atmosphere. JBL and Altec&#39;s vintage speakers are installed at one side of the café for use as a guitar or performance.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;18&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Glass bottle decoration of cafe - Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/105/5e233175-d4d0-420f-b199-b42a078f6a11.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Glass bottle decoration of cafe
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Choi Jung-hoon dreams that all spaces in Bizen Village will be used as wedding halls for small weddings, flea markets for artists, and ballrooms for dance parties. It is not a place to sleep and go to Jeju Island, but to enjoy a new culture, interact with people, and hope to be a cultural space.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;19&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Cafe Beer Round is a favorite spot for women - Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/105/383d7f9e-dfaf-4a28-8504-831033a0eb26.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Cafe Beer Round is a favorite spot for women
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Hado Beach and Bijarim with the beauty of Jeju
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Listening to nature is a way to use Bizen Village. Hado Beach is a 10-minute walk away. Woljeongri Beach and Bijarim are not far away. Hado Beach is a great place to surf. Even if you&#39;re not surfing, you can enjoy the sea with snorkeling and kayaking. You can walk on the sand while listening to the subdued sounds of the waves, or dive into the sea.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;20&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;I want to take pictures - Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/105/69c8038b-7b51-4bb9-a125-5a13d120dfad.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     I want to take pictures
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It is also happy to walk into the bizarre forest and take a refreshing wind to escape the hot sun. Bijarim is so luxuriant as the Millennium Forest. Walk the promenade and you&#39;ll find many different sized trees. The reason why it looks small compared to the age is because the growth rate of the non-tree is slow. It is the world&#39;s largest single-forest forest.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;21&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Bijarim, called the Millennium Forest - Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/105/bd6865f9-7f11-4080-aad5-e0359d108c24.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Bijarim, called the Millennium Forest
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel info
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Bizen Village
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Address: 72 Hado 9-gil, Gujwa-eup, Jeju-si, Jeju-do
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Contact: 064-784-8216
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.wiesenvillage.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.wiesenvillage.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Restaurants near
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Seokdawon: Sea urchin kalguksu / 1752 Haejeonghaean-ro, Gujwa-eup / 064-784-2329
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Hado Small Restaurant: Pasta and others / 62-9 Hado 13-gil, Gujwa-eup / 010-4177-3213
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Dharma Charcoal Fire Ribs: Pork Raw Ribs / 25, Jungang-ro 7-gil, Jeju-si / 064-725-5244
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Rooms
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -The House Pension: 2060 Haeuphaean-ro, Gujwa-eup / 064-784-6040
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Padosori Pension: 1950 Haeikhaean-ro, Gujwa-eup / 064-783-3338
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was updated in April 2018 and may change afterwards, so please check before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ The information such as text, photos and videos used in this article is copyrighted by Korea Tourism Organization, so unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seogwipo, Jeju, South Korea - Shooting while breathing with nature: ATV Experience Center, Jeju Daeyu Land</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/shooting-while-breathing-with-nature-atv-experience-center-jeju-daeyu-land-43/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 21:24:41 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/shooting-while-breathing-with-nature-atv-experience-center-jeju-daeyu-land-43/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-title=&#34;shooting-while-breathing-with-nature-atv-experience-center-jeju-daeyu-land--43&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Clay shooting in nature - Seogwipo, Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/43/d716113a-d361-4d5d-9de0-b2edc9631f6d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Clay shooting in nature
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Shooting while breathing with nature: ATV Experience Center, Jeju Daeyu Land
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Seogwipo, Jeju, South Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Jeju is open for four seasons and is a paradise for leisure sports enthusiasts. Even though autumn is over, we are on the threshold of the cold season, but in Jeju you can still enjoy various activities under the warm sunshine. In addition, special sports activities such as shooting that are not easily accessible are also possible. We visited Daeyuland to experience clay shooting, rifle and pistol shooting.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Pleasure to hit the flying disc! Clay shooting
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Daeyu Land is located in the middle mountainous area of Seogwipo City and is the only place where you can experience clay shooting in Jeju. In addition to the clay shooting range, which is made up of indoor and outdoor spaces, 330ha (about 1 million pyeong) of Jeju&#39;s nature, there are rifle, pistol shooting range, and ATV experience ground.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    bang! The sound is thrilling all over the body. The exhilarating energy of the air blows through the whole body at once. You haven&#39;t hit the target, but you will be happy regardless of your success. Follow the staff&#39;s instructions and shoulder the gun again. Second shot! The flying disc is hit by a bullet, split into two, and falls off without force. I am excited like children with more pleasure than before. I feel like old stress washed away at once. The first world of shooting is a series of curiosity and surprises. Once you have tasted clay shooting with nature, you have no choice but to fall in love with it.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Camellia blooms on the way to the shooting range. - Seogwipo, Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/43/d4c32bf2-af81-4b39-8321-12241aa234bd.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Camellia blooms on the way to the shooting range.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Clay shooting is a leisure sport in which clay disks are thrown into the air. Because you have to hit moving objects, you need a lot of quickness and concentration. Above all, the pleasure of hitting the flying disc is very exciting. Even beginners can learn without difficulty, so everyone can try it.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Professional staff members are placed one-on-one during shooting experience - Seogwipo, Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/43/04d28765-d42d-4f9e-97ed-f86b6f6b2547.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Professional staff members are placed one-on-one during shooting experience
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Clay shooting uses a shotgun. With the buttocks on your shoulders, one hand holds the trigger side and the other hand supports the muzzle unsteadily. Shotguns are large and heavy and have a large recoil after shooting. Therefore, it is necessary to keep both feet firmly on the ground and posture before shooting. When the disc is slightly below the muzzle, firing increases the hit rate. Wearing earplugs is a must since the gunfire sounds very loud after launch. Shooting a total of 16 shots, of which only 5-7 hits are great skills. If you are confident in clay shooting, you can also go hunting for wild pheasants.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Loading ammo into shotgun - Seogwipo, Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/43/4af5c2ae-a3ba-45de-89d4-5e49f9302ad5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Loading ammo into shotgun
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Aim at the target! Rifle and pistol shooting
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Opposite the Clay Shooting Range, there is another space for pistol and rifle shooting. Pistols and rifle shots aim at targets that do not move in the shooting range surrounding bulletproof glass.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;There is a rifle and pistol shooting range opposite Clay Shooting Range. - Seogwipo, Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/43/4d36f401-8cb9-4053-9e7a-06c8fb36a956.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     There is a rifle and pistol shooting range opposite Clay Shooting Range.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The scores are given for each target range, so you can also compare your shooting skills. After the experience, you can take your target as a souvenir.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Pistols and rifle ranges are bulletproof glass. - Seogwipo, Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/43/e1088bc2-73cd-4f7e-a345-31d561f1ffc4.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Pistols and rifle ranges are bulletproof glass.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The pistol extends the arm forward and holds it with both hands. Close one eye and match the target and muzzle with the other eye. And launch! Less recoil after firing than clay shots, but shots are as good as shotguns. Of course, earplugs are a must.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Aim and fire at the still target - Seogwipo, Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/43/cbc779cc-e091-4396-bf14-cd44f517b6a5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Aim and fire at the still target
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The most exciting time to check the target plate after shooting.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Hold the pistol as if it&#39;s wrapped with both hands - Seogwipo, Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/43/e16c3f35-09aa-4b8f-bcdb-d89d4028dc5f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Hold the pistol as if it&#39;s wrapped with both hands
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If the pistol is too small and the shotgun is a bit of a burden, we recommend rifle shooting. Best of all, the gun is light and easy to position. Like a pistol, close one eye and aim at the target. If you&#39;ve been to the army, rifle shooting can be quite familiar.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Travelers experiencing rifle shooting - Seogwipo, Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/43/2c3ffe42-2f36-40db-a113-5183709d1820.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Travelers experiencing rifle shooting
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Surprisingly, women enjoy shooting quite a lot of fun, but often score better than men.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Grand Master Shooter list of high scorers - Seogwipo, Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/43/4fbca670-b5e0-4e4b-832d-5fd78611ce01.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Grand Master Shooter list of high scorers
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The ammunition used in the shooting experience is all used in practice, so be careful about your safety during the experience. Daeyu Land has professional staff at the shooting range to help tourists experience shooting safely. In addition to clay shooting, pistols and rifle shooting can be enjoyed by anyone of all ages. However, you can experience from age 14 or older.
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;14&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Travelers holding their targets as souvenirs - Seogwipo, Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/43/7f0f9d0a-c9b5-49cd-a5ca-0701fbc1e624.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Travelers holding their targets as souvenirs
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   ATV instincts run on four wheels!
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Shooting experiences are somewhat short, usually taking between 15 and 20 minutes. If you feel uncomfortable, take a step to the ATV experience. You can enjoy the joy of enjoying the great nature while enjoying the blowing wind.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;ATV Experience - Seogwipo, Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/43/1783f7a5-cb60-4e07-a925-2048d6ccb6ed.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     ATV Experience
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    ATV is a popular leisure sport that runs through nature including wild off-road, mountains and fields. Anyone who can&#39;t drive can experience ATV, so many families visit. However, you can hold the steering wheel yourself at least 14 years old, and you can carry children in front of or behind the driver&#39;s seat.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Travelers trained before hands-on training - Seogwipo, Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/43/688d6571-d4cf-48eb-8376-fc03992c939b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Travelers trained before hands-on training
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Tomb The engine starts to sound up lightly. The faces of experienced visitors wearing helmets and waiting for departure signals are recalled. Finally starting! Rolling movements and vibrations are transmitted to the passengers as if the big wheel bounced off the bumpy road.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Anyone can easily experience ATV - Seogwipo, Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/43/270e0084-c08f-4070-82a1-fdc775314461.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Anyone can easily experience ATV
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Run off-road breathing with nature as if you were an explorer. Sometimes the fun will blow away the dust and your mind will be calmed. The ATV experience is very satisfying to enjoy for stress relief.
   &lt;br/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;ATV breathing with nature - Seogwipo, Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/43/7c463b3f-618c-49bd-80e3-3133a816dbc4.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     ATV breathing with nature
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel info
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Daeyuland
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Address: 381 Sangye-ro, Seogwipo-si, Jeju
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Contact: 064-738-0600
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.daeyooland.net/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.daeyooland.net/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Restaurants near
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Nolman: Seafood Ramen / 24 Aewol-ro 1-gil, Aewol-eup, Jeju-si / 064-799-3332
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.nolman.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.nolman.com/
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Gunghan Shabu Shabu: Shabu Shabu / 4, Myeongdong-ro, Seogwipo-si / 064-763-3197
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Noodle sea: meat noodle, gukbap / 26-1, Myeongdong-ro, Seogwipo-si / 064-733-9259
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Rooms
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Jewel Jazz Village: 220 Sobodangdang-ro, Seogwipo-si / 064-738-9300
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.jazzvillage.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.jazzvillage.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Benikea I-Jin Hotel: 4, Sindaero 22-gil, Jeju-si / 064-745-0700
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Grape Hotel: 863, Sannoknam-ro, Andeok-myeon, Seogwipo-si / 064-792-8000
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.podohotel.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.podohotel.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was updated in November 2016. It may change afterwards, so please check before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ The information such as text, photos and videos used in this article is copyrighted by Korea Tourism Organization, so unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jeju, South Korea - Enjoy Jeju&#39;s hidden specialties and local chicken dishes! Local Chicken Distribution Zone of Gyorae Village</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/enjoy-jejus-hidden-specialties-and-local-chicken-dishes-local-chicken-distribution-zone-of-gyorae-village-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 19:10:14 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/enjoy-jejus-hidden-specialties-and-local-chicken-dishes-local-chicken-distribution-zone-of-gyorae-village-27/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-title=&#34;enjoy-jejus-hidden-specialties-and-local-chicken-dishes-local-chicken-distribution-zone-of-gyorae-village--27&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Traditional chicken Shabu Shabu cuisine at Gyorae Village - Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/27/788a66a7-8724-4c49-8b3a-f05a73a87448.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Traditional chicken Shabu Shabu cuisine at Gyorae Village
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Enjoy Jeju&#39;s hidden specialties and local chicken dishes! Local Chicken Distribution Zone of Gyorae Village
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Jeju, South Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Chicken is a common food that can be found anywhere in the country, but in Jeju, the chicken is a delicious delicacy. This is a place where you can taste various pure chickens, which are grown with fresh air from Hallasan, with shabu shabu, white soy sauce, and kalguksu. In Kyorae-ri, Jocheon-eup, which is designated as a special chicken distribution zone of Jeju Island, let&#39;s regain the taste that was lost in summer. Your meal and your body will be healthy.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Do you know the local chicken village of Gyoraeri?
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Gyoraeri, located in the middle of the eastern part of Jeju, is famous for its local chicken village. Bijarim is located across the village, lined with local chicken restaurants. From chicken stir-fried chicken to white dishes and chicken kalguksu, as well as special menus such as chicken shabu-shabu, chicken enthusiasts can&#39;t overlook them.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Gyorae-ri became known as the Indigenous Chicken Village since the late 1970s. Located in the highlands of 400m above sea level, Gyoraeri is a rocky Gotjawal terrain and cold and snowy. Hunting and breeding have been developed instead of farming since ancient times. Although the village was ruined by 4.3 incidents around 1950, it gradually recovered and began to be called the local chicken village as the number of domestic chicken breeding farms increased in the late 1970s.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   Since then, roads have been expanded through the villages, and tourist facilities have been built nearby, creating a specialty restaurant using local chicken, a local specialty. It&#39;s a local chicken restaurant street. In 2009, it was designated as a local chicken distribution zone in Jeju Island and continues the reputation of Korean chicken villages.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Gyorae-ri, Jocheon-eup designated as a local chicken distribution zone - Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/27/888a4514-6173-488a-890e-777be0d0fa98.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Gyorae-ri, Jocheon-eup designated as a local chicken distribution zone
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   The secret of the local chicken dish is fresh ingredients
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Drinking fresh air from Hallasan and playing in green grassland, Gyoraeri chicken is definitely different in size and chewy compared to other chickens. Your muscles develop, so you don&#39;t need extra fat and you&#39;re full. Above all, native chicken is freshness. The reason why the local chicken dishes are delicious is because they eat the live chicken instead of frozen chicken.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   There are also homes where local chickens are raised, but most have small farms on one side of the restaurant and sometimes take chickens from poultry farms. Some restaurants prepare daily meals in the morning and cook them immediately after ordering. It&#39;s all about getting fresh ingredients. Even if the recipes or seasonings are slightly different from house to house, the fresh ingredients are used first of all, so the basics are wherever you go.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Gyorae-ri chicken with fresh ingredients - Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/27/5fa356d5-1ccf-430d-80a7-cf7e61480d1a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Gyorae-ri chicken with fresh ingredients
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Chicken Shabu Shabu
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In addition to general chicken dishes such as fried chicken and chicken soup, we recommend Chicken Shabu Shabu as a special menu. Thinly sliced chicken breast is slightly boiled in chicken bone broth and tastes delicious.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Temper Garden, famous for chicken shabu shabu - Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/27/0ef0fc18-9f9b-4245-951e-87a90d17716b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Temper Garden, famous for chicken shabu shabu
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you want to taste chicken Shabu Shabu, you can find &#39;Taste Garden&#39;. It is a local restaurant that attracts tourists as well as residents. Chicken shabu-shabu, white rice, and green beans are served in turn like a course meal.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Slice the plate full of chicken breast - Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/27/f4fb3581-4110-48e7-a7e2-79e225ab3f68.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Slice the plate full of chicken breast
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Chicken breasts are usually unpopular because of their rich texture. Vegetables such as cabbage, green onions, and mushrooms are mixed and soaked in sour sauce. The light taste of chicken breast is the same, but you can feel it with a thin texture. The chicken dung house and the skin that comes with it go without any refusal. The hot broth from the oil is easy to eat with a simple taste.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Slightly boil chicken breasts marinated in chicken bones - Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/27/c318b7cd-59c9-4cee-a928-0ff953dd2632.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Slightly boil chicken breasts marinated in chicken bones
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   By the time she eats all the shabu shabu, the steaming steam is on the table. Once you&#39;re impressed by the amount of food you&#39;ve filled, you&#39;ll be impressed by the chewy taste. Mung bean sprinkled like a sauce adds a delicious flavor to the simmered white meat. Chickens are so big that one chicken leg is a child&#39;s forearm.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;It is delicious when we dip in sauce with cooked vegetables - Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/27/a352da33-4b6d-4022-b76f-03670c11af8b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     It is delicious when we dip in sauce with cooked vegetables
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The lean lean meat goes well without having to chew several times. Every bite bite sticks in your mouth, so it tastes more delicious. If you have a preconception that local chickens are chewy, throw them away at home. The chewy but smooth chewy texture is very satisfying.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Chicken thighs are big and taste good - Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/27/3a277538-e729-4b3f-a1db-89bf8b215295.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Chicken thighs are big and taste good
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   By the time the dish is emptied, the mung bean is boiled with chicken broth. Chicken porridge with rich green bean flavor is a delicacy. Mung beans that pop in the mouth add to the taste of chewing.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Mung bean made with thick green beans in chicken broth - Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/27/20557b53-64a1-4fc3-9b86-64d337da0674.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Mung bean made with thick green beans in chicken broth
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Light but firm meal, chicken kalguksu
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you are traveling alone or want to taste a local chicken with a light meal, Chicken Noodle Soup is a great choice. There are several houses serving chicken kalguksu, but Gyorae Son Kalguksu and Gotjawal Son Kalguksu are popular. The chicken is put in abundantly according to the name of chicken kalguksu.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Gyorae hand kalguksu, known for its delicious chicken noodle soup - Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/27/574cf007-1880-411e-8a4f-bb4c9f40eca5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Gyorae hand kalguksu, known for its delicious chicken noodle soup
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Gyorae hand kalguksu is famous for its fresh noodles. It takes some time for the food to come out because the noodles are pulled out with the order, but the chewy noodles are good. The thick, juicy broth is like a healthy food. It&#39;s quite hungry even if I just eat chicken. At lunchtime, it&#39;s crowded with guests enough to wait for a few minutes, so it&#39;s better to skip the meal.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;It&#39;s chewy because it&#39;s freshly picked - Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/27/f58718c5-ae1e-4d7d-9d05-da4115917617.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     It&#39;s chewy because it&#39;s freshly picked
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Gotjawal Son Kalguksu also serves chicken and various vegetables. It has a lot of vegetables such as pumpkin, potatoes and onions so the aftertaste is lighter and clearer.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Gotjawal Sonkal Noodles, a hidden restaurant - Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/27/9628d7de-8164-4508-9d0b-de86f4967410.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Gotjawal Sonkal Noodles, a hidden restaurant
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   A generous amount of chicken also has a good texture. Kimchi, kakdugi, and pickles that are served as a side dish add a fresh taste.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Good compatibility with soft chicken and crispy bean sprouts - Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/27/18c17039-87b0-484e-ba41-3ea251eeb354.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Good compatibility with soft chicken and crispy bean sprouts
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Gyorae Village has many places to visit as a clean area with natural environment. Fill your stomach and enjoy the rest of your journey.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Jeju Dol Culture Park where you can meet unique Jeju stones - Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/27/f64d5d04-56e1-43a3-8345-136885244403.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Jeju Dol Culture Park where you can meet unique Jeju stones
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Gyorae Natural Recreation Forest and neighboring Jeju Stone Culture Park is a place where you can experience Jeju&#39;s unique stone and living culture. The site is so large that it is a good idea to take your time and enjoy yourself.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Jeju Stone Park Promenade - Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/27/36b75b99-ecfe-4a37-888a-57c07ff82c68.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Jeju Stone Park Promenade
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel info
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Temper Garden
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Address: 2 Gyorae 1-gil, Jocheon-eup, Jeju-si
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Contact: 064-783-7092
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Gyorae Hand Noodle Soup
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Address: 645 Bijarim-ro, Jocheon-eup, Jeju-si
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Contact: 064-782-9870
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Gotjawal Sonkal Noodles
      &lt;br/&gt;
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     Address: 685-9, Bijarim-ro, Jocheon-eup, Jeju-si
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Contact: 064-784-7997
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Jeju Stone Park
      &lt;br/&gt;
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     Address: 2023 Namjo-ro, Jocheon-eup, Jeju-si
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Contact: 064-710-7731
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.jejustonepark.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.jejustonepark.com/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Nearby destinations
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Sangumburi: 768 Bijarim-ro, Jocheon-eup, Jeju-si / 064-783-9900
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.sangumburi.net/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.sangumburi.net/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Jeju Mini Land: 606 Bijarim-ro, Jocheon-eup, Jeju-si / 064-782-7720
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.jejuminiland.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.jejuminiland.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Eco Land Theme Park: 1278-169, Beonyeong-ro, Jocheon-eup, Jeju-si / 064-802-8020
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.ecolandjeju.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.ecolandjeju.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Accommodation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Benikea The Jeju Resort: 226 Hyeopjae-ro, Hallim-eup, Jeju City / 064-796-2908
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Benikea I-Jin Hotel: 4, Sindae-ro 22-gil, Jeju City / 064-745-0700
    &lt;br/&gt;
    B &amp;amp; B White House: 9, Hyeopjae 1-gil, Hallim-eup, Jeju-si / 064-796-3640
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was made in September 2015. It may change afterwards, so please check before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Information such as text, photos, and videos used in this article is copyrighted by Korea Tourism Organization, so unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blossoming ponds and natural forest outings, Jeju Sunchulban Pond and Dongbaekdongsan Forest Trail</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/blossoming-ponds-and-natural-forest-outings-jeju-sunchulban-pond-and-dongbaekdongsan-forest-trail-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2020 12:26:37 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/blossoming-ponds-and-natural-forest-outings-jeju-sunchulban-pond-and-dongbaekdongsan-forest-trail-14/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-title=&#34;blossoming-ponds-and-natural-forest-outings-jeju-sunchulban-pond-and-dongbaekdongsan-forest-trail--14&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Small and small Sunhull Pond, located on the street - Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/14/b9d85aac-cf9a-4396-a1a5-7f896ac9098d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Small and small Sunhull Pond, located on the street
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Blossoming ponds and natural forest outings, Jeju Sunchulban Pond and Dongbaekdongsan Forest Trail
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Jeju, South Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   This is a mountain road leading to the entrance of Sunhul Village. At first glance a bunch of flowers passes by. I just missed it and pulled over. On a small pond adjacent to the road, there are plenty of water lilies. The water lilies are just beginning to bloom and open up their pink petals. The late spring is sent off with a simple yet bright smile.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Secret pond full of blooming flowers
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Sunhul Village is located in the middle mountainous area of northeast Jeju. There is a small and small pond where only acquaintances visit. This is a village pond called Seonbanban Pond. If you don&#39;t pay attention to it, it&#39;s easy to pass by.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In late spring, when the early heat begins to come in, the Sunbahn Pond is filled with water lilies. It begins to bloom one by one in early May, and by mid-day, the pond is colored pink. Blooming petals among green round leaves remind us of pure and pure children.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A bunch of water lily flowers blooming over the pond - Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/14/bd2a46cd-11ba-42ca-a97f-1a90dd82cf54.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A bunch of water lily flowers blooming over the pond
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The water lily flower that rises above the dark blue water resembles the lotus that blooms in the mud. Resistant to the environment they are in, each one is like a beautiful flower, and the appearance is similar. If the water lily and lotus are a bit confusing, look closely at the leaf shape. Water lilies have flat leaves attached to the surface of water, and one side is deeply split, while lotus flowers have rounded leaves floating on the surface, as if an umbrella was opened. Dropping water on a lotus leaf rolls around without infiltrating or getting wet.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Another water lily that looks like a lotus - Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/14/889a6ef5-51e9-414b-bb67-a756b10be0b9.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Another water lily that looks like a lotus
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The water lily flower that blooms in the sun-dried pond in Jeju&#39;s soil is hard to see. Thanks to this, Sunbahn Pond never stops.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;I bridge across the pond - Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/14/35a4ac57-6271-4d04-94fb-d761795721bd.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     I bridge across the pond
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   People who hold the camera to capture the water lily flowers and those who go out in the late spring outing will take a rest while enjoying the water lily flowers. Cross the bridge across the pond and take a souvenir picture, or slowly stroll around the pond to enjoy a relaxing afternoon. Seon-Ban-Bang-Mok, with its secluded surroundings, is a good place to visit even for travelers who visit Jeju.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sunbahn Pond Scenery - Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/14/a65d075f-f6c4-4705-af04-d1191bd79fde.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sunbahn Pond Scenery
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Camellia Garden designated as Ramsar Wetland
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   On the other side of the line, there is a forest named Camellia Garden because many camellia trees grow. The forest was once the home of the people. Camellia oil was obtained from the forest and the trees were felled and charcoal burned. Through this, children were raised and villages were built. The forest that gave generously what he had. The Camellia Garden, which was a living place for the residents, was designated as Ramsar Wetland in 2011 and is now being taken care of by people.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Dongbaekdongsan Forest Trail Entrance - Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/14/59b996a5-639f-4b15-9183-7f9dee4a2492.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Dongbaekdongsan Forest Trail Entrance
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Ramsar wetlands are the designation and protection of wetlands that are worth preserving globally through international agreements. In Jeju, four sites were registered as Ramsar Wetland, Sunli-dong Dongbaekdong, Aqua Youngorim, Water Park Orion, and Hill 1100. The village of Sunhull 1-ri, where Dongbaek Garden is located, has earned a meaningful title as &#39;The Ramsar Village&#39; for the first time in the world in 2013, thanks to the efforts of residents to keep their forests together.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Camellia Garden - Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/14/b1f110ea-5ea1-46b3-af57-ea77bf714219.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Camellia Garden
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Dongbaekdongsan Forest Trail is gentle and flat, making it easy for children to walk. You can start from the Dongbaekdongsan Visitor Information Center across the Seonchulban Pond and go out to the west exit where Sunchulbun Bridge is located or back to the Wetland Center. The entire trail is about 5km long, and you can take a short walk in 2-3 hours.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Forest path full of green - Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/14/43f3ff66-0979-4837-ab8f-a9f82434c343.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Forest path full of green
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Camellia Garden Forest Walk in Blue May
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Once you enter the forest path, you will instantly enter another world. Forests with green leaves tender young leaves wherever they come into contact with snow, and lush branches of leaves can hide even the sky. Birds sitting on branches twitter with clear sounds, and faintly roaring bells are heard from beyond the forest.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Gotjawal, the mystical nature of Jeju - Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/14/5643ee90-ead4-43fb-aef6-ee035955ad15.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Gotjawal, the mystical nature of Jeju
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Every time you step, the leaves are crushed. May in Dongbaekdongsan is a mix of autumn and spring. The young buds are pouting their faces through the thick leaves on the floor. If you turn your eyes up, it soon changes to the season of lush greenery. The mystery of Jeju created by Gotjawal&#39;s unique natural environment unfolds before your eyes.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;4.3 Bottle Cave with the Pain of Events - Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/14/f8b6f40f-f8f0-48be-8334-2ee1ab626c0d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     4.3 Bottle Cave with the Pain of Events
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The Dongbaek Garden is also a historic place that embraces the pain of the residents. The dotle cave, which was found not long after, was a hideout for the residents who fled the tombs at the time of the 4.3 incident. Although you can&#39;t go inside the cave now, you can guess the desperate situation by looking at the entrance over the wire mesh. How many days have you been hiding in a narrow cave? It is a heavy step to turn to the sad heart.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Tree Roots Exposed to the Ground - Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/14/b9b2c8da-1839-4751-a3e5-7b16562ff0a1.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Tree Roots Exposed to the Ground
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   As we crawled through the thick roots of trees that crawled over the ground and wandered through the natural forest where trees and vines intertwined, we quickly reached the wetland. This is where Ramsar Marsh is designated. Distant water moss, which has been accumulated for a long time in the pit rock lava rock, is a rare wetland that is hard to find in Jeju. The sound of birds coming in from time to time in silence and silence is like a gift from nature. I go on my way back with a calm mind.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Distant mower wetland designated as Ramsar Wetlands - Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/14/29c50d07-6282-4fff-ac54-627bc6d74e37.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Distant mower wetland designated as Ramsar Wetlands
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   After the exploration of the Dongbaekdongsan Mountain, the boats can be filled at the local restaurant &#39;Dormuk&#39; at the entrance of the village.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Local restaurant “Doormug” located at the entrance of Sunhul Village - Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/14/ac8d6820-af1e-4edc-a260-294cee2be556.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Local restaurant “Doormug” located at the entrance of Sunhul Village
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Pork stir-fry and buckwheat pancake are neatly served.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Neatly set meal - Jeju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/14/48b3d335-a2f9-437d-904e-9c219505e04e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Neatly set meal
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel info
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Seonli-dong Camellia Garden Information Center
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Address: 77, Dongbaek-ro, Jocheon-eup, Jeju-si
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Inquiries: Dongbaekdongsan Wetland Center (Information Center) 064-784-9445
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Nearby restaurants
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Earth account: Korean chicken shabu-shabu, Chinese herbal green bean samgyetang
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://cafe.daum.net/duck1950&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://cafe.daum.net/duck1950
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Cheongun Restaurant: Boiled fish / 285 Ilchul-ro, Seongsan-eup, Seogwipo-si / 064-782-3912
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Harakwon: Native chicken hotpot, native chicken lacquer hotpot / 661 Bijarim-ro, Jocheon-eup, Jeju-si / 064-784-3378
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Accommodation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Benikea Hotel Jeju: 554-10, Aewolhaean-ro, Aewol-eup, Jeju / 064-799-3544
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Hotel Leo: 14 Sammuro, Jeju / 064-754-7000
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.hotelleo.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.hotelleo.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Benikea I-Jin Hotel: 4, Sindae-ro 22-gil, Jeju City / 064-745-0700
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.ijinhotel.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.ijinhotel.com/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was made in May 2015. It may change afterwards, so please check before traveling.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Information such as text, photos, and videos used in this article is copyrighted by Korea Tourism Organization, so unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>