<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chungju on Every Corner of Korea</title>
    <link>https://codecorea.github.io/tags/chungju/</link>
    <description>Every Corner of Korea (Chungju)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 08:12:11 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="https://codecorea.github.io/tags/chungju/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet the History of Chungju Blooming along the Namhan River - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/meet-the-history-of-chungju-blooming-along-the-namhan-river-47/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 08:12:11 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/meet-the-history-of-chungju-blooming-along-the-namhan-river-47/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;meet-the-history-of-chungju-blooming-along-the-namhan-river--47&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Jodong-ri History Museum - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/47/a491d9bd-999f-40e5-ba3e-db7dbc388e08.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Jodong-ri History Museum
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Meet the History of Chungju Blooming along the Namhan River
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Chungju Chungju is the hometown of Jungwon culture. Prehistoric remains remain around the Namhan River, and in the Three Kingdoms era, it was a fierce battlefield to occupy Jungwon. It is also the place where Jungwongyeong was made among the 5 blind spots since the Three Kingdoms period. In January, a large amount of bronze artifacts from the early Iron Age were excavated in Hoam-dong, Chungju. In the early Iron Age tomb 19 artifacts were excavated all at once, including the Sejong bronze sword. Let&#39;s meet Chungju&#39;s history from prehistoric times to Goryeo dynasty along the Namhan River, which is dotted with intense historical traces and various ruins.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Meet the Bronze Artist&#39;s Life 3000 Years ago
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Since ancient times, the place where there is water has always been a place of people&#39;s living. Even now, prehistoric people who lived and settled in have chosen a place with water to live. The prehistoric ruins of Jodong-ri, located in Dongyang-myeon, Chungju-si, are large village ruins from the Neolithic Age to the Bronze Age, based on the Namhan River. The large river called Namhan River and the alluvial plains created by the flooding were suitable for people to live. Prehistoric ruins date back to approximately 7000 years. Since the Neolithic began to live for the first time, the Bronze activists continued their agricultural life 3000 years ago.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Excavation and ruins of Jodong-ri History Museum - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/47/53aa1535-c891-4c7e-8837-2bb586f2515f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Excavation and ruins of Jodong-ri History Museum
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Jodong-ri History Museum is located adjacent to the entrance of Dongyang-myeon and Namhan River. It is a place where you can see the discovery process of Jo Dong-ri and various relics. It is composed of Jodong-ri History and Culture Center on the 1st floor, Jodong-ri Farming Room on the 2nd floor, and Memorial Hall for Huh Mun-hoe, agronomist.
   &lt;br/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Bronzeman&#39;s Whirlwind - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/47/5e702f52-cf88-4eb4-9ec2-a74f0f6575f3.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Bronzeman&#39;s Whirlwind
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The prehistoric ruins of Jo Dong-ri became known to the world as the ruins were exposed in 1990 due to heavy rain. Over the next ten years, some of the ruins of the Neolithic era, as well as the ruins of the Bronze Age, as well as the burning seats and huts were excavated. The ruins reveal that prehistoric people lived on a large scale in villages and active farming.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Diorama showing the bronze life - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/47/3ac9b291-b1a2-48e0-92eb-4c78c08b1574.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Diorama showing the bronze life
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   When you cross the bridge made of tempered glass that reproduces the scene of the excavation, you will meet the dioramas that tell the life of the time based on the ruins of the excavated house, umyu-gu, and the seat of burning, earthenware and grains. It is a place where you can spread your imagination through the excavated artifacts. A huge diorama of the bronze fighter who lived in a large village based on the topography of Jodong-ri. The life of the Bronze Age unfolds like a panorama of catching fish or farming by the river, raising livestock, harvesting fruit, and burning pots and baking earthenware.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Diorama showing the bronze life - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/47/18416aa1-36dd-44aa-bd65-27dc6fe5e014.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Diorama showing the bronze life
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   You can also see the bronze life of the bronze fighter. This is a reconstruction of the 7th house found at Jo Dong-ri Prehistoric Site. The figure shows a man who trims the net, a child who grinds grains and shreds, and a woman who bakes fish on fire.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Diorama showing the bronze life - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/47/819d3580-c451-4563-a48a-bcb09e717450.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Diorama showing the bronze life
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Unification Rice with Green Revolution Found in Prehistoric Ruins
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Jodong-ri Agricultural Room on the 2nd floor of the museum is a place where you can examine the use of agricultural artifacts discovered in Jodong-ri and the grains of the time. You can see the picture of the moisturizer used to plow the ground, the vandal knife and scythe used to cut the grain, and the use of the reeds and reed used to peel the fruit or grind grain. Among them, care was not only used to plow the land, but also a multifunctional tool that played a role as a shovel and a hoe. Wouldn&#39;t it be MacGyver knife these days? In the ruins of Jo Dong-ri, various traces of grain were excavated. Wheat was the largest with 723 eggs, and barley and rice, rice, rice, and park and peach seeds were also found. Most of them are carbonized, but it&#39;s easy to see the grain from 3000 years ago.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Bronze Engineer Farm Equipment Moisturizing Restoration - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/47/da35a9e4-05f6-424b-9b3c-fe8f5616f33f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Bronze Engineer Farm Equipment Moisturizing Restoration
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Next to the farm room is a place in commemoration of Dr. Huh Mun-hui, a farmer from Chungju. Dr. Huh, who has made great contributions to Korean agricultural history, has developed a unified rice that opened the rice self-sufficiency era. In Korea, there were four springs, often called “barley hills,” until the 1970s. It was a country that mainly produces rice, but most people did not have a warm meal.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Carbonized barley found in Jodong-ri prehistoric ruins - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/47/c393fd04-c0b0-413a-8219-5490577527ab.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Carbonized barley found in Jodong-ri prehistoric ruins
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Unification rice is a hybrid of Japanese and Taiwanese rice varieties, and is a cultivar developed by three-way breeding of IR8, which was nurtured by the International Rice Research Institute. Rice grown in Korea was weak against wind and pests, and the yield was very low a year. Since the unification of rice since 1972, rice self-sufficiency rate has surpassed 100% with increasing production.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Unification rice developed by Dr. Huh Moon Hoe - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/47/e1ffef0e-46be-41ed-8ff4-182bc9717f27.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Unification rice developed by Dr. Huh Moon Hoe
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Considering the time when we worried about meals 40 years ago, is our life too undeserved? Nowadays, when rice consumption remains unprecedented, it&#39;s a good idea to reflect on Barley Hill&#39;s days. In that sense, the commemoration room for the agronomist Humunmun teacher is a meaningful place.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Agronomist - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/47/79e35059-e3dd-4cf1-b89d-783c6ce31d7d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Agronomist
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Rustic stones that meet at the central tower flowing through the Namhan River
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Various traces from the Three Kingdoms Period to the Goryeo Dynasty remain around the Namhan River, which flows through the Chungju Jungang Pagoda to Yeoju. Crossing Tangeum Bridge is Changdong-ri, the first town in the middle of Pagoda. In Changdong-ri, there are simple, majestic stone towers of the Koryo Dynasty, stone Buddhas, and Mae Buddha.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Chungju Changdong-ri Maaebul View - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/47/0636ba71-5b5d-4484-ab5f-acf869d952ec.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Chungju Changdong-ri Maaebul View
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you cross the Tangeum Bridge for about 1km, you will meet Maebul, Changdong-ri, Chungju to the right. It&#39;s a magic fire carved on a rock wall facing the Namhan River over a small hill. As you climb the hill past the entrance, you will see a steep staircase leading down the river. He unintentionally descends the stairs and is amazed by the appearance of a huge 4 meter tall Buddha. A friendly and stern expression and harsh expression are typical of the Buddha&#39;s love. It seems to be a Buddhist image that wishes for the well-being of those who cross the boat by the Mae Fire, which is seen from the Namhan River flowing toward Yeoju.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Changae-ri Maaebul overlooking the Namhan River - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/47/aad87770-dea1-464e-a40a-dcc14f0bd457.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Changae-ri Maaebul overlooking the Namhan River
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The five-story stone pagoda in Changdong-ri and the stone statue of a stone pharmacist are standing side by side within 200m from Changae-ri Maaebul. It is easy to find the Jungwon Party that makes Cheong Myeongju designated as Chungbuk Intangible Cultural Property No.2.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Five-storied pagoda and Changjo pharmacy - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/47/b885cea6-bdbf-46f5-a059-41b3972166e2.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Five-storied pagoda and Changjo pharmacy
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Changdong-ri Five Storeyed Stone Pagoda and Stone Carved Buddha Statue are also known for the Goryeo Dynasty. The stone statue of the stone pharmacist is carved from the pharmacist&#39;s standing standing on the big stone. If Chang Dong-ri&#39;s Ma-a-bul has a blunt look, the pharmacist&#39;s statue is a cute figure with a gentle smile on his vivid face.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Gentle smile of stone statue - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/47/46802480-fff4-46d2-b06f-c5e885b13541.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Gentle smile of stone statue
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The five-storied pagoda has a slim pagoda on a thick two-story podium, as if two other stones were placed on it. The stone pagoda is from a nearby abandoned site, and the pharmacist statue was taken from a nearby abandoned mine. Standing side by side in a narrow open space, it offers simple yet splendid scenery.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Chungju Changdong-ri Five-story Stone Tower - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/47/a6bad3e0-eaeb-47fb-9c8f-7116dd469dd2.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Chungju Changdong-ri Five-story Stone Tower
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Along the way from the Chungju-guguryeo Vision Exhibition Center to the Chungju-gugur Astronomical Science Museum, if you cross the hill, you will reach Bongwang-ri. On the way up the iron rod that runs along the Hanpocheon flowing into the Namhan River, there is Mae Buddha statue in Bongwangri, Chungju designated as treasure 1401.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;13&#34; id3=&#34;15&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Bonghuangri Maae Buddha Statue - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/47/e9d744e0-1a84-436d-96f5-72e8e1ad1391.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Bonghuangri Maae Buddha Statue
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Climbing steep stone staircase and iron staircase leads to the first rock climbing with 8 hearts. Various Buddha statues are engraved, including chants, offerings, and bodhisattva statues.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;15&#34; id3=&#34;16&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Travelers looking at Penghuangri Maae Buddha Statue - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/47/6b6b5e35-555a-4247-9f81-22977a57c07d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Travelers looking at Penghuangri Maae Buddha Statue
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It was difficult to find all eight Buddha statues because it was built in the Three Kingdoms period and endured a long time. As if you are searching for hidden pictures, you can find them by looking at them one by one.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;17&#34; id3=&#34;17&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Statues and chants of the Phoenix Buddha - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/47/0b8197e6-77c7-44ff-9d42-622423b461a1.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Statues and chants of the Phoenix Buddha
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you climb a little higher than the Buddha statue, there is a statue of the Buddha. Five fires which put the cross seat on the Buddha&#39;s widespread eye attract attention. If you turn your view in front of the Maae Buddha statue, you will come to the scenery of Hanpocheon, which is merged into the Namhan River, and the high mountain.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;19&#34; id3=&#34;18&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Fireworks carved on the giant boat on Ma&#39;ae - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/47/0ad2e8c3-886a-4337-afc8-dba67a601ea7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Fireworks carved on the giant boat on Ma&#39;ae
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel info
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Jodong-ri Prehistoric Museum
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Address: 15, Jodong 1-gil, Dongyang-myeon, Chungju-si, Chungbuk
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Contact: 043-850-3992
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Nearby destinations
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Madang Garden: Freshwater Maeuntang / 441, Jideung-ro, Dongyang-myeon, Chungju-si / 043-851-4077
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.마당가든.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.마당가든.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Unjeong Restaurant: Olgang Haejangguk / 3432-1, Jungwon-daero, Chungju-si / 043-847-2820
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Ahn Sungwoo Hanwoo: Hanwoo / 1512 Gagok-ro, Angseong-myeon, Chungju-si / 043-855-5808
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Accommodation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Bonghuang Natural Recreation Forest: 540, Suryongbonghwang-gil, Gaeum-myeon, Chungju-si / 043-850-7315
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Filim 37.2 Hotel: 17, Yeonwon-ro, Yeonsu-dong, Chungju-si / 043-842-0515
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Beautiful house: 268 Jideung-ro, Dongyang-myeon, Chungju-si / 043-851-4022
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was made in February 2015. It may change afterwards, so please check before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Information such as text, photos, and videos used in this article is copyrighted by Korea Tourism Organization, so unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Take the train, Chungju Samtan Amusement Park &amp; Indeungsan</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/take-the-train-chungju-samtan-amusement-park-indeungsan-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2020 16:47:42 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/take-the-train-chungju-samtan-amusement-park-indeungsan-7/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-title=&#34;take-the-train-chungju-samtan-amusement-park-indeungsan--7&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Samtan Station and Chungbuk Line Train - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/7/dd2d3621-407a-44a5-a92d-85491648882b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Samtan Station and Chungbuk Line Train
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Take the train, Chungju Samtan Amusement Park &amp;amp; Indeungsan
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Water play that reminds me of summer and water play in scenic nature is a fresh play. With the romantic romance of the train, the pleasure of traveling multiplies, regardless of time.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In front of the train station, Samtan Amusement Park where water, forest and mountains are combined. Camping is easy to leave, and it is easy to use the accommodations that are located next to the amusement park. It is also a good idea to have a regular mountain climbing mountain. On the way back, enjoy sightseeing near Chungju Station, and your trip will be more enriching. Let&#39;s leave by train, Chungju!
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Jupocheon from the Samtan Bridge - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/7/3457c21d-7a59-4b99-a0a6-5098890c3892.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Jupocheon from the Samtan Bridge
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Samtan Amusement Park by train track
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Samtan Amusement Park is located at Sancheok-myeon, Chungju-si, Chungbuk. The train to Samtan Amusement Park is good. This is because there is an amusement park about 500 meters from Samtan Station. Pass the Samtan Bridge right in front of the station and follow the road to Myeongdol Village. Samtan means three streams, such as government office, pine and barnacle. Jupocheon, which leads to the Namhan River, flows around the amusement park.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Myeongdol Village Entrance Seats and Sports Park - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/7/1055277e-1c3b-4948-be1f-b551560680f3.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Myeongdol Village Entrance Seats and Sports Park
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In the past, the people were rare enough to stay with them, but in 1958 trains passing through Samtan Station were extended to form villages and amusement parks. In June 2000, a sports park was created next to the amusement park. Recently, a natural grass soccer field has been set up in the center of the park. Most of the facilities in the amusement park can be used free of charge, but lawn parks require a maintenance fee after booking.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Athletic Park - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/7/89f15461-67ed-430b-8e1a-e73f8f84aff7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Athletic Park
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In addition to the turf field, the vacant lot can also be used as a camping ground. The large campsite makes it easy to find a place to go. There are also facilities such as toilet, drinking fountain and parking lot.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Jopocheon and amusement park gravel under the train tracks - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/7/a32e9c70-1b31-48ef-be36-24b10fa5271d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Jopocheon and amusement park gravel under the train tracks
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The malls along the funfair ramp combine restaurants, canteens and bed and breakfasts. You can rent or buy some fishing gear as well as some simple fishing gear. Every summer, residents work together to improve the environment around the park. This year, from July 16th to August 15th, an environmental information center and Saemaul Library will be run by 200 residents. The Environmental Information Center is a voluntary activity that creates a clean environment for vacationers by removing garbage and collecting recyclables around the amusement park. Saemaul Library has over 2,000 books available for free rental and leads a healthy holiday culture. Residents in charge of the river reside in preparation for safety accidents.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Midsummer Willow - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/7/4eddd09e-695f-4feb-8ec8-5d8832e23218.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Midsummer Willow
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The amusement park is surrounded by mountains, and the odd rock cliffs are superbly located across the main stream. The river is wide and the water level is varied, so it is good for children to adults. Gravel fields spread out next to the sports park. There is a lush forest on top of it, and rich trees such as willows make the shade.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Amusement park next to sports park - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/7/fd0c5b13-3333-4f3a-882b-2189ec1ef132.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Amusement park next to sports park
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Receive the energy of three
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Indeungsan is a 667m high mountain located just behind the amusement park. It belongs to Cheondeungsan (807m) in the north and Jideungsan (535m) in the south, and belongs to Samdeungsan which means Cheon, Ji, and Injae. Sandeungsan is known for being sheltered from the mountains and deep in valleys. In addition, the legend is said that if one crosses all three mountains, one wish will be fulfilled.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Train passing railroad crossing by the amusement park - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/7/38c59bea-d86c-494f-b814-2f9e9751aab8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Train passing railroad crossing by the amusement park
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Cheondeungsan Mountain is named after the top of the mountain. The trail is not easy. Along with Bakdaljae, he became famous as a popular song &amp;lt;Crying Bakdaljae&amp;gt;, but in fact, about 9km away from Cheondeungsan and Wonseocheon, it belongs to Mt.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Samtan Amusement Park from the Beginning of the Trail - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/7/ea50c910-9362-406c-ab51-93e03d8f3d65.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Samtan Amusement Park from the Beginning of the Trail
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Jideung Mountain is a mountain that is connected to Indeung Mountain. In climbing is a mountain that can be climbed without difficulty. While walking to the summit, the scenery is beautiful, and on a good day, you can look down to Chungju Lake.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Forest road heading to the observatory - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/7/cff814b1-5bce-4e6d-b443-818d2e4cc196.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Forest road heading to the observatory
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   When the weather is too hot, it&#39;s a good idea to walk along the forest road to the observation deck.
   &lt;br/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Hiking trail by the valley - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/7/93e21d10-1218-4bb6-b123-6b6285431876.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Hiking trail by the valley
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It is about 3km from Samtan Amusement Park to Observation Deck. Passing the mall opposite the amusement park leads you to the apple orchard. When you enter the road, you will be able to walk around the mountain. Do not enter the valley road, it is good to follow the road. There are no milestones on the mountain trail next to the valley, so you can wander around.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Observation Deck 700m - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/7/814ab089-28ea-49be-bc9a-0f1f14e92b55.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Observation Deck 700m
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you climb about 1.7km from the entrance, you will come to a three-way street. Follow the signs to the right for about 700m to reach the observatory. If you climb the observatory, you can see the Cheondeungsan Mountain opposite you and face the river flowing under the mountain.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The area of Jideungsan from the Cheonjiin Observatory - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/7/af0bc49d-f6ef-4237-93b7-38d7133b51e0.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The area of Jideungsan from the Cheonjiin Observatory
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The train tracks seen from the mountain are also superb views.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;14&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Village seen from the observation deck - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/7/03a5af3a-844c-4d26-9248-0c628cc3d810.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Village seen from the observation deck
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Chungju caliber on the way back
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Before heading home, let&#39;s go from Samtan Station to Chungju Station in time for the train. Jungang Top Park is located about 7km from Chungju Station. It is called the tower in the center of Korea. Its historical name is Joongwon Papyeong-ri Seven-storied pagoda. It is the largest stone pagoda in the Unified Shilla Era. It is currently designated as National Treasure No. 6. In 1992, a historic park was built around the pagoda, and in 2007, the park facility was built along with the reorganization and repair work around the central pagoda. Inside the park are Chungju Museum 1 and 2, an open-air museum and a music hall. A music fountain is installed on Tangeum Lake in front of the park.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Next to the park is the World Liquor Museum. Visit the Wine History and Culture Museum for information about wine. There is also an experience facility where you can listen to the whiskey ripening process and taste the whiskey in oak barrels. A collection of beers, spirits, and oriental alcohol from around the world. The liquor of our country attracts people&#39;s attention by displaying traditional and modern wine more carefully. In addition to the exhibition halls, a separate education center will be operated and mainstream culture and fermentation science experiences will be conducted. Anyone can join in advance.
   &lt;br/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Jungwon Tappyeong Seven-storied Pagoda in Jungang Pagoda Park - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/7/1815917a-14fb-4b55-a73e-1f0c5a1e4ff7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Jungwon Tappyeong Seven-storied Pagoda in Jungang Pagoda Park
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   There are many charming restaurants around the museum. Next door is Tangeumho International Rowing Center. Tangeum Lake was formed during the construction of Chungju Dam in 1985. Until 2004, the stadium was used as a water sports park for the general public and as a training ground for rowers. In summer, the Chungju Lake Festival is held in this area, and water sports activities are free for the general public.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;15&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Museum of World Liquor Culture - Chungju, Chungbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/7/fd614432-3993-46f5-a130-a7937fa12feb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Museum of World Liquor Culture
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel info
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Samtan Amusement Park
      &lt;br/&gt;
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     Address: Myeongseo-ri, Sancheok-myeon, Chungju-si, Chungbuk
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Contact: 043-850-2400
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Nearby tourist spots
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Joongang Pagoda Historical Park
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    : 11, Toppyeong-ri, Gaeum-myeon, Chungju-si / 043-842-0531
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     World Liquor Culture Museum Liqueurium
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    : 12, Tapjeongan-gil, Gaeum-myeon, Chungju-si / 043-855-7333
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Tangeumho International Rowing Center
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    : 124, Jungangtap-gil, Gaeum-myeon, Chungju-si / 043-850-6670
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2.Nearby restaurants and accommodations
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Orange House
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    : 6-1, Samyeoul-gil, Sancheok-myeon, Chungju-si / 010-3290-2324
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Zelkova house
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    : Myeongdol, Myeongseori, Sancheok-myeon, Chungju-si / 426-852-7795
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Samtan Minbak
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    : 4, Samyeoul-gil, Sancheok-myeon, Chungju-si / 043-852-6639
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Solbat Cottage
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    : 510-3, Myeongseo-ri, Sancheok-myeon, Chungju-si / 043-852-8495
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Ilheung Guest House
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    : 484-4, Myeongseo-ri, Sancheok-myeon, Chungju-si / 043-852-6751
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was written in July 2014. It may change afterwards, so please check before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Information such as text, photos, and videos used in this article is copyrighted by Korea Tourism Organization, so unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>