<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Yongin-si on Every Corner of Korea</title>
    <link>https://codecorea.github.io/tags/yongin-si/</link>
    <description>Every Corner of Korea (Yongin-si)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2020 10:34:23 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="https://codecorea.github.io/tags/yongin-si/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Folk Village, Winter Romantics - Yongin-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/folk-village-winter-romantics-306/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2020 10:34:23 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/folk-village-winter-romantics-306/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Yongin-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;folk-village-winter-romantics--306&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Korean Folk Village&#39;s entrance, generals looking happy - Yongin-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/306/69c10d49-bc0a-422e-93a6-0cd102024a07.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Korean Folk Village&#39;s entrance, generals looking happy
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Folk Village, Winter Romantics
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Yongin-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   I saw a piece of wood erected on a plate of water at a vinyl house flower shop. There is no root, but one green leaf growing on a piece of wood leaves a long aftertaste. Sometimes when your head is heavy and your heart feels dry, imagine putting your mind on a plate of water. Then I draw a picture of a leaf coming out of my mind, but it still works quite well. This time, I tried to raise my mind and body in the &#39;Korean Folk Village&#39;, a village where folklore is high.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    On October 3, 1974, the Korean Folk Village was opened. Beyond the door is the space where the lives of the people of the Joseon Dynasty, which became increasingly distant as time passed, were revealed. Although it is not a person&#39;s house, it is a house where people lived, but the story of flowers and folklore is engulfed by vivid reproductions of the very rare and invisible old places.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Korean folk villages on winter weekdays are relatively rare in a quiet atmosphere. Probably because it is cold. As she was discovered that she couldn&#39;t be hidden by the crowds, the beautiful scenery in every corner continues. Experience programs can be participated without waiting, and there is no need to hurry and hurry because of the waiting person. It&#39;s great to be able to sit around and watch the performances. To enjoy this, it is very helpful to wear warm clothes, attach a hot pack that can be glued close to the exposed area, and prepare warm water in a water bottle.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Winter mood in every corner of the folk village - Yongin-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/306/e033294a-8acd-44d2-9716-5ed6397cd7c7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Winter mood in every corner of the folk village
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    It is difficult to describe &#39;folklore&#39; by pinching it. It is briefly defined as &#39;a word that encompasses customs, beliefs, skills, and traditions of life related to civil life&#39;, but the depth and wide categories contained in it are not simple. It is best to move your body to find out when you do not seem to know the same thing. The Korean Folk Village is a good alternative. A village of about 1 million square meters decorated with folk-related traditional houses, performances, experience programs, exhibits, and marketplaces. This large space is full of folklore.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Winter mood in every corner of the folk village - Yongin-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/306/e5ea2f82-c67c-4ae0-a070-99181626487a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Winter mood in every corner of the folk village
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Memories reproduced from hands
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The theme prepared by the Korean Folk Village this winter is an experience to experience the wise skills and wise life of the ancestors of the &#39;Winter Dongdong Country House Story&#39;. In addition, you can feel the expert&#39;s touch in that area, which is a better opportunity.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    He enjoyed a game called kite fights. It is a game of blowing a kite and twisting each other&#39;s strings to cut the other&#39;s strings or drop the kite. So, I also fed grass with glass powder on the kite line. As I follow the hand that leads the kite making experience, memories of kites come to mind one by one. Shield kite is complete. Hanji is firm, and the flat and curved parts are clean without wrinkles.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Kite making experience - Yongin-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/306/21a42458-ad3e-48f5-a63d-94422adb9738.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Kite making experience
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Don&#39;t miss the &#39;twinning the straw&#39; experience. In early winter, farmers gathered and brooded the young. At the end of the harvest, he gathered the remaining rice straw and made a new one to replace the old sandals, yolks, and cords, and prepared for the New Year in advance. Farmer&#39;s wisdom is not unreasonable.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &#34;Don&#39;t die!&#34; After hitting the top with the line that the arm fell, it felt like I was burning white. Children seem to be playing with a horn on their tops these days. The experience of making a handcraft while showing the traditional shape of the top will be a pleasant memory for both children and adults. In addition, there is also a &#39;Ondolbang Experience&#39; where you can learn how to make a traditional ritual using Yeopjeon and Hanji, and learn the principles of Ondolbang by burning the fire yourself.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Twine experience - Yongin-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/306/fb232cbd-ab0f-4aff-847a-c2a0987bd2d8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Twine experience
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Find personality in traditional housesLearn wisdom in traditional folklore
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The reason why the traditional play experience is felt is the traditional house. There are about 270 houses in the folk village, and local and private houses and Yangban houses are located everywhere. Let&#39;s learn what the characteristics of each house are and learn the individuality. Each feature will be seen in the room where the yard lived in the Toho house, the entrance to the house of the person in the rice field, the barn of a local farmhouse, and the chimney of a mountainous farmhouse. We recommend that you stop by and take warm memories while visiting.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Southern Gate - Yongin-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/306/72ee77fc-50e8-462d-aadb-f8d02ce4aa1d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Southern Gate
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The roof rose from a house. &#34;I&#39;ll give you a bird,&#34; the roof on which my teeth were picked up when I was young. Children living in apartments do not know, and these customs are displayed in the traditional folk museum. Is this folklore only in Korea? At the World Folk Museum, folk heritage is collected and displayed in various countries.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Traditional Folk Museum, Old Maternity Tools - Yongin-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/306/f1a9f961-ae23-478d-bb24-27c6731eb04b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Traditional Folk Museum, Old Maternity Tools
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    If you are hungry, let&#39;s go to the marketplace prepared in the folk village. It is perfect to see performances or events after filling the boat. In the Korean Folk Village, you can see Nongak play, tightrope, and horse riding performances even in winter.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Winter Guest Award - Yongin-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/306/448b7a2c-c0ca-4309-828d-0c56ad000407.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Winter Guest Award
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Korean Folk Village Performances Three Musketeers: &#39;Nongak play, tightrope, horse riding&#39;
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It is best to see Nongaknori performance in the field. Impressed by television is less than half the scene. You lift your body and turn your hair and feel the wind pushed by the gesture. In the meantime, the percussion instruments and the shadow of the percussion band are busy. The child who was watching the show jumps in succession.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The National Intangible Cultural Heritage No. 58 &#39;Tightrope&#39; is also a specialty of the Korean Folk Village. In the old days, it was a precious performance that was only seen in crowded places during the holidays. The dexter on the line was called &#39;Zulkwangdae&#39; and is an old culture that has been passed down since the Three Kingdoms period. In winter, the snow melted on the strings, making them slippery, and I was worried that my hands and feet would freeze in the cold of the river, but I was worried about the delicate balance. Besides, it&#39;s fun to talk over the line and spit it out.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Nongak Play - Yongin-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/306/02b44293-cc39-4121-9b4c-fd21cd280a9c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Nongak Play
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Based on the literature, you can see &#39;Masang Martial Arts&#39;, which has been proved. Performances that lead to laughter and laughter are also seen on horses. In addition, the performances performed by horses and humans, including hiding the body next to the body of the horse, shooting a bow on the horse, and throwing a spear, are amazing and surprising.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;funambulism - Yongin-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/306/281d324c-ae3a-4db8-9811-989bec070c58.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     funambulism
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The child, who was walking around the folk village holding hands of the parents, suddenly becomes an adult and visits the folk village. A child is hanging in his hand. As such, the folk village is a place of remembrance and a place to soothe hometown nostalgia.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34; - Yongin-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/306/b2d0f817-2a70-4ba5-adf9-8a0e06eea078.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;topmr&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Restaurants near
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    -Gijijip: Sundubu Korean Restaurant / 55 Baeknamjun-ro, Giheung-gu, Yongin-si, Gyeonggi-do / 031-282-2708
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Kama Myeongga: Pot rice set meal, galbi / 638-11 Bajeong-dong, Giheung-gu, Yongin-si, Gyeonggi-do / 031-265-9231
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Gomsol Maru: Mushroom hotpot / 2181 Yonggu-daero, Giheung-gu, Yongin-si, Gyeonggi-do / 031-282-2967
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Park Cheomji: Chueotang / 128, Gongse-ro, Giheung-gu, Yongin-si, Gyeonggi-do / 031-286-3311
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Rooms
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    -Windsor Castle Tourist Hotel: 212, Sinjeong-ro, Giheung-gu, Yongin-si, Gyeonggi-do / 031-895-5000
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    -Yongin Natural Recreation Forest: 220, Chobu-ro, Mohyeon-myeon, Cheoin-gu, Yongin-si, Gyeonggi-do / 031-336-0040
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.yonginforest.net/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.yonginforest.net/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    -Hanhwa Resort Yongin: 79 Bongmu-ro 153beon-gil, Namsa-myeon, Cheoin-gu, Yongin-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.hanwharesort.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.hanwharesort.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was updated in January 2014, and may be changed later, so be sure to check it before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enjoy adventure by becoming a flying squirrel in the deep forest, Yongin Natural Recreation Forest - Yongin-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/enjoy-adventure-by-becoming-a-flying-squirrel-in-the-deep-forest-yongin-natural-recreation-forest-198/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 07:08:14 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/enjoy-adventure-by-becoming-a-flying-squirrel-in-the-deep-forest-yongin-natural-recreation-forest-198/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Yongin-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;enjoy-adventure-by-becoming-a-flying-squirrel-in-the-deep-forest-yongin-natural-recreation-forest--198&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Ecore Adventure, flying like a flying squirrel - Yongin-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/198/b6f2fe5b-f923-4fc4-a423-afe36cc5486e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Ecore Adventure, flying like a flying squirrel
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Enjoy adventure by becoming a flying squirrel in the deep forest, Yongin Natural Recreation Forest
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Yongin-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    “Yah ~” “Exciting!”
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Children&#39;s exciting cry echoes through the forest. It is a flying squirrel that can move from tree to tree in an instant. The expression that was scared of the first adventurous adventure suddenly changed to a serious expression. This is an eco-venture designed to help you enjoy the adventure by picking old trees. It is a different adventure to enjoy forest and nature with minimal facilities.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Deep mountain adventure
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The Yongin Natural Recreation Forest, Eco-D Venture, tends to be full on the weekends, but it&#39;s easy to make a reservation during the week. However, it may be convenient to make a reservation in advance, as it may not be available for group reservations.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Experienced students receiving safety training - Yongin-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/198/fff13a9e-7b52-464a-a703-3152bca4fb60.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Experienced students receiving safety training
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Make a reservation with the 10 o&#39;clock experience and go to Eco-D Venture. The morning forest road is absolutely refreshing. It is available six times a day, at 10 am, 11 am, 2 pm, 3 pm, 4 pm, and 5 pm. Each seat has 20 people except 5 pm. Even in the woods, it&#39;s hot in the middle of the day, so it&#39;s a good idea to make a reservation in the morning or late.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Safety hooks and pulleys must be carefully used - Yongin-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/198/81d57798-843a-4f8c-8213-b70bdeb99ea9.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Safety hooks and pulleys must be carefully used
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   When you arrive at Ecored Venture, check your reservation first, and then wear hard hat, gloves, and safety equipment. Children&#39;s gloves are also available, so don&#39;t worry. After all safety equipment is worn, safety training is conducted prior to the actual operation. At this time, it tells you how to use the equipment and cautions. When grabbing the pulley used to go on a rope, one hand should hold the pulley and the other hand should hold the string. When the pulley rolls, never bring your hand in front of it, as there is a risk of injury.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;How to catch pulleys safely - Yongin-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/198/043a1f9c-c787-4f73-bd66-04a6cd797a07.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     How to catch pulleys safely
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   After completing the training, move to the small practice space located next to you to practice hooking and pulling out the hook and putting on and off the pulley. When a child is young, the grip strength is weak, so it is not easy to use equipment, but if you practice a few times and learn the tips, you can do it yourself.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Monkey Course and Chimpanzee Course - Yongin-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/198/4d13b1a6-7c21-41fe-bfaf-4363a8072f6a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Monkey Course and Chimpanzee Course
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It&#39;s finally time for action. For infants, the guardians are watching the first few times, and if you need help, it is a good idea to help right away. If you have multiple visitors, you can hurry up and worry about the back person, so it is good to take time and do it one by one.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Thrilling King Kong course - Yongin-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/198/67d9932f-5e22-443e-bb0e-efe4740ee023.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Thrilling King Kong course
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Courses are divided into monkey, chimpanzee, and king kong courses. The Monkey Course can be challenged for toddlers 5-6 years old, the Chimpanzee Course is for children 7-10 years old, and the King Kong Course is for adults 11 years old and older. The King Kong course is made of taller and more distant trees than the monkey and chimpanzee courses, so it feels quite thrilling. The Monkey Course and Chimpanzee Course do not differ significantly in difficulty, so even toddlers can try the Chimpanzee Course. You can do two courses together or just one, but if you are a king, it is good to try both courses. It is too short for one course, and the children are disappointed because the equipment usage is over.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;13&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The feet shake, the more carefully - Yongin-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/198/2d22d14e-41df-4d1c-ac4f-66b3fd4fe6d1.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The feet shake, the more carefully
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Muho Descalard climbs up the tree on a ladder, Pathel crosses like a stepping stone by connecting two lines between trees, Filled Ssangju crosses the net, crosses a small house on a tree, and boards from high to low Various adventures await, such as the tyrolien slipping down and the tono passing through a wooden cylinder. The name is strange and difficult, but there is no problem at all without knowing the name of each point. All you have to do is to hang the safety rings one by one and do not hurry and do it slowly.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;15&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Landing nicely on a pulley - Yongin-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/198/6f14a356-d11a-41bf-aeb7-fd03f195f64b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Landing nicely on a pulley
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   When I receive safety education, every time a child who is overwhelmed nervously challenges one by one, he gains confidence, feels fun, and brightens his face. It is especially exciting when flying through a tree in a pulley. I feel like I&#39;m Tarzan flying freely through the jungle. After all the courses are over, the children shout “One more time!” With the above-mentioned expression. It takes about an hour to complete safety training and finish the monkey course and chimpanzee course. The duration of the King Kong course is similar. There is no age limit, but you need to be over 110cm tall to challenge.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;17&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Passing through the cylinders of the monkey course - Yongin-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/198/cf3ef2c7-cd1e-40db-bcd4-33a76db94fb8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Passing through the cylinders of the monkey course
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Campsite and trails
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Many people use Yongin Natural Recreation Forest, but campsites are also popular. Even in the middle of winter, it is difficult to grab a site on the weekend. You can get a feeling of being surrounded by nature by constructing a site naturally by cascading between dense trees and on a mountain slope. It&#39;s cumbersome to have your car parked in the parking lot and move your hand luggage, but thanks to it, you can see it separately at night and hear the bugs and camp as naturally as possible.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A campsite surrounded by forest - Yongin-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/198/028518ea-1771-4388-8bce-24a95c445a54.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A campsite surrounded by forest
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   There are several playgrounds at the entrance to the campsite, all of which are forest playgrounds for children. There are no rides common in apartment complexes. Here, the playground is also “green”. Riding a horse, climbing on a slide of a wooden house, and holding a line on a wooden barrel connected between wooden pillars and crossing it. Even if you play all day, the kids don&#39;t seem bored.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Eco-friendly forest playground decorated with wood - Yongin-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/198/72fcce19-68a8-4c46-977e-0f896b400eeb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Eco-friendly forest playground decorated with wood
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Wetland garden for walking
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Ecod Venture is located in the innermost part of the recreational forest. On the way, you will naturally pass through the wetlands. The deck is spread over the wetland area, so it is easy to walk lightly. There are also several stairs, but you can also look around with a stroller, mainly made of ramps. The sound of a frog rumbling around a small pond where you can observe lotus flowers, aquatic plants, and insects, and flowers bloom from time to time by collecting wild flowers and native flowers around us. As you climb up the promenade, there are also salamander habitats, as well as signs of “snake vigilance”. Be careful as snakes can actually pass over promenades.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Phytoncide Promenade - Yongin-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/198/5b2cae54-6916-4c4b-8c86-d5f44673def8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Phytoncide Promenade
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The lawn plaza, which is the front yard of the recreational forest, is a place where visitors on the weekend install a mat, tent, and tarp. From last spring, as the weekend visitors were switched to the reservation system, the dense grassy squares were freed up and parking and vehicle congestion problems were eliminated. If you want to enjoy outings on the weekends on the day of the Ecod Ventures and Recreation Forest, you must make a reservation. There is no need to make a separate admission reservation when using the accommodation.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Visitors observing lotus flowers in wetland garden - Yongin-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/198/bb4437f8-0f4a-428d-98cf-f0210ed364eb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Visitors observing lotus flowers in wetland garden
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Yongin Natural Recreation Forest is also a paragliding mecca. Several paragliding specialists are located at the entrance of the recreational forest, and there is an active factory at the top of Jeonggwangsan (563m) that rises behind the recreational forest. On a weekday, a paraglider that seemed rare, flies at once as if it bloomed in the sky on the weekend. The arrival point is just below the recreational forest, so it&#39;s interesting to see it landing by turning on the lawn square. There are also two-person experience flights accompanied by experts, so if you are curious, take the courage to challenge.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Paraglider gliding over the grassy square - Yongin-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/198/cdb85e78-55bc-48b1-9d93-c92201d33b50.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Paraglider gliding over the grassy square
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Yongin Natural Recreation Forest
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Address: 220, Chobu-ro, Mohyeon-myeon, Cheoin-gu, Yongin-si, Gyeonggi-do
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Inquiries: 031-336-0040
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.yonginforest.net&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     www.yonginforest.net
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Restaurants near
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Old Site: Hanwoo Flower Sirloin and Hanwoo Gukbap / 9 Neungwon-ro 132beon-gil, Mohyeon-myeon, Chein-gu, Yongin-si / 031-339-6630
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Cheil Restaurant: Sundaeguk / 11 Baekam-ro 201beon-gil, Baekam-myeon, Cheoin-gu, Yongin-si / 031-332-4608
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Kong Madang: Cheonggukjang / 18, Nampyeong-ro, Yangmyeon, Cheoin-gu, Yongin-si / 031-338-0821
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Rooms
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Hotel River: 73, Galcheon-ro 7beon-gil, Giheung-gu, Yongin-si / 031-283-3601 ~ 3
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.hotelriver.co.kr/kr/index/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.hotelriver.co.kr/kr/index/
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Q (Q) Hotel: 10-3 Jeondaero 110beon-gil, Pogok-eup, Cheoin-gu, Yongin-si / 031-339-8881 ~ 2
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.qhotel.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.qhotel.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Yangji Pine Resort: 112, Nampyeong-ro, Yangji-myeon, Cheoin-gu, Yongin-si / 031-338-2001
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.pineresort.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.pineresort.com/
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was updated in April 2018, and may be changed later, so please check before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>