<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Seongdong-gu on Every Corner of Korea</title>
    <link>https://codecorea.github.io/tags/seongdong-gu/</link>
    <description>Every Corner of Korea (Seongdong-gu)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2020 10:34:20 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="https://codecorea.github.io/tags/seongdong-gu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Autumn colored tricolor seoul landscape - Seongdong-gu, Seoul, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/autumn-colored-tricolor-seoul-landscape-303/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2020 10:34:20 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/autumn-colored-tricolor-seoul-landscape-303/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Seongdong-gu, Seoul, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;autumn-colored-tricolor-seoul-landscape--303&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Maple tree I met at the beginning of the road to Sammaksa - Seongdong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/303/c0d0661e-5649-4752-9b7b-fac025781ae0.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Maple tree I met at the beginning of the road to Sammaksa
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Autumn colored tricolor seoul landscape
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Seongdong-gu, Seoul, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Rivers, mountains, and fields are all over the country. Seoul&#39;s fall is no exception, so you can feel a deep fall by selling a little bit. Enjoy the autumn scenery of Seoul by walking through the forest path from the entrance to Gwanaksan Mountain Trail at the entrance of Gwanaksan Mountain at the main gate of Seoul National University.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   From the yellow ginkgo grove to the shining night view of Seoul
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   When you enter the entrance of Seoul Forest 9, there is a colony of ginkgo trees on the left. Although it is not large in size, dense ginkgo groves are colored yellow by forming a forest. There are many ginkgo trees in Seoul, but most of them are Garosu-gil, which is lined with two lines. However, Ginkgo biloba in Seoul Forest formed a colony in one place.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Seoul Forest Ginkgo Community - Seongdong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/303/8912b839-2d81-4de8-ac84-b3adf1ac1b50.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Seoul Forest Ginkgo Community
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   As if the bamboo forest covered the sky, the ginkgo forest covered the sky. People sit on benches all over the place to read books, talk or share food. Enjoy the romance of the ginkgo grove properly.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Seoul Forest Maple Road - Seongdong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/303/01176001-1e1b-4d5a-8086-601887c28955.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Seoul Forest Maple Road
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Exit the ginkgo grove and look around the forest in Seoul. The scenery with the pond is soft. The red maple road stands out on the way to the hills of the wind. I fold it with my legs on the deer&#39;s beach. Overlooking a deer enjoying a relaxing time under the trees in autumn. The branches of the weeping willows on the shore of the lake flutter under the snow. In the distance, the summit of Eungbongsan Mountain is visible.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Seoul Forest Deer Vendor - Seongdong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/303/1213956e-cd17-48dd-9eb1-85c3c73b5450.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Seoul Forest Deer Vendor
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   As you continue along the bridge, the road meets the Han River dune bikes and pedestrian roads. The sunset is short, and the sunset blooms early. The silhouette of Donghodaegyo Bridge and Oksudong Hill creates a deep autumn evening landscape with the Han River shining in gold.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Han River Dunchi-gil, where the sunset is colored - Seongdong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/303/718d70ac-c405-4634-b2b2-e75722a9456a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Han River Dunchi-gil, where the sunset is colored
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   When you go back to Jungnangcheon, which flows into the Han River, you will see a low bridge. It is a so-called rainbow bridge. Cross the bridge and turn left and walk about 630m until you reach the Kumho Passing Tunnel. Enter the tunnel and exit at the right exit. If you cross the crossing and go about 50m, you will see another crossing. If you walk across the street and walk to the right, there is a staircase going up to Eungbong Mountain next to the road.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Birds leisurely enjoying the sunset of the Han River - Seongdong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/303/ba4d65ab-5724-4edf-804c-ad49c44c0eb5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Birds leisurely enjoying the sunset of the Han River
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Eungbongsan Mountain is less than 100m high, so you can climb it easily. A sperm was located in the summit. It is said that Taejo Lee Seong-gye, who founded Joseon, hunted hawks here. It has been said that many people have come here to enjoy the scenery of the Hangang River as one of the most renowned places in Seoul to enjoy the scenery.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Night view from Eungbong Mountain - Seongdong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/303/563742ac-263e-4adc-904e-7aae6e778639.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Night view from Eungbong Mountain
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    As the sun goes down, a street lamp lights up on the Eungbongsan Trail. Eungbongsan Mountain is widely known as a night view location. The forest of Gangnam, the apartment complex of Apgujeong-dong, the cars on and off the road, the street lights, and the lights on the bridge along the Han River combine to create a spectacular night scene.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;14&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Night view from Eungbong Mountain - Seongdong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/303/f3f4abdb-c94b-474f-ba27-07bf5aa1acce.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Night view from Eungbong Mountain
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Exotic scenery created by Metasequoia and Italian Poplar
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    From the bus stop in front of Exit 7 of Dangsan Station, take the metro 9707 and get off at the next stop (Nanji Hangang Park), and you will see the World Cup Park Metasequoia Road.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Metasequoia trees lined up on a 900 m straight trail. Right next to the Metasequoia Road, an Italian poplar tree, much taller than this, made a huge barrier.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;World Cup Park Metasequoia Road - Seongdong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/303/ce3797cd-542f-4a5a-a21f-ae681f2e9330.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     World Cup Park Metasequoia Road
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   A trail made by two giant trees gathers at that end to a vanishing point. People walking from the vanishing point feel like a haze. In this landscape, I think it would be nice if there was at least one person passing by a bicycle, but a bicycle slowly approached from a distance. A bike runs around the dirt road. The trail looks more fresh.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;World Cup Park Metasequoia Road - Seongdong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/303/1da7c3fd-7e19-4354-9652-d5cf4c8bf413.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     World Cup Park Metasequoia Road
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Even after the Metasequoia Road, the trail continues. If you follow the path, the path to Heaven Park and the path to Peace Square and World Cup Stadium are divided.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The landscape lined with Italian poplars is also unusual. - Seongdong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/303/4a5ced2a-8b2f-4c2e-bf0f-ed63902c2923.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The landscape lined with Italian poplars is also unusual.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    When you climb the sky park, the silver grass shakes against the backdrop of the end of the sunset. When going back, choose the stairs. At the beginning of the stairs, Seomyeon World Cup Stadium, Peace Park, and the Han River can be seen at a glance. The trees in the park stained with autumn leaves are burning.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;World Cup Park from the stairs going up to Sky Park - Seongdong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/303/b9a9cff6-ae2c-4cea-a7ad-29d5effae3ef.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     World Cup Park from the stairs going up to Sky Park
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Burning mountain
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    In front of Gwanak Mountain Trail, the main gate of Seoul National University, we meet autumn on a 4.4km mountain path leading to Sammaksa Temple in front of Gwanak Mountain City Library.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Walk along a gentle pavement similar to flat land. The trees covered the sky and red maple leaves all over the place attract attention. If the base of the mountain is this much, I would like to see the autumn leaves over the top. There are several paths, but you only need to follow the paved highway. At the end of the pavement, you meet a maple tree that has been properly watered. People coming and going are too busy gathering around the trees and taking pictures.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Gwanaksan City Library at the entrance of Gwanaksan Trail - Seongdong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/303/98cd92b8-e2cb-42e9-867a-0ada8519fbf6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Gwanaksan City Library at the entrance of Gwanaksan Trail
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   There is a wave of yellow and red autumn leaves all over the mountain road, which is 100 m from there. People who stopped walking while taking pictures fill the road. Mountain roads are also stagnant. After the colors of the leaves are carved on the whole body, people begin to walk step by step. Dirt roads, stone roads, and wooden stairs repeatedly appear without steep climbs. A wooden table and a chair were placed in a wide area under the shade of a tree. It may be an implied middle shelter. Many people sit around and relax or eat food. “Sammaksa 1.8km” was written on the milestone. Now it&#39;s over half a bit.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Maple tree at the entrance to Sammaksa - Seongdong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/303/1e707c69-d113-4413-aff0-29c1d677dcb2.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Maple tree at the entrance to Sammaksa
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It is an uphill road from here to the tortoise rock before Sammaksa Temple. There is also a section known as the so-called &#39;Kalkkeokgae&#39;. However, as you go uphill and step by step, depending on your fitness level, you will find yourself arriving at the target. If you give up because it is difficult, you can only reach that day. The same goes for living the world. When I meet a steep uphill road, I sometimes think of myself in the past, present and future. Then he took a slow step.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Autumn forest road - Seongdong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/303/60b139bf-0176-40e7-90b2-ce695b3c3299.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Autumn forest road
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   People who have already arrived at the turtle rock lay down the mats and chuckle like a elementary school student on a picnic and share lunch. Autumn leaves have already fallen from the hillside to the turtle rock. It was piled up with faded leaves. In the woods overlooking the tortoise rock, the foliage is spreading. You can see Gwanaksan summit in the distance.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;15&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;You can see Gwanaksan summit in the distance. - Seongdong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/303/4a9c1290-5e6b-4cb5-8b2c-2550875ab994.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     You can see Gwanaksan summit in the distance.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It is a downhill pavement about 600 meters from Turtle Rock to Sammaksa Temple. Because it was a different slope from the road that came up, the autumn leaves were dyed properly along the road.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;16&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The Maaebu Island I met while going to Sammaksa Temple from Turtle Rock - Seongdong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/303/bdaea912-2127-47c4-87b8-74985e3d301c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The Maaebu Island I met while going to Sammaksa Temple from Turtle Rock
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    When they arrive, Sammaksa is crowded with people. Sammaksa Temple originated from the excitement of Wonhyo, costumes, and Yoonpil in the 17th year of King Munmu of Silla (677). After that, Dosunguksa Temple enshrined the Buddha and named it Gwaneumsa. After Ambassador Muhak of Joseon Dynasty resigned the temple, he acted as a treasure trove to the south of Hanyang. In modern times, Ji Seok-young, who practiced the Jongdu Act, built and built Baekryeonam. There is still a turtle &#39;gu&#39; that was engraved when the operation was retired. There is also a three-story stone pagoda known to have been built to commemorate the killing of the leader Salitai in the battle of Incheongseong, Yongin, the monk of this temple during the war against Mongolia during the Goryeo Dynasty.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;17&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sammaksa Three-story Stone Pagoda - Seongdong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/303/6569436c-00b1-41ee-bd45-767083737e31.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sammaksa Three-story Stone Pagoda
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The mountain that embraces Sammaksa is burning with autumn leaves. An old temple courtyard built over 1,300 years ago, sits beneath a yellow ginkgo tree and gazes out over the mountains. More than 1,300 autumns have already passed through this place!
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;14&#34; id3=&#34;18&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Autumn scenery at Sammaksa - Seongdong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/303/f90067cb-c9f0-46b8-9c4b-fafcdfbea39c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Autumn scenery at Sammaksa
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#000033&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Seoul Forest
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     -Address: 273 Ttukseom-ro, Seongdong-gu, Seoul
     &lt;br/&gt;
     -Inquiries: 02-460-2905
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#000033&#34;&gt;
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#000033&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      World Cup Park
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     -Address: 243-60 World Cup-ro, Mapo-gu, Seoul
     &lt;br/&gt;
     -Inquiries: 02-300-5501
     &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;/font&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;a href=&#34;http://worldcuppark.seoul.go.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
      http://worldcuppark.seoul.go.kr/
     &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Restaurants near
     &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Badalby: Hanjeongsik / 17 Bongcheon-ro 12-gil, Gwanak-gu / 02-889-2600
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.badalbi.com/src/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.badalbi.com/src/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Brotherhood: Directly grilled, sundubu / Mapo-gu World Cupbuk-ro 396 / 02-3152-8895
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Rooms
     &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    The M Hotel: 120 World Cup Buk-ro, Mapo-gu / 02-336-0001
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.hotelthem.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.hotelthem.com/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Hotel Vision: 277 Gosan-ro, Seongdong-gu / 02-2296-2244
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.hotelvision.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.hotelvision.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was updated in September 2016, and may be changed later, so please check before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Butterflies, cold forests in the sight of animals ~ Seoul forest in midwinter - Seongdong-gu, Seoul, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/butterflies-cold-forests-in-the-sight-of-animals-seoul-forest-in-midwinter-249/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 03:21:09 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/butterflies-cold-forests-in-the-sight-of-animals-seoul-forest-in-midwinter-249/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Seongdong-gu, Seoul, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;butterflies-cold-forests-in-the-sight-of-animals-seoul-forest-in-midwinter--249&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Seoul Forest Butterfly Ecological Garden - Seongdong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/249/445cc1d1-ff8c-4cda-8b19-e98defbefe01.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Seoul Forest Butterfly Ecological Garden
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Butterflies, cold forests in the sight of animals ~ Seoul forest in midwinter
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Seongdong-gu, Seoul, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Winter cannot be crouched like a pupa in the room. Children&#39;s winter vacation has also started, and it is time for a full-fledged play program. When the cold wind blows, it goes to Seoul Forest. The Seoul Forest, which stands for the ecological forest in the city center, is not only the possession of gorgeous green and foliage. When you arrive through the cold, you will encounter a gentle and lively sight. In Seoul Forest, you can meet colorful butterflies, novel insects, and animals even in the middle of winter.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   “Is it really cold, but do butterflies fly?”
   &lt;br/&gt;
   “Then, you can still see butterflies in winter.”
   &lt;br/&gt;
   The conversation between the mother and the child is interesting. Butterfly watching in the cold season is a strange reversal. There&#39;s another fun thing about smelting or mullet fishing through the ice.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A space exhibiting specimens of butterflies - Seongdong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/249/1b753db5-d8ce-4b3b-8749-2725284f59b7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A space exhibiting specimens of butterflies
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In winter, the Seoul forest is thin. Although the river breeze blows from the Han River, the open forest does not stop the bitter wind. Butterflies meet in a warm space with their hands tightly frozen.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Insect plant - Seongdong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/249/8a692c1b-6f80-4506-976b-110254d025d6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Insect plant
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    In Seoul Forest, the space where you can see butterflies is an insect botanical garden. Butterflies flying in the warm season of the butterfly garden move their nests to the interior of the 2nd floor of the Insect Botanical Garden. When you enter the Butterfly Eco Museum, which is open for free, you can meet the wings of swallowtail butterflies, wild swallowtail butterflies, and yellow butterflies. Butterflies become somewhat sluggish when the weather gets cold. Between 11 am and 2 pm during the day, a good sunshine time is when the butterfly is most active.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Botanical garden walkway - Seongdong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/249/ab2f07fc-da8b-417f-8cdc-3bf937638711.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Botanical garden walkway
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   From pupa to butterfly, butterfly ecology
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Even if Dongjang-gun tries to ride, it is another spring in Butterfly Ecological Garden. The flowers are in full bloom and the temperature is quite high. If you&#39;re wearing a thick coat, sweat is on your forehead. If you look closely, you can observe the butterflies flying on the ceiling or the wall in the corner, in addition to the butterflies flying on the flowers. The process of hanging a rope on a board like a tightrope and turning a pupa into a butterfly is also revealed.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   “It&#39;s ugly now, but if you take off the pupa as if you wake up from a hibernation, it will become a colorful butterfly.”
   &lt;br/&gt;
   If the biological common sense that was usually told to the child is reproduced as it is in front of the eyes, understanding grows in one word. At the Butterfly Ecology Center, various events are held for Christmas lovers, such as flying butterflies and giving a butterfly sample event.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Insect Botanical Garden Insect Exhibition - Seongdong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/249/377a0961-9f3f-4ae3-b62e-550676e704a6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Insect Botanical Garden Insect Exhibition
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Even if you go outside the ecological hall, there are plenty of interesting things to see. There is a separate butterfly exhibition hall where you can observe rare butterflies from all over the world, so you can learn the ecology of butterflies. In addition to butterflies, more than 100 species of insects inhabit the Insect Botanical Garden. You will encounter rare insects such as stag beetles, longevity scarabs, and double star crickets and giant spiders that you have only seen in books.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The process of transformation from pupae to butterfly - Seongdong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/249/918a8866-b44e-45cc-a9ff-4261665dcfd4.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The process of transformation from pupae to butterfly
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It is not easy to escape the warm insect garden. Watching interesting animals, such as turtles, salamanders, and tapeworms, hiding amongst tropical plants, you will forget about the winter cold for a while.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;turtle - Seongdong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/249/0a5df2c1-8902-4b46-b332-a6cfba5bb5dc.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     turtle
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Winter forest filled with cute fun
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    After walking out of the Insect Botanical Garden, we walk to the promenade with flower deer. Seoul Forest provides outdoor spaces where you can meet cute animals even in winter. In the &#39;House of Small Animals&#39; next to the observation deck, you can see the cute and busy appearance of the guinea pigs. The experience of feeding deer directly from the deer cage is also fresh. There is a time to buy food at the field and feed the deer directly in the snow field. You will experience the fact that Seoul Forest is an ecological space where wild animals such as deer, elk and squirrel play. The experience of feeding deer with winter butterflies is an unforgettable memory for children.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;guinea pig - Seongdong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/249/99c67d1e-1c30-45e0-bf9d-d919b0b38b79.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     guinea pig
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Roads that cross Seoul Forest like a maze are also good for winter walks. Among the 30 experience spaces, giant statues, etc. are transformed into hide-and-seek and slide-riding spaces in winter. The lawn, where cars and bicycles do not go, is filled with laughter from children who make snowmen and fight snow.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Flower Deer Feeding Experience - Seongdong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/249/2cb561fe-ff0f-49cf-8aec-40549cccf2ec.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Flower Deer Feeding Experience
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    First of all, it is necessary to recall the colorful modifiers attached to Seoul Forest.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    “If you have Central Park in New York and Hyde Park in London, there is Seoul Forest in Seoul.”
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Even near the place of life on a winter day, these informative and interesting experiences await. Seoul Forest is easily accessible by subway. After the Seoul Forest Station of the Bundang Line, it became possible to connect immediately without having to stay in the cold for a long time.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Seoul Forest Trail - Seongdong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/249/ba366c9c-6313-44fa-80bb-c05d41b8cc6d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Seoul Forest Trail
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p style=&#34;COLOR: #7b1f42&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Seoul Forest
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Address: 273 Ttukseom-ro, Seongdong-gu, Seoul
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Contact: 02-460-2905
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p style=&#34;COLOR: #7b1f42&#34;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://parks.seoul.go.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://parks.seoul.go.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p style=&#34;COLOR: #7b1f42&#34;&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;topmr&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1.Access
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
     * Self-driving
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34; style=&#34;MARGIN-TOP: 0px&#34;&gt;
    Olympic Boulevard → Seongsu Bridge → Turn right toward Seoul Forest
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34; style=&#34;MARGIN-TOP: 0px&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
     * public transport
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34; style=&#34;MARGIN-TOP: 0px&#34;&gt;
    5 minutes from Seoul Forest Station on the Bundang Line and 15 minutes from Ttukseom Station on Line 2
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34; style=&#34;MARGIN-TOP: 0px&#34;&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34; style=&#34;MARGIN-TOP: 0px&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Restaurants around
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Leeds House:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Steak / 1, Sangwon 12-gil, Seongdong-gu / 02-6925-6708
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Gammyok Seolleongtang:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Seolleongtang / 438 Cheonho-daero, Seongdong-gu / 02-2248-0445
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Dressed Ribs:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Pork Ribs / 292-1, Majang-ro, Seongdong-gu / 02-2292-8588
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     3.Accommodation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     JJ Hotel:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    29, Seongdong-gu Automobile Market 1-gil / 02-2245-3355
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://jjhotel.net/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://jjhotel.net/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Hotel Vision:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    277, Gosan-ro, Seongdong-gu / 02-2296-2244
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Best Western Premier Guro Hotel:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    72, Digital-ro 32-gil, Guro-gu / 02-6905-9500
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://gurohotel.co.kr/kor/html/main/main.asp&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://gurohotel.co.kr/kor/html/main/main.asp
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    ※ The above information was created in December 2013, and may change later, so be sure to check it before you travel.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>