<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Yangpyeong-gun on Every Corner of Korea</title>
    <link>https://codecorea.github.io/tags/yangpyeong-gun/</link>
    <description>Every Corner of Korea (Yangpyeong-gun)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 05:42:38 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="https://codecorea.github.io/tags/yangpyeong-gun/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Filming location of “Gwansang”, famous mountain snow plum and ginkgo tree at Yongmunsa Temple - Yangpyeong-gun, Gyeonggi-do, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/filming-location-of-gwansang-famous-mountain-snow-plum-and-ginkgo-tree-at-yongmunsa-temple-194/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 05:42:38 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/filming-location-of-gwansang-famous-mountain-snow-plum-and-ginkgo-tree-at-yongmunsa-temple-194/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Yangpyeong-gun, Gyeonggi-do, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;filming-location-of-gwansang-famous-mountain-snow-plum-and-ginkgo-tree-at-yongmunsa-temple--194&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;The view from the front yard of Naekyung&#39;s house through the silver grass - Yangpyeong-gun, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/194/38351490-f2d4-44c5-80d6-8862986e65fa.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    The view from the front yard of Naekyung&#39;s house through the silver grass
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Filming location of “Gwansang”, famous mountain snow plum and ginkgo tree at Yongmunsa Temple
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Yangpyeong-gun, Gyeonggi-do, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Seolmaejae is the filming location for the movie &amp;lt;Kwannwan&amp;gt;, the best topic in the second half of 2013. It was a time when the family of Naekyung (Song Kang-ho) lived comfortably. Looking down from the silver grass hill in front of the house, the anxiety disappears. In the autumn outing, a nearby Yongmunsa Temple with 1,100-year-old ginkgo trees is also recommended. This is a temple that the Yangyang army in &amp;lt;Contemplative&amp;gt; visited twice before and after the Gyeyujeong.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Looking for a contemplative town in Chittaksan
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It is November. The wind is quite cold along the Namhan River. Everywhere is uneven. It is late autumn. It&#39;s perfect because the pickling is in harmony. In particular, Yangpyeong is more busy in autumn because it has many famous mountains. Yumyeongsan Mountain, Yongmunsan Mountain, and Jungmisan Mountain show off slightly different charms. Then there are different statues on the mountain. Pungsu geography is a contemplation of nature.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A house of inner diameter located in the middle of a silver grass field - Yangpyeong-gun, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/194/3baf5408-1f7d-46b2-9cd6-f46605bf8dd3.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A house of inner diameter located in the middle of a silver grass field
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Not long ago, the movie &amp;lt;Contemplation&amp;gt; became popular. It was the tenth in the Korean film industry, attracting 9 million audiences. The actors&#39; strong acting also stood out, but the material of ornamental was also a significant influence on the box office. &amp;lt;Contemplation&amp;gt; is set in the background of the sedation. This was the case when the Sooyang Grand Army removed Kim Jong-seo, etc., and took Danjong&#39;s throne. At the center of its history, the ornamental contest follows Kim Nae-kyung&#39;s gaze.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Autumn scenery along the road to the location where &amp;lt;Swanaejae&amp;gt; - Yangpyeong-gun, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/194/aeef53f9-ec17-4a55-ab73-5ee22b272140.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Autumn scenery along the road to the location where &amp;lt;Swanaejae&amp;gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The first scene is the path that Gisaeng Yeon-hong (Hye-soo Kim) visits the inner diameter. The inner diameter lives like a Moorim coriander hiding in the middle of the night. There may be a factor called the family of a rebellious family, but I wonder if I already knew my contemplation and lived in hiding. Nevertheless, what about that talent? People come by hearing the word of mouth. Parasitic lotus is one of them. It is an intention to try to make a lot of money by using the talent of inner diameter. They find themselves disguised as merchants, but they cannot fool the current contemplative.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The famous Seolmaejae area is a hidden silver grass spot. - Yangpyeong-gun, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/194/dca52871-8f48-4b10-b3bd-e17558ff5491.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The famous Seolmaejae area is a hidden silver grass spot.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   “The light of the drawing turns and the lips with red lips are shameless. . ”
   &lt;br/&gt;
   The autumn scenery on the way to the house of Naekyung at first glance resembles the red lips of the red. It is the Seolmaejae Passage, which is the foot of the famous mountain. It is named after plum blossoms bloom even when it snows a lot. Since 1999, a private recreational forest has been in operation on the ridge. It is well known to camping enthusiasts with its log cabin and auto camping site. Within the recreational forest, there were Damo Forest and Soseono Forest. Drama &amp;lt;Damo&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;Jumong&amp;gt; were filmed here.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Dark autumn leaves between the silver grass fields attract attention. - Yangpyeong-gun, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/194/47f4f3a4-6586-4188-bfea-0c1bafed8912.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Dark autumn leaves between the silver grass fields attract attention.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The filming location of &amp;lt;Contemplative&amp;gt; passes through the entrance to the Seolmaejae Recreation Forest and goes up a little further to the banner. When you reach the ridge, there are ATV rental stores and small container stores. There is a road towards the mountain next to the kiosk and there is a breaker. This is the head to the location. If you walk around 30 minutes by car, you can see the house of the inner diameter in &amp;lt;Contemplation&amp;gt;.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sometimes a single autumn leaf is enough - Yangpyeong-gun, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/194/49894ed8-a76e-4b3b-b021-18cd0e96fe7c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sometimes a single autumn leaf is enough
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Thatched house in silver grass field
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   At the entrance of Naekyung&#39;s house, the entrance of Imdo is overlooked by trees growing in laughter. Although the leaves of Ebisan sometimes appear, it is not satisfactory. Fortunately, the cool landscape opens as soon as we make up for the regret. On the left side of the road, Yongmunsan and Baekwoonbong boast great pride. It is a mountain that can feel autumn. Below that is the Namhan River stem. As if taking a breath, stop walking and look at you for a long time.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;You and your house are covered with planks - Yangpyeong-gun, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/194/ba935bb5-0df9-479d-9331-51f69aade5d9.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     You and your house are covered with planks
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   When you turn back, it&#39;s a silver grass tingling. It is a sign that the house of the inner diameter is not far. Soon it is the first crossroads. There are signs on the three-way intersection, B, D course, and Wangnam course. It looks like a three-way street, but it is actually a crossroad. There is another side road behind the sign. If you take the Wangnam course, you can walk while enjoying the surrounding scenery. In particular, there was a tree in autumn with autumn leaves, and the sloping silver grass field and the surrounding mountains are impressive.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The house of the inner diameter of the movie &amp;lt;Contemplation&amp;gt; - Yangpyeong-gun, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/194/1c3f1466-ff9e-4459-bbfe-075e03d273e7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The house of the inner diameter of the movie &amp;lt;Contemplation&amp;gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you walk a little further with that afterimage, you will see Samgeori. If you cross your head slightly uphill to the right, it is the back door of the house. In the movie, the path that Yeonhong was looking for is the left side road just behind the B and D course signs. I can see the silver grass field and the house of the inner diameter grows up on the hill.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A silver grass field beyond the back door seen from the thatched house floor - Yangpyeong-gun, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/194/4227b07f-474d-46c3-ba8b-39a547aaf68b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A silver grass field beyond the back door seen from the thatched house floor
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The house of Naekyung was built on the flat of the ridge. Two houses with ‘Yu-wa’ and ‘thatched’ have been placed as ‘ㄴ’. The bosom is the courtyard. In the scene where the inner diameter and Pangheon (Cho Jung-seok), who received money from Yeonhong, boiled a teeming chicken, are young. On one side, there is a small arch made of ocher like the trace. A silver grass rises along the ridge through the back door, and the autumn landscape spreads out through the front door. In the old days, it was used as a filming location for the drama &amp;lt;The Garden of the Winds&amp;gt;. This is where Kim Hong-do and Shin Yun-bok met. It has recently been used as a filming location for the drama &amp;lt;Goddess of Fire&amp;gt; after the movie &amp;lt;Contemplation&amp;gt;. Since modern civilization is not close, it is a good place to shoot historical dramas.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The mood of the autumn day is layering. - Yangpyeong-gun, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/194/7e494fd3-b88e-4a8c-a5a8-9bd107532587.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The mood of the autumn day is layering.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Ginkgo biloba silver grass, Yongmunsa temple
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The area around Naekyung&#39;s house is a silver grass spot that attracts people, just like those who visited to see the contemplation. At one time, Hwa Jeon-min even worked the land. In the old days, there was also a dressage where horses were raised. The famous name of the famous mountain is Mayu Mountain. That is why humans are rare and secluded. It is worth taking a look at the surrounding scenery to enjoy the autumn mood.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Walking through the silver grass field leads to the famous mountain - Yangpyeong-gun, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/194/e1ddc13d-d262-4530-96cc-a6a37b37163e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Walking through the silver grass field leads to the famous mountain
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   You can take a little more steps. Paragliding active factories are not far from Limdo. In the active factory, you can see five pine trees matching the silver grass field, which is also a famous location. In the movie &amp;lt;The Man of the King&amp;gt;, Jangsaeng (Gam Woo-sung) and Gong-gil (Lee Jun-ki) played the final play. After the active factory, it leads to the top of Mt. Many people do not know the way to go to the silver grass field of &amp;lt;Kwannwan&amp;gt; because Mt.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Yongmunsan Tourist Complex - Yangpyeong-gun, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/194/9469cd0c-2a28-46ad-a9d4-05bc524e0d8f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Yongmunsan Tourist Complex
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you miss the autumn leaves than silver grass, it is better to turn your foot toward Yongmun Mountain than famous one. It takes about 30 minutes by car from Seolmaejae to Yongmunsan (it&#39;s too much to use public transportation). If there is silver grass in Seolmaejae, Yongmunsan is the autumn leaves. The best among them is the 1,100-year-old ginkgo tree of Yongmunsa Temple. As I foretell the fact, when I get close to the tourist attractions of Yongmunsan, ginkgo trees are greeted. Some still have a blue color, but the golden yellow color marks the peak of autumn. The road leading up to the entrance to Yongmunsan Mountain is perfect for a drive course.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Beautiful tulip trees in autumn - Yangpyeong-gun, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/194/354c987f-5247-4e60-8a59-06477afac233.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Beautiful tulip trees in autumn
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Ginkgo trees lined up from the parking lot of Yongmunsan to the entrance of the forest road. Ginkgo leaves fall off and a yellow road is like a fairy tale. A roadside ornamental man holds the passersby. As I passed the filming location of &amp;lt;Contemplative&amp;gt;, my heart moved. The foliage of vermilion tulip trees around the mall is also beautiful. It is one of the most coveted autumn leaves, but it is a relatively less known tree.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Road to Yongmunsan Tourist Complex - Yangpyeong-gun, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/194/42934bad-ab54-48f7-bb1f-6f2f4b371f5b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Road to Yongmunsan Tourist Complex
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   The 1,100 year old tree where the wind passes by
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Walk up 1km along the forest path to Yongmunsa Temple. As the valley opens, red maple leaves appear instead of ginkgo trees. Yongmunsa Temple was founded in 2 years (913) by King Silla of Silla. It has nothing to do with the Suyangdae army in &amp;lt;Contemplation&amp;gt;. At the age of thirty (1447), he was ordered by King Sejong and first visited Yongmunsa to build a preservation for his mother, Queen Soheon, Sim. When he was forty years old three years after he was crowned the throne, he visited Yongmunsa Temple once more to replace the temple. The stricken distress (1453) to end the discontinuation was an incident in the meantime. It is the ginkgo tree of Yongmunsa Temple that I watched all day after day. Under the shade, the last line of the inner diameter in &amp;lt;Contemplation&amp;gt; comes to mind.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Yongmun Bridge with autumn leaves in harmony - Yangpyeong-gun, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/194/20927fe8-ba47-4621-a613-770f8a5dbac2.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Yongmun Bridge with autumn leaves in harmony
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   “I only looked at the faces of people, not the times. … I need to see the wind ... It is the wind that makes the waves. You just rode high waves for a while. … Like the waves coming high break one day. ”
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;15&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The color of the road to Yongmunsa Temple - Yangpyeong-gun, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/194/3e171bf7-0de9-4058-b8a2-17ec624affa9.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The color of the road to Yongmunsa Temple
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Yongmunsa Ginkgo tree is said to have been planted on the way to Mt. Its history also matches the inner diameter. It is said that the costume ambassador&#39;s staff sprouted and became a ginkgo tree, and there is a legend that he made a sound whenever there was a big problem in the country. It is said that the Japanese army set fire to Yongmunsa Temple during the Korean War against the American Army (1907), but did not burn only ginkgo trees. You can tell by facing the ginkgo tree. It is not a tree that will be shaken by some interference. The wind is also dignified to pass. It&#39;s worth it as the leader reaches 1,100 years. It is about 42m high and the circumference of the base is 15.2m. It is the oldest and largest ginkgo tree in Korea. Even if you climb the stairs and face the Daeungjeon Hall, you cannot reach the height of the tree. So, Yongmunsa Temple is about 1,100 years ago.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;16&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Autumn mountain with foliage over Yongmunsa Yosachae - Yangpyeong-gun, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/194/6dce61a4-b7de-442a-87ef-fe7dfe698516.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Autumn mountain with foliage over Yongmunsa Yosachae
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Autumn leaves are likely to be full on the second weekend of November this year. On the first weekend in November, the greenery was so dark that those who visited Yongmunsa temple devoured the regret. On the contrary, the autumn leaves of Yongmunsan will be more colorful. It culminated in late October through early November. If the normal person, Gaesupbong, is busy, a light hike from Yongmunsa Temple to Senate Temple is also not bad. If it&#39;s overwhelming, it&#39;s good to chew the words of Jinhyeong&#39;s son Jinhyung. He replied to the question of what was the most difficult thing to do after he stopped working in the past.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   “It was not to resign from fate.”
   &lt;br/&gt;
   It&#39;s about an hour or two of walking along a certain path.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;17&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;1,100 years old ginkgo tree at Yongmunsa Temple - Yangpyeong-gun, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/194/05cac8a1-0999-48f5-8643-e45d1449454d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     1,100 years old ginkgo tree at Yongmunsa Temple
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p style=&#34;COLOR: #7b1f42&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Seolmaejae (House of Inner Diameter):
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    29-1, Yongcheon-ri, Okcheon-myeon, Yangpyeong-gun, Gyeonggi-do
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Seolmaejae Recreation Forest
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    : Mountain 29-21, Yongcheon-ri, Okcheon-myeon, Yangpyeong-gun, Gyeonggi-do, 031-772-5965,
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.snrf.co.kr/&#34; style=&#34;COLOR: #7b1f42&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;설매재휴양림 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
     www.snrf.co.kr
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Longmen Temple:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    625, Sinjeom-ri, Yangpyeong-gun, Gyeonggi-do, 031-773-3797,
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.yongmunsa.org&#34; style=&#34;COLOR: #7b1f42&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;용문사 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
     www.yongmunsa.org
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1.Access
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
     * Self-driving
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34; style=&#34;MARGIN-TOP: 0px&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Seolmaejae (House of Inner Diameter):
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Jungbu Expressway Hanam IC → Paldang Bridge → Route 6 toward Yangpyeong → Goeup Intersection toward Cheongpyeong and Seorak → Baekhyeon Intersection → Seolmaejae Recreation Forest → Banner Mijae
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Longmen Temple:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Jungbu Expressway Hanam IC → Paldang Bridge → Route 6 toward Yangpyeong → Maryong Intersection → Yongmunsa Temple
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34; style=&#34;MARGIN-TOP: 0px&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
     * public transport
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34; style=&#34;MARGIN-TOP: 0px&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Seolmaejae (Naekyungui House):
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Take bus number 6-3 at Yangpyeong Terminal and get off at Yongcheon 3-ri Village Hall. Walk 5 km to Banner Mijae. Take a taxi from Yangpyeong Station (or Yangpyeong Terminal)
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Longmen Temple:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    From Yongmun Terminal or Yongmun Station, take buses 7, 7-4, 7-8 and get off at Yongmunsa Temple
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;topmr&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Restaurants around
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Yongmunsan Farm Ssambap Village:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Ssambap Set Meal, Ssamyuk Ssambap / 176 Yongmunsan-ro, Yongmun-myeon, Yangpyeong-gun / 031-771-8389
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     yard :
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Gondrebab / 239 Yongmunsan-ro, Yongmun-myeon, Yangpyeong-gun / 031-775-0311
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.foodup.co.kr/BzHome/?param=imuroo&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.foodup.co.kr/BzHome/?param=imuroo
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Okcheon Sundubu:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Sundubu / 124, Sinbok-gil, Okcheon-myeon, Yangpyeong-gun / 031-774-4369
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     3.Accommodation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Yongmunsa Temple Stay:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    625, Sinjeom-ri, Yangpyeong-gun / 031-775-5797
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.yongmunsa.org&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;‘용문사’ 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
     www.yongmunsa.org
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Seolmaejae Recreation Forest:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    amount
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.snrf.co.kr&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;‘설매재휴양림’ 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
     www.snrf.co.kr
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Yangpyeong Valley:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    14 Baekan-gil 60beon-gil, Yangpyeong-eup, Yangpyeong-gun / 031-774-3000
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.yp-valley.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.yp-valley.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    ※ The above information was created in November 2013, and may change later, so be sure to check it before you travel.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yangpyeong-gun, South Korea - Summer trip to sunflower village and rural train station</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/summer-trip-to-sunflower-village-and-rural-train-station-66/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 12:02:54 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/summer-trip-to-sunflower-village-and-rural-train-station-66/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Yangpyeong-gun, South Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;summer-trip-to-sunflower-village-and-rural-train-station--66&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Large signstone written `` Muwang 1-ri &#39;&#39; - Yangpyeong-gun, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/66/801b2088-d924-4b92-b856-4e2477030aef.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Large signstone written `` Muwang 1-ri &#39;&#39;
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Summer trip to sunflower village and rural train station
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Yangpyeong-gun, South Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Many people are worried about where to go with their families on this summer&#39;s vacation. It is a good place for those who are looking for a place where they want to spend their time quietly rather than a place where a lot of people gather. It is the sunflower village of Yangpyeong-gun and Seokbul Station and Gudun Station, which are rural railway stations. Don&#39;t forget to take a camera with you to leave your family in a wonderful photo.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   A village where you can see sunflowers faced to the sky
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Sunflower Village, Seokbul Station and Gudun Station are located on Jipyeong-myeon, Yangpyeong-gun. This area is famous for Jipyeong Makgeolli. You can get there by train, so you don&#39;t have to waste time during a busy holiday season. Not a lot of people come to visit, but it is perfect for a day trip quietly. If you set the date well, you can also enjoy the Yongmun oil market.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sunflowers are on the road to the village - Yangpyeong-gun, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/66/9e4be841-6f29-4c52-961e-53af63041e62.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sunflowers are on the road to the village
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you take a bus from the Yongmun Intercity Bus Terminal near Yongmun Station, you can get off at the bus stop where the large signpost written &#39;Muwang 1-ri&#39; stands. 初 川 (chocheon) used together on the stone is the old name of the sunflower village. The water flowing through the Yeoju into the Namhan River began in the sunflower village and was called as follows. Pass through the stone and meet the typical rural village landscape. Sunflowers on the road seem to give the name of the village. The village boasts a peaceful landscape in the form of a basin at 300m above sea level.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A sunflower-themed mural was painted on the wall of the village. - Yangpyeong-gun, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/66/ebd997bf-8216-486e-80e8-ae4c429d0869.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A sunflower-themed mural was painted on the wall of the village.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The sunflowers that bloomed here were planted in late May and began to bloom in late July. In 2014, with the support of the Gyeonggi-do Agricultural Technology Center, sunflower seeds were planted for the income of the villagers. After the sunflower bloomed, the scenery began to spread. In the summer, photo club members often come to town to capture the flowers that fill the fields. Note that there are no restaurants or stalls in town.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sunflowers began to bloom in late July - Yangpyeong-gun, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/66/289b5b61-477d-4d9d-baaf-93723e4cb2a5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sunflowers began to bloom in late July
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Sunflowers meet like a hidden picture
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you walk about 10 minutes from the stone, you will be able to park your car. This is the village entrance. Now it&#39;s time to find the sunflowers in full bloom and take a walk as you wish. In the villages, sunflower fields are not fixed, but they are planted using land, so you can find flowers everywhere. Sunflowers are also slightly bloomed, so you can go to flower viewing as if you are looking for a hidden picture.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Travelers taking commemorative photos with sunflowers in the background - Yangpyeong-gun, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/66/9a5383e0-5ea9-4513-8a37-cad4934d41cf.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Travelers taking commemorative photos with sunflowers in the background
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In the middle of the road, the voices of those who look at the sunflowers and admire the beautifulness are often heard. There are many visitors who take commemorative photos standing side by side with sunflowers. Sunflowers are too tall or they turn their heads in the wrong direction, making them hard to see. It is also common here for children to marvel at the bees rushing toward a full-blown seed sunflower.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Bee rushing towards sunflower - Yangpyeong-gun, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/66/3f6b401d-9316-4747-a121-eb7852416e5c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Bee rushing towards sunflower
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you want to know where sunflowers are spread throughout the village, you can refer to the guide map of `` Muwangri Sunflower Road &#39;&#39; installed on the crossroads before going to the town hall. In the parking lot, you can see a lot of sunflowers on the hill road, near the town hall, and on the way to the Muwang Church.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;You can see the `` Muwang-ri Sunflower Road &#39;&#39; guide map at the crossroad - Yangpyeong-gun, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/66/469b5424-bdbd-48a2-93ed-eb3f6c0c985e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     You can see the `` Muwang-ri Sunflower Road &#39;&#39; guide map at the crossroad
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The village also held its 3rd Sunflower Festival 2016 (July 29-31). This is a village festival prepared for the flowering period of sunflowers. During the festival, visitors sold sunflower barley rice, yeolmu noodles, and pan-fried rice to visitors. There was also a marketplace selling sunflower seeds, barley, corn, potatoes, and bokbunja grown in the village. Sunflowers are expected to open until the end of August. The festival is over, but it&#39;s a good place to go to see flowers with your family.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Muwang-ri Town Hall - Yangpyeong-gun, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/66/5ac5b375-0210-4278-9312-ec09cf07dfa8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Muwang-ri Town Hall
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Seokbul Station is like a toy country
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   A simple station is a train station with few passengers. There is a station station where employees are in charge of their duties, but stop only trains without even having to. Thanks to the unique atmosphere and dignity, many people deliberately come to the station to feel romantic and memories.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   There is a working room but no staff. To take the train towards Cheongnyangni, cross the underground passage to the right of the entrance. The distance from Sunflower Village to Seokbul Station is less than 3 km. If you drive by car, it&#39;s easy to get there, but it&#39;s not convenient to use public transportation.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Seokbul Station with red roof and blue exterior wall stands out from far away - Yangpyeong-gun, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/66/9adf998b-691c-4732-a879-d6f1ce1da3c2.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Seokbul Station with red roof and blue exterior wall stands out from far away
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Originally, Seokbul Station was destined to disappear due to fewer customers. It was unfortunate that the county and the county government jointly signed a campaign to prevent the removal of the Seokbul Station and built a new building in 2013. Thanks to this, there is no atmosphere of an old building that is expected of a simple station, but rather a small and small station building.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Many visitors take commemorative photos against the blue wall. - Yangpyeong-gun, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/66/5a4ab1e2-281a-48bf-9fdf-3e72ff9464a7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Many visitors take commemorative photos against the blue wall.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The pointed red roof of Seokbul Station and the outer wall of a blue building are easy to see from afar. Thanks to this, if you travel by bus or car from Yongmun or Muwang-ri, you can see the beautiful blue building in the distance. Standing in front of Seokbul Station building, it feels like a visit to Toy Land. The exterior walls and windows are a great backdrop for taking pictures. It&#39;s like a sketchbook with pastel colored walls.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Passage for downline train from Seokbul Station - Yangpyeong-gun, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/66/3916c4ed-d037-4288-a6f6-c31eb293530e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Passage for downline train from Seokbul Station
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Gudun Station, Memory of First Love on Hill
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   three
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Climbing the hill leads to Gudun Station, a registered cultural property. - Yangpyeong-gun, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/66/f700aa47-60c8-443a-8496-57028f7fd996.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Climbing the hill leads to Gudun Station, a registered cultural property.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   After passing Muwang-ri, cross the Ilshin 2nd Bridge and you will see a hill. If you go up the street, you will come to Ilsin Church. Since you have to walk the hill road based on Ilshin 2nd Bridge, if you are visiting this place in summer, it is recommended to climb slowly. Because the road is narrow, be careful when driving with you. There is space for parking in front of Gudun Station.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Long wooden chair staying inside the station - Yangpyeong-gun, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/66/cb6844a6-87e1-40a8-b2e3-7761f4cfb086.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Long wooden chair staying inside the station
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Complete your mission to the train station, and now you&#39;ll be able to walk through the tracks at the retired Gudun Station. Gudun Station is also famous as the filming location of the film Introduction to Architecture. Like the heroes in the movie, many people walk along the railway and leave memories on the camera. It&#39;s a great place to recall the fresh memories of your first love or to explain your old train station to your children.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Memo that the person who visited Gudun Station wished - Yangpyeong-gun, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/66/7ba9ac84-6373-44e5-8fa9-42b54a91d3a1.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Memo that the person who visited Gudun Station wished
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Inside the station, there are long wooden chairs, train schedules and passenger fares. If you go out to the railroad tracks, you will see a wish tree with a memo of the people who visited this place. What did you write down? I peek at the short texts of strangers and write down my wishes and hang them by my side. Next to the tree stands a carriage that is not running. Take a walk with the whole family on a railroad train. About 100 meters of railroad tracks remain from the station building. The well-preserved closed area and the surrounding landscape are beautiful and it is a good place to spend some time.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Cars stopped at Gudun Station no longer run - Yangpyeong-gun, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/66/d50a580c-e58f-4c21-b6ca-dbc04a869660.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Cars stopped at Gudun Station no longer run
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel info
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Sunflower Village
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Address: 113-1, Chocheon-gil, Jipyeong-myeon, Yangpyeong-gun, Gyeonggi-do
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Seokbul Station
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Address: 1319-2, Manmi-ri, Jipyeong-myeon, Yangpyeong-gun, Gyeonggi-do
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Gudun Station
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Address: 1336-9 Ilsin-ri, Jipyeong-myeon, Yangpyeong-gun, Gyeonggi-do
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Restaurants near
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Moonhori Red Bean Porridge: Red Bean Porridge, Red Bean Kalguksu / 641, Bukhangang-ro, Seojong-myeon, Yangpyeong-gun, Gyeonggi-do, Korea / 031-774-5969
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.moonhori.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.moonhori.com/
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Acorn Noodle Collection: Acorn Muktangguk / 99, Sinbok-gil, Okcheon-myeon, Yangpyeong-gun, Gyeonggi-do / 031-771-7562
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://031-771-7562.모바일114.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://031-771-7562.모바일114.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Yongmunsan Central Restaurant: The Deoksan Chaesiksik / 644 Yongmunsan-ro, Yongmun-myeon, Yangpyeong-gun, Gyeonggi-do, Korea / 031-773-3422
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.yongmunsan.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.yongmunsan.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Rooms
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Yangpyeong Hanok Village Ocher Pension: 43-6 Jeon 1-gil, Gangmyeon, Yangpyeong-gun, Gyeonggi-do / 031-773-6300
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.hanok54.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.hanok54.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Breeze Pension: 49-2, Yanghyeon-gil, Okcheon-myeon, Yangpyeong-gun, Gyeonggi-do / 031-774-3429
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.pensionet.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.pensionet.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Nest Pension: 325-16 Hwangsunwon-ro, Seojong-myeon, Yangpyeong-gun, Gyeonggi-do / 031-774-9178
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.dungji-yp.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.dungji-yp.com/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was updated in July 2017. It may change afterwards, so please check before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ The information such as text, photos and videos used in this article is copyrighted by Korea Tourism Organization, so unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>