<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Haenam-gun on Every Corner of Korea</title>
    <link>https://codecorea.github.io/tags/haenam-gun/</link>
    <description>Every Corner of Korea (Haenam-gun)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2020 03:16:32 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="https://codecorea.github.io/tags/haenam-gun/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The breath of Alpine Sunsundo is scattered by the blue rain, Haenam Nokwoodang - Haenam-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/the-breath-of-alpine-sunsundo-is-scattered-by-the-blue-rain-haenam-nokwoodang-295/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2020 03:16:32 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/the-breath-of-alpine-sunsundo-is-scattered-by-the-blue-rain-haenam-nokwoodang-295/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Haenam-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;the-breath-of-alpine-sunsundo-is-scattered-by-the-blue-rain-haenam-nokwoodang--295&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Opened in 2010, the panoramic view of Gosan Yunseondo artifact exhibition hall - Haenam-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/295/377d26d2-bed3-419b-bcac-0069122b5f2f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Opened in 2010, the panoramic view of Gosan Yunseondo artifact exhibition hall
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   The breath of Alpine Sunsundo is scattered by the blue rain, Haenam Nokwoodang
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Haenam-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Everyone experiences the end in life. There are various ends, such as a scheduled one and a sudden one, but it is difficult to get used to it. It would be a similar context if we wanted to go to the &#39;end of the earth&#39; at least once. Because I have the expectation that I can start again after seeing the end of the earth and walking again. Following the expectation, people gather from Seoul to Cheonni-gil, so the land was once abandoned.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Namdo Exploration Station, Haenam, at the southern end of the Korean Peninsula
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    As the name suggests, the end of the Korean peninsula and the starting point of the land, as the name suggests, are located in the southernmost part of Haenam, the southernmost point of the peninsula. Thanks to this, people follow the symbolism of end and beginning to visit the end of Haenam. When departing from the metropolitan area, a full day is a distance you need to run. This is the reason why it is too much to look at the end of the earth after coming to Haenam. Let&#39;s take a look at every corner of Haenam. Haenam tour overflowing with highlights and food, starting from now on.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    When you open the map of Haenam, you can see the ruins of the high mountain Yunseon-do, Daeheungsa, Mihwangsa, and Gocheonam migratory birds that stretched out from side to side. A minimum of 2 nights and 3 days is required to properly explore all of this (based on self-driving from the metropolitan area). You can decide the route by adding or subtracting according to your preference and schedule. Remembering the end of the land where you can see both sunrises and sunsets, Mihwangsa, Gocheonam migratory birds, and flower gardens, which are considered as sunset points, can help you in choosing lodging and travel.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    If you enter Haenam Land after passing Haenam IC or Pyeongdong IC, there are nearby Gosan Yunseondo Historic Site and Daeheungsa Temple (Duryunsan Provincial Park). First, I visited the ruins of the Yunsan Island in Gosan and visited Daeheungsa Temple. After watching the sunset at Mihwangsa Temple, I decided to move to the end of the earth and stay for 1 night. The next day, it is a good time to see the sunrise of Memseom and look around the end of the earth. If the arrival time is in the afternoon, it is okay to first look at the end of the ground, watch the sunset and sunrise here, and then move in the opposite direction.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Haenam Yoon, a prestigious family member of the Joseon Dynasty, is full of artifacts
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The journey of Haenam starts from the ruins of Yunseon-do, Gosan. Haenam is full of attractions, but it is regrettable except for the high mountains. Let&#39;s take a look at the relics exhibition at Yunseon Island in Gosan and head to the Nokwoodang area (History No. 1, historical site No. 167). Dongseon also continues naturally.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Opened in 2010, Gosan Yunseondo Relics Exhibition shows the situation of the times through the works of Gosan and Haenam Yoon&#39;s servants. You can also naturally learn about Haenam Yoon&#39;s family, which was a prestigious father-in-law. Heirlooms from Gosan, as well as his great-grandson Yun Doo-seo&#39;s tribute portraits (National Treasure No. 240), are handed down from generation to generation. It&#39;s amazing that there are so many treasures in a house. Each of the relics that filled the exhibition hall is conveyed by the descendants of the descendants who have kept nothing but light. It seems that he is facing a distant alpine entity that he met only in textbooks through &amp;lt;The Fisherman History&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;Ouga&amp;gt;.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Artifact Exhibition Hall - Haenam-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/295/8aa86934-a617-445d-80b3-c46197e38914.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Artifact Exhibition Hall
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Let&#39;s take a look at Alpine. Gosan Yunseon (1587 ~ 1671). In 1628 (Injo 6), he started a manor at the beginning of the Byeolsimundae and became the master of Bongrimdaegun (Hyojong). Jung-soo, Noron&#39;s Yeong-su, Woo-am and Song Si-yeol. It would have been the best time of his political life filled with Guiyang and hermit. Nokwoodang is a house where the Bongrim Daegun descended to the throne and was given to the teacher, Gosan. The house in Suwon was moved to Gohaean as Hasan descended.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Artifact Exhibition Hall - Haenam-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/295/1eae8a0a-ff23-4683-8379-26abb6af6fb6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Artifact Exhibition Hall
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Alpine house in Visa Tree Forest, and Nokwoodang
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Haenam Yoon&#39;s Jongtaek, which embraces Anchae, Sarangchae, Gosan shrine, Eochoeun shrine, and Chuwondang, is also referred to as Nokwoodang (Historical Site No. 167). Dang Ho, &#39;Nokwoo&#39;, was written by Ikdong Iseo (1662 ~ 1723), the first author of Donggukjin.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Nokwoodang from the top - Haenam-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/295/531cbd2b-12ac-4a09-b8c6-59eb5aa7f71f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Nokwoodang from the top
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Nokwoodang&#39;s plate is also his work. He was close with Yoon Doo-seo, a great-grandson of high mountains. It is a &#39;green rain&#39; if you unravel the &#39;green&#39;. Rain, which falls when the grass and trees are green, means fresh water of life. In addition, it is often interpreted as the sound of ginkgo leaves in front of Nokdangdang and the wind that sweeps through the forest behind Ndungdang.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Yoon-Hik Yoon, the 14th descendant of Kosan, who protects Nokdang - Haenam-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/295/07fd6011-fe1d-4b40-acd5-006a0d32401a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Yoon-Hik Yoon, the 14th descendant of Kosan, who protects Nokdang
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Is it because it is so famous as an alpine site? Eure Nokdang is regarded as the birthplace of an alpine mountain. In fact it is not. Looking at the relics&#39; bilateral preliminary drafting document (Treasure No. 482-5), it can be seen that Alpine was adopted as a big house when he was 8 years old.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Naengwoodang, Sarangchae, where Haenam Yoon&#39;s Jongson stayed - Haenam-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/295/5cb4d4f5-0e4d-49eb-b9ee-e5693ec6833d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Naengwoodang, Sarangchae, where Haenam Yoon&#39;s Jongson stayed
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   When he first stepped on Haenam, he turned 25. Until then, he lived in Seoul. The longest stay in Seoul, except the 20 years spent in the exile in the life of Gosan in 1985, was Seoul. It is said that he stayed here in Haenam Nokwoodang for 6 years and Geumgye-dong for 9 years. I spent almost as much time in his hiding place in Bogildo, so if you want to feel more of the alpine trail, you should stop by Bogildo. At the end of the land, a passenger ship departs for Bogil Island (Ohwado Island).
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Naengwoodang, Sarangchae, where Haenam Yoon&#39;s Jongson stayed - Haenam-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/295/957904b0-bc01-4caa-b4cd-9857ffbf364e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Naengwoodang, Sarangchae, where Haenam Yoon&#39;s Jongson stayed
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It takes a lot of time to properly examine the remains of the Gosan Yunseondo Art Museum.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&amp;lt;Sanjungsingok&amp;gt; where you can see the alpine handwriting - Haenam-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/295/389eaeca-3905-44e7-953f-54b2d3e6d0e0.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     &amp;lt;Sanjungsingok&amp;gt; where you can see the alpine handwriting
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Nobi documents of the Goryeo Dynasty (Treasure No. 483), including books such as &amp;lt;Gold Chain Motive (Treasure No. 482-2)&amp;gt; &amp;lt;Sanjungsingok (Treasure No. 482-3)&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;The Fisherman&#39;s History&amp;gt; This is because there are plenty of things to see, such as the bilateral preliminary drafting document (Treasure No. 482-5).
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Manor level presentation right - Haenam-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/295/98d53f41-e9d9-4dcb-9a14-96ba163a6540.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Manor level presentation right
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The works of the great-grandson Gong-jae are also difficult. Self-portraits of the public offerings introduced earlier, including Doo-seo Yun (National Treasure No. 240), Gongjaehwahwa (Treasure No. 481), Baekmado (Treasure No. 481), Dongguk Yeoji Map (Treasure No. 481-3), still life paintings, and Jinkyungsan hydration The back is waiting.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;14&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Self-portrait of Yoon Doo-seo, a great-grandson of high mountains - Haenam-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/295/62266079-c205-48c1-b730-9d46c4c1e9c6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Self-portrait of Yoon Doo-seo, a great-grandson of high mountains
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Let&#39;s go to Nokwoodang after looking at the relics. The gently curved walls continue to shine. Interestingly, the towering gate is on the side.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;16&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The beauty figure that Yun Yong, the grandson of Gongjae, drew - Haenam-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/295/efb8c0a1-8b36-46ef-8e94-bb94d859d16c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The beauty figure that Yun Yong, the grandson of Gongjae, drew
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Haenam-gun Office&#39;s cultural commentator Park Mi-rye explained that it means &#34;I will live quietly without revealing myself to the world.&#34;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;18&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The rising gate of the alpine house facing sideways without facing Sarangchae - Haenam-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/295/645d59e5-5c43-4b0c-87a2-af1244ee3629.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The rising gate of the alpine house facing sideways without facing Sarangchae
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Nokwoodang is currently living in Gosan, the 14th descendant of Gosan. In the double eaves for heat preservation that was not used at the time by the Sadaebu, we can see the tradition of pursuing real-world poetry.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;20&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Stone wall path of a luxurious alpine house - Haenam-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/295/b3651f35-96d4-4fea-9c97-1446d27f275f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Stone wall path of a luxurious alpine house
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you go to Nokdangdan, walk along the stone wall to the Visa Tree Forest. After passing the alpine shrine, Haenam&#39;s ancestral ancestral fishery, Echo Hyo-jeong (1476 ~ 1543), passes through the shrine, and the Visa Tree Forest Road is designated as a natural monument. Eochoeun, Hyojeong Yoon, took the ground at Nokwoodang and laid the foundation for Haenam Yoon to flourish. It was said that the descendants planted the Visa tree in response to his instruction, &#34;If you see a rock on the back mountain, the village will be poor.&#34; This is also the reason why Haenam&#39;s delicacy was created. When they visited Mr. Haenam Yoon&#39;s Jongtaek, who said that farts would change, they were treated to Visa-made Korean tea and tea.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;22&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Alpine shrine - Haenam-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/295/e8c3285d-e2c1-42da-bd3d-0ff7b63617b8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Alpine shrine
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Even now, I haven&#39;t even been able to see Visa Gangjeong, but even in the middle of winter, I still soothe the rain in the midst of the rain. Did Alpine heard this rain here?
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;24&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Eochoeun Shrine - Haenam-gun, Jeollanam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/295/f5abcc1c-0b1d-433d-8204-ee2e53654109.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Eochoeun Shrine
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   TIP Gosan Yunseondo Historic Site
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    To enter the ruins of the Alpine Yunseon-do, you have to pay an admission fee. 2,000 won for adults, 1,500 won for youth and military guards, and 1,000 won for children. You can also hear explanations from cultural commentators residing at the relics exhibition hall. Closed on Mondays, from 9am to 6pm. After inspecting the relics exhibition, it takes a generous 2 hours to go all the way to Nokwoodang&#39;s Bijarim walk.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     ▶ Contact
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Gosan Yunseondo Historic Site: 061-530-5548, 135 Nokwoodang-gil, Haenam-eup, Haenam-gun, Jeollanam-do
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Haenam-gun Office Cultural Tourism 061-530-5918
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Nearby restaurants
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    There are quite a few restaurants where you can taste Korean food and sashimi in towns and tourist areas near the county office. Chicken specialty shops, known as another delicacy in Haenam, are also gathered in Dongyeon-ri. There are many restaurants and lodging facilities at the end of the earth.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Cheonil Restaurant
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Hanjeongsik / Haenam-eup, Eupnaeri / 061-536-4001
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Seongjeong Han
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Han Jeong-sik / Gugyo-ri, Haenam-eup / 061-536-1060
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Honam Restaurant
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Hanjeongsik (Mushroom Course) / Samsan-myeon Gurim-ri / 061-534-5400
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Wired pipe
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Han Jeong-sik / Samrim-myeon Gurim-ri / 061-534-2959
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Longevity Chicken
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Chicken cuisine / Haenam-eup Dongdong-ri / 061-535-1003
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Hosanjeong
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Chicken cuisine / Haenam-eup Dongdong-ri / 061-534-8844
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Land End Garden Hall
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Songji Song Hori / 061-532-3004
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     End of the sea
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Songji Songhori / 061-534-6422
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Do it
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Songji Song Hori / 061-532-0005
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2.Accommodation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Land End Motel
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Songji Songhori / 061-535-5001
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Haenam Land End Hotel
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Namdong-gil, Haenam-eup / 061-530-8000
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Blue motel
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Songji Song Hori / 061-534-6677
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Wired pipe
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Daeheungsa-gil, Samsan-myeon / 061-534-2959
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.yuseongwan.com/html/main.php&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.yuseongwan.com/html/main.php
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was created in May 2016, and may be changed later, so be sure to check it before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>