<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gongju-si on Every Corner of Korea</title>
    <link>https://codecorea.github.io/tags/gongju-si/</link>
    <description>Every Corner of Korea (Gongju-si)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 03:28:49 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="https://codecorea.github.io/tags/gongju-si/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Singing the fresh green of Magoksa Temple along Magokcheon Stream - Gongju-si, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/singing-the-fresh-green-of-magoksa-temple-along-magokcheon-stream-215/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 03:28:49 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/singing-the-fresh-green-of-magoksa-temple-along-magokcheon-stream-215/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Gongju-si, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;singing-the-fresh-green-of-magoksa-temple-along-magokcheon-stream--215&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Magoksa Temple Solbaram-gil - Gongju-si, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/215/330a4a1b-87eb-4a10-b151-078e86ac54d2.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Magoksa Temple Solbaram-gil
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Singing the fresh green of Magoksa Temple along Magokcheon Stream
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Gongju-si, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It was called ‘Chunmagok Chugapsa (春 麻 谷 秋 甲 寺)’. This means that the beauty of the season is Magoksa in spring and Gapsa in autumn. As such, the spring scenery of Magoksa Temple is beautiful enough to pick up. In the beautiful scenery, the Magoksa Temple Solbaram Road, which consists of three courses, Baekbeom-gil, Meditation Trail, and Songlim Forest Trail, was created. Take a walk with Magoksa Temple on the meditative walking trail, which is the beauty of Magoksa Temple Solbaram-gil.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   春 Magog, depicting its beauty
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   After passing the busy shopping street at the entrance to Magoksa Temple, Magokcheon Stream runs side by side and leads you to Magoksa Temple. When Magokcheon winds up one round like a Taegeuk pattern, it reaches the grounds of Magoksa Temple. Magoksa Temple is a millennium study founded by Jajangyulsa during King Munmu of Silla. It has been said that a lot of horses grew up in the valley of Taehwasan, where Magoksa Temple was inhabited.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Magokcheon, where fresh greens bloom - Gongju-si, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/215/da4f07d6-b715-43b3-9b83-fb761b3079c4.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Magokcheon, where fresh greens bloom
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Magoksa Temple is a temple with a long history, so you can&#39;t look around at any one. There are Yeongsanjeon, Daeungbojeon, Daegwangbojeon, and Five-storied Pagoda designated as treasures in the precincts, and Haetalmun, Cheonwangmun, Myeongbujeon, National History Hall, Eungjinjeon, Simgeumdang, and Gobang are designated as cultural properties.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Daegwangbojeon and Daeungbobojeon, five-storied pagoda from Magoksa Temple grounds - Gongju-si, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/215/fbc5752f-8820-4667-88b7-fa53c51a6473.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Daegwangbojeon and Daeungbobojeon, five-storied pagoda from Magoksa Temple grounds
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Among them, Daekwang Preservation is one of many places to see and it is good to take a slow tour. First, the plaque of Daekwangbojeon, which shows brilliant technique, is known as the writing of Pyoam Kang Se-hwang. Kang Se-hwang is well-known as a representative of the late Joseon Dynasty, and an instructor of Hong-do Kim. Inside the Daekwangbojeon Hall, you can meet the Virozana Buddha, which sits toward the east rather than the south, such as the Museoksujeon in Buseoksa in Yeongju or Daeungjeon in Yeonggwangbulgapsa. Behind the post-war paintings, there is the Suwol Baekwan Gwaneumdo in white clothes. In addition, there are 16 Nahan and Sichuan kings as well as various landscape paintings inside and outside Daekwang Preservation. This is because Magoksa has many masters who draw paintings in the center of the southern pixel, the great veins of Buddhist art.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Daewanggwang Conservation - Gongju-si, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/215/16d37618-080b-4547-8ab5-92e11affa18a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Daewanggwang Conservation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In Daekwangbojeon, there is also a story of a nest made of oak bark. It is a story that a person with a disease of the sick had a place for 100 days in order to offer to the Buddha, and walked leisurely after taking the place on the 100th day. It is a story that the Buddha impressed with his sincerity and showed his grace.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Daegwang Preservation - Gongju-si, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/215/85fd21ef-95d4-48ab-be08-242e44a07c75.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Daegwang Preservation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The writings of the Joseon Dynasty also remain. That&#39;s the signboard of Yeongsanjeon at the entrance of Magoksa Temple. When King Sejo visited Magoksa Temple to see Kim Si-pup, who is one of the incarnations, and he couldn&#39;t meet, he left the plaque of Yeongsanjeon and his kiln. When King Sejo seized the throne, it was Kim Si-seop, a monthly fan who cried while burning books. Sejo&#39;s regrettable desire to meet and meet him is buried. As Yeongsanjeon is currently being dismantled, it is impossible to see the plate, and it is difficult to see Sejo&#39;s kiln.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A dragon biting a fish next to a billboard - Gongju-si, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/215/76f857d3-896c-47ef-abd0-cbf4cc17e10a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A dragon biting a fish next to a billboard
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Magoksa Temple stands at the top of Daekwangbojeon and shows a very unique arrangement. When you go up the stairs behind Daekwangbojeon, there is a huge Daeungbobojeon standing like a 2nd floor pavilion. Looking down the grounds from the stairs, the roof line of the building is very beautiful in the direction of Simgeumdang and Gobang.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Roof of Magoksa Temple from Daeungbojeon - Gongju-si, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/215/087bb6ea-8f7c-4455-b9a1-ad5c980d794b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Roof of Magoksa Temple from Daeungbojeon
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Walk the white rice and Baekbeom-gil of Magoksa Temple Solbaram-gil
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Magoksa Temple also retains the traces of Baekbeom Kim Gu. Kim Gu escaped from prison while he was serving as a murderer for the murder of a Japanese army lieutenant who misunderstood Empress Myeongseong. In 1946, shortly after liberation, the teacher visited Magoksa Temple and planted juniper trees on the grounds. At that time, a planted juniper tree stands for 60 years, standing beside Eungjinjeon.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   At the foot of Mt. It is aka “Baekbeom Meditation Road”. This is the path that Kim Gu walked while hiding in Magoksa Temple. Magoksa Solbaram-gil consists of three courses. Course 1 is a 3km course that departs from Magoksa Temple and returns to Magoksa Temple after passing through Kim Saekbalteo and Gunwangdae. Course 2 is a meditation walkway starting from the parking lot of Magoksa Temple and going down to Magoksa Temple through natural pine bath, Baengnyeonam, Hwainbong, and Saenggol Village. It is 10km from Bong, Traditional Buddhist Cultural Center, and Gunwangdae to Magoksa Temple. It is a place where people of all ages, men and women can come and go, and can see the impressive pine forest path and traces of Baekbeom Kim Gu.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Juniper tree planted by teacher Baekbeom Kim - Gongju-si, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/215/991dcc71-1d4d-4bd3-91bb-4377d4477f4e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Juniper tree planted by teacher Baekbeom Kim
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Course 1 starts with a tour of the Magoksa temple grounds and a tour of the juniper trees planted by Kim Gu. If you pass by the side road of the juniper tree, you will wind up around Magoksa and meet the flowing Magokcheon. Along the road that runs alongside Magokcheon, there is a Baekbeom Kim Gu teacher Shakbalteo. It is said that the teacher was imprisoned for the murder of the Japanese army and escaped from Magoksa-ro and became a monk.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   “The priest Ho Deok-sam brought a knife to cut his hair. I went out to the stream and crushed the shaved mantra, and my coat fell on the sand. I have already made up my mind, but tears fell like my hair. ” At that time, the record remains in the Baekbeom Ilchi. The fresh green along the waterside of Magokcheon is beautiful. It seems that the first spring came with the bite of Magokcheon.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Magokcheon as seen from Baekbeom Kim Gu&#39;s teacher Shakbalteo - Gongju-si, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/215/ed1227e3-85f7-42f1-9cc9-8e6e0ad577b4.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Magokcheon as seen from Baekbeom Kim Gu&#39;s teacher Shakbalteo
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Baekbeom-gil meets Jindalrae-gil in harmony with pine trees
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Leaving Kim&#39;s shackle ground and crossing Baekbeom Bridge, the road leads straight to the mountain. The entrance is rather flat. The winter is still dim, and the pine trees have fallen all over the place due to the typhoon that hit last year. However, even for a while, if you walk uphill for about 10 minutes, a group of pine trees stretched out through the pine forests are spreading out.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Baekbeom-gil Pine Forest and Azalea - Gongju-si, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/215/5ef46554-ec62-426a-a3d1-aeaf9170fc64.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Baekbeom-gil Pine Forest and Azalea
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The procession of pine trees that stood up gracefully for a long time like a ten-thousand support in Jung Gam-rok is filled with dignity. Magoksa&#39;s fresh green is now beginning, but the light pink waves shine through the pine forest. The rhododendron that blooms through the pine forest looks like a pink cloud.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Baekbeom-gil with beautiful pine trees and rhododendrons - Gongju-si, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/215/255ec4f1-92ff-4468-b98f-cde2b7567651.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Baekbeom-gil with beautiful pine trees and rhododendrons
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The pine tree here is not a Rigida pine tree that grows straight, but is a representative pine tree in Korea that shows off its curves. The footsteps are so good that they will not fall for a while. The pine forest path and the rhododendron colony that extend over 500m are the beauty of Baekbeom-gil.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Baekbeom-gil with beautiful pine trees and rhododendrons - Gongju-si, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/215/0cb9bdfd-2aa1-4c4a-a83e-de6e74458dc0.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Baekbeom-gil with beautiful pine trees and rhododendrons
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you get drunk at the pine forest, you will soon reach the army. The Gunwangdae is named after the king of the military, and is the strongest place around Magoksa Temple. When the Joseon King Sejo stopped by Magoksa Temple, he said, “I am the king of a country, but I can&#39;t compare it to this place where I live in the world.”
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Baekbeom-gil with beautiful pine trees and rhododendrons - Gongju-si, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/215/50ae65d0-fc6a-4233-8185-3b23d2650a72.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Baekbeom-gil with beautiful pine trees and rhododendrons
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   From Gunwangdae to Magoksa Temple, it takes less than 10 minutes downhill. Baekbeom-gil of Magoksa Solbaram-gil is enough to walk for an hour.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The light pink azalea is bright - Gongju-si, Chungcheongnam-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/215/0eb0b687-e737-4857-b2ef-427c69aca82b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The light pink azalea is bright
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1.Access
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    * Self-driving
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Dangjin Sangju Expressway Magoksa IC → Turn right at Sadong Intersection towards Magoksa Temple → Local Road No. 629 towards Magoksa Temple → Magoksa Temple
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    * public transport
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Seoul → Gongju: Operates 34 times a day (06: 05-23: 05) from Seoul Express Terminal (02-6282-0114), takes 1 hour 50 minutes
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Daejeon → Gongju: Operates 22 times a day (07: 00-21: 00) from Daejeon Complex Terminal (1577-2259), takes 1 hour
    &lt;br/&gt;
    ※ From Gongju Bus Terminal (041-855-8114) to Magoksa, take bus 770 or 610
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Restaurants around
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Taehwa Restaurant: Sanchaejeongsik / 10, Magoksangga-gil, Sagok-myeon, Gongju-si / 041-841-8020
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Saehak Garden: Gukbap / 15-2, Geumgang Park-gil, Gongju-si / 041-855-7080
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Gomanaru Stone Ssambap: Ssambap / 5-9 Baekmi Goul-gil, Gongju-si / 041-857-9999
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     3.Accommodation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Oullim: 469, Yugumagoksa-ro, Yugu-eup, Gongju-si / 041-841-9963
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Ensemble Motel: 6-35 Jeonmak 1-gil, Gongju-si / 041-854-8822
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Right Pension: 126 Wolsan-ri, Jeongan-myeon, Gongju-si / 041-858-0223
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was created in April 2013, and may be changed later, so be sure to check it before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>