<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chuncheon on Every Corner of Korea</title>
    <link>https://codecorea.github.io/tags/chuncheon/</link>
    <description>Every Corner of Korea (Chuncheon)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 03:21:06 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="https://codecorea.github.io/tags/chuncheon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Late spring day, &lt;That winter, the wind blows&gt; Chuncheon Jade Garden - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/late-spring-day-that-winter-the-wind-blows-chuncheon-jade-garden-246/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 03:21:06 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/late-spring-day-that-winter-the-wind-blows-chuncheon-jade-garden-246/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;late-spring-day-that-winter-the-wind-blows-chuncheon-jade-garden--246&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox type2 clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Landmark Tuscan visitor center - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/246/2584c7f7-772c-408a-941c-7504fbb8e2a8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Landmark Tuscan visitor center
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;May flowers color the flower garden - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/246/6775f2e6-e2b2-4267-9db9-6b2e42231066.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    May flowers color the flower garden
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Late spring day, &amp;lt;That winter, the wind blows&amp;gt; Chuncheon Jade Garden
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The drama &amp;lt;That Winter, the Wind Blows&amp;gt; was the background of a snowy winter. In the late spring due to the changing seasons, Jade Garden is more attractive than May&#39;s house in May. The affectionate love of the two, Oh-young and Oh-soo, stops the lovers from walking on the young road. Children run around the blooming flower fields. The green forest can be sweet like cotton candy.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Every tragedy dreams of hope
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The previous work of writer Hee-kyung Roh was &amp;lt;The World They Live in&amp;gt;. The writer borrows the words of Junyoung (Song Hye-kyo), her lover, Geo, and secretly reflects on her inside.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   “Nothing worth saying unless it is hope. Anyone who plays a drama should know that every tragedy the world speaks of is a paradox dreaming of hope. ”
   &lt;br/&gt;
   The drama &amp;lt;That Winter, the Wind Blows&amp;gt; attracted attention as the work of artist Hee-Kyung Roh before airing. It is not easy for a writer to get more attention than an actor (of course, it is Jo In-sung and Song Hye-kyo), but her work always leads the artist&#39;s name. That&#39;s why her story has a deep echo. The original film is a Japanese drama &amp;lt;I Don&#39;t Need Love, Summer&amp;gt;. In Korea, we made a remake as a movie starring Joo-Hyuk Kim and Geun-Young Moon. It is a love story of a man who impersonates her older brother in need of money with an inherited heiress of a conglomerate. There were few opinions that the choice of writer Hee-kyung Roh was unexpected.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Anyway! About the fourth episode, the scene of “The Paradox of All Tragedy Dreams of Hope” appears. This is the &#39;Cotton Candy Kiss&#39;, which became a hot topic throughout the drama. It is the boundary between emotions that the love of two people begins, but cannot be overcome by siblings. It was filmed near the cottage garden in Jade Garden (Arboretum). In addition, many scenes including Oh Young&#39;s house were set in the background of Jade Garden. It&#39;s just that the winter landscape is different.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Visitor center appearing as Oh Young&#39;s house - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/246/d54180fd-2eea-46b1-bbd5-bba32c338219.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Visitor center appearing as Oh Young&#39;s house
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Jade Garden is an arboretum located in Chuncheon. 2,662 species of plants grow in an area of about 16,3,500㎡. This was the third year since it opened in 2011. It belongs to Chuncheon City in the administrative district, but is also close to Gapyeong-gun. Travel along the North Korean river to go to Jade Garden. Pass Gyeonggang Station in the middle. It is a small rural station. It is the location of the film &amp;lt;Letter&amp;gt; and the drama &amp;lt;Stairway to Heaven&amp;gt;. Right now, the rail bike instead of the train goes to the closed station. Gapyeong Station is a round-trip 7.2km course that takes about 1 hour and 30 minutes. Go past Ganggyeong Station and turn left at Hatgol Intersection to the foot of Myeongtaesan Mountain. Finally, he climbs towards Jade Garden.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox type2 clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;5... - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/246/ab152763-c498-48d7-a046-71f2fa4cd1f5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     5...
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Crystal scenery hanging from the window of Oh Young&#39;s room - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/246/0b99c238-6e2b-4713-95bd-1a2b3b21a9ee.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Crystal scenery hanging from the window of Oh Young&#39;s room
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   The sound of scenery that connects your heart
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   A European-style building greets you on the corner of a steep road. This is a light brown brick house reminiscent of the rural landscape of Tuscany, Italy. This is Jade Garden&#39;s visitor center. Souvenir shops and restaurants are located on the first floor, and the second floor is a multi-room. The most hilarious place is the entrance. Jade Garden is a little different, although the entrance to any arboretum is unlikely. It is a filming location for &amp;lt;The Winter, the Wind Blows&amp;gt;. The heroine Oh Young-eun is the heir of the PL group. The visitor center comes to her home. It is the most frequent place throughout the air. That&#39;s why no one moves right away. There is no hesitation in taking a commemorative photo in line. The person holding the camera waits in the front yard and the party comes out from the window on the second floor. It is a familiar frame for those who have enjoyed the drama. Ohyoung&#39;s room and Ohsu&#39;s back.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Go past the restaurant and go up to the second floor of the visitor center. The crystal scenery in the drama hangs on the window. Whenever the wind blows, the feathers shake and make a xylophone sound. It is the most important prop and metaphor in the drama. Oh-young, a blind person, meets the world through sound. I fell asleep when I heard the scenery, and always fell asleep with the window open. Shortly after Oh-young meets Oh-young and before leaving Oh-young, she reconnects the scenery of the window she remodeled and her hand twice. It is a trace of the place where love passed. Osu&#39;s self-confessing confession follows, &#34;Is there a reason to have a great reason to live?&#34;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The first garden of the maple road, Italian garden - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/246/a3e66203-f137-45dc-a1c7-aaa108757659.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The first garden of the maple road, Italian garden
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The view of the arboretum spreads out the window. The Arboretum in May is the most colorful. Fresh green is closer to high tide, and flowers in May bloom more colorfully than in spring. There is a stall selling cotton candy in front of the souvenir shop across the street. Children who go on a family outing stand in love with the sweet taste. Lovers think of drama and bite cotton candy.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   When you leave the visitor center, the British Border Garden unfolds. From here, a full-scale arboretum walk begins. At the edge flower bed, perennial flowers bloom from spring to autumn. Tulips are full at this time. For those who watch and find dramas, the flower language is new. A red tulip is a confession of love, a yellow tulip is an unseen love, and a purple tulip is an eternal love.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Flower water gorge in the middle of the tree lane - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/246/edf90516-4282-497f-915c-a64bc93e3944.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Flower water gorge in the middle of the tree lane
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Cotton candy is sweet!
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The road is divided into left and right centered on the border garden again. There are three trails in Jade Garden. This is the starting point. Go straight ahead and head towards the flower water garden. In the flower water, flowers and leaves change color according to the season to form a wavy shape. It is 800 meters to the summit Sky Garden, about 40 minutes away. On the left is the Italian garden. It was decorated with lawns and flower beds centered on the aqueduct. On the roadside, a wisteria tunnel overlooks the flower shade. Ginkgo biloba labyrinth, where ginkgo biloba with soft leaves makes a maze, also passes. It is not a maze that obscures the field of view, but the flower grass spreads finely. This maple road is 900m and takes 50 minutes one way. Head to the picnic garden to the right. It is a good way to walk quietly. Iris Garden has beautiful irises. It is called a forest road, and it takes 60 minutes to 1km.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The three roads open in the meantime, sharing colorful themed gardens. An alpine greenhouse was located between the Naeumneum-gil and the Maple-gil. It is a greenhouse planted with alpine plants living in the Alps, Himalayas, and Mt. Baekdu. In the drama, the scene of the mother&#39;s greenhouse was filmed at the Hantaek Botanical Garden in Yongin, but it is good to create an atmosphere in the play. The wooden play house on the back is recommended for families. There is a small valley leading up to the waterfall garden between the tree scent path and the maple tree path. It is perfect for taking a short break from the heat. Children enjoy more than anyone else. It is an aquatic botanical garden before reaching the waterfall garden. It is the widest waterside in the botanical garden and behind it is the cottage garden. There is a kiosk in front of the coin fountain. From the cottage garden to the road through the forest, it is the Rhoden Drone Garden. On that road, I filmed a kiss scene of Oh Young and Oh Soo&#39;s cotton candy.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox type2 clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Coin Fountain in front of Cottage Garden - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/246/e26dbf2c-9655-4b6a-9865-dd2c7e7d6f72.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Coin Fountain in front of Cottage Garden
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Cottage Garden filming a cotton candy kiss - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/246/7c03b5cd-b61b-472f-9726-9b3c08d6feab.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Cottage Garden filming a cotton candy kiss
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Cotton candy is a significant material following the crystal landscape. As a child, Ohsu took Ohyoung to a stationery store to buy cotton candy. To bring back that memory, she gives cotton candy to Oh Young. The subtle love between brothers and sisters is replaced by sharing cotton candy instead of kissing. There are many lines like gems in the Myeongdaesa series, &amp;lt;That Winter, the Wind Blows&amp;gt;. But in the most lovely cotton candy scene, there is nothing to say. It simply recalls past memories. At the end of the scene, a short word left by Oh Young concentrates his emotions.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   &#34;Sweet.&#34;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Cotton candy fan for ‘replay’ - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/246/52f9f5f8-cb55-4eb6-a80b-88e4f3048dd8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Cotton candy fan for ‘replay’
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Love is innocent
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The drama had many close-up scenes. So is the cotton candy scene. The surrounding views are not well visible. It is a winter landscape, even if it is faraway. Now, the forest in May is beautiful. The two main characters disappeared, and only the colors resembling the two emotions remained. It is a forest with fresh flowers. Stepping into the Rhoden Drone Garden makes the forest a little deeper. It is a fairly high zone within the arboretum. Native species such as Manbyeongcho, roe deer and ferns are brought up. Deep in the lungs is a refreshing feeling. The air is sweet.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   At the summit wedding garden, the scenery similar to that of the cottage garden is redone. This is a light brown single-storey brick building that looks exactly like the visitor center. In the drama &amp;lt;Love Rain&amp;gt;, this is where Hana (yoona) came to her mother&#39;s house. It is actually a kiosk. A tree in front of Baeksong stood on the railing. It is a shelter around the slope. The wedding garden was built around white plants. The flowers of the Jopop tree bloomed on the street. The slope behind is Sky Garden and high-rise support. This is the place where the view of Jade Garden comes in at a glance. Gathering under the tree shade, they enjoy May. The green mountains stretch out coolly. Time passes slowly. Calmness in my heart. Oh-young&#39;s house is underneath. Was Oh Suwa&#39;s love a tragedy or a hope for her? Maybe the wind blew the scenery.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Shady shelter under the foothills, high-rise support - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/246/f9fe80f2-4b9d-4324-939a-2b49a7f739eb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Shady shelter under the foothills, high-rise support
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   “It is innocent that you deceived me. You were a way to live, and sometimes I was happy. ”
   &lt;br/&gt;
   Oh-young forgives Oh-su. The forest in May is so green that it turns tragedy into hope. Life is not fulfilled as hoped, but hope is itself.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;] Wildflowers that show off the beauty of May - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/246/91ac2ac2-b5f4-4728-9a8e-c2e0cca6040a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     ] Wildflowers that show off the beauty of May
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    * Jade Garden
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Address: 111 Seocheon-ri, Namsan-myeon, Chuncheon-si, Gangwon-do
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Inquiries: 033-260-8300,
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.jadegarden.kr&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     www.jadegarden.kr
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    1.Access
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    * Self-driving
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Chuncheon Expressway Hwado IC → Gapyeong → Turn right at Hapgol Intersection → 1km along the village road → Jade Garden
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    * public transport
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Gyeongchun Line Sangbong Station → Gulbongsan Station → Jade Garden Shuttle Bus (10: 45-16: 45 every 1 hour, 12:45 minutes only on weekends and holidays)
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    2. Restaurants around
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Gangchon Makguksu Chicken Ribs: Chicken Ribs / 247-11, Gangchon 1-ri, Namsan-myeon, Chuncheon-si / 033-262-4304
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Gyeonggang Makguksu: Makguksu / 62-4 Seobaek-gil, Namsan-myeon, Chuncheon-si / 033-263-1138
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Yurim Chicken Ribs: Chicken Ribs and Makguksu / 7 Anmasan-ro, Chuncheon / 033-253-5489 / 033-244-5119 (New Building)
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    3.Accommodation
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Elysian Gangchon Resort: 688, Bukhangangbyeon-gil, Namsan-myeon, Chuncheon-si / 033-260-2000 /
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.elysian.co.kr/golf/gangchon/overview.asp&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;엘리시안으로 이동&#34;&gt;
     http://www.elysian.co.kr/golf/gangchon/overview.asp
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Gangchon Sky Love Pension: 279 Gangchon-ro, Namsan-myeon, Chuncheon-si / 011-208-2631 /
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.gcskylove.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;강촌하늘사랑 펜션으로 이동&#34;&gt;
     http://www.gcskylove.com/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Remembrance Pension: 291-3 Seocheon-ri, Namsan-myeon, Chuncheon-si / 010-3006-4462 /
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.rememberpension.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;리멤버펜션으로 이동&#34;&gt;
     http://www.rememberpension.com/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    ※ The above information was created in May 2013, and may change later, so be sure to check it before you travel.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Soyangho, the most beautiful view from the mountainous valley, Bugwi-ri, Oji Village, Chuncheon - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/soyangho-the-most-beautiful-view-from-the-mountainous-valley-bugwiri-oji-village-chuncheon-242/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 03:21:02 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/soyangho-the-most-beautiful-view-from-the-mountainous-valley-bugwiri-oji-village-chuncheon-242/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;soyangho-the-most-beautiful-view-from-the-mountainous-valley-bugwiri-oji-village-chuncheon--242&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;You can take a boat entering Cheongpyeongsa from Soyangho Pier. - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/242/283f8272-c71b-4392-9f28-ab9b5d1e463f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    You can take a boat entering Cheongpyeongsa from Soyangho Pier.
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Soyangho, the most beautiful view from the mountainous valley, Bugwi-ri, Oji Village, Chuncheon
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Every 30 minutes, a boat goes to Cheongpyeongsa Temple, a famous temple and tourist attraction, at the Soyangho Pier in Chuncheon. Cheongpyeongsa Temple was located on foot before the Soyang Dam in 1972.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Now, the entire stream that flows from Seoraksan to Incheon and Chuncheon through Inje and Yanggu is called Soyanggang.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Boats going between Soyangho Pier and Cheongpyeongsa Pier - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/242/c37040a9-c003-4056-8036-9f6f6e8e064a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Boats going between Soyangho Pier and Cheongpyeongsa Pier
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It is said that it took less than an hour to reach Yanggu by running the unpaved road along the Shinyeong River by bus. Of course, when the bus falls into a dirt pit or meets a hill, the guest had to get off and push it, so there were times when it took longer.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A villager I met at Hau Pass with a wealth - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/242/309aa32c-d642-40ea-a035-58e7158d1014.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A villager I met at Hau Pass with a wealth
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   By the time all of these memories were immersed, various villagers left for Chuncheon or farther. Residents who couldn&#39;t leave their hometowns moved to new houses on high hills, avoiding rising water. So, several island villages were formed along the stream of Soyang Lake. Booguri and Ohangri were also one of the island villages. The island village on the land was the only link to the outside, with boats going twice a day.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The place where Bugui Elementary School, now an ecological experience site, was located - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/242/cfbe592b-5051-46bc-b225-422f9efea54d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The place where Bugui Elementary School, now an ecological experience site, was located
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   At Buguri-ri and Ohang-ri docks in Buksan-myeon, ships leaving the Soyangho dock at 8:30 am and 4 pm (3 pm in the winter) stop by all day. In that island village, not that island, Limdo was drilled in 1999, and in 2009, an asphalt road was formed. Even though it is a thin path, it is the lifeline that left the island village.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Log cabins where residents live - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/242/e8258b4c-d5dc-4364-8301-e35006fe1dd7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Log cabins where residents live
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   There are many places where rocks and mud have been poured down on the trail of Baeryeongnyeong that passes over Chuncheon to Oumri. It was because of the landslide during the last heavy rain. I cannot see the other side of the winding road, so I have to slow down and pass carefully.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A path leading from the Booguri to the hillside - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/242/dd2bcbfd-4bc2-484c-b10f-47c695e80701.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A path leading from the Booguri to the hillside
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   This road was Route 46 connecting Chuncheon and Yanggu, but it feels a little neglected after the new highway. Turn right at the first crossroad beyond Baeryeongnyeong and cross the Obongsan Pass to Cheongpyeongsa Temple. The way to go to Cheongpyeongsa Temple is not just a boat crossing Soyang Lake.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;13&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A rock that collapsed on the way to the hillside - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/242/21833244-b481-4bcb-8a21-cb215628667a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A rock that collapsed on the way to the hillside
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Most tourists walk to the Cheongpyeongsa Temple from Cheongpyeongsa Pier or parking lot along the valley. On the way, you can see the Guangsu Falls and meet the legends of the Chinese princess and the snake.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;15&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A statue with a story of a Chinese princess and a snake - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/242/c3c3f863-4c1b-4a38-9b1e-c112292b4360.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A statue with a story of a Chinese princess and a snake
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Cheongpyeongsa Temple is worth a look as a historic temple with many cultural properties. However, no one goes through the parking lot to the back of Cheongpyeongsa Pier. It looks like a well-packed road and no road to the car. Is it because I think there is nothing to go about?
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;17&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Cheongpyeongsa valley composed of two steps up and down - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/242/aab9eb7e-e121-4b96-ab4a-8f2d245f73fa.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Cheongpyeongsa valley composed of two steps up and down
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Merchants around the parking lot just said that it was the way to Bugwi-ri, Buksan-myeon. In the name of it, it is ‘Buguiro’. Starts to run along the booby road.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;19&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Cheongpyeongsa Temple, a historic temple founded in Gwangjong, Goryeo - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/242/e67af459-c233-4857-a7d7-c4663c6576f7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Cheongpyeongsa Temple, a historic temple founded in Gwangjong, Goryeo
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Looking at the boat on the Cheongpyeongsa Pier, I ran along a winding path along the hillside, so it was a vine, weed, and wild wildflowers that I didn&#39;t know were smiling.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;21&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A nostril - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/242/8f3272d0-9f57-4d44-87f7-23234ebefeb7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A nostril
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Tree branches sweep through the face of a helmet, and a squirrel runs across the road.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;23&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Chinese cabbage field at the end of the dirt road - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/242/b3e4bd94-6c62-49e0-b550-d5c0e2cccf11.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Chinese cabbage field at the end of the dirt road
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   I wanted to go along a winding path along Buguiro, but soon it turned into a steep slope and the altitude increased. As you climb near the ridge of the Hau Pass, you can see the shape of the powerful mountain line of Obongsan and Buyongsan on the left at a glance. Soyang Lake is shined by sunlight. After stopping at the side of the road, take a sip of water and capture the scenery spread under your feet. I think he was good at stealing sweat from his forehead.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;25&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Cheongpyeong Bridge and Soyangho from the way to Geonbongryeong - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/242/5ea47acf-4f8f-4876-bc41-f8b5b8e270c7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Cheongpyeong Bridge and Soyangho from the way to Geonbongryeong
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   After crossing the ridge, a notice board called Buguri Mountain Village Eco Experience Village appears. You can also see the phrase green village. The road extends in all directions, centered on Bugwi-kyo, in front of the old manjeong of Buguri On the top of Bugwi Bridge, the unpaved road runs along the water valley, and there is a mountain village ecological experience center at the Bugwi branch of Cheonjeon Elementary School.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;27&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Nameless waterfall in the water valley - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/242/41dcfbfb-611d-47d5-b5e7-0e05e880a723.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Nameless waterfall in the water valley
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The path that extends down leads to the hillside. Although it is said to be Boogwiri, there are several houses scattered in each valley, and there are villages with different names.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;29&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The road leading to the end of the water along the valley - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/242/5880f6ea-5e5a-458d-b423-370be6f980c8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The road leading to the end of the water along the valley
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The small path continues over the hill road leading to the mountainous valley. On the way, the Soyang Lake which looks down the road is wonderful. There is a signboard called &#39;Geonbongryeong Seunghodae&#39; at the place where the mountain valley is left 2.5km. Soyangho from here is truly superb. The moment you turn around the hill, the exclamation point bursts into a fantastic view that is difficult to say. Is it the sea in the land? Or would it be called Dowonkyung in the mountains? The lakeside shines blue with the light of the sky, and small islands are floating in various places, and it seems to have met a calm sea. No, it is better than any other sea. I wonder if there is such a superb view hiding in such a place, and I am happy to touch the camera shutter as if I met a treasure.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;31&#34; id3=&#34;15&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The writing of Konbongnyeong Seungho University was written by Choi Young-sik, teacher - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/242/23af93db-b18d-404b-a991-dc735abe4236.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The writing of Konbongnyeong Seungho University was written by Choi Young-sik, teacher
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Another closing school appears when you reach the hillside, enjoying the afterglow of Soyangho&#39;s superb view from Seunghodae in Gunbongryeong. Sangcheon Elementary School was closed in 1992. A signboard stands on the grassy campus. It was founded in 1948 as Naepyeong Elementary School&#39;s Cheongpyeong Branch, and after passing through several names and was placed in a situation where it would be destroyed by the construction of Soyang Dam, it was moved to a higher position than the original site, and was closed naturally due to the decrease in residents.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;33&#34; id3=&#34;16&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Naepyeong Elementary School now closed, Cheongpyeong Branch - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/242/cb3f39ab-a51d-4304-a717-a814f1ce8e75.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Naepyeong Elementary School now closed, Cheongpyeong Branch
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   As I read the information board, the building keeper calls me to have a drink even in hot weather. It turns out that it is Korean painter and calligraphy artist Uan Choi Young-sik. The closed Cheongcheon branch teacher has been remodeled and used as a workshop, and is said to have been living for 14 years. It&#39;s an accidental meeting, but the teacher, Wuan, has a history of wealth, and he uncovers an old story related to the sinking of the Soyang Dam.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;35&#34; id3=&#34;17&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Mr. Choi Young-shik&#39;s pine tree picture - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/242/00a1be14-a295-43ed-a8dd-09edc9178986.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Mr. Choi Young-shik&#39;s pine tree picture
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Listening to an interesting story reminds me of the residents I met in Haugogae and Senggol a while ago. They also told a lot of town stories to strangers. Everyone is very attached to the village. As if to revive the past memories, I try to tell the story of a village under the water that only exists as a memory.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;37&#34; id3=&#34;18&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Pine colony in the field - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/242/4cc5ab8d-8ee1-4f4b-8bc5-f1f3135ff74d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Pine colony in the field
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Exit the mountainous valley and go to the point where the water valley is joined by Soyang Lake. Like the upper part of the upper part of the Bugyo Bridge, the downstream water valleys flow around the Soyang Lake in a charming waterway that winds around the rocks or forms waterfalls and cows.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;39&#34; id3=&#34;19&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Kindergarten students had a picnic in the valley below the bridge - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/242/84e58624-a4f9-49b7-86c3-6979981a6dcf.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Kindergarten students had a picnic in the valley below the bridge
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   As the end of the heavy rain continued, an angler was seated at the water level where the water level reached his chin. She wants to swing the bait and throw the bait and poke away, and Koyo finds it. The dragonfly flies into the landscape and sinks down on the grass.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;41&#34; id3=&#34;20&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Where Ohang-ri&#39;s dead end meets Soyangho - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/242/0792e198-1a2f-4a98-abb8-1e86a2398306.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Where Ohang-ri&#39;s dead end meets Soyangho
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Head over Ooguri to Ohang-ri. Ohhang-ri is located in Buksan-myeon. Like Boogwi-ri, it was once an island village, and it was a place where the road and road passing through Chugok-ri opened the way to escape Oji village.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;43&#34; id3=&#34;21&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Buksan-myeon Office in Ohang-ri - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/242/9bb9a45c-0c09-444b-a5c2-f395e4871ba3.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Buksan-myeon Office in Ohang-ri
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Still, there are still batters along the river, and twice a day goes in and out. If you go further from the cotton base, you can see the sperm with the plaque engraved ‘Sucheong’, and the road is divided into two branches, leading to the Naepyeong-ri and Ohang-ri batters. Soyangho is the point where it ends.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;45&#34; id3=&#34;22&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Ohangri batter with a large pine tree - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/242/9f43e244-a7b9-4c77-9d59-8ba0f664a74e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Ohangri batter with a large pine tree
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   After looking around Naeyeong-ri and Ohang-ri, if you fall towards Chugok-ri, you will meet the national road between Chuncheon and Yanggu again. Chugok-ri is famous for Chugok-ri.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;47&#34; id3=&#34;23&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Chugok distilled water discovered by Kim Won-bo, a resident of Chugok-ri in 1812 - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/242/16d48680-90e6-4bab-b9c8-b026894d01f3.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Chugok distilled water discovered by Kim Won-bo, a resident of Chugok-ri in 1812
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In search of medicinal bones, spread the mineral water over the gourd and drink it. The iron tastes bitter and the fresh energy spreads through the body. &#34;Great ~ Good!&#34; The word “healing” is very popular these days, right? After walking in Boogwi-ri and Ohang-ri, taking a clean, unspoiled energy full of body, the steps toward Chuncheon are light.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;49&#34; id3=&#34;24&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Chugok mineral water has a strong taste and refreshing taste. - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/242/626cc8e7-e826-4d75-bf39-e1ac7133e217.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Chugok mineral water has a strong taste and refreshing taste.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Chuncheon City Hall Tourism Division
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    033-250-3068
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://tour.chuncheon.go.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://tour.chuncheon.go.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Chuncheon-si Buksan-myeon Office
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    033-250-3610
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1.Access
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    * Self-driving
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Seoul Chuncheon Expressway → Chuncheon IC → National Road No. 46 → Obongsan-ro → Cheongpyeongsa Temple → Bugwi-ri
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    * public transport
    &lt;br/&gt;
    From Cheongnyangni Station, take the Gyeongchun Line train to Chuncheon Station. From Chuncheon Station, take the 18-1 city bus to Cheongpyeongsa Temple. However, only on weekends and holidays
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Restaurants around
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Transferring Grandmother&#39;s Chuncheon Central Chicken Ribs: Chicken Ribs / 13-5, Geumgang-ro 62beon-gil, Chuncheon-si / 033-253-4444
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.wonjodak.net/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.wonjodak.net/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Chuncheon Specialty Chicken Ribs: Chicken Ribs, Makguksu / 807, Old Gyeongchun-ro, Chuncheon-si / 033-255-2069, 033-257-3069
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://blog.daum.net/leek2069&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://blog.daum.net/leek2069
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Chuncheon Myeongga Makguksu: Makguksu / 39 Cheonjeon-ri, Sinbuk-eup, Chuncheon-si / 033-241-8443
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     3.Accommodation
     &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Chuncheon Youth Travel House: 3035 Yeongseo-ro, Chuncheon-si / 033-250-3560
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Radena Condo: 317 Sports Town-gil, Chuncheon-si / 033-240-8000
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.ladenaresort.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.ladenaresort.com/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    ※ The above information was created in August 2013, and may be changed later, so be sure to check it before you travel.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>REVIEW 1st Gangwon Four Lakes Canoe Touring Experience - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/review-1st-gangwon-four-lakes-canoe-touring-experience-237/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 23:27:23 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/review-1st-gangwon-four-lakes-canoe-touring-experience-237/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;review-1st-gangwon-four-lakes-canoe-touring-experience--237&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Enjoying canoeing - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/237/b32bbb51-33c1-46aa-aa88-6cc109d351e7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Enjoying canoeing
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   REVIEW 1st Gangwon Four Lakes Canoe Touring Experience
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    From the 3rd of October, the “1st Gangwon Four Lakes Canoe Touring Tournament” was held for four days in Gangwon Province, which runs four major lakes (Uiam, Chuncheon, Faro, and Soyangho). This event, which canoe the hem of Chuncheon, Hwacheon, and Yanggu in Gangwon-do as a canoe, was held jointly by Gangwon-do and the Gangwon Cooperation Foundation of the Korea Tourism Organization, Chuncheon, Hwacheon, Yanggu, and Mullegil.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The first “Gangwon-do Four Lakes Canoe Touring Tournament” was held on a tight schedule for four days. Nevertheless, I was able to successfully complete the first tournament, the protagonist “Canoe,” who swims on the water like a slippery slippery, and the ball in the lake that kept his seat silently might be big. It wasn&#39;t long, but it was enough time to know the charm of the canoe. Introducing the site of the &#39;1st Gangwon Four Lakes Canoe Touring Tournament (hereinafter referred to as the Canoe Tournament)&#39;.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Canoe competition starts with basic education - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/237/502452b5-9a53-40a3-8acb-b0ff7f4f6dd3.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Canoe competition starts with basic education
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Paddling about 20 km per day… Meet Uiam, Chuncheon, Faro and Soyangho
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    On October 3, participants began to gather at the water wheel marina located in Uiam Lake in Chuncheon. More than 50 people participated, including local government officials, related industries, club members, and the general public selected from the Internet application. After a brief opening and training of canoeing by experts, I climbed a canoe and started my first day. Most of them climbed into canoes in groups of two, each with their own partner. Experts who have prepared their own canoes enjoyed canoeing alone.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Safety training in canoes - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/237/483a1430-89b6-4e55-a843-10656ea7e58c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Safety training in canoes
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Reporter who once experienced sea kayaking from Buan Gyeokpo Port to Latitude with a small, touring kayak was confident. What is so different about &#39;paddle rowing&#39;? Kayaks and canoes were equally non-motorized, so I thought that “no” was “no” because it was paddled to light the arms.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Click during the competition, group photo - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/237/5a790c29-dba8-45c4-ac0d-56d65f5e310a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Click during the competition, group photo
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Even if the upper part of the boat is blocked or open, even if the kayak is large, it belongs to a canoe. The kayak must have been double-edged, but the canoe is a single day. Ohora, it should be much easier.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Canoe on the way to the lake - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/237/e1614178-27ff-4495-bdf2-09646754ac5b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Canoe on the way to the lake
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The point of canoeing is to &#34;take the oars that have been pushed out and bring them back horizontally to the water.&#34; I realized that most of the eco-friendly outdoor activities were “not difficult,” so I climbed a canoe with both a camera and a paddle. Iron arms, please remember the “paddling” sense of those days.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Healing in a canoe with plenty of paddling - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/237/b606bf19-e66b-4ecd-ab71-be69e5e1de83.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Healing in a canoe with plenty of paddling
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Canoes can accommodate up to three adults or two adults (up to 13 years of age). The person who came together today is Seung-Tae Lee, manager of Canoe-related company &amp;lt;Comarine&amp;gt;. Heaven helps. Even beginners can be a pair of 2 people, but they go on a boat like this.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Healing in a canoe with plenty of paddling - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/237/52e7995b-df2a-4e75-9433-07d1c3e6a58b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Healing in a canoe with plenty of paddling
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Still, the course to run today is not easy. From here, you have to drive about 20.5 km from the starting point of the waterway to Hwacheon Aquatic Resort (Chuncheon Lake). Canoeing starts by climbing the canoe. One or two of the beginners get on the canoe and the boat turns over. Grab the center and moderately widen one step at a time. Luckily, there was no Buddha statue overturned.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Healing in a canoe with plenty of paddling - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/237/5e6b7409-3421-4241-a9d3-54d35c7de7e8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Healing in a canoe with plenty of paddling
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Healing trip over the lake, canoe
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Usually, a coriander sits on the back of the canoe to keep pace with the front rower. Even if you paddle freely while changing your sore arm, it is entirely the “captain” that moves in my direction. The lake overlooking the canoe reveals a completely different expression than when viewed from the lake. I walk out of the Uiam Lake facing the blue thin sky. The more you canoeing, the more you get out of the noisy reality. Troubles on both shoulders spread out into the lake in a canoe.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Canoes can accommodate up to three adults. - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/237/e77b4c63-b744-4aab-a531-8c125b48523f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Canoes can accommodate up to three adults.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    “Listen to the dripping sound when paddling. I canoe because of this. ”
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    It is the sound that I want to hear first when it is time to reproduce the sound from the text someday. Infinitely quiet and peaceful waterdrops sing along the oars. At the starting point, I heard the sound before reaching the midway pier (7.5 km). You don&#39;t even have to row so that your arm hurts. Anyone, young or old, can start right away if you know how to get directions. The road that seems to be able to continue forever continues.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Enjoy snack time! Snack delivery to paddle! - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/237/28d15a7a-4a5f-41bc-b41c-60c742125ebf.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Enjoy snack time! Snack delivery to paddle!
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    On the afternoon of the first day, we headed from Palgakjeong to Hwacheon Aquatic Resort (13km) today. It&#39;s also fun to have a lot of canoes and snacks together on the middle water. Place the snack on the oar and deliver it to another canoe. At the end of the snack time, the boat of a participant canoe was overturned. The Aquapack was tied to a canoe, so nothing was lost, but I was unable to use my cell phone. “Wait until it is completely dry, then turn it on,” adds the advice.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;When the center shakes, it also falls into the water. - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/237/9bceceda-5695-4676-9d03-ee8e9c2a7a82.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     When the center shakes, it also falls into the water.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    In addition to canoes that can accommodate up to 3 adults, there are single canoes, which are relatively less stable. The participant in the overturned boat was transferred to the boat the reporter was on. There were experts in the front and back, so it was a consideration to take a good photo in the middle. The next day, I would like to express my gratitude to those who have joined us from the Aquatic Resort to the Yanggu Youth Training Center, which is about 22km long.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Canoes rest for a while when they come into contact with the rest - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/237/dfcaa8e8-2a04-4eab-a5cd-69ac2228a9d7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Canoes rest for a while when they come into contact with the rest
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    On the second day, after moving from Aquatic Resort to Hwacheon Batter (7.4km) in the morning, I stopped at the Faro Lake Pier at the Korean Otter Research Center (8.5km) and moved to Wolmyeong Fishing Center (6km). On the first day, the whole body throbbed in the muscle pain left by canoeing, but paddling became easier. Compared to Uiamam Lake and Chuncheon Lake, the water color of the Faro Lake, which has a blue color, also contributed to its strength.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Canoes rest for a while when they come into contact with the rest - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/237/f675ab1e-177f-4b97-9802-4da88c61ff0e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Canoes rest for a while when they come into contact with the rest
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    On the third day, it traveled about 22km from Yanggu Dock to Soyang Art Farm, and on the last day, on the fourth day, it traveled a total of 11km from Soyang Art Farm to Gongjicheon Dock. As a result, the “1st Gangwon Four Lakes Canoe Touring Tournament,” which tours the four lakes of Uiam, Chuncheon, Faro, and Soyang in Gangwon-do, has ended. Those who completed a distance of more than 80km were given a brilliant “Wanter Certificate”.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Anglers met on the lake - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/237/a5ecbc6b-bc02-4909-af8f-51fa71d6ce87.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Anglers met on the lake
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Unfortunately, the only part of the current canoe competition that can be practically experienced at this time is the Uiamam Chuncheon Waterway. It is difficult to experience in other regions except for clubs and those who enjoy canoeing personally. Don&#39;t be too sorry for that. There is a Chuncheon water wheel.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;14&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Anglers met on the lake - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/237/c028c4e4-fbf6-4002-ae01-b81965d3f0e8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Anglers met on the lake
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Tip. Should I go, Chuncheon Mullegil
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    6 times a day on weekdays (09:00, 10:30, 12:00, 13:30, 15:00, 16:30), and 2 times (07:30, 17:00) on weekends on weekends Proceeds. There are many people who visit the water fog canoeing and sunset canoeing in the morning and afternoon on the weekend thanks to the picturesque scenery. Canoe can accommodate up to 3 adults or 2 adults + 2 children in one canoe. The fee is 30,000 won for 2 people. 10,000 won per adult and 5000 won per child. Safety training and canoeing training are conducted before canoeing begins. It takes about 1 hour and 30 minutes by adding both training and tours. Touring may change depending on weather conditions.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    The trails include the Guppy Island Road (3km, 1 hour required), the Uiam Dam Road (3km, 1 hour required), and the Intermediate Road (5km, 2 hours required) for beginners and above.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    ▶ Inquiries: 070-4150-9463,
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.mullegil.org/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;물레길 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
     http://www.mullegil.org/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    ※ The above information was created in October 2013, and may change later, so be sure to check it before you travel.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chuncheon Romantic Alley, the sensibility of the rough appearance - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/chuncheon-romantic-alley-the-sensibility-of-the-rough-appearance-228/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 07:43:06 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/chuncheon-romantic-alley-the-sensibility-of-the-rough-appearance-228/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;chuncheon-romantic-alley-the-sensibility-of-the-rough-appearance--228&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox type2 clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;A humorous tiger at the entrance of Hyoja Village Romantic Alley - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/228/6444cb8f-ee07-455a-884c-aca465641482.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    A humorous tiger at the entrance of Hyoja Village Romantic Alley
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;A humorous tiger at the entrance of Hyoja Village Romantic Alley - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/228/c68d0f7a-4bb5-44eb-92a8-c8100d762922.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    A humorous tiger at the entrance of Hyoja Village Romantic Alley
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Chuncheon Romantic Alley, the sensibility of the rough appearance
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Is there another city that goes well with Chuncheon to add the modifier of romance? Chuncheon, like the word “spring”, is a fluttering excitement that makes you unheard of. The attractions that have been loved for a long time, such as the Soyang River Dam, Uiam Lake, Cheongpyeongsa Temple, and Gongjicheon Stream, may have helped make Chuncheon a romantic city, but in fact, the calm elements hidden in various parts of Chuncheon may make Chuncheon a more romantic space. Following the well-known Chuncheon Romantic Market, a romantic alley has now appeared.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Alleyway warmth, art and culture excitement
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Is there another space full of emotion and full of personality like an alleyway? Every road in the world has its own story, but here in Chuncheon Hyoja&#39;s alleyway boasts a unique story and personality. Hyoja Village Romantic Alley. I&#39;m just curious about the name, and I have a desire to walk around. Hyoja residents and local artists worked together to improve the village environment under the name of the “Romantic Alley Project,” which transforms Chuncheon&#39;s deteriorated village into a space filled with art and culture. Thus, Romantic Alley Project No. 1, Hyoja Village Romantic Alley was born.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   At the beginning of the narrow alley, there are works by young men with wild ginseng and baby tigers. The title of the work is ‘Ban Hee-an and the Little Tiger’. Ban Hee-an is a figure related to the birth of Hyoja Village. In the middle of Joseon Dynasty, Hyoja Ban Hee-an took care of a seriously ill mother with utmost care. One day, when a mountain god appeared in a dream and went to Daeryongsan, there were three corpses. Among them, the throat of the corpse was cut and orphaned and presented to the mother. Ban Hee-an followed what the Sanshin ordered. When I opened the lid of the pot to give my mother medicine, there was wild ginseng instead of the body&#39;s head. So Nomo saved his life. In the winter that year, when Nomo suddenly wanted to eat strawberries, he went to the mountain to get strawberries again. At the end of the twist, he rescued a strawberry, but was lost in a blizzard and met a tiger. But instead of harming Ban Hee-an, the tiger drove him home and disappeared. In 41 years of the Joseon Dynasty, the Hyoja purification was given to praise the filial piety of Ban Hee-an. Later, as the Hyojamun was erected at the entrance of the village, it was called Hyojamun Street and got the name Hyoja. &#39;Ban Hee-an and the Little Tiger&#39; is a work that explains the origin of Hyoja.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Let&#39;s take a look at this work and understand the neighborhood called Hyoja and then go into the alley. You can see a shop called &#39;Green Mart&#39; at the entrance of the alley. The neighborhood shop, which is gradually disappearing due to the convenience store, saves the alley. You can buy a drink or sit on the floor in front of the store and take a break. A tiger with a humorous expression greets the wall just opposite Green Mart. A mural with harmonious landscapes of Hyo-ja and characters of the Zodiac, including a tiger, is painted on a cement wall that would have been dry, giving a cozy and pleasant feeling. The title of this work is &#39;The Way to Hyoja Award&#39;. In order to welcome the visitors and wish to be a Hyoja village filled with love flowers, laughter flowers, and happy songs, we depicted tigers and zodiac animals guarding the village. When you enter the alley along the wall, there is a 3D romantic photo zone under the sign “Dongil Petroleum”. If you take a picture here, you can produce it with the feeling of entering Hyojamun.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox type2 clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Hyo-ja&#39;s origins ‘Ban Hee-an and the Little Tiger’ - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/228/8b30f897-279d-4123-9761-150cb33cfe6e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Hyo-ja&#39;s origins ‘Ban Hee-an and the Little Tiger’
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;3D photo zone with virtual Hyoja Moon as background - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/228/c37a3236-a6d9-41cd-a134-924bd3a01d94.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     3D photo zone with virtual Hyoja Moon as background
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   The secret azit hidden in the romantic alley, the small library
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Along the way, you will see a playground and a modern, modern building that doesn&#39;t match the local atmosphere. It is the Children&#39;s Library “Damjak Small Library” (033-256-6363). It is a structure that takes off the shoes on the 3rd floor, so it is a comfortable atmosphere like my home. Daljak Library, which opened in 2008, is special in that it is not a bustling city but a culturally marginalized and old small town. Maybe it&#39;s because of the neighborhood atmosphere. Damjak Library is more comfortable and warm than any other place.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   From the 1st floor space to the 3rd floor for infants and toddlers, choose a book you like anywhere and sit there. It is a place where you can lean on the wall, lie down, and become friends with books as if you were at home. It is far from any library with a hard atmosphere. Because parents are comfortable and children are comfortable, families often come together. There is also a cafe on the first floor. Café latte, cappuccino, iced tea and other breads are all 1,000 won, so there is no burden. There are also books for adults to see in this space, so it&#39;s good to drink a cup of tea with your children and fall in love with reading.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox type3 clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Family Fun Playground, Damjak Library - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/228/4cdad4fb-3fc4-4edf-9f4d-728313ccbc2f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Family Fun Playground, Damjak Library
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Modern library in harmony with the old town - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/228/82ed80cd-c0e3-4f09-b0e4-35e84830f31e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Modern library in harmony with the old town
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Modern library in harmony with the old town - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/228/e735056b-b822-4d8a-82f5-a9f203de2578.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Modern library in harmony with the old town
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   A neighborhood alley full of interesting things
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    When you come out of the library and go up the right path, you can see the mood of an alleyway with small wooden chairs and a box of fruit trees underneath the stone wall. &#39;Tell me your wishes&#39;, etc. are implemented. It is lovely to see the stones on the mossy wall wearing colorful clothes one by one, and the animals hiding there are pretty. I can feel the warmth from the grandmothers in the neighborhood sitting on the alleys and chatting and the children running around. It is not a dead alley, but a living alley. You can see works along this alley and at the end of the alley you can see the city of Chuncheon through the roofs.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Let&#39;s go down to the place where the mural called &#39;The Way to Hyojasang&#39; was located again. This time, do not bend in the 3D romantic photo zone, but go straight up. On this road, ‘Skykeeper Junk Robot’ or taekwon V made of wood, which uses waste electrical appliances, appears. When you go up the hill with Taekwon V, you can see the sperm where you can rest for a while. If you sit in the pavilion for a while, the loud noises of the grandmother and grandfather come out from the Hyoja Moon Path Hall opposite. Unlike other senior citizens, it is noticeable that grandmothers and grandfathers hang handmade items. This is where the romantic alley is different from the mural villages in other regions.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox type3 clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Fairy-tale transformation of the old stone wall - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/228/07b8cdb5-cef3-4829-b1fc-aadef89b41bf.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Fairy-tale transformation of the old stone wall
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;It&#39;s fun to find the animals hiding on the stone wall - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/228/d5675adc-1bab-4b7e-ae17-38369aff843c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     It&#39;s fun to find the animals hiding on the stone wall
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;It&#39;s fun to find the animals hiding on the stone wall - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/228/7d8f5560-bf46-4462-9d8f-676cccaef648.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     It&#39;s fun to find the animals hiding on the stone wall
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The Romantic Alley Project is part of the project to create a living and cultural community. Rather than just putting out veneer with murals or artworks, work is underway to restore the community like a rural village as residents of Hyoja 1-dong interact with each other. Opening a course for residents, such as ceramics and reform, and creating a cafe where people can communicate, provides opportunities for residents to greet each other and get to know each other. This year, regardless of academic background, residents of Hyoja 1-dong started &#39;Hyoja Village University&#39;, where they become dean, professor, and student. If you look at the flesh as well as the appearance, you will realize the charm of Hyoja Village Romantic Alley.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox type3 clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;19&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A ridiculous junk robot with filial piety in one hand - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/228/23a7afb4-8236-4e64-9f1f-0cbb64a81349.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A ridiculous junk robot with filial piety in one hand
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;20&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A ridiculous junk robot with filial piety in one hand - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/228/861fcbf3-3b62-4edc-b69e-39c618b7db6b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A ridiculous junk robot with filial piety in one hand
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;21&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;“Hi, Taekwon V!” - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/228/17be20b3-4285-4ec4-99ec-752c950da1b7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     “Hi, Taekwon V!”
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Chuncheon Romantic Walk to the Romantic Market
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If it&#39;s too bad to end with a romantic alley, then take a walk to the romantic market. Walk down from the romantic alley to ‘Festival Theater Gesture’ and walk along the Yaksa Pass Pass to see the Chuncheon Romantic Market (Central Market). The central market, one of Chuncheon&#39;s representative traditional markets, was transformed into a new space where culture, art, and relaxation blended with the concept of a simple market in 2010 following the cultural tourism market development project. Beautiful murals were painted all over the market, and signboards were also transformed into distinctive features. Changes also took place in the old and old market alleys. In some alleys, the warmth and memories of the old market appear, and in some alleys, minicars run through the old wires on the wall.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Others such as the &#39;Romantic Salon&#39;, which acts as an information center for the romantic market, the &#39;Romantic Chamber&#39; showing the history of the central market, the &#39;Space Odong&#39; where you can see the work of local artists, and a market lounge where guests and merchants can rest. There are many exotic spaces that cannot be found on the market. In the romantic market, the fun of visiting and buying things adds to the fun of finding cultural art works and spaces hidden around the market. If you run from market to market, from alley to alley, you&#39;ll get a few bags of romance.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox type3 clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;24&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The romantic market is romantic even for signs. - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/228/42c659c4-cac4-43f5-9d5c-0bd99aa91ee2.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The romantic market is romantic even for signs.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;25&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The romantic market is romantic even for signs. - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/228/9209d4ce-86a7-4d6d-9b98-5b8afdb3de4a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The romantic market is romantic even for signs.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;26&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The romantic market is romantic even for signs. - Chuncheon, Gangwon, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/228/8505df04-e2db-4a15-a977-8463da982176.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The romantic market is romantic even for signs.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    [Hyoja Village Romantic Alley]
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Location: Hyoja 1-dong, Chuncheon-si, Gangwon-do
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Inquiries: 033-262-1360 (Romantic Alley Promotion Committee), 033-251-3474 (Chuncheon City Cultural Foundation)
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    1.Access
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    * Self-driving
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Seoul Chuncheon Expressway → Chuncheon IC → Right road toward the National Chuncheon Museum in Gongji-ro → Hyoja Crossroad → Turn left at Hyomyeong 1-gil
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    * public transport
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Seoul → Chuncheon: Occasionally (06: 00-24: 00) from Dong Seoul Terminal, takes 1 hour and 10 minutes
    &lt;br/&gt;
    ITX youth runs every hour (06: 00-22: 00) from Yongsan Station or Cheongnyangni Station (some time zones are 30 minutes), and takes about 1 hour 15 minutes from Yongsan Station
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    2. Restaurants around
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Byeoldang Makguksu: Chuncheon Makguksu / 490-7, Hyoja 1-dong, Chuncheon-si / 033-254-9603
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Original Charcoal Fire Chicken Bulgogi Restaurant: Charcoal Fire Chicken Ribs / 28-4 Nakwon-gil, Chuncheon-si / 033-257-5326
    &lt;br/&gt;
    1.5 Chicken Ribs: Chicken Ribs / 77 Human-ro, Chuncheon / 033-253-8635
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Panda House: Bunsik / 49 Myeongdong-gil, Chuncheon-si / 033-256-0920
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Coffee kelly: coffee / 10, morning road in Chuncheon / 033-252-5953
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    3.Accommodation
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Chuncheon Old House (Kim Jeong-eun Traditional House): 44, Sotbal 1-gil, Sindong-myeon, Chuncheon-si / 010-2582-2923 /
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://blog.naver.com/jawana&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://blog.naver.com/jawana
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Nabiya Guesthouse: 15 Seomgol-gil, Seomyeon, Chuncheon-si / 011-377-2402
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Chuncheon Sejong Hotel: 31 Bonguisan-gil, Chuncheon / 033-252-1191 /
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.chunchonsejong.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;춘천세종호텔로 이동&#34;&gt;
     http://www.chunchonsejong.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Benikea Chuncheon Hotel: 12, Jungang-ro 68beon-gil, Chuncheon-si / 033-257-1900
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    ※ The above information was created in July 2013, and may change later, so be sure to check it before you travel.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>