<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Seongju-gun on Every Corner of Korea</title>
    <link>https://codecorea.github.io/tags/seongju-gun/</link>
    <description>Every Corner of Korea (Seongju-gun)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 23:27:25 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="https://codecorea.github.io/tags/seongju-gun/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A very special time spent at Hangae Village - Seongju-gun, Gyeongbuk, South Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/a-very-special-time-spent-at-hangae-village-239/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 23:27:25 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/a-very-special-time-spent-at-hangae-village-239/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Seongju-gun, Gyeongbuk, South Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;a-very-special-time-spent-at-hangae-village--239&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Panoramic view of Sarangchae and Anchae at Jinsa - Seongju-gun, Gyeongbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/239/38ded5bb-3d5e-46ae-8468-9c3cec80ca9d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Panoramic view of Sarangchae and Anchae at Jinsa
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   A very special time spent at Hangae Village
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Seongju-gun, Gyeongbuk, South Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Seongju Hangae Village, with its 600 years of history, retains its old appearance, but is not as loud or busy as Hahoe Village and Yangdong Village. Among them, Jinsa&#39;s house is the only place where you can experience a mansion in the village, and you can taste a well-being country table. Jinsa&#39;s house is the best place to spend a quiet time in Hangae Village.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   The only place where you can experience the old house in Hangae Village, Jinsa
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The most beautiful and full of emotion in Hangae Village is the Jinsa House, the first place in town. There is no place where there is a wide front yard and a flower bed where fine flowers bloom and fall, and well and Jangdokdae. Personally, the factor that gauges the beauty of the old house is &#39;is there a person currently living?&#39; Nature gradually breaks down when a person&#39;s hand touches or an artificial element is added, but the house maintains its appearance only when it touches a person&#39;s hand and warmth. The reason that Jinsa&#39;s house is beautiful is because it is a space where people live. The daughter of Kyung-min Lee is staying with her old couple in the office.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The new pattern and floor of the new love house of Jinsa&#39;s house - Seongju-gun, Gyeongbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/239/239d8dd8-6dcb-4eb0-ad86-8cfb2fbd86d5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The new pattern and floor of the new love house of Jinsa&#39;s house
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The history of Jinsa&#39;s house can be traced back to the Joseon Dynasty. From Anchae&#39;s Sangnyangmun Gate, it is assumed that the house was built during the reign of King Jeongjo or Cheoljong. It was called after the house of Jinsa. When Lee Kuk-hee bought a house and lived in it, he passed the last lesson of the Joseon Dynasty in 1894, and was named Jinsa&#39;s house.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The new pattern and floor of the new love house of Jinsa&#39;s house - Seongju-gun, Gyeongbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/239/4f83bd66-b884-40da-89f5-6cb6abbcec14.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The new pattern and floor of the new love house of Jinsa&#39;s house
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The house of Jinsa consists of Anchae, Sarangchae, and Saesarang. Anchae is a tiled house, and Sarangchae and Bird Sarangchae are thatched houses. On the left side of the main building, a new Sarangchae in the shape of an &#39;A&#39; stands, and in the future, three Sarangchaes overlook the wide courtyard. In front of Anchae, there are Jangdokdae, wells, and large flower beds, where various pots of various sizes are gathered together. Among the old houses, one thing to notice is the new love. Sae Sarangchae was the last building in Jinsa&#39;s house. It is unusual to place a new Sarangchae between Anchae, the female space and Sarangchae, the male space, but the floor, room, and warehouse each have 3 squares, each with 1 square, and the floor with a floor railing. It is unusual. Particularly, the &#39;卍&#39; shape was nicely displayed on the bulging windows on both sides of the entrance to the room.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The new love pattern - Seongju-gun, Gyeongbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/239/195212f8-8d83-4922-a46a-65bde0ec3638.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The new love pattern
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Jinsa&#39;s house is the only place where you can experience the old house among the numerous houses in Hangae Village. The old house experience is available in Sarangchae and Saerangchae. Sae Sarangchae is a small one-room room that can be used by two people, but it seems to have a separate space for free. Sarangchae consists of 2 rooms and Daecheong, and there is a spacious front yard, so it is good to stay in a family unit. As for the accommodation fee, the new Sarangchae is 50,000 won per day and the Sarangchae is 80,000 won per day. At Jinsa&#39;s house, you can enjoy a well-being country table made with soy sauce and hand-grown vegetables. If you pass the elaborate table prepared by the mother and daughter of the Jinsa&#39;s house, it seems to be regrettable.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Jinsa&#39;s Countryside Table - Seongju-gun, Gyeongbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/239/48d041f5-4389-4b1a-b8a6-455baf1c0cc4.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Jinsa&#39;s Countryside Table
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Jinsa&#39;s special winter, Meju landscape
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Jinsa&#39;s house is very busy making meju every winter. Even this winter, the beans were boiled to make meju, and 13 bales of beans from Cheongdo, Gyeongbuk were used. It was around the time when the beans were almost boiled that I started to see the scenery of Meju. The heat of the burning fire slowly faded away, and the seaweed steamed from the beans boiled for 5-6 hours in a cauldron. It picks up a handful of beans that have been boiled for a taste, and the aroma is amazing.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Boiled beans for 5-6 hours - Seongju-gun, Gyeongbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/239/35a57cce-c85d-4ab9-aeb2-5a05909eaac5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Boiled beans for 5-6 hours
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   There seems to be no standardized recipe in traditional recipes. I wonder if the naturalness that comes from a long experience just continues the tradition of the house.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Boiled soybeans and boiled beans to check if they are well cooked - Seongju-gun, Gyeongbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/239/4139664a-6b0b-440a-9d4e-883e4affd15f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Boiled soybeans and boiled beans to check if they are well cooked
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The same is true for making meju at Jinsa&#39;s house. There are many variables in making meju, such as the quality of the beans, the time to boil the beans, and the intensity of the fire. The taste differs depending on where the beans are grown, and the success and failure of Meju depends on the time and time of cooking the beans. This is why the way of making meju varies from house to house.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Basket with boiled beans - Seongju-gun, Gyeongbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/239/d0facf34-bb1b-4e8d-8f8e-86fa611e922e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Basket with boiled beans
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   When you put the boiled beans in a colander, the work of making meju begins in earnest. The process of making meju is largely similar. Grind the beans in a mortar, put them in a saucer and chop them with your feet to make a shape. At this time, it is important to scoop soybeans to a certain extent.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The boiled beans are being steamed. - Seongju-gun, Gyeongbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/239/dc357e35-7371-443b-8f34-d848cc8a3612.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The boiled beans are being steamed.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Meju, which came out of the frame, is decorated with rice straw. This is the most important task when making meju. Rice straw provides the microorganisms necessary for fermentation of meju. The condition varies greatly depending on which microorganisms live in the rice straw, and it is generally said that white or yellow mold is better than blue or black mold. Despite the age of eighty-six, the tips of the woven weaves of rice straw are still delicate. I can feel the rich experience of making meju for over 50 years.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Moderately crushed beans in the mold - Seongju-gun, Gyeongbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/239/d69be2a5-59e5-41c5-bd5b-0fde14d2d6ac.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Moderately crushed beans in the mold
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Meju now has to go through a fermentation process. The drying process for one month and the floating process for another month are continued until the intestine is soaked. Like the slow winter time, Meju will ferment very slowly and wildly.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Chopping with your feet to create a meju shape - Seongju-gun, Gyeongbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/239/ed662b1c-6f53-4d85-aa40-d56f34ff466e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Chopping with your feet to create a meju shape
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It is said that in Jinsa&#39;s house, the market is made in February and the market is opened in May. It&#39;s still a long way to see Jinsa&#39;s deep taste. Just like Meju is slowly fermenting, I have to wait.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;14&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The maid&#39;s servant is weaving meju in straw. - Seongju-gun, Gyeongbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/239/12c0aaa8-ead9-4da4-a785-21a7d980aaf1.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The maid&#39;s servant is weaving meju in straw.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Hangae Village with 600 years of history
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    One is a pure Korean word meaning large stream or large naru. Hangae Village has the position of a typical Baesan Forest geographically. Looking at the topography, Yeongchwisan Mountain is located at the back of the village, and to the left and right, the foot of Yeongchwisan Mountain, called Baekho Lantern and Blue Dragon Lantern, descends as if it surrounds the village. Across the village, a white stream merges with Icheon. Baekcheon was originally said to have been wide and deep enough to carry salt boats. When you look at the Baekcheon Embankment, you can see at a glance the village of Hangae, which is surrounded by Yeongchwisan Mountain.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Hangae Village is Seongsan Lee&#39;s Gipseongchon, where Iwoo, who used to be a pastor of Jinju during King Sejong in Joseon, is an incense. The entire village is an important folk cultural property No. 255, and it is a village with a long history and tradition that most of the old houses have been designated as cultural heritage.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;View of Yeongchwisan Mountain and Hangae Village from the entrance of the village - Seongju-gun, Gyeongbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/239/ab85d9d5-5c33-4359-8afc-ddcb4fe24c54.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     View of Yeongchwisan Mountain and Hangae Village from the entrance of the village
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   When you enter Hangae Village, the first step is to take a look around the old houses. There is a cultural heritage booth at the entrance of the village, and if you ask in advance, you can tour the village properly and feel free to visit the old house. The pleasure of walking on the stone wall that forms the boundary between the old house and the old house is extra.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Old fence of Hangae Village - Seongju-gun, Gyeongbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/239/042c8af6-8a60-4489-b676-060910dff7de.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Old fence of Hangae Village
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    After passing through Jinsa&#39;s house, you can tour Wolgok&#39;s house, Bukbi&#39;s house, Gyori&#39;s house, Hanju&#39;s house, Dodong&#39;s house, Pokwa&#39;s house, and Hahoe&#39;s house. The place with the most stories in Hangae Village is Bukbi Old House. The owner of Bukbi House is Don Jae-seok, a former escort officer of the apostle during the Joseon Dynasty. When the apostle saint faced the humility of being imprisoned in the back lord under the command of Yeongjo, he suffered the injustice, but he went down to the village of Hangae, where he was stripped down, cut down the wall of Sarangchae, built a gate to the north, commemorated the apostle, and bowed down to the north. It is said that. Later, when King Jeongjo succeeded to the throne, and the descendants of Lee Seok-moon gave a manor-level system, he said, &#34;Is there still a door in the north of your house?&#34; As soon as you enter the gate of Bukbi Old House, the &#39;Bukbi&#39; signboard is hung on the right. The gate to the north still wants the north as it was.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Book of North Bi&#39;s House - Seongju-gun, Gyeongbuk, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/239/2b9af1cc-5dc7-49a2-a151-446f07aba203.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Book of North Bi&#39;s House
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;topmr&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1.Access
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
     * Self-driving
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34; style=&#34;MARGIN-TOP: 0px&#34;&gt;
    Jungbu Inland Expressway Seongju IC → Gayaro toward Seongju → Turn right at Daehwang Intersection → Turn left at Seongju at Gyeongsan Intersection → Go straight along Gayaro → Turn right at Wolhang at Anpo Intersection → Hangae Village
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
     * public transport
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34; style=&#34;MARGIN-TOP: 0px&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Seoul → Seongju
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    : From Nambu Terminal (02-521-8550) 5 times a day (10: 00-16: 45), takes 3 hours 40 minutes
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Daejeon → Seongju
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    : West Intercity Bus Terminal (042-584-1615) 4 times a day (07: 05-18: 10), takes 2 hours 40 minutes
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Daegu → Seongju
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    : From Seobu Terminal (1688-2824) 15 times a day (07: 15-19: 10), takes 1 hour 20 minutes
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34; style=&#34;MARGIN-TOP: 0px&#34;&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34; style=&#34;MARGIN-TOP: 0px&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Restaurants around
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Gaboja Restaurant:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Set meal / Seongsan-ri, Seongju-eup / 054-931-7252
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Harim Jeong:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Mushroom Bath / Seongju-eup Gyeongsan-ri / 054-933-7700
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     3.Accommodation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Ace Motel:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Gyeongsan-ri, Seongju-eup / 054-933-5454
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    ※ The above information was updated in November 2013, and may be changed later, so be sure to check it before you travel.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>