<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>of on Korea Tour</title>
    <link>https://codecorea.github.io/tags/of/</link>
    <description>Korea Tour (of)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 19:55:19 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="https://codecorea.github.io/tags/of/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Республика Корея - «Секретный лес» и «Лесной лечебный лес Сеульского гранд-парка» раскрываются за 30 лет</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/secret-forest-and-seoul-grand-park-forest-healing-forest-experiences-revealed-in-30-years-38-ru/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 19:55:19 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/secret-forest-and-seoul-grand-park-forest-healing-forest-experiences-revealed-in-30-years-38-ru/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-title=&#34;secret-forest-and-seoul-grand-park-forest-healing-forest-experiences-revealed-in-30-years--38&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;и - Республика Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/6a769698-24f5-425f-8420-e36370ef139f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    и
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   «Секретный лес» и «Лесной лечебный лес Сеульского гранд-парка» раскрываются за 30 лет
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Республика Корея
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   В июле «секретный лес», который спрятал Сеульский Гранд Парк, был обнародован через 30 лет. Основной темой является «Целебный лес здоровья» в Сеульском Гранд Парке, который утешает современных людей, уставших от повседневной жизни. Представляя «Опыт исцеления», где стресс, накопленный во время прогулки, расслабляется, когда вы идете по тихой лесной тропе, которая простирается от густого леса до долины горы Чхонгьесан и природного водопада.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   «Жарко» не хватает погоды. Была новость о «тайном лесу», который появился в мире через 30 лет, когда он просто дышал на жарком солнце, как будто он сжигал все. Кроме того, название «Лесное исцеление». «Исцеление» и «исцеление» - не горячее слово для современных людей, которые провели лето, потому что они не могут нагреваться.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Пройдите через еловые и сосновые леса и прохладные водопады сразу!
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Главный герой - Сеульский Гранд Парк Исцеляющий Лес, который был открыт для публики с 13 июля. Это естественный лес, который имеет площадь 50 000 квадратных метров и содержит долину Cheonggyesan Valley и природный водопад. Чтобы защитить природу, которая отдыхает 30 лет, в день могут посещать только 50-60 человек. Сеул Гранд Парк домашняя страница
   &lt;a href=&#34;http://grandpark.seoul.go.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;[새창열림]‘서울대공원’ 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
    http://grandpark.seoul.go.kr
   &lt;/a&gt;
   ) Сеульская система бронирования общественных услуг (
   &lt;a href=&#34;http://yeyak.seoul.go.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;[새창열림]‘서울시 공공서비스예약시스템’ 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
    http://yeyak.seoul.go.kr
   &lt;/a&gt;
   Вы можете предсказать).
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Визит-центр в начале лесного лечебного леса Сеульского Гранд Парка - Республика Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/d4d69d47-c87e-4b03-9b58-048d830a8b1d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Визит-центр в начале лесного лечебного леса Сеульского Гранд Парка
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Срок подачи заявок настолько быстрый, что забронировать его немного сложно, но если вы хотите избавиться от усталости «тайного леса» и «целительного леса» бесплатно, вы можете попробовать. Вы можете испытать «лесное исцеление», что означает действия, направленные на повышение иммунитета человеческого тела и восстановление физического и психического здоровья путем использования и анализа леса. Если он не закрыт, вы можете зарегистрироваться за два дня до желаемой даты. Бронирование обычно начинается около 20 дней с даты доставки. Дата может измениться, поэтому рекомендуется заранее проверить сайт. Он настолько популярен, что закрывается в начале бронирования.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Лесная площадь, где собираются предзаказчики - Республика Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/47a6cdc2-1130-4f04-82ae-fb04df972289.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Лесная площадь, где собираются предзаказчики
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Программа, забронированная журналистом, называется Majung Forest Road, которая открыта для широкой публики. Он направлен на ознакомление с лесным лечением и его проведение, и он будет проводиться дважды со вторника по пятницу с 10:00 до 12:00 и с 16:00 до 16:00. Дети не допускаются. Кроме того, Серебряная Лесная Дорога направлена на снижение мышечной силы, предотвращение падений и повышение жизненной силы для взрослых в возрасте от 65 до 75 лет. Operate. Программы исцеления для взрослых 55 лет и старше предлагаются один раз в неделю. Объем всех программ составляет 15 в порядке очереди.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Лесной целебный лес начинается там, где начинается полномасштабная целительная прогулка - Республика Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/7c356d93-a17d-4051-901b-621634f6ad8a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Лесной целебный лес начинается там, где начинается полномасштабная целительная прогулка
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Так как он управляется системой предварительного бронирования, для подтверждения личности требуется сертификат подтверждения бронирования для того, чтобы испытать лесной целебный лес. Платье должно быть удобным, с длинными рукавами, чтобы кроссовки и комары не давали кроссовки или походные ботинки. Подготовьте шляпу для солнца и воды для своего дня. Если вы приедете до начала программы, вы можете испытать ее после проверки индекса стресса в Центре для посетителей Healing Forest.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Консультанты Лесного Исцеления Объясняют Перед Программой Исцеления - Республика Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/d9b51215-3576-45e7-94fe-6e77ccc8ba64.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Консультанты Лесного Исцеления Объясняют Перед Программой Исцеления
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   О, давайте также узнаем, как посетить лесной лечебный лес Сеульского Гранд Парка. Если вы пользуетесь своим автомобилем, найдите «7-1, Макгедон, Гвачхон, Кёнгидо» в навигации. Если вы едете на общественном транспорте, вы можете сойти на станции Grand Park в Сеуле на линии метро 4 и доехать до Forest Healing Forest или близлежащей парковки Dongmun.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Лесной лечебный лес, начинающий долину - Республика Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/88b05caf-a50c-4291-b854-f826d37888ed.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Лесной лечебный лес, начинающий долину
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   По словам гида, время в пути пешком, поездом на слонах или лесом целебного леса доходит до 40 минут. Если вы едете на поезде на слонах, вам нужно всего лишь сделать одну остановку и сойти у главного входа в зоопарк и дойти до Музея современного искусства. Вместо того, чтобы войти в Музей современного искусства, если вы идете прямо по главной дороге, вы увидите оранжевую вывеску, указывающую путь к Лесу Исцеляющего Леса. Отныне это альпинизм. Оранжевая лента поможет вам.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Лечебная лесная тропинка для пожилых людей на прогулке - Республика Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/60c3899b-9621-4a6d-8f63-a723bd3c10f9.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Лечебная лесная тропинка для пожилых людей на прогулке
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Целительная прогулка с лесным целителем
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Как долго ты ходил? Туристический центр Forest Healing Forest расположен в долине позади пустыря, где для предварительных бронировщиков имеется баннер «Трасса целительного лесного парка Seoul Grand Park». Центр для посетителей собрался для тех, кто сегодня вместе подал заявку на программу исцеления. Консультант по лесному исцелению порекомендовал чашку прохладного гречневого чая и сказал: «Давайте остынем и двинемся в долину до того, как начнется программа лечения леса».
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Немного
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Курс гемотерапии консультанта Forest Healing - Республика Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/dece20f4-99e5-4229-a95a-bfd4d1c331eb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Курс гемотерапии консультанта Forest Healing
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Лесной лечебный лес
   &lt;strong&gt;
    Лес, небесный лес, лес релаксации деревьев, лес релаксации солнечного света, лес релаксации воды
   &lt;/strong&gt;
   И так далее. Первое прибытие
   &lt;strong&gt;
    Лесная деятельность
   &lt;/strong&gt;
   Растягивайтесь и отдыхайте в тренажерном зале.
   &lt;strong&gt;
    Лесная деятельность
   &lt;/strong&gt;
   Напротив сосен
   &lt;strong&gt;
    Небесный Лес
   &lt;/strong&gt;
   Это место. Просто гулять по дереву, дышать открыто. Прогулка для всех возрастов По лесной тропинке направляйтесь к водопаду. Ели
   &lt;strong&gt;
    Релаксация дерева
   &lt;/strong&gt;
   Решил заехать по дороге домой. Название Rigida сосны
   &lt;strong&gt;
    Солнечный свет Релаксационный Лес
   &lt;/strong&gt;
   прошлое
   &lt;strong&gt;
    Водный релакс лес
   &lt;/strong&gt;
   Это касается водопада. В Сеульском Гранд Парке есть такой водопад.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Ура, живущие в прохладном, чистом первоклассном - Республика Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/0ee21d99-dfb8-486c-bcc6-2927105ad739.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Ура, живущие в прохладном, чистом первоклассном
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Хотя это временно, 10-метровый водопад приветствует участников. Окунитесь в долину, ведущую из горной долины Чонги, и отдохните, глядя на водопад. Сделайте снимок с водопадом на заднем плане, чтобы остыть и вернуться. Солнечный свет не просачивается в середине лета, поэтому он не болеет. В расслабляющем дереве, заполненном елями, происходит целительная медитация «медитация покоя». Отдых на деревянной палубе или полу здесь. Лесные целители раздают матрасы один за другим. Удобно лежать в звуках цикад, солнечный свет просачивается сквозь яркие зеленые листья и свежий воздух, который дают деревья. Все заботы и неприятности ложатся, и Орот выходит со мной. Это не долго, но эффект довольно хороший. Он проходит через ароматную лесную тропинку, где ароматные травы приветствуют вас легким шагом.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Путь от лесного релаксационного леса до солнечного релаксационного леса - Республика Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/8466e2bd-3c45-4051-ae2b-552e7a82eb19.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Путь от лесного релаксационного леса до солнечного релаксационного леса
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Это что-то отличное от 2 часов назад, чтобы насладиться «Исцелением Лесного Исцеления» с программой однодневного опыта и вернуться к реальности. Вес и лицо - это то же самое, но что-то легкое. Это потому, что деревья, которые он встретил в целебном лесу, заполняли истощенную энергию, не зная самого себя?
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Природный водопад в лесу Исцеляющий лес Гранд Парк Сеула - Республика Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/1e708be3-7afd-440b-b035-3dd9a583291d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Природный водопад в лесу Исцеляющий лес Гранд Парк Сеула
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   В Сеульском Гранд-парке Healing Forest также есть специальные долгосрочные программы для женщин в период менопаузы, детей, которые пользуются смартфонами, детей с синдромом дефицита внимания и гиперактивности (СДВГ) и их семей. Если вы подаете заявку на долгосрочную программу, ваша регистрация будет подтверждена после консультации с лесным целителем. Свяжитесь с лесным целительным лесом Сеула Гранд (02-500-7575, 7576, 7511).
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Участники отдыхают у водопада - Республика Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/3e9921a4-e695-4707-ba4f-399c1ac2d592.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Участники отдыхают у водопада
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   ЧАЕВЫЕ. Как использовать Лесной Целебный Лес в Сеульском Гранд Парке
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Открытый в 30 лет Сеульский лесной заповедник Grand Park Forest работает по предварительному заказу, чтобы сохранить лес. Работают Majung Forest Road (вт ~ пт, два раза в день) для взрослых, Серебряный лесной путь для пожилых людей от 65 до 75 лет (один раз в неделю) и Золотой лесной путь для взрослых от 55 до 65 лет (один раз в неделю). Крайний срок - быстрый, с ограничением в 15 посетителей на программу. Для бронирования, пожалуйста, посетите веб-сайт Seoul Grand Park (
   &lt;a href=&#34;http://grandpark.seoul.go.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;[새창열림]‘서울대공원’ 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
    http://grandpark.seoul.go.kr
   &lt;/a&gt;
   ) Сеульская система бронирования общественных услуг (
   &lt;a href=&#34;http://yeyak.seoul.go.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;[새창열림]‘서울시 공공서비스예약시스템’ 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
    http://yeyak.seoul.go.kr
   &lt;/a&gt;
   Вы можете сделать все бесплатно. Он также имеет специальные долгосрочные программы для женщин в период менопаузы, детей с высоким уровнем использования смартфонов, детей с синдромом дефицита внимания и гиперактивности (СДВГ) и их семей.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Информация о путешествии
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Близлежащие рестораны
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Hill of Roses: Gwacheon-si Makgye-Dong / Ребра, холодная лапша / 02-504-5311
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Внутренний Домашний Суп из Фруктового котла с фруктами: Кванчан-ро, Гвачхон / Суп из мороженого с фруктами / 02-3679-1175
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Ипподром Duck House: Gwacheon-si Gungmal-ro / Жареная серная утиная глина / 02-502-7500
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Seorabul: Gwacheon Byeolyangsangga / Сосновый Шабу Шабу / 02-502-8384
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Размещение
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Природный кемпинг Grand Park в Сеуле (открыт с марта по ноябрь): 159-1, Макгедон, Гвачхон / 02-500-7870
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Grace Hotel: 2, торговая улица Сонъян, Гвачхон / 02-504-6700
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://hotelgrace6700.tnaru.net/web/index&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://hotelgrace6700.tnaru.net/web/index
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ Приведенная выше информация была написана в августе 2015 года и может впоследствии измениться. Пожалуйста, проверьте перед путешествием.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Информация, такая как текст, фотографии и видео, используемые в этой статье, защищены авторским правом Корейской туристической организации, поэтому несанкционированное использование статьи запрещено.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>République de Corée - Expériences «Forêt secrète» et «Forêt de guérison de la forêt du Grand Parc de Séoul» révélées en 30 ans</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/secret-forest-and-seoul-grand-park-forest-healing-forest-experiences-revealed-in-30-years-38-fr/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 19:52:07 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/secret-forest-and-seoul-grand-park-forest-healing-forest-experiences-revealed-in-30-years-38-fr/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-title=&#34;secret-forest-and-seoul-grand-park-forest-healing-forest-experiences-revealed-in-30-years--38&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;et - République de Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/6a769698-24f5-425f-8420-e36370ef139f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    et
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Expériences «Forêt secrète» et «Forêt de guérison de la forêt du Grand Parc de Séoul» révélées en 30 ans
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    République de Corée
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   En juillet, la &#34;forêt secrète&#34; que le Grand Parc de Séoul avait cachée a été rendue publique en 30 ans. Le thème principal est la «forêt de guérison de la santé» dans le Grand Parc de Séoul, qui réconforte les personnes modernes qui sont fatiguées de la vie quotidienne. Présentation de `` l&#39;expérience de guérison &#39;&#39; où le stress accumulé dans la promenade est détendu pendant que vous marchez le long du chemin forestier calme qui s&#39;étend de la forêt luxuriante à la vallée de la montagne Cheonggyesan et à la cascade naturelle.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   «Chaud» n&#39;est pas assez météo. Il y a eu des nouvelles de la &#34;forêt secrète&#34; qui est apparue dans le monde en 30 ans, alors qu&#39;elle respirait juste le soleil brûlant comme si elle brûlait tout. En outre, le nom «Forest Healing». «Guérison» et «guérison» ne sont pas un mot chaud pour les gens modernes qui ont passé l&#39;été parce qu&#39;ils ne peuvent pas avoir chaud.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Traversez à la fois les forêts de sapins et de pins et les cascades fraîches!
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Le protagoniste est Seoul Grand Park Healing Forest, qui est ouvert au public depuis le 13 juillet. C&#39;est une forêt naturelle de 50 000 mètres carrés qui contient la vallée de la vallée de Cheonggyesan et une cascade naturelle. Pour protéger la nature, qui se repose depuis 30 ans, seules 50 à 60 personnes par jour peuvent visiter. Page d&#39;accueil du Grand Parc de Séoul
   &lt;a href=&#34;http://grandpark.seoul.go.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;[새창열림]‘서울대공원’ 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
    http://grandpark.seoul.go.kr
   &lt;/a&gt;
   ) Et le système de réservation du service public de Séoul (
   &lt;a href=&#34;http://yeyak.seoul.go.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;[새창열림]‘서울시 공공서비스예약시스템’ 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
    http://yeyak.seoul.go.kr
   &lt;/a&gt;
   Vous pouvez prédire par).
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Centre d&#39;accueil au début de la forêt de guérison de la forêt du Grand Parc de Séoul - République de Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/d4d69d47-c87e-4b03-9b58-048d830a8b1d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Centre d&#39;accueil au début de la forêt de guérison de la forêt du Grand Parc de Séoul
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   La date limite est si rapide qu&#39;il est un peu difficile de réserver, mais si vous voulez dissiper la fatigue de la «forêt secrète» et de la «forêt de guérison» gratuitement, vous pouvez essayer. Vous pouvez expérimenter la «guérison des forêts», ce qui signifie des activités pour augmenter l&#39;immunité du corps humain et restaurer la santé physique et mentale en utilisant et en analysant la forêt. S&#39;il n&#39;est pas fermé, vous pouvez vous inscrire deux jours avant la date souhaitée. Les réservations commencent généralement environ 20 jours après la date de livraison. La date peut changer, c&#39;est donc une bonne idée de consulter le site Web au préalable. Il est si populaire qu&#39;il ferme au début de la réservation.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Place de la forêt où se réunissent les pré-réservations - République de Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/47a6cdc2-1130-4f04-82ae-fb04df972289.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Place de la forêt où se réunissent les pré-réservations
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Le programme réservé par le journaliste est Majung Forest Road, qui est ouvert au grand public. Il vise à introduire et à expérimenter la guérison des forêts, et il se tiendra deux fois du mardi au vendredi de 10h00 à 12h00 et de 22h00 à 16h00. Les enfants ne sont pas admis. De plus, la Silver Forest Road vise à réduire la force musculaire, à prévenir les chutes et à améliorer la vitalité des adultes de 65 à 75 ans. Fonctionner. Des programmes de guérison pour les adultes de 55 ans et plus sont offerts une fois par semaine. La capacité de tous les programmes est de 15 selon le principe du premier arrivé, premier servi.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Forêt qui guérit la forêt où commence la marche de guérison à grande échelle - République de Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/7c356d93-a17d-4051-901b-621634f6ad8a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Forêt qui guérit la forêt où commence la marche de guérison à grande échelle
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Comme il est exploité par le système de réservation à l&#39;avance, un certificat de confirmation de réservation est requis pour la vérification d&#39;identité afin de découvrir la forêt de guérison de la forêt. La robe doit être confortable et à manches longues pour empêcher les espadrilles et les moustiques de chaussures de course ou de bottes de randonnée. Ayez un chapeau prêt pour le soleil et de l&#39;eau pour votre journée. Si vous arrivez avant le début du programme, vous pouvez en faire l&#39;expérience après avoir vérifié l&#39;indice de stress au Healing Forest Visitor Center.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Les conseillers en guérison forestière expliquent avant le programme de guérison - République de Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/d9b51215-3576-45e7-94fe-6e77ccc8ba64.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Les conseillers en guérison forestière expliquent avant le programme de guérison
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Oh, savons aussi comment visiter la forêt de guérison de la forêt du Grand Parc de Séoul. Si vous utilisez votre propre voiture, recherchez «7-1, Makgye-dong, Gwacheon-si, Gyeonggi-do» sur la navigation. Si vous prenez les transports en commun, vous pouvez descendre à la station Seoul Grand Park sur la ligne 4 du métro et vous rendre à la forêt de guérison ou au parking Dongmun à proximité.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Forêt guérison forêt début vallée - République de Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/88b05caf-a50c-4291-b854-f826d37888ed.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Forêt guérison forêt début vallée
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Selon le guide, le temps de trajet à pied, en train d&#39;éléphants ou en forêt de guérison est similaire à 40 minutes. Si vous montez dans un train d&#39;éléphants, il vous suffit de vous déplacer d&#39;un arrêt et de descendre à l&#39;entrée principale du zoo et de marcher vers le musée d&#39;art moderne. Au lieu d&#39;entrer dans le musée d&#39;art moderne, si vous continuez tout droit sur la route principale, vous verrez une signalisation orange indiquant le chemin vers la forêt de guérison de la forêt. Désormais c&#39;est de l&#39;escalade. Le ruban orange vous guidera gentiment.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sentier forestier de guérison pour les personnes âgées à marcher - République de Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/60c3899b-9621-4a6d-8f63-a723bd3c10f9.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sentier forestier de guérison pour les personnes âgées à marcher
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Promenade de guérison avec guérisseur forestier
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Combien de temps as-tu marché? Le Forest Healing Forest Visitor Center est situé dans la vallée derrière le terrain vacant où la bannière du «Seoul Grand Park Healing Forest Path est à la disposition des pré-réservations». Le centre d&#39;accueil s&#39;est réuni pour ceux qui ont demandé un programme de guérison ensemble aujourd&#39;hui. Le conseiller en guérison forestière a recommandé une tasse de thé de sarrasin frais et a dit: «Rafraîchissons-nous et allons dans la vallée avant le début du programme de guérison forestière.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Un peu
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Cours d&#39;hémothérapie du conseiller en guérison forestière - République de Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/dece20f4-99e5-4229-a95a-bfd4d1c331eb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Cours d&#39;hémothérapie du conseiller en guérison forestière
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Forêt guérison forêt
   &lt;strong&gt;
    Forêt, forêt du ciel, forêt de relaxation des arbres, forêt de relaxation du soleil, forêt de relaxation de l&#39;eau
   &lt;/strong&gt;
   Etc. Première arrivée
   &lt;strong&gt;
    Activité forestière
   &lt;/strong&gt;
   Étirez-vous et détendez-vous au gymnase.
   &lt;strong&gt;
    Activité forestière
   &lt;/strong&gt;
   Face aux pins
   &lt;strong&gt;
    Sky Forest
   &lt;/strong&gt;
   Cet endroit. Juste marcher dans l&#39;arbre, respirer ouvertement. Marcher pour tous les âges Le long du chemin forestier, direction la cascade. Sapins
   &lt;strong&gt;
    Détente dans les arbres
   &lt;/strong&gt;
   J&#39;ai décidé de m&#39;arrêter sur le chemin du retour. Le nom des pins de Rigida
   &lt;strong&gt;
    Forêt de relaxation au soleil
   &lt;/strong&gt;
   Passé
   &lt;strong&gt;
    Forêt de relaxation aquatique
   &lt;/strong&gt;
   Cela touche la cascade. Il y a une telle cascade dans le Grand Parc de Séoul.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Acclamations vivant dans une première classe fraîche et propre - République de Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/0ee21d99-dfb8-486c-bcc6-2927105ad739.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Acclamations vivant dans une première classe fraîche et propre
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Bien que temporaire, une cascade de 10 mètres de haut accueille les participants. Faites tremper vos pieds dans la vallée qui s&#39;étend de la vallée de la montagne Cheonggye et reposez-vous en regardant la cascade. Prenez une photo avec une cascade en arrière-plan pour vous rafraîchir et revenir en arrière. La lumière du soleil ne fuit pas au milieu de l&#39;été, elle n&#39;est donc pas malade. Dans l&#39;arbre de relaxation rempli de sapins, la méditation de guérison «méditation de repos» a lieu. Reposez-vous ici sur une terrasse ou un plancher en bois. Les guérisseurs forestiers distribuent les matelas un par un. Allongé confortablement au son des cigales, le soleil qui s&#39;échappe à travers les feuilles d&#39;un vert vif et l&#39;air frais fourni par les arbres. Tous les soucis et les ennuis sont posés et Orot sort avec moi. Ce n&#39;est pas long, mais l&#39;effet est assez bon. Il vous emmène à travers le chemin forestier parfumé où les herbes parfumées vous accueillent d&#39;un pas léger.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Chemin de la forêt de relaxation des arbres à la forêt de relaxation du soleil - République de Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/8466e2bd-3c45-4051-ae2b-552e7a82eb19.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Chemin de la forêt de relaxation des arbres à la forêt de relaxation du soleil
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   C&#39;est quelque chose de différent d&#39;il y a 2 heures pour profiter de «Healing Forest Healing» avec un programme d&#39;expérience d&#39;une journée et revenir à la réalité. Le poids et le visage sont les mêmes soucis, mais quelque chose est léger. Est-ce parce que les arbres qu&#39;il a rencontrés dans la forêt curative ont rempli l&#39;énergie épuisée sans se connaître?
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Chutes naturelles dans la forêt Forêt de guérison du Grand Parc de Séoul - République de Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/1e708be3-7afd-440b-b035-3dd9a583291d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Chutes naturelles dans la forêt Forêt de guérison du Grand Parc de Séoul
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   La forêt de guérison de Grand Parc de Séoul propose également des programmes spéciaux à long terme pour les femmes ménopausées, les enfants qui utilisent des smartphones, les enfants atteints de trouble d&#39;hyperactivité avec déficit de l&#39;attention (TDAH) et leurs familles. Si vous postulez pour un programme à long terme, votre inscription sera confirmée après avoir consulté un guérisseur forestier. Contactez la forêt de guérison de la forêt du Grand Parc de Séoul (02-500-7575, 7576, 7511).
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Les participants font une pause pour se rafraîchir à la cascade - République de Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/3e9921a4-e695-4707-ba4f-399c1ac2d592.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Les participants font une pause pour se rafraîchir à la cascade
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   POINTE. Comment utiliser la forêt de guérison des forêts dans le Grand Parc de Séoul
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Ouverte en 30 ans, la forêt de guérison du Grand Parc de Séoul est exploitée sur réservation à l&#39;avance pour préserver la forêt. Majung Forest Road (du mardi au vendredi, deux fois par jour) pour les adultes, Silver Forest Trail pour les personnes âgées de 65 à 75 ans (une fois par semaine) et Gold Forest Trail pour les adultes de 55 à 65 ans (une fois par semaine). Le délai est rapide, avec une limite de 15 visiteurs par programme. Pour les réservations, veuillez visiter le site Web de Seoul Grand Park (
   &lt;a href=&#34;http://grandpark.seoul.go.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;[새창열림]‘서울대공원’ 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
    http://grandpark.seoul.go.kr
   &lt;/a&gt;
   ) Et le système de réservation du service public de Séoul (
   &lt;a href=&#34;http://yeyak.seoul.go.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;[새창열림]‘서울시 공공서비스예약시스템’ 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
    http://yeyak.seoul.go.kr
   &lt;/a&gt;
   Vous pouvez faire tout est gratuit. Il propose également des programmes spéciaux à long terme pour les femmes ménopausées, les enfants qui utilisent beaucoup leur smartphone, les enfants atteints de trouble d&#39;hyperactivité avec déficit de l&#39;attention (TDAH) et leurs familles.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Info voyage
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Restaurants à proximité
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Hill of Roses: Gwacheon-si Makgye-dong / Ribs, Cold Noodles / 02-504-5311
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Inner Home Chaudron Sundae Soup: Gwangchang-ro, Gwacheon / Sundae Soup / 02-3679-1175
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Racecourse Duck House: Gwacheon-si Gungmal-ro / Argile de canard au soufre grillé / 02-502-7500
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Seorabul: Gwacheon Byeolyangsangga / Pin naturel Shabu Shabu / 02-502-8384
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Hébergement
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Seoul Grand Park Nature Campground (ouvert de mars à novembre): 159-1, Makgye-dong, Gwacheon-si / 02-500-7870
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Grace Hotel: 2, Seongyang Shopping Street, Gwacheon / 02-504-6700
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://hotelgrace6700.tnaru.net/web/index&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://hotelgrace6700.tnaru.net/web/index
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ Les informations ci-dessus ont été rédigées en août 2015 et peuvent changer par la suite. Veuillez vérifier avant de voyager.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Les informations telles que le texte, les photos et les vidéos utilisées dans cet article sont protégées par les droits d&#39;auteur de l&#39;Organisation coréenne du tourisme, de sorte que l&#39;utilisation non autorisée de l&#39;article est interdite.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>República de Corea - Experiencias de &#34;Bosque secreto&#34; y &#34;Bosque curativo del gran parque de Seúl&#34; reveladas en 30 años</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/secret-forest-and-seoul-grand-park-forest-healing-forest-experiences-revealed-in-30-years-38-es/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 19:48:47 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/secret-forest-and-seoul-grand-park-forest-healing-forest-experiences-revealed-in-30-years-38-es/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-title=&#34;secret-forest-and-seoul-grand-park-forest-healing-forest-experiences-revealed-in-30-years--38&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;y - República de Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/6a769698-24f5-425f-8420-e36370ef139f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    y
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Experiencias de &#34;Bosque secreto&#34; y &#34;Bosque curativo del gran parque de Seúl&#34; reveladas en 30 años
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    República de Corea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   En julio, el &#34;bosque secreto&#34; que el Gran Parque de Seúl había escondido fue lanzado al público en 30 años. El tema principal es el &#34;Bosque de Salud&#34; en el Gran Parque de Seúl, que consuela a las personas modernas que están cansadas de la vida cotidiana. Presentamos la `` Experiencia de curación &#39;&#39; donde el estrés acumulado en la caminata se relaja mientras caminas por el tranquilo sendero del bosque que se extiende desde el exuberante bosque hasta el valle de la montaña Cheonggyesan y la cascada natural.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &#34;Caliente&#34; no es suficiente clima. Hubo una noticia sobre el &#34;bosque secreto&#34; que apareció en el mundo en 30 años, cuando solo respiraba el ardiente sol como si quemara todo. Además, el nombre &#39;Forest Healing&#39;. &#34;Curación&#34; y &#34;curación&#34; no son una palabra candente para las personas modernas que han pasado el verano porque no pueden calentarse.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   ¡Atraviesa los bosques de abetos y pinos y cascadas frescas a la vez!
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   El protagonista es Seúl Grand Park Healing Forest, que ha estado abierto al público desde el 13 de julio. Es un bosque natural que cuenta con 50,000 metros cuadrados y contiene el valle del valle de Cheonggyesan y una cascada natural. Para proteger la naturaleza, que ha estado descansando durante 30 años, solo pueden visitar de 50 a 60 personas por día. Página de inicio del Gran Parque de Seúl
   &lt;a href=&#34;http://grandpark.seoul.go.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;[새창열림]‘서울대공원’ 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
    http://grandpark.seoul.go.kr
   &lt;/a&gt;
   ) Y el sistema de reserva de servicio público de Seúl (
   &lt;a href=&#34;http://yeyak.seoul.go.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;[새창열림]‘서울시 공공서비스예약시스템’ 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
    http://yeyak.seoul.go.kr
   &lt;/a&gt;
   Puedes predecir por).
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Centro de visitantes al comienzo del bosque que cura el bosque del Gran Parque de Seúl - República de Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/d4d69d47-c87e-4b03-9b58-048d830a8b1d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Centro de visitantes al comienzo del bosque que cura el bosque del Gran Parque de Seúl
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   T
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Plaza del bosque donde se reúnen los prereservadores - República de Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/47a6cdc2-1130-4f04-82ae-fb04df972289.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Plaza del bosque donde se reúnen los prereservadores
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   El programa reservado por el periodista es Majung Forest Road, que está abierto al público en general. Su objetivo es presentar y experimentar la curación forestal, y se llevará a cabo dos veces de martes a viernes de 10:00 a.m. a 12:00 p.m. y de p.m. a 16:00 p.m. No se permiten niños. Además, Silver Forest Road tiene como objetivo reducir la fuerza muscular, prevenir caídas y mejorar la vitalidad para adultos de 65 a 75 años. Funcionar. Se ofrecen programas de curación para adultos mayores de 55 años una vez por semana. La capacidad de todos los programas es de 15 por orden de llegada.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;El bosque de curación comienza donde comienza la caminata de curación a gran escala - República de Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/7c356d93-a17d-4051-901b-621634f6ad8a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     El bosque de curación comienza donde comienza la caminata de curación a gran escala
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Como es operado por un sistema de reserva anticipada, se requiere un certificado de confirmación de reserva para la verificación de identidad con el fin de experimentar el bosque de curación forestal. El vestido debe ser cómodo, de manga larga para evitar que las zapatillas de deporte y los mosquitos de zapatos para correr o botas de montaña. Tenga un sombrero listo para el sol y agua para su día. Si llega antes de que comience el programa, puede experimentarlo después de verificar el índice de estrés en el Centro de Visitantes del Bosque Curativo.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Los asesores de curación forestal explican antes del programa de curación - República de Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/d9b51215-3576-45e7-94fe-6e77ccc8ba64.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Los asesores de curación forestal explican antes del programa de curación
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Oh, también sepamos cómo visitar el bosque de curación forestal del Gran Parque de Seúl. Si está utilizando su propio automóvil, busque &#34;7-1, Makgye-dong, Gwacheon-si, Gyeonggi-do&#34; en la navegación. Si va en transporte público, puede bajarse en la estación Seoul Grand Park Station en la línea 4 del metro e ir al bosque Forest Healing o al cercano estacionamiento Dongmun.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Bosque curativo bosque comenzando valle - República de Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/88b05caf-a50c-4291-b854-f826d37888ed.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Bosque curativo bosque comenzando valle
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Según la guía, el tiempo de viaje para caminar, el tren de elefantes o el bosque de curación forestal es similar a 40 minutos. Si viaja en un tren de elefantes, solo necesita moverse una parada y bajarse en la entrada principal del zoológico y caminar hacia el Museo de Arte Moderno. En lugar de ingresar al Museo de Arte Moderno, si va directamente por la carretera principal, verá una señalización naranja que indica el camino hacia el Bosque de Curación Forestal. De ahora en adelante es alpinismo. La cinta naranja te guiará amablemente.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sendero forestal curativo para que las personas mayores caminen - República de Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/60c3899b-9621-4a6d-8f63-a723bd3c10f9.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sendero forestal curativo para que las personas mayores caminen
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Caminata curativa con sanador del bosque
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   ¿Cuánto tiempo caminaste? El Centro de visitantes del bosque Forest Healing está ubicado en el valle detrás del terreno baldío, donde la pancarta del &#34;Sendero del bosque curativo del Gran Parque de Seúl está disponible para los que reserven previamente&#34;. El Centro de Visitantes se reunió para aquellos que solicitaron un programa de curación juntos hoy. El Asesor de Sanación Forestal recomendó una taza de té frío de trigo sarraceno y dijo: &#34;Enfríemos y avancemos en el valle antes de que comience el programa de curación forestal&#34;.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Un poco
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Curso de hemoterapia del consejero de curación forestal - República de Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/dece20f4-99e5-4229-a95a-bfd4d1c331eb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Curso de hemoterapia del consejero de curación forestal
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Bosque curativo bosque
   &lt;strong&gt;
    Bosque, bosque de cielo, bosque de relajación de árboles, bosque de relajación de luz solar, bosque de relajación de agua
   &lt;/strong&gt;
   Y así. Primera llegada
   &lt;strong&gt;
    Actividad forestal
   &lt;/strong&gt;
   Estírate y relájate en el gimnasio.
   &lt;strong&gt;
    Actividad forestal
   &lt;/strong&gt;
   Frente a los pinos
   &lt;strong&gt;
    Bosque del cielo
   &lt;/strong&gt;
   Este lugar. Simplemente caminando en el árbol, respirando abierta. Caminatas para todas las edades A lo largo del sendero del bosque, dirígete a la cascada. Abetos
   &lt;strong&gt;
    Relajación del árbol
   &lt;/strong&gt;
   Decidí pasar por el camino a casa. El nombre de pinos Rígida
   &lt;strong&gt;
    Bosque de relajación de luz solar
   &lt;/strong&gt;
   Pasado(남성)
   &lt;strong&gt;
    Bosque de relajación de agua
   &lt;/strong&gt;
   Eso toca la cascada. Hay una cascada en el Gran Parque de Seúl.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Saludos que viven en un lugar fresco y limpio de primera clase - República de Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/0ee21d99-dfb8-486c-bcc6-2927105ad739.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Saludos que viven en un lugar fresco y limpio de primera clase
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Aunque es temporal, una cascada de 10 m de altura da la bienvenida a los participantes. Sumérjase en el valle que corre desde el valle de la montaña Cheonggye y descanse mientras mira la cascada. Tome una fotografía con una cascada en el fondo para refrescarse y regresar. La luz del sol no se filtra en pleno verano, por lo que no está enferma. En el árbol de relajación lleno de abetos, tiene lugar la meditación curativa &#39;meditación de descanso&#39;. Descansa en una terraza o piso de madera aquí. Los curanderos reparten los colchones uno por uno. Acostado cómodamente en el sonido de las cigarras, la luz del sol que se filtra a través de las hojas de color verde vivo, y el aire fresco proporcionado por los árboles. Todas las preocupaciones y problemas se establecen y Orot sale conmigo. No es largo, pero el efecto es bastante bueno. Te lleva por el sendero fragante del bosque donde las hierbas aromáticas te saludan con un paso ligero.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Camino del bosque de relajación del árbol al bosque de relajación de la luz solar - República de Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/8466e2bd-3c45-4051-ae2b-552e7a82eb19.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Camino del bosque de relajación del árbol al bosque de relajación de la luz solar
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Es algo diferente a hace 2 horas disfrutar de &#34;Healing Forest Healing&#34; con un programa de experiencia de un día y volver a la realidad. El peso y la cara son las mismas preocupaciones, pero algo es ligero. ¿Es porque los árboles que conoció en el bosque curativo llenaron la energía que se agotó sin conocerse a sí mismo?
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Cataratas Naturales en el Bosque Curativo Bosque del Gran Parque de Seúl - República de Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/1e708be3-7afd-440b-b035-3dd9a583291d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Cataratas Naturales en el Bosque Curativo Bosque del Gran Parque de Seúl
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   El bosque curativo Grand Park de Seúl también tiene programas especiales a largo plazo para mujeres menopáusicas, niños que usan teléfonos inteligentes, niños con trastorno de déficit de atención e hiperactividad (TDAH) y sus familias. Si solicita un programa a largo plazo, su registro se confirmará después de consultar a un sanador forestal. Póngase en contacto con el Bosque de Curación Forestal del Gran Parque de Seúl (02-500-7575, 7576, 7511).
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Los participantes toman un descanso para refrescarse en la cascada - República de Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/3e9921a4-e695-4707-ba4f-399c1ac2d592.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Los participantes toman un descanso para refrescarse en la cascada
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   PROPINA. Cómo usar el bosque de curación forestal en el Gran Parque de Seúl
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Inaugurado en 30 años, el Bosque de Curación Forestal del Gran Parque de Seúl se opera con reserva previa para preservar el bosque. Majung Forest Road (martes ~ viernes, dos veces al día) para adultos, Silver Forest Trail para personas mayores de 65 a 75 años (una vez a la semana) y Gold Forest Trail para adultos de 55 a 65 años (una vez a la semana) operan. La fecha límite es rápida, con un límite de 15 visitantes por programa. Para reservaciones, visite el sitio web del Gran Parque de Seúl (
   &lt;a href=&#34;http://grandpark.seoul.go.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;[새창열림]‘서울대공원’ 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
    http://grandpark.seoul.go.kr
   &lt;/a&gt;
   ) Y el sistema de reserva de servicio público de Seúl (
   &lt;a href=&#34;http://yeyak.seoul.go.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;[새창열림]‘서울시 공공서비스예약시스템’ 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
    http://yeyak.seoul.go.kr
   &lt;/a&gt;
   Puedes hacer Todo es gratis. También tiene programas especiales a largo plazo para mujeres menopáusicas, niños con altos niveles de uso de teléfonos inteligentes, niños con trastorno de déficit de atención e hiperactividad (TDAH) y sus familias.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Información de viaje
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Restaurantes cercanos
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Cerro de las Rosas: Gwacheon-si Makgye-dong / Costillas, Fideos Fríos / 02-504-5311
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Sopa de helado de caldero casero interno: Gwangchang-ro, Gwacheon / Sopa de helado / 02-3679-1175
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Hipódromo Duck House: Gwacheon-si Gungmal-ro / Arcilla de pato de azufre a la parrilla / 02-502-7500
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Seorabul: Gwacheon Byeolyangsangga / Pino Natural Shabu Shabu / 02-502-8384
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Alojamiento
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Seúl Grand Park Nature Campground (inaugurado en marzo ~ noviembre): 159-1, Makgye-dong, Gwacheon-si / 02-500-7870
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Grace Hotel: 2, calle comercial Seongyang, Gwacheon / 02-504-6700
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://hotelgrace6700.tnaru.net/web/index&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://hotelgrace6700.tnaru.net/web/index
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ La información anterior se escribió en agosto de 2015 y puede cambiar después. Por favor verifique antes de viajar.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ La información como texto, fotos y videos utilizados en este artículo tiene copyright de la Organización de Turismo de Corea, por lo que está prohibido el uso no autorizado del artículo.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Republik Korea - Erfahrungen aus „Secret Forest“ und „Seoul Grand Park Forest Healing Forest“ in 30 Jahren</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/secret-forest-and-seoul-grand-park-forest-healing-forest-experiences-revealed-in-30-years-38-de/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 19:45:34 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/secret-forest-and-seoul-grand-park-forest-healing-forest-experiences-revealed-in-30-years-38-de/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-title=&#34;secret-forest-and-seoul-grand-park-forest-healing-forest-experiences-revealed-in-30-years--38&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;und - Republik Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/6a769698-24f5-425f-8420-e36370ef139f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    und
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Erfahrungen aus „Secret Forest“ und „Seoul Grand Park Forest Healing Forest“ in 30 Jahren
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Republik Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Im Juli wurde der &#34;geheime Wald&#34;, den der Seoul Grand Park versteckt hatte, in 30 Jahren der Öffentlichkeit zugänglich gemacht. Das Hauptthema ist der „Health Healing Forest“ im Seoul Grand Park, der moderne Menschen tröstet, die den Alltag satt haben. Einführung in die &#34;Heilerfahrung&#34;, bei der der während des Spaziergangs angesammelte Stress entspannt wird, wenn Sie den ruhigen Waldweg entlang gehen, der sich vom üppigen Wald bis zum Tal des Cheonggyesan-Berges und dem natürlichen Wasserfall erstreckt.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &#34;Heiß&#34; ist nicht genug Wetter. Es gab eine Nachricht über den &#34;geheimen Wald&#34;, der in 30 Jahren auf der Welt auftauchte, als er nur die heiße Sonne einatmete, als würde er alles verbrennen. Außerdem der Name &#34;Waldheilung&#34;. &#34;Heilen&#34; und &#34;Heilen&#34; sind kein heißes Wort für moderne Menschen, die den Sommer vergangen sind, weil sie nicht heiß werden können.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Gehen Sie sofort durch die Tannen- und Kiefernwälder und kühlen Wasserfälle!
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Der Protagonist ist der Seoul Grand Park Healing Forest, der seit dem 13. Juli für die Öffentlichkeit zugänglich ist. Es ist ein natürlicher Wald mit 50.000 Quadratmetern und enthält das Cheonggyesan-Tal und einen natürlichen Wasserfall. Zum Schutz der Natur, die seit 30 Jahren ruht, können nur 50-60 Menschen pro Tag besuchen. Seoul Grand Park Homepage
   &lt;a href=&#34;http://grandpark.seoul.go.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;[새창열림]‘서울대공원’ 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
    http://grandpark.seoul.go.kr
   &lt;/a&gt;
   ) Und Seoul Public Service Reservierungssystem (
   &lt;a href=&#34;http://yeyak.seoul.go.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;[새창열림]‘서울시 공공서비스예약시스템’ 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
    http://yeyak.seoul.go.kr
   &lt;/a&gt;
   Sie können vorhersagen durch).
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Besucherzentrum am Anfang des Waldheilwaldes des Seoul Grand Park - Republik Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/d4d69d47-c87e-4b03-9b58-048d830a8b1d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Besucherzentrum am Anfang des Waldheilwaldes des Seoul Grand Park
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Die Frist ist so schnell, dass es etwas schwierig ist, sie zu buchen. Wenn Sie jedoch die Müdigkeit des &#34;geheimen Waldes&#34; und des &#34;heilenden Waldes&#34; kostenlos wegblasen möchten, können Sie es versuchen. Sie können „Waldheilung“ erleben, dh Aktivitäten zur Stärkung der Immunität des menschlichen Körpers und zur Wiederherstellung der körperlichen und geistigen Gesundheit durch Nutzung und Analyse des Waldes. Wenn es nicht geschlossen ist, können Sie sich zwei Tage vor Ihrem gewünschten Datum registrieren. Reservierungen beginnen in der Regel ca. 20 Tage nach dem Liefertermin. Das Datum kann sich ändern, daher ist es eine gute Idee, die Website vorher zu überprüfen. Es ist so beliebt, dass es zu Beginn der Buchung geschlossen wird.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Waldplatz, auf dem sich Vorbucher versammeln - Republik Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/47a6cdc2-1130-4f04-82ae-fb04df972289.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Waldplatz, auf dem sich Vorbucher versammeln
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Das vom Reporter gebuchte Programm ist die Majung Forest Road, die für die breite Öffentlichkeit zugänglich ist. Ziel ist es, die Waldheilung einzuführen und zu erleben. Sie findet zweimal von Dienstag bis Freitag von 10:00 bis 12:00 Uhr und von PM bis 16:00 Uhr statt. Kinder sind nicht erlaubt. Darüber hinaus zielt die Silver Forest Road darauf ab, die Muskelkraft zu reduzieren, Stürze zu verhindern und die Vitalität für Erwachsene im Alter von 65 bis 75 Jahren zu verbessern. Arbeiten. Einmal pro Woche werden Heilprogramme für Erwachsene ab 55 Jahren angeboten. Die Kapazität aller Programme beträgt 15, je nach Verfügbarkeit.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Waldheilungswald beginnt dort, wo der vollständige Heilungsspaziergang beginnt - Republik Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/7c356d93-a17d-4051-901b-621634f6ad8a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Waldheilungswald beginnt dort, wo der vollständige Heilungsspaziergang beginnt
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Da es vom Vorreservierungssystem betrieben wird, ist für die Identitätsprüfung ein Reservierungsbestätigungszertifikat erforderlich, um Waldheilungswald zu erleben. Das Kleid sollte bequem und langärmelig sein, um zu verhindern, dass Turnschuhe und Mücken Laufschuhe oder Wanderschuhe tragen. Halten Sie einen Hut für die Sonne und Wasser für Ihren Tag bereit. Wenn Sie vor Programmbeginn ankommen, können Sie das Programm nach Überprüfung des Stressindex im Besucherzentrum des Heilwaldes erleben.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Waldheilungsberater erklären vor dem Heilungsprogramm - Republik Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/d9b51215-3576-45e7-94fe-6e77ccc8ba64.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Waldheilungsberater erklären vor dem Heilungsprogramm
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Oh, lassen Sie uns auch wissen, wie man den Waldheilungswald des Seoul Grand Park besucht. Wenn Sie Ihr eigenes Auto benutzen, suchen Sie in der Navigation nach &#34;7-1, Makgye-dong, Gwacheon-si, Gyeonggi-do&#34;. Wenn Sie mit öffentlichen Verkehrsmitteln anreisen, können Sie an der Seoul Grand Park Station der U-Bahnlinie 4 aussteigen und zum Forest Healing Forest oder zum nahe gelegenen Dongmun-Parkplatz fahren.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Waldheilendes Waldanfangstal - Republik Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/88b05caf-a50c-4291-b854-f826d37888ed.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Waldheilendes Waldanfangstal
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Laut dem Führer beträgt die Reisezeit für Spaziergänge, Elefantenzüge oder Waldheilungswälder ungefähr 40 Minuten. Wenn Sie mit einem Elefantenzug fahren, müssen Sie nur eine Haltestelle zurücklegen und am Haupteingang des Zoos aussteigen und zum Museum of Modern Art gehen. Anstatt das Museum of Modern Art zu betreten, sehen Sie auf der Hauptstraße eine orangefarbene Beschilderung, die den Weg zum Forest Healing Forest anzeigt. Von nun an geht es bergauf. Das orangefarbene Band wird Sie freundlich führen.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Heilender Waldweg für ältere Menschen zu Fuß - Republik Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/60c3899b-9621-4a6d-8f63-a723bd3c10f9.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Heilender Waldweg für ältere Menschen zu Fuß
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Heilungsspaziergang mit Waldheiler
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Wie lange bist du gelaufen? Das Besucherzentrum Forest Healing Forest befindet sich im Tal hinter dem freien Grundstück, auf dem Vorbuchern das Banner des „Seoul Grand Park Healing Forest Path“ zur Verfügung steht. Das Besucherzentrum versammelte sich für diejenigen, die sich heute gemeinsam für ein Heilungsprogramm beworben haben. Der Waldheilungsberater empfahl eine Tasse kühlen Buchweizentee und sagte: &#34;Lassen Sie uns abkühlen und uns im Tal bewegen, bevor das Waldheilungsprogramm beginnt.&#34;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Ein bisschen
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Hämotherapiekurs des Waldheilungsberaters - Republik Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/dece20f4-99e5-4229-a95a-bfd4d1c331eb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Hämotherapiekurs des Waldheilungsberaters
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Waldheilungswald
   &lt;strong&gt;
    Wald, Himmelswald, Baumentspannungswald, Sonnenlichtentspannungswald, Wasserentspannungswald
   &lt;/strong&gt;
   Und so weiter. Erste Ankunft
   &lt;strong&gt;
    Waldaktivität
   &lt;/strong&gt;
   Dehnen und entspannen Sie sich im Fitnessstudio.
   &lt;strong&gt;
    Waldaktivität
   &lt;/strong&gt;
   Gegenüber den Kiefern
   &lt;strong&gt;
    Himmelswald
   &lt;/strong&gt;
   Dieser Ort. Einfach in den Baum gehen und aufatmen. Wandern für alle Altersgruppen Gehen Sie auf dem Waldweg zum Wasserfall. Tannenbäume
   &lt;strong&gt;
    Baumentspannung
   &lt;/strong&gt;
   Beschlossen, auf dem Heimweg vorbeizuschauen. Der Name Rigida-Kiefern
   &lt;strong&gt;
    Sonnenlicht-Entspannungswald
   &lt;/strong&gt;
   Vergangenheit
   &lt;strong&gt;
    Wasserentspannungswald
   &lt;/strong&gt;
   Das berührt den Wasserfall. Es gibt so einen Wasserfall im Seoul Grand Park.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Prost auf coole, saubere First Class - Republik Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/0ee21d99-dfb8-486c-bcc6-2927105ad739.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Prost auf coole, saubere First Class
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Obwohl es nur vorübergehend ist, begrüßt ein 10 m hoher Wasserfall die Teilnehmer. Tauchen Sie ein in das Tal, das vom Cheonggye Mountain Valley ausgeht, und ruhen Sie sich aus, während Sie den Wasserfall betrachten. Machen Sie ein Foto mit einem Wasserfall im Hintergrund, um sich abzukühlen und zurück zu gehen. Im Hochsommer tritt kein Sonnenlicht aus, daher ist es nicht krank. In dem mit Tannen gefüllten Entspannungsbaum findet die Heilmeditation „Ruhemeditation“ statt. Ruhen Sie sich hier auf einem Holzdeck oder Boden aus. Waldheiler verteilen die Matratzen nacheinander. Bequem im Klang von Zikaden liegen, der Sonnenschein durch die leuchtend grünen Blätter und die frische Luft der Bäume. Alle Sorgen und Nöte sind niedergelegt und Orot kommt mit mir heraus. Es ist nicht lange, aber der Effekt ist ziemlich gut. Es führt Sie durch den duftenden Waldweg, wo duftende Kräuter Sie mit einem leichten Schritt begrüßen.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Weg vom Baumentspannungswald zum Sonnenlichtentspannungswald - Republik Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/8466e2bd-3c45-4051-ae2b-552e7a82eb19.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Weg vom Baumentspannungswald zum Sonnenlichtentspannungswald
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Es ist etwas anderes als vor 2 Stunden, „Healing Forest Healing“ mit einem eintägigen Erlebnisprogramm zu genießen und zur Realität zurückzukehren. Das Gewicht und das Gesicht sind die gleichen Sorgen, aber etwas ist leicht. Liegt es daran, dass die Bäume, die er im Heilwald traf, die Energie auffüllten, die erschöpft war, ohne sich selbst zu kennen?
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Natürliche Fälle im Waldheilungswald des Seoul Grand Park - Republik Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/1e708be3-7afd-440b-b035-3dd9a583291d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Natürliche Fälle im Waldheilungswald des Seoul Grand Park
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Der Seoul Grand Park Healing Forest bietet auch spezielle Langzeitprogramme für Frauen in den Wechseljahren, Kinder, die Smartphones verwenden, Kinder mit Aufmerksamkeitsdefizit-Hyperaktivitätsstörung (ADHS) und ihre Familien. Wenn Sie sich für ein Langzeitprogramm bewerben, wird Ihre Registrierung nach Rücksprache mit einem Waldheiler bestätigt. Wenden Sie sich an den Seoul Grand Park Forest Healing Forest (02-500-7575, 7576, 7511).
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Die Teilnehmer machen eine Pause, um sich am Wasserfall abzukühlen - Republik Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/3e9921a4-e695-4707-ba4f-399c1ac2d592.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Die Teilnehmer machen eine Pause, um sich am Wasserfall abzukühlen
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   TRINKGELD. Wie man den Waldheilungswald im Seoul Grand Park benutzt
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Der in 30 Jahren eröffnete Seoul Grand Park Forest Healing Forest wird nach vorheriger Reservierung betrieben, um den Wald zu erhalten. Die Majung Forest Road (Di ~ Fr, zweimal täglich) für Erwachsene, der Silver Forest Trail für Senioren zwischen 65 und 75 Jahren (einmal pro Woche) und der Gold Forest Trail für Erwachsene zwischen 55 und 65 Jahren (einmal pro Woche) sind in Betrieb. Die Frist ist schnell, mit einem Limit von 15 Besuchern pro Programm. Für Reservierungen besuchen Sie bitte die Website des Seoul Grand Park (
   &lt;a href=&#34;http://grandpark.seoul.go.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;[새창열림]‘서울대공원’ 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
    http://grandpark.seoul.go.kr
   &lt;/a&gt;
   ) Und Seoul Public Service Reservierungssystem (
   &lt;a href=&#34;http://yeyak.seoul.go.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;[새창열림]‘서울시 공공서비스예약시스템’ 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
    http://yeyak.seoul.go.kr
   &lt;/a&gt;
   Sie können alles kostenlos tun. Es gibt auch spezielle Langzeitprogramme für Frauen in den Wechseljahren, Kinder mit hoher Smartphone-Nutzung, Kinder mit Aufmerksamkeitsdefizit-Hyperaktivitätsstörung (ADHS) und deren Familien.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Reiseinformationen
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Restaurants in der Nähe
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Hügel der Rosen: Gwacheon-si Makgye-dong / Rippen, kalte Nudeln / 02-504-5311
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Inner Home Cauldron Eisbechersuppe: Gwangchang-ro, Gwacheon / Eisbechersuppe / 02-3679-1175
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Racecourse Duck House: Gwacheon-si Gungmal-ro / Gegrillter Schwefel-Ententon / 02-502-7500
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Seorabul: Gwacheon Byeolyangsangga / Naturkiefer Shabu Shabu / 02-502-8384
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Unterkunft
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Seoul Grand Park Naturcampingplatz (eröffnet im März bis November): 159-1, Makgye-dong, Gwacheon-si / 02-500-7870
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Grace Hotel: 2, Seongyang Einkaufsstraße, Gwacheon / 02-504-6700
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://hotelgrace6700.tnaru.net/web/index&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://hotelgrace6700.tnaru.net/web/index
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ Die oben genannten Informationen wurden im August 2015 verfasst und können sich später ändern. Bitte überprüfen Sie vor Reiseantritt.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Die in diesem Artikel verwendeten Informationen wie Text, Fotos und Videos sind von der Korea Tourism Organization urheberrechtlich geschützt. Daher ist die unbefugte Verwendung des Artikels untersagt.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>大韩民国 - 30年来展现的“秘密森林”和“首尔大公园森林治愈林”的经验</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/secret-forest-and-seoul-grand-park-forest-healing-forest-experiences-revealed-in-30-years-38-zh-cn/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 19:42:27 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/secret-forest-and-seoul-grand-park-forest-healing-forest-experiences-revealed-in-30-years-38-zh-cn/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-title=&#34;secret-forest-and-seoul-grand-park-forest-healing-forest-experiences-revealed-in-30-years--38&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;和 - 大韩民国 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/6a769698-24f5-425f-8420-e36370ef139f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    和
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   30年来展现的“秘密森林”和“首尔大公园森林治愈林”的经验
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    大韩民国
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   7月，首尔大公园隐藏的“秘密森林”在30年内向公众释放。 首尔主题公园是首尔大公园的“健康疗养林”，为那些厌倦了日常生活的现代人提供安慰。 引入``疗愈体验&#39;&#39;，让您沿着安静的林间小径行走，缓解步行中积累的压力，该林间小径从茂密的森林延伸到清溪山山谷和天然瀑布。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   “热”天气不足。 有消息说，“秘密森林”在30年间出现在世界上，当时它在烈日下呼吸，好像在燃烧一切。 另外，名字“森林愈合”。 对于已经过了暑假的现代人来说，“恢复健康”和“恢复健康”并不是一个热门词汇，因为他们不会变热。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   立即穿过冷杉和松树林以及凉爽的瀑布！
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   主角是首尔大公园愈合林，自7月13日起对公众开放。 它是一个拥有50,000平方米的天然森林，并包含清溪谷山谷和天然瀑布。 为了保护已经休息30年的自然，每天只能参观50至60人。 首尔大公园主页
   &lt;a href=&#34;http://grandpark.seoul.go.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;[새창열림]‘서울대공원’ 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
    http://grandpark.seoul.go.kr
   &lt;/a&gt;
   ）和首尔公共服务预定系统（
   &lt;a href=&#34;http://yeyak.seoul.go.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;[새창열림]‘서울시 공공서비스예약시스템’ 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
    http://yeyak.seoul.go.kr
   &lt;/a&gt;
   您可以预测）。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;首尔大公园森林治愈森林的起点的游客中心 - 大韩民国 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/d4d69d47-c87e-4b03-9b58-048d830a8b1d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     首尔大公园森林治愈森林的起点的游客中心
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   截止日期是如此之快，以至于预订有些困难，但是如果您想免费摆脱“秘密森林”和“治愈森林”的疲劳，可以尝试一下。 您可以体验“森林恢复”，这意味着可以通过利用和分析森林来提高人体免疫力并恢复身心健康。 如果尚未关闭，您可以在所需日期的前两天进行注册。 预订通常在交货日期的20天左右开始。 日期可能会更改，因此最好事先检查网站。 它是如此受欢迎，以至于预订开始时就关闭。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;预订者聚集的森林广场 - 大韩民国 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/47a6cdc2-1130-4f04-82ae-fb04df972289.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     预订者聚集的森林广场
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   记者预定的节目是向公众开放的麻将林道。 它的目的是介绍和体验森林愈合，它将在星期二至星期五上午10:00至12:00 pm和下午pm至16:00 pm举行两次。 不允许儿童入内。 此外，银林之路旨在降低65岁至75岁成年人的肌肉力量，防止跌倒并增强活力。 操作。 每周提供一次针对55岁以上成年人的康复计划。 所有程序的容量为15个，先到先得。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;森林恢复森林的起点，全面的恢复步行开始 - 大韩民国 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/7c356d93-a17d-4051-901b-621634f6ad8a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     森林恢复森林的起点，全面的恢复步行开始
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   由于它是由提前预订系统操作的，因此需要预订确认证书来进行身份验证，以便体验森林愈合的森林。 穿着应舒适，长袖，以防止运动鞋和蚊子穿上跑步鞋或登山靴。 为您的一天准备一顶帽子，准备好防晒和浇水。 如果您在计划开始之前到达，则可以在Healing Forest Visitor Center检查压力指数后体验该计划。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;森林修复顾问在修复计划之前进行解释 - 大韩民国 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/d9b51215-3576-45e7-94fe-6e77ccc8ba64.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     森林修复顾问在修复计划之前进行解释
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   哦，让我们也知道如何参观首尔大公园的森林。 如果您使用的是自己的汽车，请在导航栏中搜索“京畿道果川市麦溪洞7-1”。 如果乘坐公共交通工具，可以在地铁4号线的首尔大公园站下车，然后前往森林疗愈森林或附近的东门停车场。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;森林愈合森林开始谷 - 大韩民国 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/88b05caf-a50c-4291-b854-f826d37888ed.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     森林愈合森林开始谷
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   根据指南，步行，大象训练或森林治愈森林所需的时间大约为40分钟。 如果您乘坐大象火车，则只需停一站然后在动物园的正门下车，然后步行至现代艺术博物馆。 如果您直接沿着主要道路行驶，则无需进入现代艺术博物馆，而是会看到橙色的标牌，指示通往森林修复森林的道路。 从现在开始就是登山。 橘色的丝带会引导您。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;老人走路的疗愈林间小径 - 大韩民国 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/60c3899b-9621-4a6d-8f63-a723bd3c10f9.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     老人走路的疗愈林间小径
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   与森林治疗师一起散步
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   你走了多久？ 森林疗养森林游客中心位于空地后面的山谷中，“预订首尔大公园疗养森林路径”的标语可供预订者使用。 访客中心聚集了今天一起申请康复计划的人。 森林修复顾问建议喝一杯凉的荞麦茶，并说：“让我们冷却下来，然后在森林修复计划开始之前在山谷中移动。”
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   一点
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;森林修复顾问的血液疗法课程 - 大韩民国 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/dece20f4-99e5-4229-a95a-bfd4d1c331eb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     森林修复顾问的血液疗法课程
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   森林恢复森林
   &lt;strong&gt;
    森林，天空森林，树木松弛森林，阳光松弛森林，水松弛森林
   &lt;/strong&gt;
   等等。 先到
   &lt;strong&gt;
    森林活动
   &lt;/strong&gt;
   在健身房伸展和放松。
   &lt;strong&gt;
    森林活动
   &lt;/strong&gt;
   在松树对面
   &lt;strong&gt;
    天空森林
   &lt;/strong&gt;
   这个地方。 只是在树上行走，呼吸打开。 各个年龄段的人漫步沿着森林小径，前往瀑布。 枞树
   &lt;strong&gt;
    树木放松
   &lt;/strong&gt;
   决定在回家的路上停下来。 里吉达松树的名字
   &lt;strong&gt;
    阳光休闲林
   &lt;/strong&gt;
   过去
   &lt;strong&gt;
    水放松森林
   &lt;/strong&gt;
   那碰到瀑布了。 首尔大公园有这样的瀑布。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;生活在凉爽，干净的一流环境中的欢呼声 - 大韩民国 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/0ee21d99-dfb8-486c-bcc6-2927105ad739.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     生活在凉爽，干净的一流环境中的欢呼声
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   尽管是临时的，但还是有一个10m高的瀑布欢迎参与者。 将脚浸在清溪山谷的山谷中，然后看着瀑布休息一下。 拍摄背景为瀑布的照片以使其冷却并返回。 仲夏阳光不会泄漏，因此没有病。 在充满冷杉的放松树中，进行了冥想的“静息冥想”。 在这里在木甲板或地板上休息。 森林医务人员一张一张地分发床垫。 舒适地躺在蝉鸣的声音中，阳光从鲜艳的绿色叶子中漏出，树木提供新鲜的空气。 所有的烦恼和烦恼都被解决了，奥罗特也和我一起走了出来。 时间不长，但是效果很好。 它带您穿过芬芳的森林小径，芬芳的草药向您招手致意。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;从树松弛森林到阳光松弛森林的路径 - 大韩民国 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/8466e2bd-3c45-4051-ae2b-552e7a82eb19.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     从树松弛森林到阳光松弛森林的路径
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   与2小时前通过一日体验计划享受“森林康复疗养”并回到现实世界有所不同。 体重和脸庞是一样的担心，但有些轻。 是因为他在疗愈的森林中遇到的树木充满了不知不觉耗尽的能量吗？
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;首尔大公园森林疗养林中的自然瀑布 - 大韩民国 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/1e708be3-7afd-440b-b035-3dd9a583291d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     首尔大公园森林疗养林中的自然瀑布
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   首尔大公园治愈森林还为绝经妇女，使用智能手机的儿童，患有注意力缺陷多动障碍（ADHD）的儿童及其家人提供了特殊的长期计划。 如果您申请长期计划，请先咨询森林治疗师，然后确认您的注册。 请与首尔大公园森林治疗林（02-500-7575，7576，7511）联系。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;参加者在瀑布休息一下以放松身心 - 大韩民国 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/3e9921a4-e695-4707-ba4f-399c1ac2d592.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     参加者在瀑布休息一下以放松身心
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   小费。 如何在首尔大公园使用森林疗养林
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   首尔大公园森林疗养林开放已有30年，需要事先预约以保护该森林。 成人可使用Majung森林路（周二至周五，每天两次），65至75岁（老年人）的老年人的银林步道，以及55至65岁（老年人）的成年人的金林步道。 截止日期很快，每个程序最多只能有15位访问者。 如需预订，请访问首尔大公园网站（
   &lt;a href=&#34;http://grandpark.seoul.go.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;[새창열림]‘서울대공원’ 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
    http://grandpark.seoul.go.kr
   &lt;/a&gt;
   ）和首尔公共服务预定系统（
   &lt;a href=&#34;http://yeyak.seoul.go.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;[새창열림]‘서울시 공공서비스예약시스템’ 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
    http://yeyak.seoul.go.kr
   &lt;/a&gt;
   您可以做所有事情都是免费的。 它还为更年期妇女，使用智能手机的儿童较多，患有注意力缺陷多动障碍（ADHD）的儿童及其家庭提供特殊的长期计划。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   旅游信息
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1.附近的餐馆
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    玫瑰山：果川市麦溪洞/排骨，冷面/ 02-504-5311
    &lt;br/&gt;
    内家大锅圣代汤：果川广昌路/圣代汤/ 02-3679-1175
    &lt;br/&gt;
    跑马场鸭子之家：果川市Gungmal-ro /烤硫鸭粘土/ 02-502-7500
    &lt;br/&gt;
    雪岳山：果川边良姜/天然松Pine锅/ 02-502-8384
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2.住宿
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    首尔大公园自然露营地（3月至11月开放）：果川市麦溪洞159-1 / 02-500-7870
    &lt;br/&gt;
    格雷斯酒店：果川市城阳购物街2号/ 02-504-6700
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://hotelgrace6700.tnaru.net/web/index&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://hotelgrace6700.tnaru.net/web/index
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※以上信息为2015年8月的内容，之后可能会有变更。 请在旅行前检查。
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※本文中使用的文字，照片和视频等信息受韩国旅游组织版权保护，因此禁止未经授权使用本文。
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Republic of Korea - “Secret Forest” and “Seoul Grand Park Forest Healing Forest” Experiences Revealed in 30 Years</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/secret-forest-and-seoul-grand-park-forest-healing-forest-experiences-revealed-in-30-years-38/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 19:39:13 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/secret-forest-and-seoul-grand-park-forest-healing-forest-experiences-revealed-in-30-years-38/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-title=&#34;secret-forest-and-seoul-grand-park-forest-healing-forest-experiences-revealed-in-30-years--38&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;and - Republic of Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/6a769698-24f5-425f-8420-e36370ef139f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    and
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   “Secret Forest” and “Seoul Grand Park Forest Healing Forest” Experiences Revealed in 30 Years
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Republic of Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In July, the &#34;secret forest&#34; that Seoul Grand Park had hidden was released to the public in 30 years. The main theme is the “Health Healing Forest” in Seoul Grand Park, which comforts modern people who are tired of everyday life. Introducing the `` Healing Experience &#39;&#39; where the stress accumulated in the walk is relaxed as you walk along the quiet forest path that stretches from the lush forest to the valley of Cheonggyesan Mountain and the natural waterfall.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &#39;Hot&#39; is not enough weather. There was a news about the &#34;secret forest&#34; that appeared in the world in 30 years, when it was just breathing in the hot sun as if it burned everything. In addition, the name &#39;Forest Healing&#39;. &#39;Healing&#39; and &#39;healing&#39; are not a hot word for modern people who have passed the summer because they can&#39;t get hot.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Go through the fir and pine forests and cool waterfalls at once!
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The protagonist is Seoul Grand Park Healing Forest, which has been open to the public since July 13th. It is a natural forest boasting 50,000 square meters and contains Cheonggyesan valley valley and natural waterfall. To protect nature, which has been resting for 30 years, only 50-60 people a day can visit. Seoul Grand Park homepage
   &lt;a href=&#34;http://grandpark.seoul.go.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;[새창열림]‘서울대공원’ 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
    http://grandpark.seoul.go.kr
   &lt;/a&gt;
   ) And Seoul Public Service Reservation System (
   &lt;a href=&#34;http://yeyak.seoul.go.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;[새창열림]‘서울시 공공서비스예약시스템’ 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
    http://yeyak.seoul.go.kr
   &lt;/a&gt;
   You can predict by).
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Visitor center at the beginning of the forest healing forest of Seoul Grand Park - Republic of Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/d4d69d47-c87e-4b03-9b58-048d830a8b1d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Visitor center at the beginning of the forest healing forest of Seoul Grand Park
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The deadline is so fast that it&#39;s a bit difficult to book, but if you want to blow away the fatigue from the &#39;secret forest&#39; and the &#39;healing forest&#39; for free, you can try. You can experience &#39;forest healing&#39; which means activities to increase the immunity of the human body and restore physical and mental health by utilizing and analyzing the forest. If it is not closed, you can register two days before your desired date. Reservations usually begin around 20 days of the delivery date. The date may change, so it&#39;s a good idea to check the website beforehand. It is so popular that it closes at the beginning of the booking.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Forest square where pre-bookers gather - Republic of Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/47a6cdc2-1130-4f04-82ae-fb04df972289.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Forest square where pre-bookers gather
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The program booked by the reporter is Majung Forest Road, which is open to the general public. It aims to introduce and experience forest healing, and it will be held twice from Tuesday to Friday from 10:00 am to 12:00 pm and from pm to 16:00 pm. Children are not allowed. In addition, the Silver Forest Road aims to reduce muscle strength, prevent falls, and improve vitality for adults aged 65 to 75 years. Operate. Healing programs for adults 55 and older are offered once a week. The capacity of all programs is 15 on a first come, first served basis.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Forest healing forest beginning where full-scale healing walk begins - Republic of Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/7c356d93-a17d-4051-901b-621634f6ad8a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Forest healing forest beginning where full-scale healing walk begins
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   As it is operated by advance reservation system, a reservation confirmation certificate is required for identity verification in order to experience forest healing forest. Dress should be comfortable, long-sleeved to prevent sneakers and mosquitoes from running shoes or hiking boots. Have a hat ready for the sun and water for your day. If you arrive before the program starts, you can experience the program after checking the stress index at the Healing Forest Visitor Center.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Forest Healing Advisors Explain Before the Healing Program - Republic of Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/d9b51215-3576-45e7-94fe-6e77ccc8ba64.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Forest Healing Advisors Explain Before the Healing Program
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Oh, let&#39;s also know how to visit the forest healing forest of Seoul Grand Park. If you are using your own car, search for ‘7-1, Makgye-dong, Gwacheon-si, Gyeonggi-do’ on the navigation. If you go by public transport, you can get off at Seoul Grand Park Station on Subway Line 4 and go to the Forest Healing Forest or the nearby Dongmun Parking Lot.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Forest healing forest beginning valley - Republic of Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/88b05caf-a50c-4291-b854-f826d37888ed.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Forest healing forest beginning valley
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   According to the guide, the journey time to walk, elephant train or forest healing forest is similar to 40 minutes. If you are riding an elephant train, you only need to move one stop and get off at the main entrance to the zoo and walk toward the Museum of Modern Art. Instead of entering the Museum of Modern Art, if you go straight down the main road, you will see an orange signage indicating the way to the Forest Healing Forest. From now on it is mountain climbing. The orange ribbon will guide you kindly.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Healing forest path for elderly people to walk - Republic of Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/60c3899b-9621-4a6d-8f63-a723bd3c10f9.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Healing forest path for elderly people to walk
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Healing walk with forest healer
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   How long did you walk? The Forest Healing Forest Visitor Center is located in the valley behind the vacant lot where the banner of &#39;Seoul Grand Park Healing Forest Path is available to pre-bookers&#39;. The Visitor Center gathered for those who applied for a healing program together today. The Forest Healing Advisor recommended a cup of cool buckwheat tea and said, &#34;Let&#39;s cool down and move in the valley before the forest healing program begins.&#34;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   A little
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Forest Healing Advisor&#39;s Hemotherapy Course - Republic of Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/dece20f4-99e5-4229-a95a-bfd4d1c331eb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Forest Healing Advisor&#39;s Hemotherapy Course
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Forest healing forest
   &lt;strong&gt;
    Forest, sky forest, tree relaxation forest, sunlight relaxation forest, water relaxation forest
   &lt;/strong&gt;
   And so on. First arrival
   &lt;strong&gt;
    Forest activity
   &lt;/strong&gt;
   Stretch and relax at the gym.
   &lt;strong&gt;
    Forest activity
   &lt;/strong&gt;
   Opposite the pine trees
   &lt;strong&gt;
    Sky Forest
   &lt;/strong&gt;
   This place. Just walking in the tree, breathing open. Walking for all ages Along the forest path, head for the waterfall. Fir trees
   &lt;strong&gt;
    Tree relaxation
   &lt;/strong&gt;
   Decided to stop by on the way home. The name Rigida pine trees
   &lt;strong&gt;
    Sunlight Relaxation Forest
   &lt;/strong&gt;
   Past
   &lt;strong&gt;
    Water relaxation forest
   &lt;/strong&gt;
   That touches the waterfall. There is such a waterfall in Seoul Grand Park.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Cheers living in cool, clean first-class - Republic of Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/0ee21d99-dfb8-486c-bcc6-2927105ad739.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Cheers living in cool, clean first-class
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Although it is temporary, a 10m high waterfall welcomes the participants. Soak your feet in the valley that runs from the Cheonggye Mountain Valley and take a rest while looking at the waterfall. Take a picture with a waterfall in the background to cool down and go back. Sunlight does not leak in midsummer, so it is not sick. In the relaxation tree filled with firs, the healing meditation &#39;rest meditation&#39; takes place. Rest on a wooden deck or floor here. Forest healers hand out the mattresses one by one. Lying comfortably in the sound of cicadas, the sunshine leaking through the vivid green leaves, and the fresh air provided by the trees. All the worries and troubles are laid down and Orot comes out with me. It&#39;s not long, but the effect is quite good. It takes you through the fragrant forest path where fragrant herbs greet you with a light step.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Path from tree relaxation forest to sunlight relaxation forest - Republic of Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/8466e2bd-3c45-4051-ae2b-552e7a82eb19.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Path from tree relaxation forest to sunlight relaxation forest
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It&#39;s something different from 2 hours ago to enjoy “Healing Forest Healing” with a one-day experience program and get back to reality. The weight and face are the same worries, but something is light. Is it because the trees that he met in the healing forest filled up the energy that was exhausted without knowing himself?
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Natural Falls in the Forest Healing Forest of Seoul Grand Park - Republic of Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/1e708be3-7afd-440b-b035-3dd9a583291d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Natural Falls in the Forest Healing Forest of Seoul Grand Park
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Seoul Grand Park Healing Forest also has special long-term programs for menopausal women, children who use smartphones, children with Attention Deficit Hyperactivity Disorder (ADHD) and their families. If you apply for a long-term program, your registration will be confirmed after consulting a forest healer. Contact the Seoul Grand Park Forest Healing Forest (02-500-7575, 7576, 7511).
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Participants take a break to cool off at the waterfall - Republic of Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/38/3e9921a4-e695-4707-ba4f-399c1ac2d592.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Participants take a break to cool off at the waterfall
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   TIP. How to use the Forest Healing Forest in Seoul Grand Park
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Opened in 30 years, the Seoul Grand Park Forest Healing Forest is operated by reservation in advance to preserve the forest. Majung Forest Road (Tue ~ Fri, Twice a Day) for Adults, Silver Forest Trail for Seniors 65 to 75 Years (Once a Week), and Gold Forest Trail for Adults 55 to 65 Years (Once a Week) Operate. The deadline is fast, with a limit of 15 visitors per program. For reservations, please visit the Seoul Grand Park website (
   &lt;a href=&#34;http://grandpark.seoul.go.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;[새창열림]‘서울대공원’ 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
    http://grandpark.seoul.go.kr
   &lt;/a&gt;
   ) And Seoul Public Service Reservation System (
   &lt;a href=&#34;http://yeyak.seoul.go.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;[새창열림]‘서울시 공공서비스예약시스템’ 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
    http://yeyak.seoul.go.kr
   &lt;/a&gt;
   You can do All is free. It also has special long-term programs for menopausal women, children with high levels of smartphone use, children with Attention Deficit Hyperactivity Disorder (ADHD) and their families.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel info
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Nearby restaurants
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Hill of Roses: Gwacheon-si Makgye-dong / Ribs, Cold Noodles / 02-504-5311
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Inner Home Cauldron Sundae Soup: Gwangchang-ro, Gwacheon / Sundae Soup / 02-3679-1175
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Racecourse Duck House: Gwacheon-si Gungmal-ro / Grilled Sulfur Duck Clay / 02-502-7500
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Seorabul: Gwacheon Byeolyangsangga / Natural Pine Shabu Shabu / 02-502-8384
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Accommodation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Seoul Grand Park Nature Campground (opened in March ~ November): 159-1, Makgye-dong, Gwacheon-si / 02-500-7870
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Grace Hotel: 2, Seongyang Shopping Street, Gwacheon / 02-504-6700
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://hotelgrace6700.tnaru.net/web/index&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://hotelgrace6700.tnaru.net/web/index
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was written in August 2015, and may change afterwards. Please check before traveling.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ The information such as text, photos and videos used in this article is copyrighted by Korea Tourism Organization, so unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Седжонг, Республика Корея - Sejong Lake Park, день в городе</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/sejong-lake-park-a-day-in-the-city-26-ru/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 22:47:23 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/sejong-lake-park-a-day-in-the-city-26-ru/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-title=&#34;sejong-lake-park-a-day-in-the-city--26&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Серебряный пляж в Седжон Лейк Парк - Седжонг, Республика Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/97d74f26-f9df-4539-8b97-69a6ac4db265.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Серебряный пляж в Седжон Лейк Парк
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Sejong Lake Park, день в городе
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Седжонг, Республика Корея
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   В центре особого самоуправляющегося города Сечжона находится парк озера Седжон, место отдыха жителей Сечжона и место отдыха туристов. Вокруг широкого озера есть пять тематических парков, так что каждый может выбрать свое любимое место и отдохнуть.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Рядом с парком проложена велосипедная дорожка с полевыми цветами, проложенная под мостом Хандури, и место для кемпинга Hapgang Park, обеспечивающее комфорт с просторными и чистыми удобствами.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Седжонг Лейк Парк Централ Плаза - Седжонг, Республика Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/9fd50aea-bce0-41bb-be8e-8571340701d2.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Седжонг Лейк Парк Централ Плаза
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Sejong Lake Park, искусственное озеро, напоминающее природу
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Парк Седжон Лейк, расположенный в центре города, является крупнейшим в Корее и имеет размер 62 футбольных полей вместе взятых. Парк украшен пятью темами: Остров Фестивалей, Остров Сцена, Остров Уотер, Остров Уотер Флауэр и Остров Марш. На первый взгляд, он достаточно большой, чтобы осмотреться, но все просто. Разные парки предлагают разные ландшафты и укрытия.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Сценический остров с острова фестиваля - Седжонг, Республика Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/5eae923d-2795-419e-92b1-49738f247e47.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Сценический остров с острова фестиваля
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Когда вы войдете в центральный вход в парк Лейк, вы будете первым, кто увидит здание. Это сценический остров, установленный на мосту через центр озера. Он имеет 670 мест для проведения различных мероприятий и фестивалей. Когда никаких специальных мероприятий не проводится, это становится большим укрытием тени с видом на окружающий ландшафт.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Место для слушания, чтобы очистить реку Гум и отправить ее к озеру - Седжонг, Республика Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/22b17601-b216-4db1-bc41-15bc89707eb4.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Место для слушания, чтобы очистить реку Гум и отправить ее к озеру
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Есть также гидропоника вокруг озера, где вы можете насладиться прохладной водой со своими детьми. Первое место - квадратный фонтан под надземными воротами рядом с главным входом. Дети прыгают в поднимающиеся фонтаны, а взрослые укладывают коврики под повышенную тень. В парке также есть специальные помещения для управления качеством воды. Это слушающее растение, засаженное очищенным растением для очистки воды. Это водоочистное сооружение, которое использует природные ценности для того, чтобы очистить воду реки Геум и подать ее в озеро.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Семья играет с песком на серебряном пляже - Седжонг, Республика Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/2b4640db-5afd-4e41-8d83-73e05a5fe0f0.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Семья играет с песком на серебряном пляже
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Серебряный пляж, где вы можете сделать песчаную отмель на краю озера и играть как пляж, а остров для водных игр, где вы можете заняться водными видами спорта, такими как лодки, водные лыжи и серфинг, которые представляют собой маленькие яхты, - это красота озерного парка. Водные виды спорта проводятся с четверга по воскресенье, с мая по сентябрь каждый год.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Лягушка на серебряном пляже - Седжонг, Республика Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/afbfc166-3e4c-45e5-85d4-4a219f500d1f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Лягушка на серебряном пляже
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Есть также место с темой прохладного бриза, чтобы охладить жар. Это холм ветра, который мягко изгибает ветер. Это место, где вы хотите остаться и отдохнуть самостоятельно. Сядьте здесь и посмотрите на озеро, и весь парк в поле зрения. Вы не знаете, как провести время в комфорте зданий и холмов, расположенных через озеро. Но есть и недостатки. В этом пространстве нет тени, чтобы избежать жаркого летнего солнца. Возьмите широкую шляпу или зонтик. Если вы готовите прохладную ледяную воду, это хорошее место для дневного путешествия.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Water Play Island, где вы можете заняться песком и водными видами спорта - Седжонг, Республика Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/e4f273d7-03a9-4839-b742-156f7af365bf.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Water Play Island, где вы можете заняться песком и водными видами спорта
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Существует также пространство, которое показывает другой пейзаж от холмов ветра. Это восьмиугольный павильон «Jangnamjeong», расположенный в прибрежном традиционном парке. Его название взято из его прежнего места, старшего сына равнины. Посмотрев на парк, вы можете увидеть лес и небо. Равнина старшего сына заполнена зданиями, но лес, кажется, создал новую равнину.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Вид на озеро и город с холма ветра - Седжонг, Республика Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/9b41595e-7264-4cd4-b294-5ef1a5005dc2.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Вид на озеро и город с холма ветра
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Парк открыт с 5 до 23 часов, вход свободный. С заката до 22:00 освещаются ландшафтные огни, такие как водная сцена и мост Сехо. Фонтан в центре озера открыт на 20 минут в будние дни в 12 и 8 часов, а в 12, 4, 6 и 8 часов в праздничные дни. Там нет мусора в парке, как часть вывоз мусора. Минимизируйте свой мусор и заберите свой мусор назад.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;14&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Джангнамджонг в традиционном парке Уотерсайд - Седжонг, Республика Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/b0929ccf-bc55-4cfd-a6e0-639d693546f9.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Джангнамджонг в традиционном парке Уотерсайд
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Поездка по тропам полевых цветов на общественном велосипеде Pulling
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Мост Ханду-ри находится в 4 км от парка Лейк. Под мостом были набережные, велосипедные дорожки и прибрежные парки. До того, как был построен парк, он был известен своими прибрежными полевыми цветами. Даже сейчас дикие полевые цветы вместе с цветами, посаженными во время украшения парка, являются лучшими. В это время цветы раннего лета расцветают по обе стороны дороги. Нетоксичные маки разбрасывают красные цветы и желтые паразиты, обитающие в Северной Америке. Ganoderma lucidum, также известный как цветок яйца, застенчивый. Это пейзаж, который очень хорошо сочетается с мостом Хандури, на котором есть выдающийся закаленный рис.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Колония полевого цветка под мостом Хандури - Седжонг, Республика Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/7daa4a00-3f64-4372-b458-194a95f37f65.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Колония полевого цветка под мостом Хандури
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   В большом парке Сечжона ездить удобнее, чем гулять. Вы можете взять напрокат велосипед в общественном прокате велосипедов Oulling. В Седжон-Сити действует 29 висячих пунктов проката и 386 люлек, поэтому его можно бесплатно арендовать и вернуть в любую точку города. Вы можете проверить местоположение и положение пункта проката и колыбели в режиме реального времени через домашнюю страницу Oulling.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Велосипедная дорожка у цветочного поля - Седжонг, Республика Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/ee806b36-005b-4a04-ba2e-513fdabcc17b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Велосипедная дорожка у цветочного поля
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Публичные велосипеды могут использовать лица старше 19 лет со своим номером мобильного телефона. Аренда производится с использованием беспилотных информационных терминалов. Однодневный проездной стоит 1000 вон. Однако каждые 90 минут после сдачи в аренду вы должны возвращаться и повторно арендовать в терминале. Если без повторной аренды прошло более 90 минут, каждые 30 минут взимается дополнительная плата в размере 1000 вон.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Общественный прокат велосипедов в Сечжоне - Седжонг, Республика Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/1378442b-a07b-4b54-bbd3-090cfd38087d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Общественный прокат велосипедов в Сечжоне
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Даже для прогулок, кемпинга и отдыха ОК! Авто кемпинг Hapgang Park
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   30 минут езды по дороге от Лейк-парка до автокемпинга Hapgang Park. Этот кемпинг, который был недавно открыт в 2015 году, управляется городом Сечжон. Он расположен в месте слияния реки Geum и ручья Miho. В 4 районах имеется 102 авто кемпинга. Все объекты оснащены электрическим оборудованием, а также средствами безопасности, такими как огнетушители, спасатели и системы видеонаблюдения. Каждый участок может быть оборудован очень большой палаткой, а пространство между участками можно расслабить, чтобы вы могли наслаждаться уютным кемпингом.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Кемпинг с видом на реку - Седжонг, Республика Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/0bf77113-39f0-4185-b6a0-c8b851732df5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Кемпинг с видом на реку
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Набережная была создана для безопасной прогулки. Велосипедные дорожки в сельской местности пролегают по обеим сторонам кемпинга. Туристы могут взять напрокат велосипеды бесплатно. Свяжитесь с администрацией при входе в кемпинг. Вокруг площадки для кемпинга стоят большие зонтики, восьмиугольные тротуары и скамейки. Независимо от того, кемпинг, любой может войти, и все объекты, кроме спортивных сооружений и зон отдыха могут быть использованы бесплатно.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Авто кемпинг Hapgang Park - Седжонг, Республика Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/b7a54a10-1d09-45f1-9a06-d448282b4e88.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Авто кемпинг Hapgang Park
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Сайт кемпинга основан на онлайн-бронировании, но он также доступен в течение дня по телефону в будние дни и в низкий сезон. Базовая плата составляет 15 000 вон в будни и низкий сезон, 20 000 вон в выходные и высокий сезон, и 3000 вон добавляется при использовании электрических средств. На территории кемпинга нет магазинов, ресторанов или кафе, поэтому обязательно возьмите с собой необходимые вещи.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Широкая дорога и кемпинг - Седжонг, Республика Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/fa618673-a684-4a4c-ac3f-8acf2f8ee558.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Широкая дорога и кемпинг
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Информация о путешествии
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Седжон Лейк Парк
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Адрес: 216 Дасом-ро, особый самоуправляемый город Седжон
     &lt;br/&gt;
     дверь
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Общественный велосипед &#34;Ouling&#34;
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Адрес: 93, Guncheong-ro, Jochiwon-eup, специальный самоуправляемый город Седжон
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Контактное лицо: 1899-9161
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.sejongbike.kr/mainPageAction.do?process=mainPage&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.sejongbike.kr/mainPageAction.do?process=mainPage
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Авто кемпинг Hapgang Park
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Адрес: 329, Taesan-ro, Yeong-dong, Особый самоуправляемый город Сечжон.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Контакт: 044-862-5985
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Близлежащие рестораны
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Dabokjeong Корейский набор блюд: Hansiksik / 157 Hannuri-daero, Sejong City / 044-862-3371
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Мин: Чоу Мён / 27, Нури-ро, Седжон / 044-866-8933
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Хванг Вудже: Оори Мэтанг / 101-12, Тэсан-ро, Ён-дон, Сечонг-си / 044-866-1141
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Размещение
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Пансионат Geumgang под небом: 205-14, Donam 2-gil, Geumnam-myeon, Sejong City / 010-5548-4518
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Geumgang Природно-рекреационный лес: 110, Музей-музей леса, Geumnam-myeon, Sejong City / 041-635-7400
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Защита Чонгволл: 161, Кымсонг-ро, Чанггун-Мёон, Седжон-Сити / 044-881-7755
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ Приведенная выше информация была сделана в июне 2015 года. Впоследствии она может измениться, поэтому, пожалуйста, проверьте это перед поездкой.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Информация, такая как текст, фотографии и видео, используемые в этой статье, защищены авторским правом Корейской туристической организации, поэтому несанкционированное использование статьи запрещено.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sejong, République de Corée - Sejong Lake Park, une journée en ville</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/sejong-lake-park-a-day-in-the-city-26-fr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 22:44:35 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/sejong-lake-park-a-day-in-the-city-26-fr/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-title=&#34;sejong-lake-park-a-day-in-the-city--26&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Silver Beach à Sejong Lake Park - Sejong, République de Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/97d74f26-f9df-4539-8b97-69a6ac4db265.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Silver Beach à Sejong Lake Park
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Sejong Lake Park, une journée en ville
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Sejong, République de Corée
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Au centre de la ville autonome spéciale de Sejong, se trouve le parc du lac Sejong, un lieu de repos pour les citoyens de Sejong et un lieu de repos pour les touristes. Il y a cinq parcs à thème autour du grand lac, afin que chacun puisse choisir son espace préféré et se détendre.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Près du parc se trouve la piste cyclable bordée de fleurs sauvages qui passe sous le pont Handuri et le terrain de camping Hapgang Park Auto, qui garantit le confort avec des installations spacieuses et propres.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sejong Lake Park Central Plaza - Sejong, République de Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/9fd50aea-bce0-41bb-be8e-8571340701d2.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sejong Lake Park Central Plaza
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Sejong Lake Park, un lac artificiel ressemblant à la nature
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Le parc du lac Sejong, situé au centre de la ville, est le plus grand de Corée et a la taille de 62 terrains de football combinés. Le parc est décoré selon cinq thèmes: l&#39;île Festival, l&#39;île Stage, l&#39;île Water, l&#39;île Water Flower et l&#39;île Marsh. À première vue, il est assez grand pour jeter un coup d&#39;œil, mais les étapes sont faciles. Différents parcs offrent différents paysages et abris.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;L&#39;île de la scène depuis l&#39;île du Festival - Sejong, République de Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/5eae923d-2795-419e-92b1-49738f247e47.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     L&#39;île de la scène depuis l&#39;île du Festival
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Lorsque vous entrez dans l&#39;entrée centrale de Lake Park, vous serez le premier à voir le bâtiment. C&#39;est une île d&#39;étape installée sur le pont traversant le centre du lac. Il dispose de 670 sièges pour divers événements et festivals. Quand aucun événement spécial n&#39;est organisé, il devient un grand abri ombragé avec vue sur le paysage environnant.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Lieu d&#39;audience pour purifier la rivière Geum et l&#39;envoyer au lac - Sejong, République de Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/22b17601-b216-4db1-bc41-15bc89707eb4.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Lieu d&#39;audience pour purifier la rivière Geum et l&#39;envoyer au lac
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Il y a aussi des cultures hydroponiques autour du lac où vous pourrez profiter de l&#39;eau fraîche avec vos enfants. La première place est la fontaine carrée sous la porte surélevée à côté de l&#39;entrée principale. Les enfants sautent dans les fontaines montantes et les adultes déposent les nattes sous l&#39;ombre surélevée. Le parc dispose également d&#39;installations spéciales pour la gestion de la qualité de l&#39;eau. C&#39;est une plante d&#39;écoute plantée de plante purifiée pour nettoyer l&#39;eau. Il s&#39;agit d&#39;une installation de purification de l&#39;eau qui utilise des valeurs naturelles pour rendre l&#39;eau de la rivière Geum plus claire et la fournir au lac.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Famille jouant avec du sable sur la plage d&#39;argent - Sejong, République de Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/2b4640db-5afd-4e41-8d83-73e05a5fe0f0.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Famille jouant avec du sable sur la plage d&#39;argent
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   La plage d&#39;argent où vous pouvez faire un banc de sable au bord du lac et jouer comme une plage, et l&#39;île de jeux aquatiques où vous pourrez pratiquer des sports nautiques comme le canot, le ski nautique et le surf, qui sont de petits yachts, sont la beauté du parc du lac. Les expériences nautiques ont lieu du jeudi au dimanche, de mai à septembre de chaque année.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Grenouille sur la plage d&#39;argent - Sejong, République de Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/afbfc166-3e4c-45e5-85d4-4a219f500d1f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Grenouille sur la plage d&#39;argent
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Il y a aussi un espace sur le thème de la brise fraîche pour refroidir la chaleur. C&#39;est une colline de vent qui incarne le vent dans une courbe douce. C&#39;est un endroit où vous voulez rester et vous reposer seul. Asseyez-vous ici et regardez le lac et tout le parc est en vue. Vous ne savez pas comment passer votre temps dans le confort des bâtiments et des collines situés de l&#39;autre côté du lac. Mais il y a aussi des inconvénients. Il n&#39;y a pas d&#39;ombre dans cet espace pour échapper au chaud soleil d&#39;été. Prenez un chapeau large ou un parasol. Si vous préparez de l&#39;eau glacée fraîche, c&#39;est un bon endroit pour se reposer pour une excursion d&#39;une journée.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Water Play Island où vous pourrez faire du sable et des sports nautiques - Sejong, République de Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/e4f273d7-03a9-4839-b742-156f7af365bf.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Water Play Island où vous pourrez faire du sable et des sports nautiques
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Il y a aussi un espace qui montre un paysage différent des collines du vent. Il s&#39;agit du pavillon octogonal «Jangnamjeong» situé dans le parc traditionnel au bord de l&#39;eau. Son nom vient de son ancien lieu, le fils aîné de la plaine. En regardant le parc, vous pouvez voir la forêt et le ciel. La plaine du fils aîné est remplie de bâtiments, mais la forêt semble avoir fait une nouvelle plaine.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Vue sur le lac et la ville depuis la colline du vent - Sejong, République de Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/9b41595e-7264-4cd4-b294-5ef1a5005dc2.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Vue sur le lac et la ville depuis la colline du vent
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Le parc est ouvert de 5 h à 23 h et l&#39;entrée est gratuite. Du coucher du soleil à 22h00, les lumières du paysage telles que la scène de l&#39;eau et le pont Seho sont illuminées. La fontaine au centre du lac est ouverte pendant 20 minutes en semaine à 12 et 8 heures, et à 12, 4, 6 et 8 heures les jours fériés. Il n&#39;y a pas de déchets dans le parc dans le cadre de la récupération des ordures. Minimisez vos déchets et récupérez vos déchets.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;14&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Jangnamjeong dans le parc traditionnel au bord de l&#39;eau - Sejong, République de Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/b0929ccf-bc55-4cfd-a6e0-639d693546f9.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Jangnamjeong dans le parc traditionnel au bord de l&#39;eau
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Sur les pistes de fleurs sauvages en vélo public `` Pulling &#39;&#39;
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Le pont Handu-ri est à 4 km du Lake Park. Sous le pont, il y avait des promenades, des pistes cyclables et des parcs au bord de la rivière. Il était célèbre pour ses fleurs sauvages au bord de la rivière avant la construction du parc. Même maintenant, les fleurs sauvages sauvages ainsi que les fleurs plantées lors de la décoration du parc sont les meilleures. A cette époque, les fleurs du début de l&#39;été sont en pleine floraison des deux côtés de la route. Les coquelicots non toxiques dispersent des fleurs rouges et des parasites jaunes originaires d&#39;Amérique du Nord. Ganoderma lucidum, également connue sous le nom de fleur d&#39;oeuf, est timide. C&#39;est un paysage qui va très bien avec le pont Handuri, qui a un riz tempéré exceptionnel.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Colonie de fleurs sauvages sous le pont Handuri - Sejong, République de Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/7daa4a00-3f64-4372-b458-194a95f37f65.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Colonie de fleurs sauvages sous le pont Handuri
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Le grand parc de Sejong est plus confortable à conduire qu&#39;à se promener. Vous pouvez louer un vélo à «Oulling», un lieu public de location de vélos. Sejong City exploite 29 stations de location suspendues et 386 berceaux, il est donc gratuit de louer et de retourner n&#39;importe où dans la ville. Vous pouvez vérifier l&#39;emplacement et la situation de la station de location et du berceau en temps réel via la page d&#39;accueil d&#39;Oulling.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Piste cyclable près du champ de fleurs - Sejong, République de Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/ee806b36-005b-4a04-ba2e-513fdabcc17b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Piste cyclable près du champ de fleurs
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Les vélos publics peuvent être utilisés par toute personne âgée de plus de 19 ans avec son numéro de téléphone portable. Les locations se font via des terminaux d&#39;information sans pilote. Le pass d&#39;une journée coûte 1000 won. Cependant, toutes les 90 minutes après la location, vous devez retourner et relouer au terminal. S&#39;il est supérieur à 90 minutes sans relocation, un supplément de 1 000 won sera facturé toutes les 30 minutes.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Location de vélos publics à Sejong City - Sejong, République de Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/1378442b-a07b-4b54-bbd3-090cfd38087d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Location de vélos publics à Sejong City
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Même pour la marche, le camping et la détente OK! Terrain de camping automobile Hapgang Park
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   30 minutes en voiture le long de la route de Lake Park à Hapgang Park Auto Camping Ground. Ce camping, nouvellement exploité en 2015, est géré par la ville de Sejong. Il est situé au point de rencontre de la rivière Geum et du ruisseau Miho. Il y a 102 sites de camping auto dans 4 districts. Tous les sites sont équipés d&#39;installations électriques, ainsi que d&#39;installations de sécurité telles que des extincteurs, des sauveteurs et des caméras de surveillance. Chaque site peut être équipé d&#39;une très grande tente, et l&#39;espace entre les sites peut être détendu, pour que vous puissiez profiter d&#39;un camping confortable.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Camping avec vue sur la rivière - Sejong, République de Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/0bf77113-39f0-4185-b6a0-c8b851732df5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Camping avec vue sur la rivière
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   La promenade au bord de la rivière a été créée pour marcher en toute sécurité. Des pistes cyclables de campagne longent les deux côtés du terrain de camping. Les campeurs peuvent louer des vélos gratuitement. Contactez le bureau de gestion lors de l&#39;entrée du camping. Il y a de grands parasols, une chaussée octogonale et des bancs tout autour du camping. Quel que soit le camping, tout le monde peut y entrer et toutes les installations, à l&#39;exception des installations sportives et des aires de repos, peuvent être utilisées gratuitement.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Site de camping automobile Hapgang Park - Sejong, République de Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/b7a54a10-1d09-45f1-9a06-d448282b4e88.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Site de camping automobile Hapgang Park
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Le camping est basé sur des réservations en ligne, mais il est également disponible le jour par téléphone sur demande en semaine et en basse saison. Le tarif de base est de 15 000 wons en semaine et en basse saison, 20 000 wons le week-end et en haute saison, et 3 000 wons sont ajoutés lors de l&#39;utilisation des installations électriques. Il n&#39;y a pas de magasins, de restaurants ou de cafés sur le terrain de camping, alors assurez-vous d&#39;apporter les articles nécessaires avec vous.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Large route et aire de camping - Sejong, République de Corée (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/fa618673-a684-4a4c-ac3f-8acf2f8ee558.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Large route et aire de camping
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Info voyage
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Parc du lac Sejong
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Adresse: 216 Dasom-ro, ville autonome spéciale de Sejong
     &lt;br/&gt;
     porte
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      P
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Adresse: 93, Guncheong-ro, Jochiwon-eup, Sejong Special Self-Governing City
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Contact: 1899-9161
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.sejongbike.kr/mainPageAction.do?process=mainPage&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.sejongbike.kr/mainPageAction.do?process=mainPage
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Terrain de camping automobile Hapgang Park
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Adresse: 329, Taesan-ro, Yeong-dong, Sejong Special Self-Governing City
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Contact: 044-862-5985
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Restaurants à proximité
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Dabokjeong Korean Set Repas: Hansiksik / 157 Hannuri-daero, Sejong City / 044-862-3371
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Ming: Chow Myeon / 27, Nuri-ro, Sejong-si / 044-866-8933
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Hwang Wooje: Oori Maetang / 101-12, Taesan-ro, Yeong-dong, Sejong-si / 044-866-1141
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Hébergement
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Pension Geumgang sous le ciel: 205-14, Donam 2-gil, Geumnam-myeon, Sejong City / 010-5548-4518
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Geumgang Natural Recreation Forest: 110, Forest Museum Museum, Geumnam-myeon, Sejong City / 041-635-7400
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Cheongwall Vival Defense: 161, Geumsong-ro, Janggun-myeon, Sejong City / 044-881-7755
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ Les informations ci-dessus ont été fournies en juin 2015. Elles peuvent changer par la suite, veuillez donc vérifier avant de voyager.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Les informations telles que le texte, les photos et les vidéos utilisées dans cet article sont protégées par les droits d&#39;auteur de l&#39;Organisation coréenne du tourisme, de sorte que l&#39;utilisation non autorisée de l&#39;article est interdite.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sejong, República de Corea - Sejong Lake Park, un día en la ciudad</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/sejong-lake-park-a-day-in-the-city-26-es/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 22:41:47 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/sejong-lake-park-a-day-in-the-city-26-es/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-title=&#34;sejong-lake-park-a-day-in-the-city--26&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Playa de plata en el parque del lago Sejong - Sejong, República de Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/97d74f26-f9df-4539-8b97-69a6ac4db265.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Playa de plata en el parque del lago Sejong
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Sejong Lake Park, un día en la ciudad
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Sejong, República de Corea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   En el centro de la ciudad especial autónoma de Sejong, se encuentra el parque del lago Sejong, un lugar de descanso para los ciudadanos de Sejong y un lugar de descanso para los turistas. Hay cinco parques temáticos alrededor del amplio lago, por lo que cualquiera puede elegir su espacio favorito y relajarse.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Cerca del parque se encuentra el sendero para bicicletas con flores silvestres que se extiende bajo el puente Handuri y el Hapgang Park Auto Camping Ground, que garantiza la comodidad con instalaciones amplias y limpias.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Plaza central del parque del lago Sejong - Sejong, República de Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/9fd50aea-bce0-41bb-be8e-8571340701d2.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Plaza central del parque del lago Sejong
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Sejong Lake Park, un lago artificial parecido a la naturaleza
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   El parque del lago Sejong, ubicado en el centro de la ciudad, es el más grande de Corea y tiene el tamaño de 62 campos de fútbol combinados. El parque está decorado con cinco temas: Festival Island, Stage Island, Water Island, Water Flower Island y Marsh Island. A primera vista, es lo suficientemente grande como para echar un vistazo, pero los pasos son fáciles. Diferentes parques ofrecen diferentes paisajes y refugio.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Stage Island de la Isla Festival - Sejong, República de Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/5eae923d-2795-419e-92b1-49738f247e47.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Stage Island de la Isla Festival
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Cuando ingrese a la entrada central de Lake Park, será el primero en ver el edificio. Es una isla de escenario instalada en el puente que cruza el centro del lago. Cuenta con 670 asientos como sede de diversos eventos y festivales. Cuando no se realizan eventos especiales, se convierte en un gran refugio de sombra con vistas del paisaje circundante.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Audiencia para purificar el río Geum y enviarlo al lago - Sejong, República de Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/22b17601-b216-4db1-bc41-15bc89707eb4.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Audiencia para purificar el río Geum y enviarlo al lago
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   También hay hidroponía alrededor del lago donde puede disfrutar del agua fría con sus hijos. El primer lugar es la fuente cuadrada debajo de la puerta elevada al lado de la entrada principal. Los niños saltan a las fuentes ascendentes y los adultos colocan las esteras bajo la sombra elevada. El parque también cuenta con instalaciones especiales para la gestión de la calidad del agua. Es una planta de escucha plantada con planta purificada para limpiar el agua. Es una instalación de purificación de agua que utiliza valores naturales para aclarar el agua del río Geum y suministrarla al lago.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Familia jugando con arena en la playa plateada - Sejong, República de Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/2b4640db-5afd-4e41-8d83-73e05a5fe0f0.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Familia jugando con arena en la playa plateada
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   La playa plateada donde puedes hacer un banco de arena en el borde del lago y jugar como una playa, y la isla de juegos acuáticos donde puedes disfrutar de deportes acuáticos como el bote, el esquí acuático y el surf, que son pequeños yates, son la belleza. del parque del lago. Las experiencias de deportes acuáticos se llevan a cabo de jueves a domingo, de mayo a septiembre de cada año.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Rana en la playa plateada - Sejong, República de Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/afbfc166-3e4c-45e5-85d4-4a219f500d1f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Rana en la playa plateada
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   También hay un espacio con el tema de la brisa fresca para enfriar el calor. Es una colina de viento que encarna el viento en una curva suave. Es un lugar donde desea quedarse y descansar por su cuenta. Siéntate aquí y mira el lago y todo el parque está a la vista. No sabe cómo pasar el tiempo en la comodidad de los edificios y las colinas que se encuentran al otro lado del lago. Pero también hay desventajas. No hay sombra en este espacio para escapar del cálido sol del verano. Tome un sombrero ancho o sombrilla. Si prepara agua helada fría, es un buen lugar para descansar durante una excursión de un día.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Water Play Island donde puedes experimentar la arena y los deportes acuáticos. - Sejong, República de Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/e4f273d7-03a9-4839-b742-156f7af365bf.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Water Play Island donde puedes experimentar la arena y los deportes acuáticos.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   También hay un espacio que muestra un paisaje diferente de las colinas de viento. Es el pabellón octogonal &#39;Jangnamjeong&#39; ubicado en el parque tradicional ribereño. Su nombre está tomado de su antiguo lugar, el hijo mayor llano. Mirando hacia el parque, puedes ver el bosque y el cielo. La planicie del hijo mayor está llena de edificios, pero el bosque parece haber hecho una planicie nueva.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Vista del lago y la ciudad vista desde la colina del viento - Sejong, República de Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/9b41595e-7264-4cd4-b294-5ef1a5005dc2.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Vista del lago y la ciudad vista desde la colina del viento
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   El parque está abierto de 5 am a 11 pm y la entrada es gratuita. Desde el atardecer hasta las 10:00 p. M., Se iluminan las luces del paisaje, como el escenario de agua y el Puente Seho. La fuente en el centro del lago está abierta durante 20 minutos de lunes a viernes a las 12 y 8 en punto, y a las 12, 4, 6 y 8 en días festivos. No hay basura en el parque como parte de la recogida de basura. Minimice su basura y llévela de vuelta.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;14&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Jangnamjeong en Waterside Traditional Park - Sejong, República de Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/b0929ccf-bc55-4cfd-a6e0-639d693546f9.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Jangnamjeong en Waterside Traditional Park
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Montar senderos de flores silvestres en la bicicleta pública &#39;Pulling&#39;
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   El puente Handu-ri está a 4 km del Lake Park. Debajo del puente había paseos marítimos, ciclovías y parques ribereños. Era famoso por las flores silvestres de la ribera antes de que se construyera el parque. Incluso ahora, las flores silvestres silvestres junto con las flores plantadas mientras decoran el parque son las mejores. En este momento, las flores de principios de verano están en plena floración a ambos lados del camino. Las amapolas no tóxicas esparcen flores rojas y parásitos amarillos nativos de América del Norte. Ganoderma lucidum, también conocida como flor de huevo, es tímidamente tímida. Es un paisaje que combina muy bien con el puente Handuri, que tiene un excelente arroz templado.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Colonia de flores silvestres bajo el puente Handuri - Sejong, República de Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/7daa4a00-3f64-4372-b458-194a95f37f65.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Colonia de flores silvestres bajo el puente Handuri
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   El gran parque de Sejong es más cómodo para pasear que para pasear. Puede alquilar una bicicleta en &#39;Oulling&#39;, un lugar público de alquiler de bicicletas. Sejong City opera 29 estaciones de alquiler colgantes y 386 cunas, por lo que es gratis alquilar y regresar a cualquier lugar de la ciudad. Puede verificar la ubicación y la situación de la estación de alquiler y la cuna en tiempo real a través de la página de inicio de Oulling.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Carril bici por el campo de flores - Sejong, República de Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/ee806b36-005b-4a04-ba2e-513fdabcc17b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Carril bici por el campo de flores
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Las bicicletas públicas pueden ser utilizadas por cualquier persona mayor de 19 años con su número de teléfono móvil. Los alquileres se realizan utilizando terminales de información no tripuladas. El pase de un día cuesta 1,000 wones. Sin embargo, cada 90 minutos después del alquiler, debe regresar y volver a alquilar en la terminal. Si son más de 90 minutos sin volver a alquilar, se cobrará una tarifa adicional de 1,000 wones cada 30 minutos.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Alquiler de bicicletas públicas de la ciudad de Sejong - Sejong, República de Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/1378442b-a07b-4b54-bbd3-090cfd38087d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Alquiler de bicicletas públicas de la ciudad de Sejong
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Incluso para caminar, acampar y relajarse, ¡está bien! Hapgang Park Auto Camping Ground
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   A 30 minutos en coche por la carretera desde Lake Park hasta Hapgang Park Auto Camping Ground. Este camping, que fue operado recientemente en 2015, es administrado por la ciudad de Sejong. Se encuentra en el punto donde se encuentran el río Geum y el arroyo Miho. Hay 102 sitios para auto acampar en 4 distritos. Todos los sitios están equipados con instalaciones eléctricas, así como instalaciones de seguridad como extintores de incendios, socorristas y CCTV. Cada sitio puede estar equipado con una carpa muy grande, y el espacio entre los sitios puede ser relajado, para que pueda disfrutar de un campamento acogedor.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Camping con vista al rio - Sejong, República de Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/0bf77113-39f0-4185-b6a0-c8b851732df5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Camping con vista al rio
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   El paseo ribereño ha sido creado para caminar con seguridad. Los senderos para bicicletas de campo corren a ambos lados del campamento. Los campistas pueden alquilar bicicletas de forma gratuita. Póngase en contacto con la oficina de administración al ingresar al campamento. Hay grandes sombrillas, pavimento octogonal y bancos alrededor del campamento. Independientemente del campamento, cualquiera puede ingresar, y todas las instalaciones además de las instalaciones deportivas y las áreas de descanso se pueden usar de forma gratuita.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Camping Hapgang Park Auto - Sejong, República de Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/b7a54a10-1d09-45f1-9a06-d448282b4e88.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Camping Hapgang Park Auto
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   El sitio para acampar se basa en reservas en línea, pero también está disponible durante el día mediante consultas telefónicas durante la semana y en temporada baja. La tarifa básica es de 15,000 wones entre semana y temporada baja, 20,000 wones los fines de semana y temporada alta, y se agregan 3,000 wones cuando se utilizan instalaciones eléctricas. No hay tiendas, restaurantes o cafeterías en el camping, así que asegúrese de llevar los artículos necesarios.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Amplia carretera y zona de acampada - Sejong, República de Corea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/fa618673-a684-4a4c-ac3f-8acf2f8ee558.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Amplia carretera y zona de acampada
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Información de viaje
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Parque del lago Sejong
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Dirección: 216 Dasom-ro, Sejong Ciudad especial autónoma
     &lt;br/&gt;
     puerta
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Bicicleta pública &#34;Ouling&#34;
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Dirección: 93, Guncheong-ro, Jochiwon-eup, Sejong Special Self-Governing City
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Contacto: 1899-9161
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.sejongbike.kr/mainPageAction.do?process=mainPage&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.sejongbike.kr/mainPageAction.do?process=mainPage
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Hapgang Park Auto Camping Ground
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Dirección: 329, Taesan-ro, Yeong-dong, Sejong Ciudad especial autónoma
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Contacto: 044-862-5985
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Restaurantes cercanos
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Comidas del conjunto coreano Dabokjeong: Hansiksik / 157 Hannuri-daero, Sejong City / 044-862-3371
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Ming: Chow Myeon / 27, Nuri-ro, Sejong-si / 044-866-8933
    &lt;br/&gt;
    H
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Alojamiento
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Pensión Geumgang bajo el cielo: 205-14, Donam 2-gil, Geumnam-myeon, Sejong City / 010-5548-4518
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Geumgang Natural Recreation Forest: 110, Museo del Museo del Bosque, Geumnam-myeon, Ciudad Sejong / 041-635-7400
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Defensa Vival de Cheongwall: 161, Geumsong-ro, Janggun-myeon, Ciudad Sejong / 044-881-7755
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ La información anterior se realizó en junio de 2015. Puede cambiar después, así que verifique antes de viajar.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ La información como texto, fotos y videos utilizados en este artículo tiene copyright de la Organización de Turismo de Corea, por lo que está prohibido el uso no autorizado del artículo.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sejong, Republik Korea - Sejong Lake Park, ein Tag in der Stadt</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/sejong-lake-park-a-day-in-the-city-26-de/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 22:39:06 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/sejong-lake-park-a-day-in-the-city-26-de/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-title=&#34;sejong-lake-park-a-day-in-the-city--26&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Silberstrand im Sejong Lake Park - Sejong, Republik Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/97d74f26-f9df-4539-8b97-69a6ac4db265.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Silberstrand im Sejong Lake Park
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Sejong Lake Park, ein Tag in der Stadt
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Sejong, Republik Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Im Zentrum der Sejong Special Self-Governing City befindet sich der Sejong Lake Park, ein Rastplatz für Sejong-Bürger und ein Rastplatz für Touristen. Rund um den breiten See gibt es fünf Themenparks, sodass jeder seinen Lieblingsplatz auswählen und sich entspannen kann.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In der Nähe des Parks befindet sich der Wildblumen-Radweg, der unter der Handuri-Brücke verläuft, und der Hapgang Park Auto Camping Ground, der Komfort mit geräumigen und sauberen Einrichtungen gewährleistet.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sejong Lake Park Central Plaza - Sejong, Republik Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/9fd50aea-bce0-41bb-be8e-8571340701d2.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sejong Lake Park Central Plaza
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Sejong Lake Park, ein künstlicher See, der der Natur ähnelt
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Der Sejong Lake Park im Zentrum der Stadt ist der größte in Korea und hat die Größe von 62 Fußballfeldern zusammen. Der Park ist mit fünf Themen dekoriert: Festival Island, Stage Island, Water Island, Water Flower Island und Marsh Island. Auf den ersten Blick ist es groß genug, um sich umzuschauen, aber die Schritte sind einfach. Verschiedene Parks bieten unterschiedliche Landschaften und Schutz.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Stage Island von der Festival Island - Sejong, Republik Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/5eae923d-2795-419e-92b1-49738f247e47.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Stage Island von der Festival Island
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Wenn Sie den zentralen Eingang des Lake Park betreten, sehen Sie als erster das Gebäude. Es ist eine Bühneninsel, die auf der Brücke über die Mitte des Sees installiert ist. Es verfügt über 670 Sitzplätze als Veranstaltungsort für verschiedene Veranstaltungen und Festivals. Wenn keine besonderen Veranstaltungen stattfinden, wird es zu einem großen Schattenschutz mit Blick auf die umliegende Landschaft.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Hörplatz, um den Geum River zu reinigen und zum See zu schicken - Sejong, Republik Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/22b17601-b216-4db1-bc41-15bc89707eb4.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Hörplatz, um den Geum River zu reinigen und zum See zu schicken
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Es gibt auch Hydrokultur rund um den See, wo Sie mit Ihren Kindern das kühle Wasser genießen können. Der erste Platz ist der quadratische Brunnen unter dem erhöhten Tor neben dem Haupteingang. Die Kinder springen in die aufsteigenden Brunnen, und die Erwachsenen legen die Matten im erhöhten Schatten ab. Der Park verfügt auch über spezielle Einrichtungen für das Wasserqualitätsmanagement. Es ist eine Hörpflanze, die mit gereinigten Pflanzen bepflanzt ist, um das Wasser zu reinigen. Es handelt sich um eine Wasseraufbereitungsanlage, die natürliche Werte verwendet, um das Wasser des Geum River klarer zu machen und es dem See zuzuführen.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Familie spielt mit Sand am silbernen Strand - Sejong, Republik Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/2b4640db-5afd-4e41-8d83-73e05a5fe0f0.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Familie spielt mit Sand am silbernen Strand
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Der silberne Strand, an dem Sie eine Sandbank am Rande des Sees bauen und wie ein Strand spielen können, und die Wasserspielinsel, auf der Sie Wassersportarten wie Beiboot, Wasserski und Surfen, kleine Yachten, ausüben können, sind die Schönheit des Seeparks. Wassersport-Erlebnisse finden jedes Jahr von Donnerstag bis Sonntag von Mai bis September statt.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Frosch am silbernen Strand - Sejong, Republik Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/afbfc166-3e4c-45e5-85d4-4a219f500d1f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Frosch am silbernen Strand
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Es gibt auch einen Raum mit dem Thema kühle Brise, um die Hitze abzukühlen. Es ist ein Windhügel, der den Wind in einer sanften Kurve verkörpert. Es ist ein Ort, an dem Sie alleine bleiben und sich ausruhen möchten. Sitzen Sie hier und schauen Sie auf den See und der gesamte Park ist in Sicht. Sie wissen nicht, wie Sie Ihre Zeit im Komfort von Gebäuden und Hügeln verbringen sollen, die sich auf der anderen Seite des Sees befinden. Es gibt aber auch Nachteile. In diesem Raum gibt es keinen Schatten, um der heißen Sommersonne zu entkommen. Nehmen Sie einen breiten Hut oder Sonnenschirm. Wenn Sie kühles Eiswasser zubereiten, ist dies ein guter Ort, um sich für einen Tagesausflug auszuruhen.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Wasserspielinsel, auf der Sie Sand- und Wassersport betreiben können - Sejong, Republik Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/e4f273d7-03a9-4839-b742-156f7af365bf.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Wasserspielinsel, auf der Sie Sand- und Wassersport betreiben können
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Es gibt auch einen Raum, der eine andere Landschaft zeigt als die Hügel des Windes. Es ist der achteckige Pavillon &#39;Jangnamjeong&#39; im traditionellen Park am Wasser. Sein Name stammt von seinem früheren Ort, der ältesten Sohnebene. Wenn Sie zum Park hinaufblicken, können Sie den Wald und den Himmel sehen. Die älteste Sohnebene ist voller Gebäude, aber der Wald scheint eine neue Ebene geschaffen zu haben.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Blick auf den See und die Stadt vom Windhügel aus gesehen - Sejong, Republik Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/9b41595e-7264-4cd4-b294-5ef1a5005dc2.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Blick auf den See und die Stadt vom Windhügel aus gesehen
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Der Park ist von 5 bis 23 Uhr geöffnet und der Eintritt ist frei. Von Sonnenuntergang bis 22:00 Uhr werden die Landschaftslichter wie die Wasserbühne und die Seho-Brücke beleuchtet. Der Brunnen in der Mitte des Sees ist an Wochentagen um 12 und 8 Uhr und an Feiertagen um 12, 4, 6 und 8 Uhr für 20 Minuten geöffnet. Es gibt keinen Müll im Park als Teil der Müllrücknahme. Minimieren Sie Ihren Müll und nehmen Sie Ihren Müll zurück.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;14&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Jangnamjeong im Waterside Traditional Park - Sejong, Republik Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/b0929ccf-bc55-4cfd-a6e0-639d693546f9.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Jangnamjeong im Waterside Traditional Park
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Wildblumenpfade mit dem öffentlichen Fahrrad &#39;Pulling&#39; fahren
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Die Handu-ri-Brücke liegt 4 km vom Lake Park entfernt. Unter der Brücke gab es Promenaden, Radwege und Flussparks. Es war berühmt für Wildblumen am Fluss, bevor der Park gebaut wurde. Sogar jetzt sind die wilden Wildblumen zusammen mit den Blumen, die beim Dekorieren des Parks gepflanzt wurden, die besten. Zu dieser Zeit blühen die Blüten des Frühsommers auf beiden Seiten der Straße in voller Blüte. Ungiftige Mohnblumen streuen rote Blüten und gelbe Parasiten aus Nordamerika. Ganoderma lucidum, auch als Eierblume bekannt, ist schüchtern schüchtern. Es ist eine Landschaft, die sehr gut zur Handuri-Brücke passt, die hervorragenden gehärteten Reis hat.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Wildblumenkolonie unter der Handuri-Brücke - Sejong, Republik Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/7daa4a00-3f64-4372-b458-194a95f37f65.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Wildblumenkolonie unter der Handuri-Brücke
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Sejongs großer Park ist bequemer zu fahren als herumzulaufen. Sie können ein Fahrrad bei &#39;Oulling&#39;, einem öffentlichen Fahrradverleih, mieten. Sejong City betreibt 29 hängende Mietstationen und 386 Wiegen, sodass Sie überall in der Stadt kostenlos mieten und zurückkehren können. Über die Oulling-Homepage können Sie den Standort und die Situation der Mietstation und der Ladestation in Echtzeit überprüfen.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Radweg am Blumenfeld - Sejong, Republik Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/ee806b36-005b-4a04-ba2e-513fdabcc17b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Radweg am Blumenfeld
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Öffentliche Fahrräder können von jedem über 19 Jahren mit seiner Handynummer benutzt werden. Die Vermietung erfolgt über unbemannte Informationsterminals. Die Tageskarte kostet 1.000 Won. Nach der Anmietung müssen Sie jedoch alle 90 Minuten am Terminal zurückkehren und erneut mieten. Wenn es mehr als 90 Minuten ohne Neuvermietung ist, wird alle 30 Minuten eine zusätzliche Gebühr von 1.000 Won berechnet.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Öffentlicher Fahrradverleih der Stadt Sejong - Sejong, Republik Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/1378442b-a07b-4b54-bbd3-090cfd38087d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Öffentlicher Fahrradverleih der Stadt Sejong
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Auch zum Spazierengehen, Zelten und Entspannen OK! Hapgang Park Auto Campingplatz
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   30 Autominuten entlang der Straße vom Lake Park zum Hapgang Park Auto Camping Ground. Dieser Campingplatz, der 2015 neu betrieben wurde, wird von Sejong City verwaltet. Es befindet sich an dem Punkt, an dem sich Geum River und Miho Stream treffen. Es gibt 102 Autocampingplätze in 4 Bezirken. Alle Standorte sind mit elektrischen Einrichtungen sowie Sicherheitseinrichtungen wie Feuerlöschern, Rettungsschwimmern und Videoüberwachungsgeräten ausgestattet. Jeder Platz kann mit einem sehr großen Zelt ausgestattet werden, und der Raum zwischen den Plätzen kann entspannt werden, so dass Sie gemütliches Camping genießen können.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Camping mit Blick auf den Fluss - Sejong, Republik Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/0bf77113-39f0-4185-b6a0-c8b851732df5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Camping mit Blick auf den Fluss
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Die Uferpromenade wurde geschaffen, um sicher zu gehen. Auf beiden Seiten des Campingplatzes verlaufen Radwege auf dem Land. Wohnmobile können kostenlos Fahrräder mieten. Wenden Sie sich beim Betreten des Campingplatzes an die Geschäftsstelle. Rund um den Campingplatz gibt es große Sonnenschirme, achteckige Gehwege und Bänke. Unabhängig vom Campingplatz kann jeder eintreten und alle Einrichtungen außer Sportanlagen und Rastplätzen können kostenlos genutzt werden.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Hapgang Park Auto Campingplatz - Sejong, Republik Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/b7a54a10-1d09-45f1-9a06-d448282b4e88.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Hapgang Park Auto Campingplatz
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Der Campingplatz basiert auf Online-Reservierungen, ist aber auch tagsüber telefonisch an Wochentagen und in der Nebensaison verfügbar. Die Grundgebühr beträgt 15.000 Won an Wochentagen und in der Nebensaison, 20.000 Won an Wochenenden und in der Hochsaison und 3.000 Won werden bei Nutzung elektrischer Einrichtungen hinzugefügt. Auf dem Campingplatz gibt es keine Geschäfte, Restaurants oder Cafés. Bringen Sie daher unbedingt die erforderlichen Gegenstände mit.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Breite Straße und Campingplatz - Sejong, Republik Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/fa618673-a684-4a4c-ac3f-8acf2f8ee558.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Breite Straße und Campingplatz
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Reiseinformationen
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Sejong Lake Park
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Adresse: 216 Dasom-ro, Sejong Besondere selbstverwaltete Stadt
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Tür
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Öffentliches Fahrrad ‘Ouling’
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Adresse: 93, Guncheong-ro, Jochiwon-eup, Sejong Special Self-Governing City
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Kontakt: 1899-9161
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.sejongbike.kr/mainPageAction.do?process=mainPage&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.sejongbike.kr/mainPageAction.do?process=mainPage
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Hapgang Park Auto Campingplatz
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Adresse: 329, Taesan-ro, Yeong-dong, Sejong Besondere selbstverwaltete Stadt
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Kontakt: 044-862-5985
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Restaurants in der Nähe
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Dabokjeong Koreanische Mahlzeiten: Hansiksik / 157 Hannuri-daero, Sejong City / 044-862-3371
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Ming: Chow Myeon / 27, Nuri-ro, Sejong-si / 044-866-8933
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Hwang Wooje: Oori Maetang / 101-12, Taesan-ro, Yeong-dong, Sejong-si / 044-866-1141
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Unterkunft
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Geumgang Pension unter freiem Himmel: 205-14, Donam 2-Gil, Geumnam-Myeon, Sejong City / 010-5548-4518
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Geumgang Natural Recreation Forest: 110, Waldmuseum Museum, Geumnam-myeon, Stadt Sejong / 041-635-7400
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Cheongwall Vival Defense: 161, Geumsong-ro, Janggun-myeon, Stadt Sejong / 044-881-7755
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ Die oben genannten Informationen wurden im Juni 2015 erstellt. Sie können sich später ändern. Bitte überprüfen Sie dies, bevor Sie reisen.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Informationen wie Text, Fotos und Videos, die in diesem Artikel verwendet werden, sind von der Korea Tourism Organization urheberrechtlich geschützt. Daher ist die unbefugte Verwendung des Artikels verboten.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>韩国世宗 - 世宗湖公园，城市一日游</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/sejong-lake-park-a-day-in-the-city-26-zh-cn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 22:36:23 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/sejong-lake-park-a-day-in-the-city-26-zh-cn/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-title=&#34;sejong-lake-park-a-day-in-the-city--26&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;世宗湖公园的银滩 - 韩国世宗 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/97d74f26-f9df-4539-8b97-69a6ac4db265.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    世宗湖公园的银滩
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   世宗湖公园，城市一日游
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    韩国世宗
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   世宗特别自治市的中心有世宗湖公园，世宗市民的休憩处和游客的休憩处。 宽阔的湖泊周围有五个主题公园，因此任何人都可以选择自己喜欢的空间并放松身心。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   靠近公园的是在Handuri桥和Hapgang公园汽车露营地下方的野花束缚的自行车道，宽敞，整洁的设施可确保舒适性。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;世宗湖公园中央广场 - 韩国世宗 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/9fd50aea-bce0-41bb-be8e-8571340701d2.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     世宗湖公园中央广场
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   世宗湖公园，与大自然相似的人工湖
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   世宗湖公园位于城市中心，是韩国最大的公园，面积总计62个足球场。 公园装饰着五个主题：节日岛，舞台岛，水岛，水花岛和沼泽岛。 乍一看，它足够大，可以四处看看，但是步骤很简单。 不同的公园提供不同的景观和庇护所。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;节日岛的舞台岛 - 韩国世宗 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/5eae923d-2795-419e-92b1-49738f247e47.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     节日岛的舞台岛
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   当您进入湖公园的中央入口时，您将是第一个看到该建筑物的人。 它是一个舞台岛，安装在横跨湖心的桥上。 它有670个座位，可举办各种活动和节日。 如果没有举行任何特别活动，它将变成一个大型遮荫棚，可欣赏周围景观。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;净化金河并将其发送到湖边的听觉场所 - 韩国世宗 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/22b17601-b216-4db1-bc41-15bc89707eb4.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     净化金河并将其发送到湖边的听觉场所
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   湖周围也有水培法，您可以和孩子们一起享受凉水。 首先是高架大门下方正门旁边的方形喷泉。 孩子们跳进上升的喷泉，成人则把垫子放在高架的树荫下。 该公园还设有特殊的水质管理设施。 这是一种聆听植物，种植有净化水的纯净植物。 这是一家利用自然价值来净化锦江河水并将其供应至湖泊的净水设施。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;在银色的沙滩上玩沙子的家庭 - 韩国世宗 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/2b4640db-5afd-4e41-8d83-73e05a5fe0f0.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     在银色的沙滩上玩沙子的家庭
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   可以在湖边做沙洲并像沙滩一样玩耍的银色沙滩，以及可以玩橡皮艇，滑水和冲浪等小型游艇的水上运动的水上游乐岛，是美丽的 湖公园。 每年四月至周日，每年五月至九月举行水上运动体验。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;银色沙滩上的青蛙 - 韩国世宗 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/afbfc166-3e4c-45e5-85d4-4a219f500d1f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     银色沙滩上的青蛙
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   还有一个以凉风为主题的空间，用于冷却热量。 它是风的小山，以柔和的曲线体现了风。 这是一个您想自己休息和休息的地方。 坐在这里，看着湖泊，整个公园就在眼前。 您不知道如何度过舒适的时光，在湖对岸的建筑物和山丘上度过。 但是也有缺点。 这个空间没有阴影可以躲避炎热的夏天的阳光。 戴上宽阔的帽子或遮阳伞。 如果准备凉爽的冰水，这里是一日游的好地方。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;水上游戏岛，您可以体验沙滩和水上运动 - 韩国世宗 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/e4f273d7-03a9-4839-b742-156f7af365bf.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     水上游戏岛，您可以体验沙滩和水上运动
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   还有一个空间展示了与风丘不同的景观。 它是位于水边传统公园中的八角亭“江南井”。 它的名字取自其长子平原。 抬头看着公园，您可以看到森林和天空。 长子平原上堆满了建筑物，但森林似乎成了新的平原。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;从风山眺望的湖泊和城市风景 - 韩国世宗 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/9b41595e-7264-4cd4-b294-5ef1a5005dc2.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     从风山眺望的湖泊和城市风景
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   公园开放时间为上午5点至晚上11点，免费入场。 从日落到下午10:00，水灯和Seho桥等景观灯都亮起。 湖中心的喷泉在工作日的12和8点开放20分钟，在假日12、4、6和8点开放。 作为垃圾回收的一部分，公园内没有垃圾。 尽量减少垃圾，将垃圾带回去。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;14&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;江南亭在水边传统公园 - 韩国世宗 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/b0929ccf-bc55-4cfd-a6e0-639d693546f9.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     江南亭在水边传统公园
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   在“拉动”公共自行车上骑野花小径
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Handu-ri桥距离湖公园有4公里。 桥下有长廊，自行车道和河滨公园。 公园建成之前，它以河边的野花而闻名。 即使到了现在，野生野花和装饰公园时种下的花都是最好的。 此时，初夏的花朵在马路两旁盛开。 无毒罂粟散布于北美本地的红色花朵和黄色寄生虫。 灵芝，也称为蛋花，害羞害羞。 这与Handuri桥相得益彰，Handuri桥有出色的回火米。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Handuri桥下的野花殖民地 - 韩国世宗 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/7daa4a00-3f64-4372-b458-194a95f37f65.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Handuri桥下的野花殖民地
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   世宗的大型公园比四处逛逛更舒适。 您可以在公共自行车租赁处“ Oulling”租用自行车。 世宗市有29个悬挂式出租站和386个摇篮，因此可以在城市的任何地方免费租借和归还。 您可以通过Oulling主页实时查看租赁站和通讯座的位置和状况。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;花场的自行车道 - 韩国世宗 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/ee806b36-005b-4a04-ba2e-513fdabcc17b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     花场的自行车道
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   19岁以上的人可以使用公共自行车的手机号码。 使用无人值守的信息终端进行出租。 一日通行证的费用为1,000韩元。 但是，租赁后每90分钟，您必须返回并在终端重新租借。 如果超过90分钟而没有重新租借，则每30分钟将收取1,000韩元的额外费用。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;世宗市公共自行车租赁 - 韩国世宗 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/1378442b-a07b-4b54-bbd3-090cfd38087d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     世宗市公共自行车租赁
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   即使是散步，露营和放松也可以！ 哈普冈公园汽车露营地
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   从湖公园到哈普冈公园汽车露营地的路上只有30分钟车程。 该露营地由世宗市于2015年新运营。 它位于锦江和美穗溪汇合处。 在4个地区中有102个汽车露营地。 所有场所均配备了电气设施以及安全设施，例如灭火器，救生员和闭路电视。 每个站点都可以配备一个非常大的帐篷，站点之间的空间可以放松，因此您可以享受舒适的露营。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;露营俯瞰河 - 韩国世宗 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/0bf77113-39f0-4185-b6a0-c8b851732df5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     露营俯瞰河
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   滨河长廊已经创建，可以安全行走。 乡村自行车道在露营地的两侧延伸。 露营者可以免费租用自行车。 进入露营地时，请与管理办公室联系。 露营地周围遍布大型阳伞，八角形人行道和长凳。 无论露营如何，任何人都可以进入，除体育设施和休息区外的所有设施均可免费使用。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;哈普冈公园汽车露营地 - 韩国世宗 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/b7a54a10-1d09-45f1-9a06-d448282b4e88.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     哈普冈公园汽车露营地
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   露营地是基于在线预订的，但也可以在工作日和淡季的当天通过电话查询获得露营地。 基本费用是，平日和淡季为15,000韩元，周末和旺季为20,000韩元，使用电力设施时的基本费用为3,000韩元。 露营地上没有商店，饭店或咖啡馆，因此请确保携带必要的物品。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;广阔的道路和露营区 - 韩国世宗 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/fa618673-a684-4a4c-ac3f-8acf2f8ee558.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     广阔的道路和露营区
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   旅游信息
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      世宗湖公园
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     地址：世宗特别自治市道松路216
     &lt;br/&gt;
     门
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      公共自行车“ Ouling”
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     地址：世宗特别自治市七原邑军清路93
     &lt;br/&gt;
     联络电话：1899-9161
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.sejongbike.kr/mainPageAction.do?process=mainPage&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.sejongbike.kr/mainPageAction.do?process=mainPage
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      哈普冈公园汽车露营地
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     地址：世宗特别自治市永洞泰山路329
     &lt;br/&gt;
     联络电话：044-862-5985
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1.附近的餐馆
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Dabokjeong韩国套餐：Hansiksik /世宗市Hannuri-daero 157 / 044-862-3371
    &lt;br/&gt;
    明：周面/世宗市Nuri-ro 27 / 044-866-8933
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Hwang Wooje：Oori Maetang /世宗市杨洞泰山路101-12 / 044-866-1141
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2.住宿
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    天空下的金刚养老金：世宗市金南面多南2街205-14 / 010-5548-4518
    &lt;br/&gt;
    金刚自然休闲森林：世宗市金南面森林博物馆博物馆110 / 041-635-7400
    &lt;br/&gt;
    长城自动防御：世宗市长郡面锦松路161 / 044-881-7755
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※以上信息为2015年6月的信息。之后可能会发生变化，因此请在旅行前确认。
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※本文中使用的文字，照片和视频等信息均受韩国旅游组织版权保护，因此禁止未经授权使用本文。
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sejong, Republic of Korea - Sejong Lake Park, a day in the city</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/sejong-lake-park-a-day-in-the-city-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 19:07:21 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/sejong-lake-park-a-day-in-the-city-26/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-title=&#34;sejong-lake-park-a-day-in-the-city--26&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Silver Beach in Sejong Lake Park - Sejong, Republic of Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/97d74f26-f9df-4539-8b97-69a6ac4db265.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Silver Beach in Sejong Lake Park
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Sejong Lake Park, a day in the city
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Sejong, Republic of Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In the center of Sejong Special Self-Governing City, there is Sejong Lake Park, a resting place for Sejong citizens and a resting place for tourists. There are five theme parks around the wide lake, so anyone can choose their favorite space and relax.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Close to the park is the wildflower-bound bike trail that runs under the Handuri Bridge and the Hapgang Park Auto Camping Ground, which ensures comfort with spacious and clean facilities.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sejong Lake Park Central Plaza - Sejong, Republic of Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/9fd50aea-bce0-41bb-be8e-8571340701d2.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sejong Lake Park Central Plaza
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Sejong Lake Park, an artificial lake resembling nature
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Sejong Lake Park, located in the center of the city, is the largest in Korea and is the size of 62 soccer fields combined. The park is decorated with five themes: Festival Island, Stage Island, Water Island, Water Flower Island, and Marsh Island. At first glance, it&#39;s huge enough to take a look around, but the steps are easy. Different parks offer different landscapes and shelter.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Stage Island from the Festival Island - Sejong, Republic of Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/5eae923d-2795-419e-92b1-49738f247e47.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Stage Island from the Festival Island
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   When you enter the central entrance of Lake Park, you will be the first to see the building. It is a stage island installed on the bridge across the center of the lake. It has 670 seats as a venue for various events and festivals. When no special events are held, it becomes a large shade shelter with views of the surrounding landscape.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Hearing place to purify the Geum River and send it to the lake - Sejong, Republic of Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/22b17601-b216-4db1-bc41-15bc89707eb4.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Hearing place to purify the Geum River and send it to the lake
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   There are also hydroponics around the lake where you can enjoy the cool water with your children. The first place is the square fountain below the elevated gate next to the main entrance. The children jump into the rising fountains, and the adults lay down the mats under the elevated shade. The park also has special facilities for water quality management. It is a listening plant planted with purified plant to clean the water. It is a water purification facility that uses natural values to make the water of Geum River clearer and supply it to the lake.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Family playing with sand on the silver beach - Sejong, Republic of Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/2b4640db-5afd-4e41-8d83-73e05a5fe0f0.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Family playing with sand on the silver beach
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The silver beach where you can make a sandbar at the edge of the lake and play like a beach, and the water play island where you can enjoy water sports such as dinghy, water skiing, and surfing, which are small yachts, are the beauty of the lake park. Watersports experiences are held from Thursday to Sunday, from May to September every year.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Frog on the silver beach - Sejong, Republic of Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/afbfc166-3e4c-45e5-85d4-4a219f500d1f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Frog on the silver beach
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   There is also a space with the theme of cool breeze to cool down the heat. It is a hill of wind that embodies the wind in a gentle curve. It is a place where you want to stay and rest on your own. Sit here and look at the lake and the entire park is in sight. You don&#39;t know how to spend your time in the comfort of buildings and hills that are located across the lake. But there are also disadvantages. There is no shade in this space to escape the hot summer sunshine. Take a wide hat or sunshade. If you prepare cool ice water, it is a good place to rest for a day trip.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Water Play Island where you can experience sand and water sports - Sejong, Republic of Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/e4f273d7-03a9-4839-b742-156f7af365bf.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Water Play Island where you can experience sand and water sports
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   There is also a space that shows a different landscape from the hills of wind. It is the octagonal pavilion &#39;Jangnamjeong&#39; located in the waterside traditional park. Its name is taken from its former place, the eldest son plain. Looking up at the park, you can see the forest and the sky. The eldest son plain is filled with buildings, but the forest seems to have made a new plain.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;View of the lake and the city as viewed from the hill of wind - Sejong, Republic of Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/9b41595e-7264-4cd4-b294-5ef1a5005dc2.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     View of the lake and the city as viewed from the hill of wind
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The park is open from 5 am to 11 pm and admission is free. From sunset to 10:00 pm, the landscape lights such as the water stage and Seho Bridge are illuminated. The fountain in the center of the lake is open for 20 minutes on weekdays at 12 and 8 o&#39;clock, and at 12, 4, 6 and 8 o&#39;clock on holidays. There is no trash in the park as part of the garbage take-back. Minimize your trash and take your trash back.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;14&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Jangnamjeong in Waterside Traditional Park - Sejong, Republic of Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/b0929ccf-bc55-4cfd-a6e0-639d693546f9.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Jangnamjeong in Waterside Traditional Park
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Riding wildflower trails in the &#39;Oulling&#39; public bike
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Handu-ri Bridge is 4 km from Lake Park. Under the bridge there were promenades, bike paths and riverside parks. It was famous for riverside wildflowers before the park was built. Even now, the wild wildflowers along with the flowers planted while decorating the park are the best. At this time, the flowers of early summer are in full bloom on both sides of the road. Non-toxic poppies scatter red flowers and yellow parasites native to North America. Ganoderma lucidum, also known as egg flower, is shyly shy. It is a landscape that goes very well with the Handuri Bridge, which has outstanding tempered rice.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Wildflower colony under the Handuri Bridge - Sejong, Republic of Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/7daa4a00-3f64-4372-b458-194a95f37f65.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Wildflower colony under the Handuri Bridge
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Sejong&#39;s large park is more comfortable to ride than to walk around. You can rent a bicycle at &#39;Oulling&#39;, a public bicycle rental place. Sejong City operates 29 hanging rental stations and 386 cradles, so it is free to rent and return anywhere in the city. You can check the location and situation of the rental station and the cradle in real time through the Oulling homepage.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Bicycle path by the flower field - Sejong, Republic of Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/ee806b36-005b-4a04-ba2e-513fdabcc17b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Bicycle path by the flower field
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Public bicycles can be used by anyone over the age of 19 with their mobile phone number. Rentals are made using unmanned information terminals. The one-day pass costs 1,000 won. However, every 90 minutes after rental, you must return and re-rent at the terminal. If it is over 90 minutes without re-renting, an additional fee of 1,000 won will be charged every 30 minutes.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sejong City public bicycle rentals - Sejong, Republic of Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/1378442b-a07b-4b54-bbd3-090cfd38087d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sejong City public bicycle rentals
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Even for walking, camping, and relaxation OK! Hapgang Park Auto Camping Ground
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   30 minutes&#39; drive along the road from Lake Park to Hapgang Park Auto Camping Ground. This camping site, which was newly operated in 2015, is managed by Sejong City. It is located at the point where Geum River and Miho Stream meet. There are 102 auto camping sites in 4 districts. All sites are equipped with electrical facilities, as well as safety facilities such as fire extinguishers, lifeguards and CCTVs. Each site can be equipped with a very large tent, and the space between the sites can be relaxed, so you can enjoy cozy camping.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Camping overlooking the river - Sejong, Republic of Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/0bf77113-39f0-4185-b6a0-c8b851732df5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Camping overlooking the river
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The riverside promenade has been created to walk safely. Countryside bike trails run along both sides of the camping ground. Campers can rent bicycles free of charge. Contact the management office when entering the campsite. There are large parasols, octagonal pavement, and benches all around the camping ground. Regardless of camping, anyone can enter, and all facilities besides sports facilities and rest areas can be used free of charge.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Hapgang Park Auto Camping Site - Sejong, Republic of Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/b7a54a10-1d09-45f1-9a06-d448282b4e88.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Hapgang Park Auto Camping Site
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The camping site is based on online reservations, but it is also available on the day by telephone inquiries on weekdays and low season. The basic fee is 15,000 won on weekdays and low season, 20,000 won on weekends and high season, and 3,000 won is added when using electric facilities. There are no shops, restaurants, or cafes on the camping grounds, so make sure you bring the necessary items with you.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Wide road and camping area - Sejong, Republic of Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/26/fa618673-a684-4a4c-ac3f-8acf2f8ee558.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Wide road and camping area
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel info
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Sejong Lake Park
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Address: 216 Dasom-ro, Sejong Special Self-Governing City
     &lt;br/&gt;
     door
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Public Bicycle ‘Ouling’
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Address: 93, Guncheong-ro, Jochiwon-eup, Sejong Special Self-Governing City
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Contact: 1899-9161
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.sejongbike.kr/mainPageAction.do?process=mainPage&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.sejongbike.kr/mainPageAction.do?process=mainPage
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Hapgang Park Auto Camping Ground
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Address: 329, Taesan-ro, Yeong-dong, Sejong Special Self-Governing City
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Contact: 044-862-5985
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Nearby restaurants
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Dabokjeong Korean Set Meals: Hansiksik / 157 Hannuri-daero, Sejong City / 044-862-3371
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Ming: Chow Myeon / 27, Nuri-ro, Sejong-si / 044-866-8933
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Hwang Wooje: Oori Maetang / 101-12, Taesan-ro, Yeong-dong, Sejong-si / 044-866-1141
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Accommodation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Geumgang Pension under the Sky: 205-14, Donam 2-gil, Geumnam-myeon, Sejong City / 010-5548-4518
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Geumgang Natural Recreation Forest: 110, Forest Museum Museum, Geumnam-myeon, Sejong City / 041-635-7400
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Cheongwall Vival Defense: 161, Geumsong-ro, Janggun-myeon, Sejong City / 044-881-7755
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was made in June 2015. It may change afterwards, so please check before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Information such as text, photos, and videos used in this article is copyrighted by Korea Tourism Organization, so unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>