<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gyeongju on Every Corner of Korea</title>
    <link>https://codecorea.github.io/tags/gyeongju/</link>
    <description>Every Corner of Korea (Gyeongju)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 18:18:29 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="https://codecorea.github.io/tags/gyeongju/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How did the rich in the Joseon Dynasty live? Yangnam mountain range of Yeongnam rich man &#39;Gyeongju richest &amp; deepest in Cheongsong&#39; - Gyeongju, Gyeongbuk, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/how-did-the-rich-in-the-joseon-dynasty-live-yangnam-mountain-range-of-yeongnam-rich-man-gyeongju-richest-deepest-in-cheongsong-276/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 18:18:29 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/how-did-the-rich-in-the-joseon-dynasty-live-yangnam-mountain-range-of-yeongnam-rich-man-gyeongju-richest-deepest-in-cheongsong-276/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Gyeongju, Gyeongbuk, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;how-did-the-rich-in-the-joseon-dynasty-live-yangnam-mountain-range-of-yeongnam-rich-man-gyeongju-richest-deepest-in-cheongsong--276&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Deokcheon Village from the back mountain of Songjeong Gotaek - Gyeongju, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/276/bd0daff5-dc4e-49cf-9e9e-5fd8c4db80af.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Deokcheon Village from the back mountain of Songjeong Gotaek
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   How did the rich in the Joseon Dynasty live? Yangnam mountain range of Yeongnam rich man &#39;Gyeongju richest &amp;amp; deepest in Cheongsong&#39;
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Gyeongju, Gyeongbuk, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    In the Joseon Dynasty, the rich man (in Yeongnam Province) was called &#39;Manseokman&#39;. I&#39;m a full-timer. Grain Bay is a horse that is rich with rice fields that are about to be harvested. Stones and islands can be viewed in the same unit. Even if it is not necessarily full, it means that it is rich. As a modern person living in the age of cash, I wonder. How rich is it now? For easy calculation, let&#39;s hit an island of rice with a bale. One bale weighs 80 kg. Currently, if the price of rice is about 20,000 won at about 20 kg, one bale is 200,000 won. It is 200,000 won on an island, so if it is an island, it is 2 billion won. If one island of rice (180 liters) is hit with two bales, the value is even higher. In other words, when converting Manseok-man in modern times, it means the rich with the lowest annual income of over 2 billion won. Manseokman is so rich in radishes, and the mind that looked a little shallow disappears like snow in the spring sun.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    According to Man Seok-man, the annual salary, it is almost 100 times the amount of workers now. Moreover, given that it was a time when even eating full was considered a luxury, &#39;Manseokman&#39; would have been very rich. If you dare to compare, it might be the total number of large companies now. I&#39;m curious about this. Where and how did the rich people live in the old days? Why don&#39;t we visit the residence of the sign that represents Yeongnam in the Joseon Dynasty, the richest of the Gyeongju and the deepest of Cheongsong, and examine the living spaces of those who were considered the richest of the Joseon Dynasty?
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Mr. Choi&#39;s oldest residence in Gyeongju Gyodong
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Gyeongju is often known only as the royal family of Silla. Since it was the only capital of Silla for a thousand years, it is also true that Gyeongju and Silla cannot be separated. However, Gyeongju does not have only Silla. Since the millennium of Silla, a new millennium has been lived in &#39;Koryo&#39;, &#39;Chosun&#39; and &#39;South Korea&#39;, so Gyeongju has a longer time in other eras than &#39;Silla&#39;. Of course, the aura of Gyeongju, which occupied the &#39;Kingdom&#39; all the time during the Han Dynasty, is clearly different from the &#39;Gyeongju&#39;, which was chosen by other times.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The top gate of Gyeongju&#39;s richest sock is low and modest. - Gyeongju, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/276/f399a138-be84-4d69-b84d-ca49450140aa.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The top gate of Gyeongju&#39;s richest sock is low and modest.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Gyeongju, which we will look at today, is Choi&#39;s old house in Gyo-dong, Gyeongju. It is a space more famous as &#39;Gyeongju Choibujapjija&#39; than real name. Gyeongju Choi Bu-jak, who is considered to be the representative of Yeongnam Manseok-gun along with Cheongsong&#39;s rich man, is famous for being &#39;the rich man who has been in his twenties for over 300 years,&#39; but it is more meaningful in that he practiced &#39;Noblesse Oblige&#39;. Let&#39;s go to Gyeongju Gyodong.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Inside the richest house from the Sarangchae - Gyeongju, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/276/f72cd9da-cf19-4718-a7e4-7db69c365d34.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Inside the richest house from the Sarangchae
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It is known that the space where Choi&#39;s closet, Gyeongju Choi&#39;s rich house is located, was the site of Yoseokgung Palace, the residence of Yoseok Princess in the Silla period. It was said to have been built around 1700 and maintained wealth for over 300 years in 12 generations. It was built in ninety-nine squares, but in 1970, Sarangchae and Byeoldang were burned down. Still, it has great value because it preserves the original form of the Joseon Dynasty.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sarangchae was restored in 2006. - Gyeongju, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/276/b74d45e5-af2b-46b6-926b-26df1a7d323b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sarangchae was restored in 2006.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The Gyeongju Gyodong Beopju, Gyeongju Hyanggyo, and Gyeongju Gyochon Village, which opened in January 2013, are located nearby. Gyo-dong was the center of traditional Confucian education, as well as the home of the wealthiest and the home of Silla&#39;s nationality, Goryeo, and Joseon.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Anchae was the residence of the girls - Gyeongju, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/276/2cb76028-2d6e-43e8-9db2-7c746bd0a55f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Anchae was the residence of the girls
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   When you enter Gyeongju&#39;s richest family, the &#39;Teaching of the richest family&#39; greets people. `` Look at the past, but do not crush more than the shrine &#39;&#39; `` Give back to society for more than 10,000 seats &#39;&#39; `` Don&#39;t increase the land in the midst of menopause &#39;&#39; Treat hospitality generously &#39;&#39; &#39;Yuk-hun&#39;, a daughter-in-law&#39;s daughter-in-law who wears cotton clothes for three years, stands out. It seems that they know a little why the rich have been in their twenties because it is difficult for them to go. If they were dead, would they have been in line to become the wealthiest farmers?
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Choi Bu-jak Warehouse, which has been in 12 generations for 300 years - Gyeongju, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/276/a294acca-59a8-4535-bc87-5856dfb82a82.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Choi Bu-jak Warehouse, which has been in 12 generations for 300 years
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   They practiced &#39;Noblesse Oblige&#39; by succeeding in generations and building wealth. But why did the richest man end in twelve? Let&#39;s listen to the story of Choi Bu-jak, who is told for a moment.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Commentator explaining Choi Bu-jak&#39;s warehouse - Gyeongju, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/276/a605cd21-55ae-4d2b-af92-4319931e3a2d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Commentator explaining Choi Bu-jak&#39;s warehouse
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   One of the richest is Choi Jinlip. The 2nd Choi Dong-ryang inherits a lot of property and purchases large land. And after that, Choi Kuk-sun, who was unable to pay for the farmers to borrow the rice after a bad harvest, destroyed all of the mortgage documents in front of his son and gave them to the beggars. When you are hungry, give 100 rice.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;14&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The girls peeked out through the hole in the wall. - Gyeongju, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/276/f2d2fea1-05c2-419c-a81f-0ae12a6a2dd8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The girls peeked out through the hole in the wall.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Was it because of the good deeds of the richest man who said, &#39;Let there be no one who is starving in white berry&#39;? Even in the flames of the living party, Choi Bu-jak survives. However, when he reached the twelveth-century Choi Jun and took the country to Japan, he gave his wealth to the independent funding with the belief that there would be no rich without a country. After independence, donate all the wealth to the education project. That is why the richest man ended in his twenties and 300 years.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;16&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Anchae and shrine are located behind the big Sarangchae house - Gyeongju, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/276/b988b107-96fb-4a84-9f90-d322766d4740.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Anchae and shrine are located behind the big Sarangchae house
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Unfortunately, it is not possible to stay in Gyeongju&#39;s richest home. It is not yet clear whether or not to stay in Gyochon village in Gyeongju, where various experience programs including Korean traditional music experience are prepared. First, let&#39;s be satisfied by looking around. It&#39;s safe to just draw a picture of the grain that filled the large space and give it to the hungry neighbors. Now, it is a difficult scene to see in the space where descendants live.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;18&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Gyo-dong Beopju, known as Gayangju in Gyeongju Choi&#39;s family - Gyeongju, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/276/1d6ce095-3a7a-4f2a-ac9f-b541e1ffa53c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Gyo-dong Beopju, known as Gayangju in Gyeongju Choi&#39;s family
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   As a side note, Choi Yun, the younger brother of the last richest child, Choi Joon, met his daughter, the daughter of Cheongsong&#39;s rich family, as his wife. Currently, Chairman Su-Hyun Kim of the Korea Traditional Culture Agency is their granddaughter. If you really want to experience the old house in Gyeongju, you can use Suojae (054-748-1310) in Baeban-dong, located 10 minutes away by car from the oldest house.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;20&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Gyeongju Gyochon Village in Gyo-dong, the home of the richest - Gyeongju, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/276/bb714915-63b7-400e-b836-925b7aa90b05.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Gyeongju Gyochon Village in Gyo-dong, the home of the richest
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Song So-taek, a deep-stayed person in Cheongsong ... Both accommodation and observation
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The space where deep-hearted people in Cheongsong stayed is more famous as &#39;Songso Old House&#39;. You may have heard about it once. Since 2002, there have been many people who visited while visiting the old house experience facility. In 2011, it was selected as the &#39;Star of Korean Tourism&#39;.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The mouth that will fill the lower neck warmly - Gyeongju, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/276/c532f910-ace7-4c38-9a95-b781fc9f33af.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The mouth that will fill the lower neck warmly
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It is only an hour and a half from the Seoan-dong IC on National Road 35 and Local Road 914. On the road to Cheongsong, you can notice that this town is a remote area in Yeongnam. I wonder how this sign lived in these hills.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The fire burns the chimney and sterilizes the whole house. - Gyeongju, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/276/ab5a2cf4-0862-4d20-a13a-1cda80a36a6c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The fire burns the chimney and sterilizes the whole house.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Cheongsong Simbu Pine Nut House is located in Deokcheon Village, Pacheon-myeon. Thanks to this, it is also called &#39;Dukcheon-dong&#39;s Deep-Duty House&#39;. In addition to the Songso old house, there are many old houses, such as the Songjeong old house and the Bangjonggong house, so if you look down from the hill behind the Songjeong old house, the old houses unfold. Thanks to this, Deokcheon Village was listed as Slow City in 2011.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Soaring Gate with almost no chin - Gyeongju, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/276/f7e41585-b88f-4b3f-8cc9-197739cbeb6e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Soaring Gate with almost no chin
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It is said that Cheongsong&#39;s rich bakery produced 20,000 stone workers in nine generations from Shimcheong University to the 1960s. It is &#39;the house where the sun of the Joseon Dynasty does not go down&#39;, saying that even if you go anywhere in the Joseon Dynasty, there is enough land for you. The deep-hearted person in Cheongsong is the prestigious &#39;Cheongsong Sim&#39;, the Joseon dynasty. Throughout the Joseon Dynasty, 13 Jeongseung, 3 Queen and 4 Buma were produced.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;When you pass through the gate, you face the big Sarangchae in front. - Gyeongju, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/276/f5700f7c-d6ba-4367-ac56-0f5241c1c488.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     When you pass through the gate, you face the big Sarangchae in front.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Now, let&#39;s take a look at Song So-taek, the famous prodigy. Song So-taek was built in 1880 (17th year of King Gojong) by Song-so Shim Ho-taek, the seventh grandson of Simcheo University, a man-in-law during the Joseon Dynasty.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;15&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Inside of Anchae with Jangdokdae - Gyeongju, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/276/6ee16fce-a355-4820-b97f-7beef87a72c1.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Inside of Anchae with Jangdokdae
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The Joseon Dynasty, which was a strong social status society, limited the size of the saga to less than ninety-nine, excluding palaces, according to the law. If only one pillar is added to the ninety-nine squares, there are no palaces and chalices. Song So-taek is ninety-nine. The largest house allowed in Saga.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;16&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The raving sound of the bamboo caught the intruder. - Gyeongju, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/276/65939a0c-c797-424b-8566-a3b43374ab37.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The raving sound of the bamboo caught the intruder.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The starting point of Song So-taek, the towering towering tower is proud of the greatness of the Daegat house. The story continues through Haengrangchae where Haengrang Abum and Gilson stayed.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;14&#34; id3=&#34;17&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;From Sotdaemun Gate, pass through Sarangchae and go to Anchae - Gyeongju, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/276/266c9ac9-1e5f-49a6-a279-2a36530ef9eb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     From Sotdaemun Gate, pass through Sarangchae and go to Anchae
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It is a wall built between a large Sarangchae and Anchae, which is purposefully made so that it cannot be easily seen from Sarangchae when girls and women living in the Anchae pass through the gate. You can get a glimpse of the life of a woman in a unique Confucian society and the Joseon Dynasty.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;16&#34; id3=&#34;18&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The girls looked out through the hole. - Gyeongju, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/276/a4fa3939-e312-4396-b447-f5fe6e3c00b0.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The girls looked out through the hole.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In Anchae, the hostess and children stayed. In the large Sarangchae, the outside man was staying, but there is a slight difference in the floor height of the space where the grandfather, father, and son stayed. A smirkful laugh is mingled with the cough of the alumni who were &#39;hem&#39; in the story of 툇 maru, a thankful means to move from Sarangchae to Anchae.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;18&#34; id3=&#34;19&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Soongdaemun, seen from Sarangchae, the deepest pine house in Cheongsong - Gyeongju, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/276/5a3313d5-d189-44bf-b106-a4dbef9e75c0.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Soongdaemun, seen from Sarangchae, the deepest pine house in Cheongsong
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The situation at the time of Confucian society is drawn. Also add a small hole in the fence of the main building. It&#39;s a &#39;breath hole&#39; for girls. Through this, I watched the outside world. After passing through the side door of Sarangchae, a villa appears. This is the space where my daughter&#39;s time to marry was staying.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;20&#34; id3=&#34;20&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The ridge that connects Sarangchae and Anchae - Gyeongju, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/276/deb88d38-4174-4b13-9952-6953e486e56c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The ridge that connects Sarangchae and Anchae
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Although the day is cold, after looking around the Songso old house, I dream of &#39;one night at the old house&#39;. Lying on a warm lower throat, passing through Sotdaedaemun, seeing Sarangchae, and looking around Anchae and taking a round to the villa, the ninety-nine houses of the richest in the Joseon Dynasty are drawn at a glance. It&#39;s a bonus to imagine as if you were rich at the time. You can visit the old house without staying.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;22&#34; id3=&#34;21&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The condominium where the daughter of a married woman stayed - Gyeongju, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/276/ebefc1df-b6ef-4ceb-b4ca-2f03ce4a4c07.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The condominium where the daughter of a married woman stayed
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p style=&#34;COLOR: #7b1f42; FONT-SIZE: 11pt&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     - Gyeongju -
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;topmr&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1.Nearby Restaurants
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Choi...
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    / Gyo-dong, Gyo-dong, Gyeongju-si / 054-775-7557
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Hwangnam Millstone Sundubu
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    / 155 Hwangnam-dong, Gyeongju-si / 054-771-7171
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Sampo Ssambap
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    / 90-2 Hwangnam-dong, Gyeongju-si / 054-749-5776
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Hwangnam Bread
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    / Hwang O-dong, Gyeongju / 054-749-5599
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Lee Pung-nyeo Gussam Rice
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    / Hwangnam-dong, Gyeongju-si / 054-749-0600
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2.Accommodation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Suojae (Town house experience)
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    / 217 Baeban-dong, Gyeongju-si / 054-748-1310
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Tohamsan Natural Recreation Forest
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    / Yangbuk-myeon, Gyeongju-si / 054-772-1254
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Gyeongju Hilton Hotel
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    / Sinpyeong-dong, Gyeongju / 054-745-7788
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Daemyung Resort
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Gyeongju / Sinpyeong-dong, Gyeongju-si / 1588-4888
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Gyeongju Kensington Resort
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    / Bukgun-dong, Gyeongju / 054-748-8400
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Bulguksa Youth Hostel
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    / Jinhyeon-dong, Gyeongju-si / 054-746-0826
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p style=&#34;COLOR: #7b1f42; FONT-SIZE: 11pt&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     -Cheongsong-
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;topmr&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1.Nearby Restaurants
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    There are several hundreds of specialty shops around the specialty sweets.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Gyeongnam Restaurant
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    054-873-4859
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Seoul Inn Restaurant
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    054-873-2177
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Dalgi Yaksuchon
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    054-873-2662
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2.Accommodation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    Songso Gotaek in Cheongsong, North Gyeongsang Province is the largest ninety-nine mansion house among the largest private saga. It was founded in 1880 by Song So-Shim, Simho-Taek, the seventh generation of Shim Che-Dae, who enjoyed the wealth of the Joseon Dynasty. Most rooms such as Sarangchae, Haengrangchae, and Anchae open to the public. The daily accommodation fee (for 2 people) starts at 50,000 won.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    Reservations and Inquiries, 054-874-6556,
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.송소고택.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;송소고택 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
     www.송소고택.kr
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    In addition, in Deokcheon Village, Songjeong Gotaek (054-873-6695) built by Sim Jeong-gwang, the second son of Shim Ho-taek, and Cheongbang Sim-taek (010-9502-7611), the chief of Shim-dang, the 9-year-old son of Eung Eun-gong of Cheongsong Sim Experience is possible. In winter, it is necessary to light the fire, so be sure to ask beforehand.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;red&#34;&gt;
    ※ The above information was updated in April 2014, and may be changed later, so please check before you travel.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stroll through the royal tombs with unique beauty - Gyeongju, Gyeongbuk, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/stroll-through-the-royal-tombs-with-unique-beauty-275/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 18:18:28 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/stroll-through-the-royal-tombs-with-unique-beauty-275/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Gyeongju, Gyeongbuk, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;stroll-through-the-royal-tombs-with-unique-beauty--275&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Pine forest road to Jeonggang Royal Tombs - Gyeongju, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/275/c8bded3a-a232-4780-9b5f-b8f0d261c104.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Pine forest road to Jeonggang Royal Tombs
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Stroll through the royal tombs with unique beauty
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Gyeongju, Gyeongbuk, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    In the Millennium Altitude Gyeongju, there are many royal tombs in harmony with the city. It has an ancient city that has been around for a thousand years, such as Hwangnamdaechong and Daereungwon with Cheonmachong, Hwangnamdae with hundreds of years old trees, and beautiful Samneung and Queen Seondeok with pine forests. However, it is not easy to find all the royal tombs in Gyeongju, which is hard to find even for a week. So it is often not found even though it is a special place. Here are three unique royal tombs you should visit in Gyeongju.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Jeongneung Royal Tombs and Heunggang Royal Tombs with beautiful pine forest
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Anyone who has seen photographer Byung-Woo Bae&#39;s pine forest in Queen Seondeok wants to go there. There are many royal tombs where the kings of Silla are asleep. And there is a pine tree on the royal tomb. The path leading to the royal tomb along the pine forest is the first beautiful scenery that impresses before the history of Silla and the achievements of the king.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Pine forest path at the entrance of Heungwangwangneung - Gyeongju, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/275/3f3bd552-2fab-4a62-830b-3c6c561d21f6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Pine forest path at the entrance of Heungwangwangneung
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Among the royal tombs of Gyeongju where pine forests are beautiful, Queen Seondeok and Samneung are indispensable, but pine forests in Jeonggang and Heunggang are also beautiful. Kings of Heongang and King Jeonggang are kings of the period of the end of the Unified Silla period, when the country was inclined. Jeongneung Royal Tombs and Heunggang Royal Tombs are not only close to the Tongiljeon, which is located on the eastern side of Namsan in Gyeongju, but also have two royal tombs side by side.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Heongang Royal Tombs - Gyeongju, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/275/4f1956a6-1cbe-48ef-b081-83f9614f9034.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Heongang Royal Tombs
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   King Heongang is the son of King Gyeongmun, who is known for his “King&#39;s ears are donkey ears.” It is also interesting that since King Heongang, King Jeonggang, King Jinseong, and King Hyogong are all the sons and daughters of King Gyeongmun. At least until the Hwanggang Dynasty, I can feel Silla&#39;s national cloud that flourished after the unification of the Three Kingdoms. One day King Heongang climbed down on the top of the moon with his servants and looked down at the crowded private house. King Heongang asked the civilian public. “I heard that people say that they are roofing with tile, not straw, and charcoal, not wood. Is that true?” In response to this, there is an article in the book &#34;The Three Kingdoms History&#34; in which the civilians of the city replied that they were. When King Heongang climbed in 11 years of reign, King Jeonggang was crowned. King Jeonggang is the younger brother of King Heongang. King Jeonggang passed away after he passed the throne to his younger sister, Queen Jinseong, within a year of reign without any time to continue the reign of King Heongang.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Stones built to protect the Heunggang Royal Tombs - Gyeongju, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/275/183f58f5-662c-4852-acfa-a4aa75c413d7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Stones built to protect the Heunggang Royal Tombs
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The Heunggang Royal Mausoleum and the Jeonggang Royal Mausoleum can be found in the road along the pine forest. Although the pines are not thick, they are densely packed and feel lush. The feast of pine trees spreading through the wind is three-dimensional.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Pine forest road to Jeonggang Royal Tombs - Gyeongju, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/275/b02032c1-2f91-432c-8f68-316b3093e635.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Pine forest road to Jeonggang Royal Tombs
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The royal tombs of Heunggang and the royal tombs of Jeonggang are not large, but simple and modest, such as the tombs of Daereungwon, Labor, and Noseo-dong. The royal tomb of Heongang was built in four steps, returning to the grave to prevent the soil from flowing down as a circular soil. The royal tomb of Jeonggang also looks similar, but is said to be a special case among the royal tombs of Silla. It is recommended to visit Heongang Royal Tombs and Jeonggang Royal Tombs to Namsan at around 3 ~ 4 pm when the sun is overlooked. This is because the last sunlight of the day spreads over the pine forest and is spectacular. Heunggang Royal Mausoleum is designated as Historic Site No. 187, while Jeonggang Royal Mausoleum is designated as Historic Site No. 186.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Jeonggang Royal Tombs - Gyeongju, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/275/255fffb4-aca6-48f4-a95a-ab8805281b4d.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Jeonggang Royal Tombs
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Meet Royal Mausoleum, Royal Mausoleum, Royal Mausoleum
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Each of the royal tombs of Silla welcomes visitors with special features, such as the huge Daereungwon&#39;s Hwangnamdaegun, the old trees growing at Dongdong-gun&#39;s Bongwangdae, and the Seogye Impression. Many royal tombs were found in the name ‘total’ without being able to find my name.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In the meantime, you can meet the most certain and most beautiful royal tomb, which is Seongdeok Royal Tombs. King Seongdeok is the first person to meet at the National Gyeongju Museum, the so-called &#39;Emileson&#39;. King Gyeongdeok made this bell in honor of his father King Seongdeok&#39;s merit. King Seongdeok succeeded King Munmu and King Shinmun, who are the main characters of the Three Kingdoms Unification, and became king after the King of Enzymes. After the reunification of the Three Kingdoms, he was the king who led the heyday of Silla, with a reign of 36 years.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Seongdeok Royal Tombs - Gyeongju, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/275/cd4031c0-d78a-4ba8-9073-31c9d4905e74.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Seongdeok Royal Tombs
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Seongdeok Royal Mausoleum is located in a place where accessibility is poor, so people have the best footing. The road is also not easy. You can meet only by crossing the train path into the forest at the Korean Advertising and Video Museum near National Road No. 7 to Bulguksa Temple. It&#39;s not easy to find, but once you&#39;re there, you&#39;ll find a meaningful treasure on a Gyeongju trip, so your effort is not in vain.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Zodiac statue with stone and neck fleeing - Gyeongju, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/275/ae41e294-d948-44f0-9245-173e136a374f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Zodiac statue with stone and neck fleeing
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The Royal Tomb of Seongdeok is a royal tomb that remains almost completely in shape as a royal tomb of the Unified Silla period. In order to protect a large tomb that is 46m in diameter, a wide stone about 90cm high was put on it and a cover stone was placed on it. In addition, a triangular stone was supported outside the tomb to prevent the wide stone from falling.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A lion statue erected in four directions to the royal tomb of Seongdeok - Gyeongju, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/275/2a070160-f5bc-4fed-ab6b-b7052f6129d6.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A lion statue erected in four directions to the royal tomb of Seongdeok
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   What is unusual is that the zodiac is erected around the grave. They were all placed outside the tombs, but this is the only one among the royal tombs of Silla. However, the head disappears and only the torso in the armor remains, leaving a regret.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Seongdeok Royal Mausoleum - Gyeongju, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/275/6db1615f-1ee9-4a73-8312-cdf45b4a6f06.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Seongdeok Royal Mausoleum
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Four lions guard the four sides like the gwangneung, and the leftover Moon In-suk stands alone. The Royal Tomb of Seongdeok is designated as Historic Site No. 28. At the bottom of the tomb of King Seongdeok, there is a tombstone-shaped tombstone, and the tomb of King Seongdeok&#39;s brother, Enzyme King, can also be seen.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Enzyme Royal Tombs near Seongdeok Royal Tombs - Gyeongju, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/275/2a9a8723-da61-47a9-bb3a-5885bd6c9851.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Enzyme Royal Tombs near Seongdeok Royal Tombs
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Jinpyeong Royal Mausoleum protected by an elegant pine tree
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    If you follow the National Highway No. 7 from Seongdeok Royal Tombs and head toward Gyeongju City, you will meet Sinmun Royal Tombs, Sacheon Wangsaji, and Queen Seondeok. After passing the Gyeongju Neungjitop and descending along Soro, the farm road in Bomundeul-eul continues. There is a tomb to the left of the field head, the tomb of Queen Jinpyeong, Queen of Queen Seondeok. Could there have been more dynamic times in the history of Silla than the times of King Jinheung and King Jinpyeong? As it appeared in the drama &amp;lt;Queen Seondeok&amp;gt;, Queen Seondeok succeeded King Jinpyeong, Queen Seongdeok who was known for Gyeongguk, Sadada and Munno, well-known as galleries, and Muyeolwang and Kim Yusin, the leading roles of the Three Kingdoms Unification. It was.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The royal tomb of Jinpyeong remains large and large. The dignity of the Silla royal family cannot be found, but it feels simple and elegant. A small pine tree bows its head toward the Royal Mausoleum like a municipal bell, and it seems to be shooting Hwaryong Peak in the landscape. The royal tomb of Jinpyeong overlooks Mt. It&#39;s as if you&#39;re looking at Queen Seondeok, a daughter sleeping in Nansan. The royal tomb of Jinpyeong is designated as the historic site No. 180.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The sun is setting over the royal tomb of Jinpyeong - Gyeongju, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/275/9f869722-4448-49ea-b90b-732a205e5631.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The sun is setting over the royal tomb of Jinpyeong
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Bomun evening was originally the site of Bomunsa Temple. In the field, there are Bogansa temple Dangganji, stonework, and Dangganji with engraved Yeonhwamun. In the Bomun village, there is a tomb that is said to be the tomb of the snowy chong.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Jinpyeong Royal Tombs - Gyeongju, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/275/3a758cdc-d100-4353-adb7-a6edaa027c91.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Jinpyeong Royal Tombs
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p style=&#34;COLOR: #7b1f42&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Jeongneung Royal Tombs:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    53, Namsan-dong, Gyeongju-si
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Heunggang Royal Tombs:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Namsan-dong, Gyeongju-si 55
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Seongdeok Royal Tombs:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    8, Joyang-dong, Gyeongju-si
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Jinpyeong Royal Tombs:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    608, Bomun-dong, Gyeongju
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     * question :
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Historical Park Management Office 054-779-8745
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1.Access
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
     * Self-driving
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34; style=&#34;MARGIN-TOP: 0px&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Heunggang Royal Mausoleum, Jeonggang Royal Mausoleum:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Gyeongbu Expressway Gyeongju IC → Turn right at Buban Intersection toward Bulguksa Temple → Turn right at Sacheonwangsaji Intersection toward Unification → Turn Tongil → Hwanggangwangneung, Jeonggangwangneung
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Seongdeok Royal Tombs:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Gyeongbu Expressway Gyeongju IC → Turn right at the direction of Bulguksa at Baeban Intersection → Korea Advertising and Video Museum → Seongdeokdaewangneung
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Jinpyeong Royal Tombs:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Gyeongbu Expressway Gyeongju IC → Baeban Underpass → Turn right at Gampo at Guhwanggyo Intersection → Turn right at Bomun Village, Wangpyeong Royal Tombs → Jinpyeong Royal Tombs
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
     * public transport
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34; style=&#34;MARGIN-TOP: 0px&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Seongdeok Royal Tombs:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Take the No. 11 bus to Bulguksa from Gyeongju Intercity Bus Terminal and get off at the Korean Advertising and Video Museum
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Jeongneung Royal Tombs and Heunggang Royal Tombs:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Take the 11th bus bound for Bulguksa from Gyeongju Intercity Bus Terminal and get off in front of Unification
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Jinpyeong Royal Tombs:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    From Gyeongju Intercity Bus Terminal, take bus # 100 to Gimpo and get off at the entrance to Bomun Village
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;topmr&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Restaurants around
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     National Collection:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Songuk-si / 410 Geumseong-ro, Gyeongju-si / 054-773-3050
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Pahljeong Haejangguk:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Haejangguk / 810-1, Taejong-ro, Gyeongju-si / 054-742-6515
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Octopus drink:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    Stir-fried Nakji / 9 Bukgun-gil, Gyeongju-si / 054-749-0048
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.njfood.co.kr&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;‘낙지마실’ 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
     www.njfood.co.kr
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     3.Accommodation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Wolamjae:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    5-8 Namganan-gil, Gyeongju-si / 054-774-1950
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://경주고택.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;‘경주고택’ 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
     경주고택.kr
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Lagoon:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    55-12 Expo-ro, Gyeongju-si / 054-778-2100
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.smpark.co.kr&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;‘라궁’ 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
     www.smpark.co.kr
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Herb Castle:
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    158-83, Mohwabuk 1-gil, Oedong-eup, Gyeongju-si / 054-742-0890
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.herbcastle.co.kr&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;‘허브캐슬’ 홈페이지로 이동&#34;&gt;
     www.herbcastle.co.kr
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p class=&#34;gray padding10&#34;&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    ※ The above information was created in February 2014, and may change later, so be sure to check it before you travel.
    &lt;br/&gt;
    ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mountain bearing the moon, ‘King ’s way’, Gyeongju Hamwolsan ’s way - Gyeongju, Gyeongbuk, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/mountain-bearing-the-moon-king-s-way-gyeongju-hamwolsan-s-way-227/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 07:43:05 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/mountain-bearing-the-moon-king-s-way-gyeongju-hamwolsan-s-way-227/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Gyeongju, Gyeongbuk, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;mountain-bearing-the-moon-king-s-way-gyeongju-hamwolsan-s-way--227&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;The king&#39;s path is spacious enough for carriages and wagons - Gyeongju, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/227/cc59bb90-1c48-45aa-8068-4c9611b1aabc.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    The king&#39;s path is spacious enough for carriages and wagons
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Mountain bearing the moon, ‘King ’s way’, Gyeongju Hamwolsan ’s way
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Gyeongju, Gyeongbuk, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The road that led to the funeral procession of King Munmu who unified the Three Kingdoms, the way that King Munmu&#39;s son, Shinmunwang, went to the father&#39;s underwater tomb, and now the descendants of the road cool down the heat and remember history, I trace the old road with my feet.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Deep forest path like a deep man
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   As it is itself an open-air museum, there are so many ruins and artifacts from the Silla period that Gyeongju is too difficult to count. So, Gyeongju is new every time you go, and it is hard to measure its depth on a day or two or a few days. When the full moon rises, the moonlight travels, and when the stars are bright, the starlight travels, and you can feel the charm of the infinitely high altitude at night.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;King&#39;s Road to the entrance of Churyeong Tunnel - Gyeongju, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/227/db4d979a-8505-4b3f-8ac9-8f4c87c90b0e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     King&#39;s Road to the entrance of Churyeong Tunnel
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   A new route was recently added to such a race. It is the way of the king connecting Churyeong Tunnel and Girimsa Temple. It is a good forest path with a walking distance of 3.9km from the bottom of Hamwol Mountain. Like a deeply hidden treasure, I haven&#39;t yet made myself visible to the world, but it&#39;s more cozy and cozy.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Beginning with a small trail - Gyeongju, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/227/c1908fd8-cdf7-4729-b11c-1bd5a50c122c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Beginning with a small trail
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you go out of downtown Gyeongju and go toward Gampo, there is a Churyeong tunnel at the foot of Mt. Hamwol. There is an access road to the King&#39;s Road next to this Churyeong Tunnel. The road does not show me from the beginning. It takes 40-50 minutes to walk through the 2.5km country road along the driveway to reach the entrance of Mochagol, the entrance of the king&#39;s road. Like a good person, a good way does not reveal its deep inside from the beginning. It takes a little preparation to meet the deep forest.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Hwang Yong-soo at the entrance of Mochagol - Gyeongju, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/227/542b1625-fe15-41e1-9d2f-6241eac448aa.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Hwang Yong-soo at the entrance of Mochagol
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The road from Churyeong Tunnel to Mochagol is not a forest path, but it is quite a quiet path. As you walk, you&#39;ll meet Hwang Yong-soo, who is a little crazy. It is water that is good for the body so that the stones in the place where water falls due to its high iron content turn yellow. If you quench your neck with this mineral water, the thirst in the middle of the summer will go away.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Yellowish stone with high iron content in mineral water - Gyeongju, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/227/ff8f873f-5afe-4b1e-907a-1cd5aaaf2da1.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Yellowish stone with high iron content in mineral water
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Newspaper King Hoguk Haeng-gil&#39;s Road to Father&#39;s Underwater Tombs
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Once a bowl of mineral water is infused, it comes into contact with the mocha bone. Mochagol was called ‘Machagol’ because it was the place where the carriage went. This is where the king&#39;s path begins. Then why was this road called this name?
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Milestone from Mochagol to Suretjae - Gyeongju, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/227/a8042304-4c83-4f55-8581-d6729d1f70ea.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Milestone from Mochagol to Suretjae
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   King Sinmun is the first son of King Munmu who unified the Three Kingdoms as the 31st king of Silla. It is regarded as the king who stabilized the situation after the reunification of the Three Kingdoms and established a strong supreme kingship. When he inherited the throne from his father, King Munmu, in 681, Silla seemed calm on the surface, but it was a time of struggling with tension after the unification and conflict with the nobles.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A tree that exudes courageous energy - Gyeongju, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/227/5284a40a-7fa0-42f8-9f4e-3184b2357e7f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A tree that exudes courageous energy
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Saying to The Three Kingdoms Journal, “When you come to the near kingdom and you are in the throne with no morals, justice is different from the meaning of the sky. The same. ”
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Deep forest that is cool even in midsummer - Gyeongju, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/227/f8e5a497-fa02-4100-a847-e118bb3ac9fa.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Deep forest that is cool even in midsummer
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   This is the content of the ritual that the king of the newspaper gave to the ancestors of his ancestral rites. At that time, right after the unification, it was a difficult time to rule the country because of the constant rebellion and the danger of war with the outside. According to The Three Kingdoms Yu, the king of the newspaper went to the sea of the East Sea where his father Moon Moo&#39;s underwater mausoleum was located in 682, the year following his crown, and met a dragon to obtain a full-fledged and jade belt. It is said that when the manpasik, a flute made of bamboo, blows, the enemy soldiers retreat and get sick. As such, the peace and well-being of the country was desperate. The Manpasik was probably a story created to strengthen the king&#39;s kingship and stabilize the situation.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Deep forest is a heaven for frogs and insects - Gyeongju, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/227/2bbd1333-44d7-489a-ae0d-7fe387977585.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Deep forest is a heaven for frogs and insects
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   So this is the way the King of Newspapers goes to the grave of King Munmu, the father of the wagon, and has the power to save the country. It is also the way that King Munmu&#39;s funeral procession passed. It was first called Newspaper King Road or Newspaper King&#39;s Road, and now it is officially called King&#39;s Road. It was based on the speculation that not only the king of newspapers would have gone, but that the various kings had passed this road to the East Sea.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Clear water washes away the heart - Gyeongju, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/227/256fbbc8-4b4d-460c-a229-6cda1d1ac7fc.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Clear water washes away the heart
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Cool forest washes away heat, Yongyeon Falls where dragons ascend
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   At the entrance, the forest road overflows with wild beauty. The valley where the only aikiman forgets to embroider the road and flows sideways follows the road constantly. Crossing a small valley is dozens of times. As it enters midsummer, the forest grows countless small animals like all kinds of plants, insects, and frogs. Cicada cries in the tall trees, and the valley flows without rippling.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The king&#39;s way through a small valley all the time - Gyeongju, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/227/12575f69-52d6-4f9b-8d8b-6f479e66e464.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The king&#39;s way through a small valley all the time
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The way to go is like this. All kinds of trees and plants create a cool shade even in the middle of summer, and it feels like they are in the forest. Even on a sunny day, it is cool to enter this road. The forest bath is free. The road was a path that could be passed by a person at the beginning, but soon it became wide enough to have a wagon and wagon. As you walk, you meet various milestones. Imagine the old road going through the wheelbarrows that the carts have crossed, the bends of the horses dragging the carts on a steep slope, the washroom that the newspaper king has been washing for a while, and the fire sign that prevented cutting trees.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Yongyeon Falls, the dragon ascended - Gyeongju, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/227/4a143c58-ab11-4e34-b975-fc8d63881699.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Yongyeon Falls, the dragon ascended
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The road reaches its peak at Yongyeon Falls. It is said that this waterfall was created when the king of the newspaper ascended into a dragon when he put a piece of jade waistband obtained with the Manpasik. The waterfall exudes a cool energy even when you go nearby. The great effect of the water flowing from the waterfall is great. Even if you don&#39;t have to go into the water, the summer heat is washed away. It is like a chimney, but it is forbidden to get it because it is a sanctuary reserve. Wash your hands and face in cold water, and you will be satisfied. Heal the sadness by staying by the waterfall for a long time.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The rough water stream upstream of Yongyeon Falls - Gyeongju, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/227/d27218c9-4472-4ce4-9968-6c997ce39214.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The rough water stream upstream of Yongyeon Falls
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you go down about 800m from Yongyeon Falls, you will meet Girimsa, an ancient temple that was built before Bulguksa. The tour ends with a tour of the wide grounds of Kirimsa Temple, where the Virozana Buddha is located. You can go back to the way you came from here or take a bus to the city. Since the section is not long, even a round trip is 8 km, so it is suitable as a day course.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The grounds of Kirimsa Temple, which has a deeper history than Bulguksa Temple - Gyeongju, Gyeongbuk, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/227/8149abf0-ddcc-4c12-acad-ec4b96fb6a94.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The grounds of Kirimsa Temple, which has a deeper history than Bulguksa Temple
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Restaurants near
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Byeolchaeban Gyodong Ssambap: Ssambap / 77 Cheomseong-ro, Gyeongju-si, Gyeongsangbuk-do / 054-773-3322
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Lee Jo Han-sik: Han Jeong-sik / 136, Forest Head-gil, Gyeongju-si, Gyeongsangbuk-do / 054-775-3260
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Palwoojeong Haejangguk: Haejangguk / 810-1, Taejong-ro, Gyeongju-si, Gyeongsangbuk-do / 054-742-6515
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Hwangnam Millstone Sundubu: Tofu cuisine / 3 Nodjeon 2-gil, Gyeongju-si, Gyeongsangbuk-do / 054-771-7171
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Rooms
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Hotel Hyundai Gyeongju: 338 Bomun-ro, Gyeongju-si, Gyeongsangbuk-do / 054-748-2233
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.hyundaihotel.com/gyeongju/index.jsp&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.hyundaihotel.com/gyeongju/index.jsp
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Commodore Hotel Gyeongju: 422 Bomun-ro, Gyeongju-si, Gyeongsangbuk-do / 054-745-7701
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.commodorehotel.co.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.commodorehotel.co.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Daemyung Resort Gyeongju: 402-12, Bomun-ro, Gyeongju-si, Gyeongsangbuk-do / 054-778-8323
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.daemyungresort.com/gj&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.daemyungresort.com/gj
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Equus Motel: 10, Hwarang-ro 49beon-gil, Gyeongju-si, Gyeongsangbuk-do / 054-746-5700
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was created in July 2013, and may change later, so be sure to check it before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>