<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gangneung-si on Every Corner of Korea</title>
    <link>https://codecorea.github.io/tags/gangneung-si/</link>
    <description>Every Corner of Korea (Gangneung-si)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 09:00:53 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="https://codecorea.github.io/tags/gangneung-si/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Takju factory, mill, refined trend of refinery, Gangneung upcycling spot 3 - Gangneung-si, Gangwon-do, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/takju-factory-mill-refined-trend-of-refinery-gangneung-upcycling-spot-3-154/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 09:00:53 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/takju-factory-mill-refined-trend-of-refinery-gangneung-upcycling-spot-3-154/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Gangneung-si, Gangwon-do, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;takju-factory-mill-refined-trend-of-refinery-gangneung-upcycling-spot-3--154&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Willow Brewery, one of the best hot places in Gangneung - Gangneung-si, Gangwon-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/154/803367f7-1c91-463e-9b8c-bd044ac0a0fb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Willow Brewery, one of the best hot places in Gangneung
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Takju factory, mill, refined trend of refinery, Gangneung upcycling spot 3
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Gangneung-si, Gangwon-do, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Sneakers made by collecting PET bottles discarded in the sea, tarpaulins for old trucks, airbags for scrapped cars, bags made of seat belts, and watches made from scrapped bicycle chains are sold at a higher price than ordinary products. Some are not available because they are limited edition. Literally, the junk is transformed into a masterpiece. In the world, &#39;UpCycling&#39; is the trend. In Europe, upcycling crazes have been blowing in Korea since several years ago. Upcycling is derived from recycling, which means recycling, and refers to adding new values such as design beyond simply reusing discarded objects. Where is the fashion field? Upcycling spaces are emerging in Korea these days. Many places called hot places across the country are attracting attention by upcycling abandoned spaces. We can&#39;t introduce all the famous spots across the country, so let&#39;s start with Gangneung, the representative summer vacation destination. Trendy transformation of old Takju factory, mill, and refinery unfolds.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   &#39;Gangneung&#39; beer, willow brewery at the old Takju brewery
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   First, I visited the Takju factory, which has transformed into a chic Brewery. In short, it is &#39;Bird Tree Brewery&#39;, one of the best hot places in Gangneung. This is the third visit in the past two months. It&#39;s a frequent visit that the employee asks, &#34;Are you Gangneung?&#34; I enjoyed the willow brewery leisurely with good timing. The third visit was on the Saturday of July, which entered the summer. I was anxious. I rolled my own hair. &#39;There will be few people who are looking for a Mack house from the early afternoon of Saturday.&#39; However, the expectations were wrong. From Saturday afternoon, McDuck (beer Deokhoo) and travelers were filling the store. We realized the popularity of willow brewery and waited for a while before we settled inside.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The reason why we frequent the willow brewery, which is not close, is simple. The atmosphere is good and the beer tastes good. The biggest attraction of the willow brewery is that the elements that are unlikely to match are nicely harmonized.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;You can see the brewing facility through the glass window. - Gangneung-si, Gangwon-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/154/c591f7a5-ff52-42a7-8f11-9428978e8364.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     You can see the brewing facility through the glass window.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The prettiness and trendyness, and the conflicting things of Korea and the West make a beautiful sum. It is a Western sake of beer, which is made in the Korean space where makgeolli was made.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Korean beer is produced in the Takju brewery space - Gangneung-si, Gangwon-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/154/d77bbd92-5781-4949-916c-84d1484aebca.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Korean beer is produced in the Takju brewery space
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   This site was originally a Takju factory, with traces of time. Founded in 1926, it was the Gangneung Takju brewery that succeeded Gangneung Hapdong Brewery. The exact construction year of the current building is unknown, but traces of remaining objects are estimated to be in the 1970s.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Adding sensational elements to the traces of old buildings - Gangneung-si, Gangwon-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/154/088fe8f2-4847-4c82-a9eb-6c9a930de809.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Adding sensational elements to the traces of old buildings
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The Gangneung Takju factory, which had been closed by students from Susuboria Academy, a brewing educational institution co-founded by Gyeonggi University and the Agricultural Technology Commercialization Foundation, was transformed into a beer brewery in 2015. In the space where fermented rice wine was fermented, beer is now ripening deliciously. The transformation from makgeolli to beer does not completely exclude Korean colors. Here, extremely Korean, &#39;Gangneung&#39; beer is made.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Adding sensational elements to the traces of old buildings - Gangneung-si, Gangwon-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/154/631d6c18-f296-46f1-bd51-97cd1a5314fe.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Adding sensational elements to the traces of old buildings
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   You can tell from the beer name. It is unique in Minori sessions, Hasla IPA, irises, and Pine City Pale Ale. The Minori session is made using rice produced in Minori, Sacheon-myeon, Gangneung, and Changpo Ale is made with irises that symbolize Gangneung Danoje.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;12&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;There is also a &#39;sampler&#39; menu where you can taste various beers. - Gangneung-si, Gangwon-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/154/5fc7c502-0417-4afb-b70b-48eb343e386b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     There is also a &#39;sampler&#39; menu where you can taste various beers.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Hasla is the old name for Gangneung, and Pine City is the name of the slogan &#39;Solhyang Gangneung&#39;. As such, the willow tree produces a uniquely strong beer that captures the local characteristics of Gangneung by utilizing the mission of brewery rooted in Gangneung.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;14&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Hongje pizza with kimchi is popular - Gangneung-si, Gangwon-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/154/db569346-7e72-43de-bc36-4c685879535a.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Hongje pizza with kimchi is popular
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Space is the same. The basic framework of the old brewery was preserved. Old wooden ceilings, shabby walls, heavy iron doors, old iron desks, and faded wooden window frames are the highlights here.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;16&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Full of vintage items - Gangneung-si, Gangwon-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/154/721a7082-c1ab-4731-8fa3-f644bc725612.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Full of vintage items
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Vintage elements are not the end here. You can also see the clunky dishes and plates that you might have seen in your old grandmother&#39;s house, and the door-to-door television used as a cup and a water stand. Some of the tools used in the Takju plant remain. Strangely, the items that would be considered ugly become icons of &#39;cool&#39; here.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;18&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Full of vintage items - Gangneung-si, Gangwon-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/154/c5164e6e-7ced-434c-a257-f56e3f2f0956.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Full of vintage items
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Sarangbang, Bonbong Mill, where coffee is picked instead of rice cakes
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   I drank a glass of beer, so driving is prohibited. Find a place to go on foot. We steamed the neighborhood Myeongju-dong next to Hongje-dong, where Willow Brewery is located. I had to go once before, and I always headed for the sea. This time I decided to head to Myeongju-dong. Myeongju-dong was once a downtown area of Gangneung, but now it has become a secluded old city center. The moment I entered the alley, I realized. After all, the power of time cannot be ignored. The traces and stories that the years have accumulated silently captured the stranger&#39;s footsteps at one point. Myeongju Sarangchae, a small performance hall, and a few cute cafes were seen. Someone might say, &#39;Is this all?&#39; It was good not to overdo it like alleys, which are hot places in Seoul, so the slow speed of the old alleys remained true.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Myeongju-dong&#39;s representative caffeine bonbon mill - Gangneung-si, Gangwon-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/154/6e786d3c-dde6-42ff-84b1-938eb933abab.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Myeongju-dong&#39;s representative caffeine bonbon mill
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you come to Myeongju-dong, this is a must-visit place. It is a 10-minute walk from the willow brewery. I wandered for a moment in the alley and asked someone I met on the road to find the location of the Bonbong Mill. I think the local specialty is right. It tells the location at once. The name &#39;Bongbong Mill&#39; is painted on a building with a pointed roof.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The first floor of a comfortable atmosphere like a neighborhood love room - Gangneung-si, Gangwon-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/154/d3b6a825-7e4e-494a-93b6-4a4ff6b51fa3.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The first floor of a comfortable atmosphere like a neighborhood love room
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Like the name, this was a real mill. It was once a place where people lined up and made rice cakes. In the course of the years, the mill was closed and left as an empty house for more than 10 years, and then in 2010, it made connections with people in the field of culture and art. After a year of manual space, the bonbong mill was opened in 2011, where coffee, culture and art and people coexist.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A cafe and a second floor space like a gallery - Gangneung-si, Gangwon-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/154/c56fe5b6-a318-4fff-84a3-7b9365a812db.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A cafe and a second floor space like a gallery
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It&#39;s more stylish because it&#39;s unfamiliar with painted walls, old tiled floors, and old windows. It is comfortable because it is not decorated. The owner of the hand drip coffee greets the people in the village. Instead of plucking rice cakes and squeezing sesame oil, they just bake cookies and brew coffee. The Gentiles are also tied to the atmosphere and rest as comfortable as the people in this town.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Local artists&#39; works are displayed throughout the year - Gangneung-si, Gangwon-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/154/1e223862-eb62-48e2-a7d6-1d80a51fbd64.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Local artists&#39; works are displayed throughout the year
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   All coffee is roasted and hand-dried. Coffee that has passed through the human hand and mind, not the machine, has a warmer sensibility. There are windows everywhere, and there is a work hanging in between. Even the scenery outside the ordinary window feels like a work here.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Works and props created by cultural artists are also displayed and sold. - Gangneung-si, Gangwon-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/154/c5bcdf9d-3056-44be-a475-2dc2f974e0b1.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Works and props created by cultural artists are also displayed and sold.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Would you like a cup of coffee at the refinery? Coffee Refinery per Second
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   I was immersed in the charm of Gangneung&#39;s upcycling spaces. He shouted &#39;one more place for my best friend&#39; and went to Chodang-dong, famous for Sundang tofu. I only went to eat Champon Sundubu and Chodang Sundubu, but today I head to the rice mill instead of the restaurant. Enter the side street slightly from Chodang Sundubu Village lined with restaurants. As we walk along the alleys of a cozy neighborhood, we see a shabby building with a wooden signboard called &#39;chodangjeongmiso&#39;. Stop walking there where time has stopped.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;An old rice mill turned into a cafe - Gangneung-si, Gangwon-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/154/71453619-c196-409d-b252-e3290e4639f9.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     An old rice mill turned into a cafe
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   I open the cafe door with the feeling of entering the refinery. The refinery machine, which still occupies a place among the owners, attracts attention. On the wall of the cafe, a transparent plate was laid and rice bran was filled in between. Although it has been transformed into a cafe, there are traces of it all over the place that you don&#39;t want to forget that this place was a refinery. Snow moves along the old trail, including uneven ceiling wood, refinery machine belts, and an old clock that seems to be telling no more time.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;4&#34; id3=&#34;15&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;It is more special by keeping the atmosphere of the refinery intact - Gangneung-si, Gangwon-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/154/331798de-2b58-4457-bf7f-362c0fb6a032.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     It is more special by keeping the atmosphere of the refinery intact
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   A record of 1963 is recorded in Sangnyangmun, which records the history of building or repairing a house. It is a fairly old building. In the days when food production was a national task, and during the time when rice paddies were built to fill the surroundings of Gyeongpo Lake, the Chodangjeongso was an important space for cultivating rice in this town. As the world changed over the years, Chodangjeongmi, which was filled with people, closed.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;6&#34; id3=&#34;16&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;There are traces of the refinery inside and outside the cafe. - Gangneung-si, Gangwon-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/154/20cfab57-25f8-4b72-8fc3-858bb3a9e4fc.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     There are traces of the refinery inside and outside the cafe.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The owner, who is a native of Chodang-dong, was sorry that the place of memories, Jeongmiso, disappeared. So, he took over Jeongmiso and turned it into a cafe where anyone can relax. Of course, the traces of the refinery remained as much as possible. As expressed by the architect on the wall, the architecture of the Chodang Coffee Refinery was faithful to the role of `` Lessing less resources and leaving many memories. &#39;&#39;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;8&#34; id3=&#34;17&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;There are traces of the refinery inside and outside the cafe. - Gangneung-si, Gangwon-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/154/f9a7b13d-4413-41bc-b718-6bbc9c770e89.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     There are traces of the refinery inside and outside the cafe.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The cafe is not finished just because the traces of the refinery remain. There are savory coffees and various drinks here. Also, the menu utilizing local characteristics of Chodang Sundubu Village is also noticeable. Chodang tofu banana smoothie, condibi cookie, condibi pound cake It is a menu created by the owner who runs the Chodang Sundubu restaurant nearby. It&#39;s a meeting between bean cake, cookies and pound cake ... . I can&#39;t imagine the taste of the combination. In this case, try eating it yourself. The savory and plain taste is attractive. The more you chew like rice, which is the main character of Jeongmiso, the more you sue it.
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    The reason why the upcycling spots in Gangneung met deeply is that the traces of heavy years and people&#39;s stories have been added to the space. This is because yesterday, where we live today wants to go back sometimes, remain in the space.
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;10&#34; id3=&#34;18&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Coffee and bean cookies are a blend of fantasy! - Gangneung-si, Gangwon-do, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/154/194a6422-f8fa-448c-b517-cacda2171dbf.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Coffee and bean cookies are a blend of fantasy!
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Willow Brewery
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Address: 1961 Gyeonggang-ro, Gangneung-si, Gangwon-do
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Opening hours: 12: 00 ~ 24: 00 (only beer and drinks can be ordered from 16:00 to 17:00)
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Inquiries: 033-920-9380
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Bonbon mill
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Address: 17-1 Gyeonggang-ro 2024beon-gil, Gangneung-si, Gangwon-do
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Opening hours: 11: 00 ~ 21: 00 (until 18:00 on Sundays), closed every Monday
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Inquiries: 070-8237-1155
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Coffee Refinery per Second
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Address: 67, Chodangwon-gil, Gangneung-si, Gangwon-do
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Business hours: 10: 00 ~ 22: 00
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Inquiries: 033-653-2313
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Nearby destinations
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Gangneung Jungang Market: 21, Geumseong-ro / 033-648-2285
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.gncmarket.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.gncmarket.com/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Ojukheon: 24 Yulgok-ro 3139beon-gil / 033-660-3301
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Heoyun &amp;amp; Heonan Seolheon Memorial Park: 1-16 / 193beon-gil, Nanseolheon-ro 033-640-4798
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Rooms
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Gangneung Ojuk Hanok Village: 114 Jukheon-gil / 033-655-1117
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://ojuk.or.kr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://ojuk.or.kr/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Gangneung Guesthouse Central Store: 17, Gyeonggang-ro 2103beon-gil / 010-9299-7199 / Korean Tourism Quality Certification
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://gnguesthouse4.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://gnguesthouse4.com/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Principal Gangneung Mission: 63 Unjeong-gil / 033-646-3270 / Korea Tourism Quality Certification
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.knsgj.net/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.knsgj.net/
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was created in July 2017, and may be changed later, so please check before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>