<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gwangsan-gu on Korea Tour</title>
    <link>https://codecorea.github.io/tags/gwangsan-gu/</link>
    <description>Korea Tour (Gwangsan-gu)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 21:04:01 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="https://codecorea.github.io/tags/gwangsan-gu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Квангсан-гу, Кванджу, Южная Корея - Линия Honam KTX в Надую, Горный район Кванджу</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/honam-line-ktx-to-naduya-gwangju-mining-area-42-ru/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 21:04:01 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/honam-line-ktx-to-naduya-gwangju-mining-area-42-ru/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-title=&#34;honam-line-ktx-to-naduya-gwangju-mining-area--42&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Станция Кванджу Сончжон - Квангсан-гу, Кванджу, Южная Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/acf39ebe-6300-4c75-b577-2546cf4ee2a3.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Станция Кванджу Сончжон
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Линия Honam KTX в Надую, Горный район Кванджу
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Квангсан-гу, Кванджу, Южная Корея
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Секция Honam Line KTX Express была расширена до станции Кванджу Сонгчон в Кванджу. KTX, который отправился со станции Yongsan, прибыл на станцию Gwangju Songjeong за 1 час 33 минуты, и можно было отправиться в Кванджу, совершив однодневную поездку в столичном регионе. В непосредственной близости от станции Кванджу Сунчжон находятся такие достопримечательности, как место рождения Йонга, Вулбонг Сеуон, Вольге-донг Чанггобун, парк Сончжон и руины Синьчан-донг.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Удобен для поездок на метро или по городу перед станцией Кванджу Сончжон
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   До того, как в 2001 году было завершено строительство автомагистрали Западного побережья, туристам в столичном районе было удобно использовать платные ворота шахты Хонам для поездок в такие провинции Хонама, как Мокпхо, Йонгам и Наджу. С тех пор появление скоростной автомагистрали Гочан-Дамьянг последовало за появлением скоростной автомагистрали Западного побережья, в результате чего название «добыча полезных ископаемых» стало слабым в головах туристов. Затем, с недавним открытием линии Honam KTX, горнодобывающий район со станцией Gwangju Songjeong был восстановлен в качестве горячей темы. Местные жители ожидают, что число посетителей станции Кванджу Сунчжон увеличится с 4000 в среднем до 12000.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;KTX на станции Кванджу Сончжон - Квангсан-гу, Кванджу, Южная Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/a8d01ab7-1597-41ac-9729-c41f541ee3be.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     KTX на станции Кванджу Сончжон
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Имя «Квангсан-гу» родилось в 1988 году, когда Сунчжон и округ Майнинг были включены в Кванджу. Из пяти районов, составляющих Кванджу, этот район занимает 222,9㎢ (44,05%), самый большой. Прямо перед новой станцией станции Кванджу Сунчжон находится станция метро с тем же названием. Метро в Кванджу курсирует между станцией Окдонг, станцией Кванджу Сончжон, аэропортом Кванджу, конференц-центром Kimdaejung, Geumnam-ro, Культурным залом, въездом в Хакдонг и Чжунгсимса и станцией Юнсан. Иностранные путешественники могут сесть на линию Honam Line KTX и сойти на станции Кванджу Сончжон и доехать до метро для удобной транспортировки вокруг Кванджу.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Озеро Мугунхва останавливается у станции Кванджу Сонгчон - Квангсан-гу, Кванджу, Южная Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/8e923e82-af6f-4390-b796-dc64894bc9dc.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Озеро Мугунхва останавливается у станции Кванджу Сонгчон
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Парк Йонг-А наслаждается литературным путешествием на родине
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Место рождения Йонга - одна из самых популярных туристических достопримечательностей возле станции Кванджу Сунчжон в Квангсан-гу. «Юн-а» - ребенок Пак Юн-чхоль (1904–1938), который работал поэтом во время японской оккупации. Он родился в Гвансан-гу, работал с Юнг-Рангом Кимом и Юнгом Чжи-Ёном над публикацией литературной литературы. Поэт опубликовал свои ведущие произведения «Оставляя лодки и отправляя тебя в ночной поезд», в «Первой поэтической литературе». Вот посмотрите на его стихотворение «Покидая корабль». Специальность выгравирована на гранитном оплодотворении клумбы дракончика.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     Я пойду / мой молодой возраст /
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     Собираетесь ли вы отправить слезы?
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Этим уютным укрывателям будет легко?
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     Даже водянистые глаза, как туман
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Зрелая форма клюва на каждой ноге долины /
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     Морщины тоже спелые глаза! Любимые //
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Я не могу забыть того, кто выбрасывает это
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     Чем отличается погоня?
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Облака оглядываются назад, ветер белый /
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     Будут ли перед нами альпинисты //
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Я такая красивая / мой молодой возраст /
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     Ты отпустишь со слезами?
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Оплодотворение установлено в месте рождения дракона - Квангсан-гу, Кванджу, Южная Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/ddb73935-d6cc-4c49-864e-add053f35644.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Оплодотворение установлено в месте рождения дракона
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Вероятно, из-за песни певца Ким Су Чула это стихотворение близко к нам. Ким Су Чул цитирует часть стихов поэта Пак Ён Чула в песне &amp;lt;Go To Me Too&amp;gt;. Желание расстаться с молодыми веками со слезами и найти мечту было независимостью страны для поэта Пак Ён-чула и для певца Ким Су Чула. Несмотря на то, что направление отличается в зависимости от времени, ценность по-прежнему так много людей любят свои слова и слова.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Портрет поэтов, охраняющих двор - Квангсан-гу, Кванджу, Южная Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/75ab670b-5ac5-47c2-993a-f500d165eb45.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Портрет поэтов, охраняющих двор
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Невысказанные разговоры с поэтами
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Давайте еще немного продолжим литературную жизнь парка Йонга. Он также публиковал «Литературный ежемесячник» и «Литературу», переводил и представлял иностранные стихи и пьесы. Он также работал литературным критиком, но, к сожалению, он умер в возрасте около 30 лет. Причиной смерти стал туберкулез. В дополнение к его месту рождения, его оплодотворение, которое гравирует Оставляющую Лодку, также установлено на склоне Yangji, который приводит к Парку Songjeong.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   Место рождения поэта окружено каменными стенами, очищенными от охры. Это соломенный дом с широким двором, цветником и джангдокдае. Возможно, из-за его литературной деятельности с Юнгом Чжи-ёнгом и Ким Янг-рангом взгляд на каждый уголок его места рождения, естественно, напоминает ему о таких стихах, как &amp;lt;Духи&amp;gt; и Ким Янг-Ранга «Солнце на каменной стене».
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Еще одна вещь, которая бросается в глаза, это большая кисть, которая рисовала лица шести поэтов. Он использовался на литературном фестивале Yonga в 2014 году, и во дворе даже есть доска для рисования, поэтому он менее оживленный. Поэтические поэты, такие как Ким Юн-сик, Юнг Ин-бо, Бюн Янг-ро, Юнг Юн-Ён, Пак Юн-Чхоль и Ли Ха-Юн расцвели, как цветочное вино. Их следы также можно найти в Музее литературы и литературы (открыт в 2012 году) в Ганджин-эуп, Ганджин-гун. Кан Джин является родиной Ким Янга Рана. Покидая место рождения Юн-Аха, я вспоминаю другой репрезентативный фильм Пак Юн-чула &#34;Отправка тебя в ночной поезд&#34;.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Соломенный дом - Квангсан-гу, Кванджу, Южная Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/17fcbc08-8b03-47ee-9313-e72b7ea6ccbf.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Соломенный дом
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     Теперь далекой зимой весенний день
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     Я посмотрю на это.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Смеясь, как весенний день, он бросается в поезд
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     Я буду ждать.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     «Забудь» означает Смеяться так /
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     Позволь мне учиться
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Идя по неровной дороге,
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     Давайте последуем примеру.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Наконец он будет последователем.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Лицо поэта, как видно из оплодотворения парка Сончжон - Квангсан-гу, Кванджу, Южная Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/6793ad6d-7d7d-4a0d-a54c-f922b0bddfda.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Лицо поэта, как видно из оплодотворения парка Сончжон
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Учился у Wolbongseowon, высокий пик
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Шаги путешественников, которые наслаждались литературными путешествиями, ведут к исследованию их обетов. Wolbongseowon, расположенный в Gwangsan-gu, Gwangsan-gu, довольно старомоден от пути от парковки до входа в Seowon. Это потому, что низкая деревенская стена, аккуратно выложенная плиткой, проходит по сельской дороге. Wolbongseowon был основан в 1578 году, после смерти учителя. В настоящее время считается одной из восьми сцен Кванджу.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Гобонг известен как ученый, который обменялся теорией с Тогье Ли Хван. Главная аудитория Seowon называется Bingwoldang. Чунджо купил благородные школьные добродетели Гобонга и дал название «Снежная стена Бингсим». Любезное чтение присяжных с корейским переводом любезно добавляет к наслаждению обетом. Книга начинается с «Возьми книгу, найди учителя и поднимись к высшему отшельнику» и заканчивая среднюю часть: «Что будет потом оплакиваться, разделить на драконов и свиней? ». «Стремитесь сегодня» содержит уроки.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   «Основа государства - сделать людей спокойными. Только после того, как люди почувствуют себя комфортно, можно достичь просветления. Этому нужно учить после того, как люди сначала укрепятся, и люди станут богатыми. »
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Wolbongseowon View - Квангсан-гу, Кванджу, Южная Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/db196ed4-3eac-4115-b420-18d04fcf5c49.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Wolbongseowon View
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Если у вас будет достаточно времени, давайте пойдем по пути философов. Это пешеходная трасса от Вулбонга Сеуона до Бэквуджонга, руин Кючжонам, мавзолея Гобонга и Хуфуджи.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;T - Квангсан-гу, Кванджу, Южная Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/0ec9602f-f344-483a-acce-20a9d9212d73.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     T
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Руины в центре города, руины Синьчан-донг и Вольге-донг Чанггобун
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   После изучения места рождения и обетов поэта он посещает культурные останки, которые не очень известны иностранным туристам, даже если они находятся в центре города. Руины Синьчан-донг и Чанггобун из Вольге-дон находятся возле развязки шахты скоростной дороги Хонам.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Руины Синьчан-донга (Исторический № 375) могут быть разочарованы, потому что это поле без улиц и музеев. Однако, согласно описанию Национального музея Кванджу, есть много реликвий, таких как глиняная посуда, дерево, киль и лакированные изделия, которые дают представление о сельскохозяйственной культуре первого века до нашей эры. Представьте себе дни, когда не было бы подъездных путей или жилых комплексов, и вы можете представить, что люди были очень хорошим местом для жизни в группах. В частности, Шин Чанг-дон получил прозвище «Древняя текстильная фабрика» за то, что были выкопаны самые старые в Корее реликвии из шелка и мешковины, тела, шпульки и костяные иглы, необходимые для производства этих тканей. В главном зале на первом этаже Национального музея Кванджу до 25 мая будет проходить специальная выставка «Шелковая страна, текстильная культура Синьчан-дон, Кванджу».
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;5&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Синьчан-дон Историческое место - Квангсан-гу, Кванджу, Южная Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/4e0190e6-2f28-430d-a7a6-8cae29027cf7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Синьчан-дон Историческое место
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Janggobun, Wolgye-Dong (местный памятник № 20 столичного города Кванджу) назван в честь формы гробницы. Он был обнаружен во время строительства передового научного парка Кванджу в 1990-х годах, и считается, что он был построен в 5-6 веках. Торговый центр и жилой комплекс построены вокруг гробницы, и это культурное наследие, которое любят граждане для прогулок.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;5&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Wolgye-Dong Janggobun - Квангсан-гу, Кванджу, Южная Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/4839be3a-141d-484f-89f6-6cea258f06a3.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Wolgye-Dong Janggobun
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Завершите свое путешествие с Ттеокгалби, Наксамтангом и Сундэ Гукбапом.
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Вернитесь на станцию Кванджу Сончжон, чтобы попробовать фирменные блюда. Улица Tteokgalbi была сформирована вокруг Офиса Gwangsan-gu давным-давно, привлекая вкусы путешественников. Если запах печеного ттеокгалби наполняет переулок, каким бы жадным он ни был, вы не можете не расслабиться. В настоящее время японские и китайские туристы также приходят, чтобы услышать слухи. Вкус Songjeongri Tteokgalbi немного отличается от дома к дому, поэтому вам не нужно рекомендовать дом.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;6&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Сончжон-ри Ттеокгалби - Квангсан-гу, Кванджу, Южная Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/12f8958a-72eb-48ff-bf36-d845ebd7adb8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Сончжон-ри Ттеокгалби
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Naksamtang также деликатес в Кванджу. Вареную кашу из мунг с костным бульоном, положить в нее женьшень, каштаны и мармелад, а затем добавить одну к осьминогу. Усамтанг - это стиль вареного вареного яйца вместо осьминога.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;6&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Naksamtang - Квангсан-гу, Кванджу, Южная Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/8d5fd99c-b6c5-4184-a7f7-6eb398302745.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Naksamtang
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   В начале шахты, напротив входа на станцию Сончжон, есть пять или шесть ресторанов с фруктовым супом.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;6&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Уличный рынок станции Сончон - Квангсан-гу, Кванджу, Южная Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/e219acf6-393b-4493-8246-41ff3b59c163.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Уличный рынок станции Сончон
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   В дополнение к Sundae Gukbap, суп из супа Naejang Gukbap, Seonji Gukbap и Ampoon Sundae делают желудки легких путешественников более легкими.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;6&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Мороженое с фруктами - Квангсан-гу, Кванджу, Южная Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/58f2aec1-160e-4487-a499-f37b4c1ad57e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Мороженое с фруктами
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;7&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;15&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Васаби на рынке - Квангсан-гу, Кванджу, Южная Корея (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/f1b982b8-478e-4d38-9086-64a8c830ecf5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Васаби на рынке
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Информация о путешествии
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Дракончик
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Адрес: 24 Sochon-ro 46beon-Gil, Квангсан-гу, Кванджу
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Запросы: Управление шахтной культуры, Спортивный отдел 062-960-8251
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Wolbong Seowon
      &lt;br/&gt;
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     Адрес: Гвангсан-гу, 133, Гвангсан-гу, Кванджу
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Контакт: 062-432-1318
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.wolbong.org/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
      http://www.wolbong.org/
     &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Близлежащие рестораны
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Джанган Осьминог: Наксамтанг / 5, Гвангсан-ро 30бен-гиль / Гвангсан-гу / 062-942-4545
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Сончхон Ттеокгалби (1-я ветвь): Ттеокгалби / 1, Квангсан-ро 29беон-гиль, Квангсан-гу / 062-944-1439
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Jangsu Gukbap: Sundae Gukbap / 1-1, Mine-ro, Gwangsan-gu / 062-945-8533
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Размещение
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Гостиница Santamo Tourist: 10-11, Saam-ro 216beon-gil, Gwangsan-gu / 062-956-5000
    &lt;br/&gt;
    e-Motel: 13-12, Mujin-daero 231beon-gil, Gwangsan-gu / 062-430-5707
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Роскошный мотель: 13-20, Mujin-daero 212beon-gil, Gwangsan-gu / 062-714-2110
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ Приведенная выше информация была предоставлена в феврале 2015 года. Впоследствии она может измениться, поэтому, пожалуйста, проверьте это перед поездкой.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Информация, такая как текст, фотографии и видео, используемые в этой статье, защищены авторским правом Корейской туристической организации, поэтому несанкционированное использование статьи запрещено.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, Corée du Sud - Honam Line KTX à Naduya, zone minière de Gwangju</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/honam-line-ktx-to-naduya-gwangju-mining-area-42-fr/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 21:00:04 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/honam-line-ktx-to-naduya-gwangju-mining-area-42-fr/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-title=&#34;honam-line-ktx-to-naduya-gwangju-mining-area--42&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Station Gwangju Songjeong - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, Corée du Sud (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/acf39ebe-6300-4c75-b577-2546cf4ee2a3.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Station Gwangju Songjeong
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Honam Line KTX à Naduya, zone minière de Gwangju
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, Corée du Sud
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   La section Honam Line KTX Express a été étendue à la station Gwangju Songjeong à Gwangju. KTX, qui a quitté la gare de Yongsan, est arrivé à la gare de Gwangju Songjeong en 1 heure 33 minutes, et il était possible de sortir à Gwangju en faisant une excursion d&#39;une journée dans la région métropolitaine. Dans les environs de la gare de Gwangju Songjeong, il y a des attractions telles que le lieu de naissance de Yonga, Wolbong Seowon, Wolgye-dong Janggobun, le parc Songjeong et les ruines de Sinchang-dong.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Pratique pour voyager en métro ou en ville devant la gare de Gwangju Songjeong
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Avant l&#39;achèvement de l&#39;autoroute de la côte ouest en 2001, il était pratique pour les touristes de la région métropolitaine d&#39;utiliser le péage de la mine de l&#39;autoroute Honam pour se rendre dans les provinces de Honam telles que Mokpo, Yeongam et Naju. Depuis lors, l&#39;émergence de l&#39;autoroute Gochang-Damyang a suivi l&#39;émergence de l&#39;autoroute West Coast Expressway, ce qui rend le nom «minier» évanoui dans la tête des touristes. Puis, avec l&#39;ouverture récente de la Honam Line KTX, le district minier avec la station Gwangju Songjeong a été relancé comme un sujet brûlant. Les résidents locaux s&#39;attendent à ce que le nombre de visiteurs à la gare de Gwangju Songjeong passe de 4 000 en moyenne à 12 000.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;KTX à la station Gwangju Songjeong - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, Corée du Sud (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/a8d01ab7-1597-41ac-9729-c41f541ee3be.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     KTX à la station Gwangju Songjeong
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Le nom «Gwangsan-gu» est né en 1988 lorsque Songjeong et le comté minier ont été incorporés à Gwangju. Des cinq districts qui composent Gwangju, la zone occupe 222,9㎢ (44,05%), le plus grand. Il y a une station de métro du même nom juste en face de la nouvelle station de la station Gwangju Songjeong. Le métro de Gwangju relie la gare d&#39;Okdong, la gare de Gwangju Songjeong, l&#39;aéroport de Gwangju, le centre de convention de Kimdaejung, Geumnam-ro, le Culture Hall, l&#39;entrée Hakdong et Jeungsimsa et la station de véhicules Yongsan. Les voyageurs étrangers peuvent prendre la Honam Line KTX et descendre à la station Gwangju Songjeong et prendre le métro pour un transport facile autour de Gwangju.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Le lac Mugunghwa s&#39;arrête à la station Gwangju Songjeong - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, Corée du Sud (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/8e923e82-af6f-4390-b796-dc64894bc9dc.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Le lac Mugunghwa s&#39;arrête à la station Gwangju Songjeong
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Le parc Yong-A profite d&#39;un voyage littéraire au lieu de naissance
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Le lieu de naissance de Yonga est l&#39;une des attractions touristiques les plus populaires près de la gare de Gwangju Songjeong à Gwangsan-gu. &#39;Yong-ah&#39; est un enfant de Park Yong-cheol (1904 ~ 1938) qui a travaillé comme poète pendant l&#39;occupation japonaise. Né à Gwangsan-gu, il a travaillé avec Young-Rang Kim et Jung Ji-yong pour publier la littérature littéraire. Le poète a publié ses principaux ouvrages, Leaving Boats et Sending You in the Night Train, dans The First of Poetry Literature. Voici un aperçu de son poème Leaving Ship. La spécialité est gravée sur la fertilisation granitique du parterre de l&#39;enfant dragon.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     Je vais y aller / mon jeune age /
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     Allez-vous envoyer des larmes?
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Ces portiers confortables vont-ils être faciles?
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     Même les yeux larmoyants comme le brouillard
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Forme de bec mûr à chaque pied de la vallée /
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     Les rides ont également des yeux mûrs! Bien-aimés //
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Je ne peux pas oublier celui qui le jette /
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     Qu&#39;est-ce qui est différent d&#39;être poursuivi?
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Les nuages regardent en arrière, le vent est blanc /
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     Y aura-t-il des grimpeurs en face de nous //
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Je suis si jolie / mon jeune âge /
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     Voulez-vous vous laisser aller avec des larmes?
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Jeu de fertilisation au berceau du dragon - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, Corée du Sud (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/ddb73935-d6cc-4c49-864e-add053f35644.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Jeu de fertilisation au berceau du dragon
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   C&#39;est probablement à cause de la chanson de la chanteuse Kim Soo-chul que ce poème se rapproche de nous. Kim Soo-cheol cite une partie des poèmes du poète Park Yong-chul dans la chanson &amp;lt;Go To Me Too&amp;gt;. Le désir de quitter les plus jeunes avec des larmes et de trouver un rêve était l&#39;indépendance du pays pour le poète Park Yong-chul et pour la chanteuse Kim Soo-chul. Même si la direction est différente selon les époques, la valeur est toujours tellement de gens aiment leurs mots et leurs paroles.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Portrait de poètes gardant la cour - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, Corée du Sud (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/75ab670b-5ac5-47c2-993a-f500d165eb45.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Portrait de poètes gardant la cour
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Conversations tacites avec des poètes
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Suivons un peu plus la vie littéraire de Yonga Park. Il a également publié Literary Monthly and Literature, et traduit et présenté des poèmes et des pièces de théâtre étrangers. Il a également travaillé comme critique littéraire, mais malheureusement, il est décédé au milieu de la trentaine. La cause du décès était la tuberculose. En plus de son lieu de naissance, sa fertilisation, qui grave Leaving Boat, est également installée sur la pente de Yangji, qui mène au parc Songjeong.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   Le lieu de naissance du poète est entouré de murs en pierre dégagés d&#39;ocre. C&#39;est une maison au toit de chaume avec une grande cour, un parterre de fleurs et un jangdokdae. Peut-être en raison de ses activités littéraires avec Jung Ji-yong et Kim Young-rang, regarder chaque recoin de son lieu de naissance lui rappelle naturellement des poèmes tels que &amp;lt;Parfum&amp;gt; et &amp;lt;Sunshine on a Stone Wall&amp;gt; de Kim Young-rang.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Une autre chose qui attire votre attention est le grand pinceau qui a peint les visages de six poètes. Il a été utilisé au Yonga Literary Festival en 2014, et il y a même un tableau de peinture dans la cour, donc il est moins vivant. Des poètes tels que Kim Yun-sik, Jung In-bo, Byun Young-ro, Jung Yong-yong, Park Yong-cheol et Lee Ha-yun ont fleuri comme du vin de fleur. Leurs empreintes peuvent également être trouvées au Musée de la littérature et de la littérature (ouvert en 2012) à Gangjin-eup, Gangjin-gun. Kang Jin est le lieu de naissance de Kim Young Rang. En quittant le lieu de naissance de Yong-Ah, je me souviens de l&#39;autre film représentatif de Park Yong-chul, Sending You to the Night Train.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Maison au toit de chaume - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, Corée du Sud (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/17fcbc08-8b03-47ee-9313-e72b7ea6ccbf.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Maison au toit de chaume
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     Maintenant, dans le lointain hiver, jour de printemps
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     Je vais le regarder.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Riant comme un jour de printemps, il précipite son train
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     J&#39;attendrai.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     &#34;Oubliez&#34; Meaners Riez comme ceci /
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     Laisse moi apprendre
     &lt;br/&gt;
     En marchant sur la route accidentée,
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     Suivons l&#39;exemple.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Il sera enfin un disciple.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Le visage du poète vu de la fertilisation du parc Songjeong - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, Corée du Sud (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/6793ad6d-7d7d-4a0d-a54c-f922b0bddfda.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Le visage du poète vu de la fertilisation du parc Songjeong
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Tiré de Wolbongseowon, le haut sommet
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Les pas des voyageurs qui ont apprécié les voyages littéraires conduisent à l&#39;exploration de leurs vœux. Wolbongseowon, situé à Gwangsan-gu, Gwangsan-gu, est assez désuet depuis le chemin du parking jusqu&#39;à l&#39;entrée de Seowon. En effet, un muret en terre battue, soigneusement carrelé, traverse une route de village. Wolbongseowon a été fondée en 1578, après la mort du professeur. Il est maintenant considéré comme l&#39;une des huit scènes de Gwangju.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Gobong est célèbre en tant qu&#39;érudit qui a échangé la théorie avec Toegye Lee Hwang. L&#39;auditorium principal de Seowon s&#39;appelle Bingwoldang. Chungjo a acheté les nobles vertus scolaires de Gobong et a donné le titre de «Bingsim Snowwall». La bonne lecture du jury avec la traduction coréenne ajoute gentiment à la jouissance du vœu. Le livre commence par «Obtenez un livre et trouvez un professeur et montez vers un ermite élevé», et termine la section du milieu par «Qu&#39;est-ce qui sera déploré plus tard divisé en dragons et porcs? ». «Efforcez-vous aujourd&#39;hui» contient des leçons.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   «Le fondement de l&#39;État est de mettre les gens à l&#39;aise. Ce n&#39;est qu&#39;après que les gens sont à l&#39;aise que l&#39;illumination peut être faite. Elle doit être enseignée une fois que le peuple a été renforcé et que le peuple est devenu riche. &#34;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Vue de Wolbongseowon - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, Corée du Sud (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/db196ed4-3eac-4115-b420-18d04fcf5c49.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Vue de Wolbongseowon
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Si vous avez beaucoup de temps, parcourons le chemin des philosophes. Il s&#39;agit d&#39;un cours de marche de Wolbong Seowon à Baekwoojeong, aux ruines de Kyujeonam, au mausolée de Gobong et à Khufujae.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;La quantité de Bingwoldang, la principale salle de conférence de Wolbong Seowon - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, Corée du Sud (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/0ec9602f-f344-483a-acce-20a9d9212d73.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     La quantité de Bingwoldang, la principale salle de conférence de Wolbong Seowon
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Ruines du centre-ville, ruines de Sinchang-dong et Wolgye-dong Janggobun
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Après avoir exploré le lieu de naissance et les vœux du poète, il visite des vestiges culturels qui ne sont pas bien connus des touristes étrangers, même s&#39;ils sont dans le centre-ville. Les ruines de Sinchang-dong et Janggobun de Wolgye-dong sont situées près de l&#39;échangeur de la mine Honam Expressway.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Les ruines de Sinchang-dong (historique n ° 375) peuvent être déçues car c&#39;est un champ sans rues et sans musées. Cependant, selon la description du Musée national de Gwangju, il existe de nombreuses reliques telles que la faïence, le bois, la quille et la laque qui donnent un aperçu de la culture agricole du premier siècle avant JC. Imaginez les jours où il n&#39;y aurait pas d&#39;allées ou de complexes d&#39;appartements, et vous pouvez imaginer que les gens étaient un très bon endroit pour vivre en groupe. En particulier, Shin Chang-dong a été surnommée `` l&#39;ancienne usine de textile &#39;&#39; en ce que les plus anciennes reliques de soie et de toile de jute de Corée, les corps, les bobines de fil et les aiguilles à os nécessaires pour produire ces tissus ont été fouillés. Dans le hall principal du premier étage du Musée national de Gwangju, une exposition spéciale se tiendra jusqu&#39;au 25 mai, «Le pays de la soie, la culture textile de Sinchang-dong, Gwangju».
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;5&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Site historique de Sinchang-dong - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, Corée du Sud (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/4e0190e6-2f28-430d-a7a6-8cae29027cf7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Site historique de Sinchang-dong
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Janggobun, Wolgye-dong (monument local n ° 20 de la ville métropolitaine de Gwangju) est nommé d&#39;après la forme de la tombe. Il a été découvert lors de la construction du parc scientifique avancé de Gwangju dans les années 1990 et aurait été construit entre le 5 et le 6e siècle. Un centre commercial et un complexe d&#39;appartements sont construits autour de la tombe et c&#39;est un patrimoine culturel qui est apprécié comme lieu de promenade pour les citoyens.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;5&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Wolgye-dong Janggobun - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, Corée du Sud (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/4839be3a-141d-484f-89f6-6cea258f06a3.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Wolgye-dong Janggobun
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Terminez votre voyage avec Tteokgalbi, Naksamtang et Sundae Gukbap
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Retournez à la station Gwangju Songjeong pour déguster les spécialités de la mine. La rue Tteokgalbi s&#39;est formée il y a longtemps autour du bureau de Gwangsan-gu, attirant les goûts des voyageurs. Si l&#39;odeur de la cuisson du tteokgalbi remplit la ruelle, peu importe sa gourmandise, vous ne pouvez pas vous empêcher de vous détendre. De nos jours, les touristes japonais et chinois viennent également entendre les rumeurs. Songjeongri Tteokgalbi a un goût légèrement différent d&#39;une maison à l&#39;autre, vous n&#39;avez donc pas à recommander de maison.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;6&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Songjeong-ri Tteokgalbi - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, Corée du Sud (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/12f8958a-72eb-48ff-bf36-d845ebd7adb8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Songjeong-ri Tteokgalbi
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Le Naksamtang est aussi une délicatesse à Gwangju. Bouillie de haricot mungo bouillie avec du bouillon d&#39;os, mettez du ginseng, des châtaignes et du jujube, puis ajoutez-en un à la pieuvre. L&#39;Usamtang est un style d&#39;oeuf à la coque au lieu de la pieuvre.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;6&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Naksamtang - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, Corée du Sud (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/8d5fd99c-b6c5-4184-a7f7-6eb398302745.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Naksamtang
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Il y a cinq ou six restaurants de soupe sundae au début de la mine, en face de l&#39;entrée de la station Songjeong.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;6&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Marché de rue de la gare de Songjeong - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, Corée du Sud (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/e219acf6-393b-4493-8246-41ff3b59c163.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Marché de rue de la gare de Songjeong
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   En plus de Sundae Gukbap, la soupe de tête, Naejang Gukbap, Seonji Gukbap et Ampoon Sundae éclaircissent l&#39;estomac des voyageurs plus légers.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;6&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sundae Gukbap - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, Corée du Sud (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/58f2aec1-160e-4487-a499-f37b4c1ad57e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sundae Gukbap
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;7&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;15&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Wasabi sur le marché - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, Corée du Sud (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/f1b982b8-478e-4d38-9086-64a8c830ecf5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Wasabi sur le marché
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Info voyage
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Dragon Baby
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Adresse: 24 Sochon-ro 46beon-gil, Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Renseignements: Bureau de la culture minière, Division des sports 062-960-8251
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Wolbong Seowon
      &lt;br/&gt;
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     Adresse: 133 Gwanggok-gil, Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Contact: 062-432-1318
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.wolbong.org/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
      http://www.wolbong.org/
     &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Restaurants à proximité
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Poulpe Jangan: Naksamtang / 5, Gwangsan-ro 30beon-gil / Gwangsan-gu / 062-942-4545
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Songjeong Tteokgalbi (1re branche): Tteokgalbi / 1, Gwangsan-ro 29beon-gil, Gwangsan-gu / 062-944-1439
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Jangsu Gukbap: Sundae Gukbap / 1-1, Mine-ro, Gwangsan-gu / 062-945-8533
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Hébergement
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Santamo Tourist Hotel: 10-11, Saam-ro 216beon-gil, Gwangsan-gu / 062-956-5000
    &lt;br/&gt;
    e-Motel: 13-12, Mujin-daero 231beon-gil, Gwangsan-gu / 062-430-5707
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Motel de luxe: 13-20, Mujin-daero 212beon-gil, Gwangsan-gu / 062-714-2110
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ Les informations ci-dessus ont été fournies en février 2015. Elles peuvent changer par la suite, veuillez donc vérifier avant de voyager.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Les informations telles que le texte, les photos et les vidéos utilisées dans cet article sont protégées par les droits d&#39;auteur de l&#39;Organisation coréenne du tourisme, de sorte que l&#39;utilisation non autorisée de l&#39;article est interdite.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, Corea del Sur - Honam Line KTX a Naduya, área minera de Gwangju</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/honam-line-ktx-to-naduya-gwangju-mining-area-42-es/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 20:56:07 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/honam-line-ktx-to-naduya-gwangju-mining-area-42-es/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-title=&#34;honam-line-ktx-to-naduya-gwangju-mining-area--42&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Estación Gwangju Songjeong - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, Corea del Sur (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/acf39ebe-6300-4c75-b577-2546cf4ee2a3.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Estación Gwangju Songjeong
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Honam Line KTX a Naduya, área minera de Gwangju
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, Corea del Sur
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   La sección de Honam Line KTX Express se ha extendido a la estación Gwangju Songjeong en Gwangju. KTX, que partió de la estación de Yongsan, llegó a la estación de Gwangju Songjeong en 1 hora y 33 minutos, y fue posible salir a Gwangju haciendo un viaje de un día en el área metropolitana. En las cercanías de la estación de Gwangju Songjeong, hay atracciones como el lugar de nacimiento de Yonga, Wolbong Seowon, Wolgye-dong Janggobun, el parque Songjeong y las ruinas de Sinchang-dong.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Conveniente para viajar en metro o ciudad frente a la estación Gwangju Songjeong
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Antes de que se completara la autopista de la costa oeste en 2001, era conveniente que los turistas en el área metropolitana usaran el peaje de la mina de la autopista de Honam para viajar a las provincias de Honam como Mokpo, Yeongam y Naju. Desde entonces, la aparición de la Autopista Gochang-Damyang siguió a la aparición de la Autopista West Coast, haciendo que el nombre de &#34;minería&#34; se desvaneciera en las cabezas de los turistas. Luego, con la reciente apertura de la línea KTX de Honam, el distrito minero con la estación Gwangju Songjeong revivió como un tema candente. Los residentes locales esperan que el número de visitantes a la estación Gwangju Songjeong aumente de 4,000 en promedio a 12,000.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;KTX en la estación de Gwangju Songjeong - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, Corea del Sur (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/a8d01ab7-1597-41ac-9729-c41f541ee3be.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     KTX en la estación de Gwangju Songjeong
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   El nombre &#39;Gwangsan-gu&#39; nació en 1988 cuando Songjeong y el condado minero se incorporaron a Gwangju. De los cinco distritos que conforman Gwangju, el área ocupa 222.9㎢ (44.05%), la más grande. Hay una estación de metro con el mismo nombre justo en frente de la nueva estación de la estación Gwangju Songjeong. El metro en Gwangju se extiende entre la estación de Okdong, la estación de Gwangju Songjeong, el aeropuerto de Gwangju, el centro de convenciones de Kimdaejung, Geumnam-ro, el salón de la cultura, la entrada de Hakdong y Jeungsimsa y la estación de vehículos de Yongsan. Los viajeros extranjeros pueden tomar la línea KTX de Honam y bajar en la estación de Gwangju Songjeong y trasladarse al metro para facilitar el transporte por Gwangju.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;El lago Mugunghwa se detiene en la estación Gwangju Songjeong - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, Corea del Sur (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/8e923e82-af6f-4390-b796-dc64894bc9dc.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     El lago Mugunghwa se detiene en la estación Gwangju Songjeong
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Parque Yong-A disfruta viaje literario en lugar de nacimiento
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Una de las atracciones turísticas más populares cerca de la estación Gwangju Songjeong en Gwangsan-gu es el lugar de nacimiento de Yonga. &#39;Yong-ah&#39; es un hijo de Park Yong-cheol (1904 ~ 1938) que trabajó como poeta durante la ocupación japonesa. Nacido en Gwangsan-gu, trabajó con Young-Rang Kim y Jung Ji-yong para publicar literatura literaria. El poeta publicó sus obras principales, Dejando barcos y enviándote en el tren nocturno, en La primera literatura de poesía. Aquí hay un vistazo a su poema Leaving Ship. La especialidad está grabada en la fertilización de granito de la cama de flores del niño dragón.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     Voy a ir / mi corta edad /
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     ¿Vas a enviar lágrimas?
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ¿Serán fáciles estos acogedores abrigos?
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     Incluso los ojos llorosos como la niebla
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Forma de pico maduro en cada pie del valle /
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     ¡Arrugas también ojos maduros! Seres queridos //
     &lt;br/&gt;
     No puedo olvidar al que lo tira /
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     ¿Qué tiene de diferente ser perseguido?
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Las nubes miran hacia atrás, el viento es blanco /
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     ¿Habrá escaladores frente a nosotros //(남성)
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Soy tan bonito / mi corta edad /(남성)
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     ¿Vas a soltarte con lágrimas?
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Fertilización ambientada en el lugar de nacimiento del dragón - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, Corea del Sur (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/ddb73935-d6cc-4c49-864e-add053f35644.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Fertilización ambientada en el lugar de nacimiento del dragón
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Probablemente sea por la canción del cantante Kim Soo-chul que este poema se nos acerca. Kim Soo-cheol cita una parte de los poemas del poeta Park Yong-chul en la canción &amp;lt;Go To Me Too&amp;gt;. El deseo de dejar las edades más jóvenes con lágrimas y encontrar un sueño fue la independencia del país para el poeta Park Yong-chul y para el cantante Kim Soo-chul. Aunque la dirección es diferente según los tiempos, el valor sigue siendo que mucha gente ama sus palabras y letras.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Retrato de poetas custodiando el patio - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, Corea del Sur (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/75ab670b-5ac5-47c2-993a-f500d165eb45.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Retrato de poetas custodiando el patio
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Conversaciones tácitas con poetas.
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Sigamos un poco más la vida literaria de Yonga Park. También publicó Literary Monthly y Literature, y tradujo e introdujo poemas y obras de teatro extranjeros. También trabajó como crítico literario, pero desafortunadamente murió a los 30 años. La causa de la muerte fue la tuberculosis. Además de su lugar de nacimiento, su fertilización, que graba Leaving Boat, también se establece en la ladera de Yangji, que conduce al Parque Songjeong.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   El lugar de nacimiento del poeta está rodeado de muros de piedra despejados con ocre. Es una casa de paja con un amplio patio, macizo de flores y jangdokdae. Quizás debido a sus actividades literarias con Jung Ji-yong y Kim Young-rang, mirar cada rincón de su lugar de nacimiento le recuerda naturalmente poemas como &amp;lt;Perfume&amp;gt; y Kim Young-rang&#39;s &amp;lt;Sunshine on a Stone Wall&amp;gt;.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Otra cosa que llama la atención es el gran pincel que pintó las caras de seis poetas. Fue utilizado en el Festival Literario de Yonga en 2014, e incluso hay un tablero de pintura en el patio, por lo que es menos animado. Los poetas de poesía como Kim Yun-sik, Jung In-bo, Byun Young-ro, Jung Yong-yong, Park Yong-cheol y Lee Ha-yun florecieron como vino de flores. Sus huellas también se pueden encontrar en el Museo de Literatura y Literatura (inaugurado en 2012) en Gangjin-eup, Gangjin-gun. Kang Jin es el lugar de nacimiento de Kim Young Rang. Al dejar el lugar de nacimiento de Yong-Ah, recuerdo la otra película representativa de Park Yong-chul, Sending You to the Night Train.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Casa de paja - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, Corea del Sur (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/17fcbc08-8b03-47ee-9313-e72b7ea6ccbf.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Casa de paja
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     Ahora, en el lejano invierno, día de primavera
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     Lo miraré
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Riendo como un día de primavera, apresura su tren
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     Esperaré.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     &#34;Olvídate&#34; Meaners Ríe así /
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     Dejame aprender
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Mientras camina por el camino áspero,
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     Sigamos el ejemplo.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Por fin será un seguidor.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;La cara del poeta vista desde la fertilización del parque Songjeong - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, Corea del Sur (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/6793ad6d-7d7d-4a0d-a54c-f922b0bddfda.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     La cara del poeta vista desde la fertilización del parque Songjeong
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Aprendí de Wolbongseowon, el pico alto
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Los pasos de los viajeros que disfrutan de los viajes literarios conducen a la exploración de sus votos. Wolbongseowon, ubicado en Gwangsan-gu, Gwangsan-gu, está bastante anticuado desde el estacionamiento hasta la entrada de Seowon. Esto se debe a que un muro de tierra bajo, perfectamente alicatado, pasa a través de un camino de la aldea. Wolbongseowon fue fundado en 1578, después de la muerte del maestro. Ahora se considera una de las ocho escenas de Gwangju.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Gobong es famoso como un erudito que intercambió la teoría con Toegye Lee Hwang. El auditorio principal de Seowon se llama Bingwoldang. Chungjo compró las nobles virtudes escolares de Gobong y le dio el título de &#34;Bingsim Snowwall&#34;. La amable lectura del jurado con la traducción al coreano se suma amablemente al disfrute del voto. El libro comienza con ‘Obtenga un libro y encuentre un maestro y ascienda a un ermitaño alto &#39;, y termina la sección central con‘ ¿Qué se lamentará luego dividido en dragones y cerdos? ’. &#39;Esforzarse hoy&#39; contiene lecciones.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   “La base del estado es tranquilizar a las personas. Solo después de que las personas se sientan cómodas se puede lograr la iluminación. Debe enseñarse después de que las personas se hayan fortalecido primero y las personas se hayan enriquecido. &#34;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Wolbongseowon View - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, Corea del Sur (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/db196ed4-3eac-4115-b420-18d04fcf5c49.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Wolbongseowon View
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Si tienes mucho tiempo, recorramos el camino de los filósofos. Este es un curso a pie desde Wolbong Seowon hasta Baekwoojeong, las ruinas de Kyujeonam, el mausoleo de Gobong y Khufujae.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;La cantidad de Bingwoldang, la sala de conferencias principal de Wolbong Seowon - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, Corea del Sur (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/0ec9602f-f344-483a-acce-20a9d9212d73.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     La cantidad de Bingwoldang, la sala de conferencias principal de Wolbong Seowon
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Ruinas en el centro, ruinas de Sinchang-dong y Wolgye-dong Janggobun
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Después de explorar el lugar de nacimiento y los votos del poeta, visita restos culturales que los turistas extranjeros no conocen bien, aunque estén en el centro de la ciudad. Las ruinas de Sinchang-dong y Janggobun de Wolgye-dong se encuentran cerca del intercambio de minas de la autopista de Honam.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Las ruinas de Sinchang-dong (número histórico 375) pueden decepcionarse porque es un campo sin calles ni museos. Sin embargo, según la descripción del Museo Nacional de Gwangju, hay muchas reliquias como la loza, la madera, la quilla y la laca que dan una idea de la cultura agrícola del primer siglo antes de Cristo. Imagine los días en que no habría entradas de auto o complejos de apartamentos, y puede imaginar que las personas eran un muy buen lugar para vivir en grupos. En particular, Shin Chang-dong recibió el sobrenombre de &#39;Fábrica Textil Antigua&#39; en la que se excavaron las reliquias de seda y arpillera más antiguas de Corea, cuerpos, bobinas de hilo y agujas de hueso necesarias para producir estas telas. En la sala principal del primer piso del Museo Nacional de Gwangju, se llevará a cabo una exposición especial hasta el 25 de mayo, &#34;El país de la seda, cultura textil de Sinchang-dong, Gwangju&#34;.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;5&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sitio histórico de Sinchang-dong - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, Corea del Sur (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/4e0190e6-2f28-430d-a7a6-8cae29027cf7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sitio histórico de Sinchang-dong
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Janggobun, Wolgye-dong (Monumento Local de la Ciudad Metropolitana de Gwangju Nº 20) lleva el nombre de la forma de la tumba. Fue descubierto durante la construcción del Parque de Ciencias Avanzadas de Gwangju en la década de 1990 y se cree que se construyó en los siglos 5 y 6. Un centro comercial y un complejo de apartamentos están construidos alrededor de la tumba y es un patrimonio cultural que es amado como un lugar para pasear por los ciudadanos.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;5&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Wolgye-dong Janggobun - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, Corea del Sur (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/4839be3a-141d-484f-89f6-6cea258f06a3.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Wolgye-dong Janggobun
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Termine su viaje con Tteokgalbi, Naksamtang y Sundae Gukbap
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Regrese a la estación de Gwangju Songjeong para probar las especialidades de la mina. La calle Tteokgalbi se formó alrededor de la oficina de Gwangsan-gu hace mucho tiempo, atrayendo los gustos de los viajeros. Si el olor a tteokgalbi horneado llena el callejón, no importa cuán codicioso, no puedes evitar relajarte. Hoy en día, los turistas japoneses y chinos también vienen a escuchar los rumores. Songjeongri Tteokgalbi tiene un sabor ligeramente diferente de una casa a otra, por lo que no tiene que recomendar una casa.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;6&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Songjeong-ri Tteokgalbi - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, Corea del Sur (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/12f8958a-72eb-48ff-bf36-d845ebd7adb8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Songjeong-ri Tteokgalbi
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Naksamtang también es un manjar en Gwangju. Gachas de frijol mungo hervidas con caldo de hueso de hueso, agregue ginseng, castañas y azufaifa, y luego agregue una al pulpo. Usamtang es un estilo de huevo cocido en lugar de pulpo.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;6&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Naksamtang - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, Corea del Sur (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/8d5fd99c-b6c5-4184-a7f7-6eb398302745.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Naksamtang
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Hay cinco o seis restaurantes de sopa de helado al comienzo de la mina, frente a la entrada de la estación de Songjeong.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;6&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Mercado callejero de la estación Songjeong - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, Corea del Sur (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/e219acf6-393b-4493-8246-41ff3b59c163.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Mercado callejero de la estación Songjeong
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Además de Sundae Gukbap, la sopa de cabeza, Naejang Gukbap, Seonji Gukbap y Ampoon Sundae hacen que el estómago de los viajeros más ligeros sea más ligero.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;6&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sundae Gukbap - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, Corea del Sur (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/58f2aec1-160e-4487-a499-f37b4c1ad57e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sundae Gukbap
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;7&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;15&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Wasabi en el mercado - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, Corea del Sur (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/f1b982b8-478e-4d38-9086-64a8c830ecf5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Wasabi en el mercado
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Información de viaje
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Bebé dragón
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Dirección: 24 Sochon-ro 46beon-gil, Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Consultas: Oficina de Cultura Minera, División de Deportes 062-960-8251
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Wolbong Seowon
      &lt;br/&gt;
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     Dirección: 133 Gwanggok-gil, Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Contacto: 062-432-1318
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.wolbong.org/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
      http://www.wolbong.org/
     &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Restaurantes cercanos
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Jangan Octopus: Naksamtang / 5, Gwangsan-ro 30beon-gil / Gwangsan-gu / 062-942-4545
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Songjeong Tteokgalbi (1.a rama): Tteokgalbi / 1, Gwangsan-ro 29beon-gil, Gwangsan-gu / 062-944-1439
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Jangsu Gukbap: Sundae Gukbap / 1-1, Mine-ro, Gwangsan-gu / 062-945-8533
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Alojamiento
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Santamo Tourist Hotel: 10-11, Saam-ro 216beon-gil, Gwangsan-gu / 062-956-5000
    &lt;br/&gt;
    e-Motel: 13-12, Mujin-daero 231beon-gil, Gwangsan-gu / 062-430-5707
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Motel de lujo: 13-20, Mujin-daero 212beon-gil, Gwangsan-gu / 062-714-2110
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ La información anterior se realizó en febrero de 2015. Puede cambiar después, así que verifique antes de viajar.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ La información como texto, fotos y videos utilizados en este artículo tiene copyright de la Organización de Turismo de Corea, por lo que está prohibido el uso no autorizado del artículo.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, Südkorea - Honam Line KTX nach Naduya, Bergbaugebiet Gwangju</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/honam-line-ktx-to-naduya-gwangju-mining-area-42-de/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 20:52:12 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/honam-line-ktx-to-naduya-gwangju-mining-area-42-de/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-title=&#34;honam-line-ktx-to-naduya-gwangju-mining-area--42&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Gwangju Songjeong Station - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, Südkorea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/acf39ebe-6300-4c75-b577-2546cf4ee2a3.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Gwangju Songjeong Station
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Honam Line KTX nach Naduya, Bergbaugebiet Gwangju
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, Südkorea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Der Abschnitt Honam Line KTX Express wurde auf die Station Gwangju Songjeong in Gwangju erweitert. KTX, das vom Bahnhof Yongsan abfuhr, erreichte den Bahnhof Gwangju Songjeong in 1 Stunde 33 Minuten, und es war möglich, einen Tagesausflug in die Metropolregion nach Gwangju zu unternehmen. In der Nähe des Bahnhofs Gwangju Songjeong befinden sich Sehenswürdigkeiten wie der Geburtsort Yonga, Wolbong Seowon, Wolgye-dong Janggobun, der Songjeong-Park und die Ruinen Sinchang-dong.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Bequem für Reisen mit der U-Bahn oder Stadt vor dem Bahnhof Gwangju Songjeong
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Bevor der West Coast Highway im Jahr 2001 fertiggestellt wurde, war es für Touristen in der Metropolregion praktisch, die Honam Highway Mine Tollgate zu nutzen, um in die Provinzen Honam wie Mokpo, Yeongam und Naju zu reisen. Seitdem folgte die Entstehung des Gochang-Damyang Expressway dem Aufkommen des West Coast Expressway, wodurch der Name „Bergbau“ in den Köpfen der Touristen in Ohnmacht fiel. Mit der kürzlichen Eröffnung der Honam Line KTX wurde der Bergbaubezirk mit der Gwangju Songjeong Station als heißes Thema wiederbelebt. Die Anwohner erwarten, dass die Zahl der Besucher der Station Gwangju Songjeong von durchschnittlich 4.000 auf 12.000 steigen wird.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;KTX an der Gwangju Songjeong Station - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, Südkorea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/a8d01ab7-1597-41ac-9729-c41f541ee3be.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     KTX an der Gwangju Songjeong Station
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Der Name &#39;Gwangsan-gu&#39; wurde 1988 geboren, als Songjeong und Mining County in Gwangju eingemeindet wurden. Von den fünf Bezirken, aus denen Gwangju besteht, nimmt das Gebiet 222,9㎢ (44,05%) ein, den größten. Direkt vor der neuen Station der Gwangju Songjeong Station befindet sich eine gleichnamige U-Bahnstation. Die U-Bahn in Gwangju verkehrt zwischen dem Bahnhof Okdong, dem Bahnhof Gwangju Songjeong, dem Flughafen Gwangju, dem Kongresszentrum Kimdaejung, dem Geumnam-ro, der Kulturhalle, dem Eingang Hakdong und Jeungsimsa und der Fahrzeugstation Yongsan. Ausländische Reisende können die Honam Line KTX nehmen und am Bahnhof Gwangju Songjeong aussteigen und zur U-Bahn umsteigen, um Gwangju bequem zu transportieren.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Der Mugunghwa-See hält an der Gwangju Songjeong Station - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, Südkorea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/8e923e82-af6f-4390-b796-dc64894bc9dc.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Der Mugunghwa-See hält an der Gwangju Songjeong Station
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Yong-A Park genießt literarische Reise am Geburtsort
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Eine der beliebtesten Touristenattraktionen in der Nähe des Bahnhofs Gwangju Songjeong in Gwangsan-gu ist der Geburtsort von Yonga. &#39;Yong-ah&#39; ist ein Kind von Park Yong-cheol (1904 ~ 1938), das während der japanischen Besatzung als Dichter arbeitete. Er wurde in Gwangsan-gu geboren und arbeitete mit Young-Rang Kim und Jung Ji-yong zusammen, um literarische Literatur zu veröffentlichen. Der Dichter veröffentlichte seine Hauptwerke &#34;Leaving Boats&#34; und &#34;Sending You in the Night Train&#34; in &#34;The First of Poetry Literature&#34;. Hier ist ein Blick auf sein Gedicht Leaving Ship. Die Spezialität ist in die Granitdüngung des Blumenbeets des Drachenkindes eingraviert.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     Ich werde gehen / mein junges Alter /
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     Wirst du Tränen senden?
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Werden diese gemütlichen Hafenarbeiter einfach sein?
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     Sogar die tränenden Augen mögen den Nebel
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Reife Schnabelform an jedem Fuß des Tals /
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     Falten auch reife Augen! Geliebte //
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Ich kann den nicht vergessen, der es wegwirft /
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     Was ist anders daran, verfolgt zu werden?
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Die Wolken schauen zurück, der Wind ist weiß /
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     Wird es Bergsteiger vor uns geben?
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Ich bin so hübsch / mein junges Alter /
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     Wirst du mit Tränen loslassen?
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Befruchtung im Geburtsort des Drachen - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, Südkorea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/ddb73935-d6cc-4c49-864e-add053f35644.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Befruchtung im Geburtsort des Drachen
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Es ist wahrscheinlich wegen des Liedes von Sänger Kim Soo-chul, dass dieses Gedicht uns nahe kommt. Kim Soo-cheol zitiert einen Teil der Gedichte des Dichters Park Yong-chul im Lied &amp;lt;Go To Me Too&amp;gt;. Der Wunsch, das jüngere Alter mit Tränen zu verlassen und einen Traum zu finden, war die Unabhängigkeit des Landes für den Dichter Park Yong-chul und für den Sänger Kim Soo-chul. Obwohl die Richtung je nach Zeit unterschiedlich ist, ist der Wert immer noch so groß, dass viele Menschen ihre Worte und Texte lieben.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Porträt von Dichtern, die den Hof bewachen - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, Südkorea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/75ab670b-5ac5-47c2-993a-f500d165eb45.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Porträt von Dichtern, die den Hof bewachen
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Unausgesprochene Gespräche mit Dichtern
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Lassen Sie uns das literarische Leben von Yonga Park etwas länger verfolgen. Er veröffentlichte auch Literary Monthly und Literature und übersetzte und führte ausländische Gedichte und Theaterstücke ein. Er arbeitete auch als Literaturkritiker, starb aber leider Mitte 30. Die Todesursache war Tuberkulose. Zusätzlich zu seinem Geburtsort befindet sich seine Befruchtung, in die das Leaving Boat eingraviert ist, am Hang des Yangji, der zum Songjeong Park führt.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   Der Geburtsort des Dichters ist von mit Ocker gerodeten Steinmauern umgeben. Es ist ein strohgedecktes Haus mit einem breiten Garten, einem Blumenbeet und Jangdokdae. Vielleicht aufgrund seiner literarischen Aktivitäten mit Jung Ji-yong und Kim Young-rang erinnert ihn das Betrachten jeder Ecke seines Geburtsortes natürlich an Gedichte wie &amp;lt;Perfume&amp;gt; und Kim Young-rangs &amp;lt;Sunshine on a Stone Wall&amp;gt;.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Eine andere Sache, die auffällt, ist der große Pinsel, der die Gesichter von sechs Dichtern bemalt. Es wurde 2014 beim Yonga Literary Festival verwendet und es gibt sogar ein Malbrett im Hof, so dass es weniger lebhaft ist. Dichter wie Kim Yun-sik, Jung In-bo, Byun Young-ro, Jung Yong-yong, Park Yong-cheol und Lee Ha-yun blühten wie Blumenwein. Ihre Spuren finden sich auch im Museum für Literatur und Literatur (2012 eröffnet) in Gangjin-eup, Gangjin-gun. Kang Jin ist der Geburtsort von Kim Young Rang. Ich verlasse Yong-Ahs Geburtsort und erinnere mich an Park Yong-chuls anderen repräsentativen Film, Sending You to the Night Train.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Strohes Haus - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, Südkorea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/17fcbc08-8b03-47ee-9313-e72b7ea6ccbf.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Strohes Haus
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     Jetzt, im fernen Winter, Frühlingstag
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     Ich werde es mir ansehen.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Er lacht wie ein Frühlingstag und eilt mit seinem Zug
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     Ich werde warten.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     &#34;Vergessen&#34; bedeutet Lachen Sie so /
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     Lass mich lernen
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Während Sie durch die holprige Straße gehen,
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     Folgen wir dem Beispiel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Endlich wird er ein Anhänger sein.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Das Gesicht des Dichters von der Befruchtung im Songjeong Park aus gesehen - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, Südkorea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/6793ad6d-7d7d-4a0d-a54c-f922b0bddfda.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Das Gesicht des Dichters von der Befruchtung im Songjeong Park aus gesehen
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Gelernt von Wolbongseowon, dem hohen Gipfel
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Die Spuren von Reisenden, die literarische Reisen genossen, führen zur Erforschung ihrer Gelübde. Wolbongseowon in Gwangsan-gu, Gwangsan-gu, ist vom Weg vom Parkplatz bis zum Eingang von Seowon ziemlich altmodisch. Dies liegt daran, dass eine niedrige, ordentlich geflieste Erdmauer durch eine Dorfstraße führt. Wolbongseowon wurde 1578 nach dem Tod des Lehrers gegründet. Es gilt heute als eine der acht Szenen von Gwangju.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Gobong ist berühmt als Gelehrter, der die Theorie mit Toegye Lee Hwang austauschte. Das Hauptauditorium von Seowon heißt Bingwoldang. Chungjo kaufte Gobongs edle Schultugenden und gab den Titel &#34;Bingsim Snowwall&#34;. Die freundliche Lektüre der Jury mit der koreanischen Übersetzung trägt zum Vergnügen des Gelübdes bei. Das Buch beginnt mit „Holen Sie sich ein Buch und finden Sie einen Lehrer und erheben Sie sich zu einem hohen Einsiedler“. Der mittlere Abschnitt endet mit „Was wird später beklagt, unterteilt in Drachen und Schweine? ’. &#39;Strive today&#39; enthält Lektionen.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   „Die Grundlage des Staates ist es, die Menschen zu beruhigen. Erst wenn sich die Menschen wohl fühlen, kann Erleuchtung gemacht werden. Es muss gelehrt werden, nachdem die Menschen zuerst gestärkt und die Menschen reich gemacht wurden. ”
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Wolbongseowon Ansicht - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, Südkorea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/db196ed4-3eac-4115-b420-18d04fcf5c49.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Wolbongseowon Ansicht
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Wenn Sie viel Zeit haben, gehen wir den Weg der Philosophen. Dies ist ein Wanderkurs von Wolbong Seowon nach Baekwoojeong, zu den Ruinen von Kyujeonam, zum Gobong-Mausoleum und nach Khufujae.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Die Menge von Bingwoldang, dem Hauptvortragssaal von Wolbong Seowon - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, Südkorea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/0ec9602f-f344-483a-acce-20a9d9212d73.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Die Menge von Bingwoldang, dem Hauptvortragssaal von Wolbong Seowon
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Ruinen in der Innenstadt, Ruinen von Sinchang-dong und Wolgye-dong Janggobun
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Nachdem er den Geburtsort und die Gelübde des Dichters erkundet hat, besucht er kulturelle Überreste, die ausländischen Touristen nicht gut bekannt sind, obwohl sie sich im Stadtzentrum befinden. Die Ruinen von Sinchang-dong und Janggobun von Wolgye-dong befinden sich in der Nähe des Honam Expressway Mine Interchange.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Die Ruinen von Sinchang-dong (historische Nr. 375) können enttäuscht sein, da es sich um ein Feld ohne Straßen und ohne Museen handelt. Nach der Beschreibung des Gwangju-Nationalmuseums gibt es jedoch viele Relikte wie Steingut, Holz, Kiel und Lackwaren, die einen Einblick in die landwirtschaftliche Kultur des ersten Jahrhunderts vor Christus geben. Stellen Sie sich die Tage vor, an denen es keine Zufahrten oder Apartmentkomplexe geben würde, und Sie können sich vorstellen, dass Menschen ein sehr guter Ort waren, um in Gruppen zu leben. Insbesondere wurde Shin Chang-dong als &#34;Alte Textilfabrik&#34; bezeichnet, da die ältesten Relikte aus Seide und Sackleinen in Korea, Körper, Fadenspulen und Knochennadeln, die zur Herstellung dieser Stoffe benötigt wurden, ausgegraben wurden. In der Haupthalle im ersten Stock des Gwangju-Nationalmuseums findet bis zum 25. Mai eine Sonderausstellung „Das Seidenland, Textilkultur von Sinchang-dong, Gwangju“ statt.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;5&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sinchang-dong Historische Stätte - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, Südkorea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/4e0190e6-2f28-430d-a7a6-8cae29027cf7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sinchang-dong Historische Stätte
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Janggobun, Wolgye-dong (Gwangju Metropolitan City Local Monument Nr. 20) ist nach der Grabform benannt. Es wurde während des Baus des Gwangju Advanced Science Park in den 1990er Jahren entdeckt und wurde vermutlich im 5. bis 6. Jahrhundert erbaut. Rund um das Grab befinden sich ein Einkaufszentrum und ein Apartmentkomplex. Es ist ein kulturelles Erbe, das als Ort für Bürger zum Bummeln geliebt wird.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;5&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Wolgye-dong Janggobun - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, Südkorea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/4839be3a-141d-484f-89f6-6cea258f06a3.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Wolgye-dong Janggobun
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Beenden Sie Ihre Reise mit Tteokgalbi, Naksamtang und Sundae Gukbap
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Gehen Sie zurück zur Gwangju Songjeong Station, um die Spezialitäten der Mine zu probieren. Die Tteokgalbi-Straße wurde vor langer Zeit um das Gwangsan-gu-Büro herum gegründet und zog den Geschmack von Reisenden an. Wenn der Geruch des Backens von Tteokgalbi die Gasse füllt, egal wie gierig, können Sie nicht anders, als sich zu entspannen. Heutzutage kommen auch japanische und chinesische Touristen, um die Gerüchte zu hören. Songjeongri Tteokgalbi schmeckt von Haus zu Haus etwas anders, sodass Sie kein Haus empfehlen müssen.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;6&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Songjeong-ri Tteokgalbi - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, Südkorea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/12f8958a-72eb-48ff-bf36-d845ebd7adb8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Songjeong-ri Tteokgalbi
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Naksamtang ist auch eine Delikatesse in Gwangju. Gekochter Mungbohnenbrei mit Knochenknochenbrühe, Ginseng, Kastanien und Jujube hineingeben und dann zum Oktopus geben. Usamtang ist eine Art gekochtes gekochtes Ei anstelle von Tintenfisch.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;6&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Naksamtang - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, Südkorea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/8d5fd99c-b6c5-4184-a7f7-6eb398302745.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Naksamtang
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Es gibt fünf oder sechs Eisbecher-Suppen-Restaurants am Anfang der Mine, gegenüber dem Eingang zur Songjeong-Station.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;6&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Straßenmarkt der Station Songjeong - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, Südkorea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/e219acf6-393b-4493-8246-41ff3b59c163.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Straßenmarkt der Station Songjeong
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Neben Sundae Gukbap machen Kopfsuppe, Naejang Gukbap, Seonji Gukbap und Ampoon Sundae den Magen leichter Reisender leichter.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;6&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Eisbecher Gukbap - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, Südkorea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/58f2aec1-160e-4487-a499-f37b4c1ad57e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Eisbecher Gukbap
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;7&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;15&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Wasabi auf dem Markt - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, Südkorea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/f1b982b8-478e-4d38-9086-64a8c830ecf5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Wasabi auf dem Markt
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Reiseinformationen
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Drachenbaby
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Adresse: 24 Sochon-ro 46beon-gil, Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Anfragen: Minenkulturbüro, Sportabteilung 062-960-8251
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Wolbong Seowon
      &lt;br/&gt;
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     Adresse: 133 Gwanggok-gil, Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Kontakt: 062-432-1318
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.wolbong.org/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
      http://www.wolbong.org/
     &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Restaurants in der Nähe
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Jangan Octopus: Naksamtang / 5, Gwangsan-ro 30beon-gil / Gwangsan-gu / 062-942-4545
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Songjeong Tteokgalbi (1. Zweig): Tteokgalbi / 1, Gwangsan-ro 29beon-gil, Gwangsan-gu / 062-944-1439
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Jangsu Gukbap: Eisbecher Gukbap / 1-1, Mine-ro, Gwangsan-gu / 062-945-8533
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Unterkunft
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Santamo Tourist Hotel: 10-11, Saam-ro 216beon-gil, Gwangsan-gu / 062-956-5000
    &lt;br/&gt;
    e-Motel: 13-12, Mujin-daero 231beon-gil, Gwangsan-gu / 062-430-5707
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Luxus-Motel: 13-20, Mujin-daero 212beon-gil, Gwangsan-gu / 062-714-2110
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ Die oben genannten Informationen wurden im Februar 2015 erstellt. Sie können sich später ändern. Bitte überprüfen Sie dies, bevor Sie reisen.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Die in diesem Artikel verwendeten Informationen wie Text, Fotos und Videos sind von der Korea Tourism Organization urheberrechtlich geschützt. Daher ist die unbefugte Verwendung des Artikels untersagt.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>韩国光州光山区 - 湖南线KTX至光州矿区纳杜亚</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/honam-line-ktx-to-naduya-gwangju-mining-area-42-zh-cn/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 20:48:14 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/honam-line-ktx-to-naduya-gwangju-mining-area-42-zh-cn/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-title=&#34;honam-line-ktx-to-naduya-gwangju-mining-area--42&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;光州松井站 - 韩国光州光山区 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/acf39ebe-6300-4c75-b577-2546cf4ee2a3.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    光州松井站
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   湖南线KTX至光州矿区纳杜亚
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    韩国光州光山区
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   湘南线KTX Express区段已扩展到光州的光州松亭站。 从龙山站出发的KTX在1小时33分钟内到达了光州松亭站，可以通过在大都会地区进行一日游去光州。 光州松井站附近有景点，例如永嘉出生地，卧龙水原，卧溪洞长谷本，松亭公园和新昌洞遗址。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   在光州松井站前乘地铁或城市旅行都很方便
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   在2001年完成西海岸高速公路之前，大都市地区的游客可以方便地使用湖南高速公路矿山收费站前往湖南省，如木浦，灵岩和那曲。 从那时起，高昌至丹阳高速公路的出现紧随西海岸高速公路的出现，使“采矿”这个名字在游客的脑海中隐约可见。 然后，随着湖南线KTX的最近通车，光州松亭站的采矿区成为一个热门话题。 当地居民预计光州松井站的游客人数将从平均4,000人增加到12,000人。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;光州松井站KTX - 韩国光州光山区 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/a8d01ab7-1597-41ac-9729-c41f541ee3be.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     光州松井站KTX
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   “光山区”这个名字诞生于1988年，当时的松亭和矿山县并入光州。 在组成光州的五个区中，面积最大的是222.9㎢（44.05％）。 光州松亭站新站前有一个同名地铁站。 光州的地铁在玉洞站，光州松亭站，光州机场，金大中会展中心，金南路，文化馆，八洞洞和正心寺入口与龙山汽车站之间运行。 外国游客可以乘坐湖南线KTX，在光州松井站下车，然后乘地铁到光州周围，交通便利。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Mugunghwa湖在光州松亭站停靠 - 韩国光州光山区 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/8e923e82-af6f-4390-b796-dc64894bc9dc.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Mugunghwa湖在光州松亭站停靠
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   雍雅公园出生地文学之旅
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   光山区的光州松井站附近最受欢迎的旅游景点之一是永嘉的发源地。 “永亚”是朴容哲（1904〜1938）的孩子，在日本占领期间曾担任诗人。 他出生于光山区，曾与金扬朗和郑智勇一起出版文学作品。 诗人在《诗歌的第一部》中发表了他的主要著作《夜行中的离开船和送你》。 这是他的诗《离开船》。 该专业刻在龙孩花坛的花岗岩施肥上。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     我要去/我的年纪/
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     你要送眼泪吗？
     &lt;br/&gt;
     这些舒适的港口人会变得容易吗？
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     即使是水汪汪的眼睛也像雾一样
     &lt;br/&gt;
     山谷的每只脚上都有成熟的喙形/
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     皱纹也成熟的眼睛！ 亲人//
     &lt;br/&gt;
     我不能忘记丢掉它的那个人/
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     被追逐有什么不同？
     &lt;br/&gt;
     乌云回望，风是白/
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     我们面前会不会有登山者//
     &lt;br/&gt;
     我好漂亮/我的年幼/
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     你会流泪吗？
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;受精者在龙的出生地 - 韩国光州光山区 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/ddb73935-d6cc-4c49-864e-add053f35644.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     受精者在龙的出生地
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   这首诗离我们很近，可能是因为歌手金秀哲的歌。 金秀哲在歌曲《 Go To Me Too》中引用了诗人朴容哲的诗。 诗人朴容哲和歌手金秀哲的祖国独立，是他们渴望流泪，寻求梦想的愿望。 尽管根据时代的不同方向不同，但仍然有很多人喜欢他们的单词和歌词。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;守卫院子里的诗人的肖像 - 韩国光州光山区 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/75ab670b-5ac5-47c2-993a-f500d165eb45.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     守卫院子里的诗人的肖像
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   与诗人的无声对话
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   让我们再来看一下永嘉公园的文学生涯。 他还出版了《文学月刊》和《文学》，并翻译和介绍了外国诗歌和戏剧。 他还曾担任文学评论家，但不幸的是他在30多岁时去世。 死因是肺结核。 除他的出生地外，还在通往松井公园的杨吉山坡上刻有施肥，刻有“离开船”的字样。
   &lt;br/&gt;
   诗人的出生地被stone石清除的石墙包围。 这是一间茅草的房子，有一个宽院子，花坛和jangdokdae。 也许由于与郑智勇和金英朗的文学活动，注视着出生地的每个角落自然使他想起了《香水》和金英朗的《石墙上的阳光》等诗。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   引起您注意的另一件事是用大笔刷画了六位诗人的脸。 它曾在2014年的Yonga文学节上使用过，院子里甚至还没有油漆板，所以不太热闹。 金允植，郑仁波，边永禄，郑容勇，朴容哲，李河云等诗人如花开酒。 他们的足迹也可以在江津郡江津邑文学博物馆（2012年开业）中找到。 康镇是金英R的出生地。 我离开了雍亚的出生地，回想起了朴容哲的另一部代表性电影《送你去夜行》。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;茅草屋 - 韩国光州光山区 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/17fcbc08-8b03-47ee-9313-e72b7ea6ccbf.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     茅草屋
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     现在，在遥远的冬天，春日
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     我看看。
     &lt;br/&gt;
     笑得像春日，他赶火车
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     我会等。
     &lt;br/&gt;
     像这样的“忘记”意味着笑/
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     让我学习
     &lt;br/&gt;
     在崎the的道路上行走时，
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     让我们跟随这个例子。
     &lt;br/&gt;
     最后，他将成为追随者。
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;从松亭公园施肥看诗人的脸 - 韩国光州光山区 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/6793ad6d-7d7d-4a0d-a54c-f922b0bddfda.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     从松亭公园施肥看诗人的脸
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   从Wolbongseowon中学到
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   享受文学之旅的旅行者的足迹导致了对誓言的探索。 Wolbongseowon位于光山区的光山区，从停车场到水原入口一直很老套。 这是因为干净整齐的低泥土墙穿过乡村道路。 Wolbongseowon在老师去世后于1578年成立。 现在被认为是光州八景之一。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   高邦是著名的学者，他与Toegye Lee Hwang交换了理论。 Seowon的主要礼堂被称为Bingwoldang。 Chungjo购买了Gobong高贵的学校美德，并冠以“ Bingsim Snowwall”的头衔。 陪审团友善地阅读并附上韩文译本，使誓言更加有趣。 这本书以“得到一本书并找到一位老师并升为高隐士”开始，并在中间部分以“结尾”结尾，随后会感叹什么呢？ ’。 “今天奋斗”包含课程。
   &lt;br/&gt;
   “国家的基础是使人民安心。 只有在人们感到舒适之后，才能做出启迪。 必须先增强人民能力，使人民富裕之后再教它。 ”
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Wolbongseowon视图 - 韩国光州光山区 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/db196ed4-3eac-4115-b420-18d04fcf5c49.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Wolbongseowon视图
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   如果您有足够的时间，让我们走哲学家的道路。 这是从Wolbong Seowon到Baekwoojeong，Kyujeonam遗址，高邦陵墓和Khufujae的步行路线。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;卧龙水原主讲堂宾武堂 - 韩国光州光山区 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/0ec9602f-f344-483a-acce-20a9d9212d73.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     卧龙水原主讲堂宾武堂
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   市区，新昌洞遗址和卧溪洞杨甲洞的废墟
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   在探索了诗人的出生地和誓言之后，他参观了外国游客不太了解的文化遗迹，即使它们在市中心。 新昌洞遗址和沃基洞的Janggobun位于湖南高速公路矿山立交桥附近。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   新昌洞遗址（第375号历史遗迹）可能令人失望，因为它是一个没有街道，没有博物馆的领域。 但是，根据光州国家博物馆的描述，有许多文物，如陶器，木材，龙骨和漆器，使人们对公元前一世纪的农业文化有所了解。 想象一下没有车道或公寓大楼的日子，您可以想象人们是一个非常适合集体生活的地方。 特别是，申昌东被昵称为“古代纺织工厂”，因为它挖掘出了韩国最古老的丝绸和粗麻布文物，生产这些织物所需的尸体，线轴和骨针。 在光州国家博物馆二楼的主厅中，将举办一次特别展览，展览持续至5月25日，“光州新昌洞的丝绸之乡，纺织文化”。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;5&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;新昌洞古迹 - 韩国光州光山区 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/4e0190e6-2f28-430d-a7a6-8cae29027cf7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     新昌洞古迹
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   月陵洞的Janggobun（光州广域市地方古迹第20号）以这座陵墓的形状命名。 它是在1990年代光州高级科学园区的建设中发现的，据信建于5至6世纪。 坟墓周围建有购物中心和公寓大楼，这是一种文化遗产，备受市民欢迎。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;5&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Wolgye-dong Janggobun - 韩国光州光山区 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/4839be3a-141d-484f-89f6-6cea258f06a3.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Wolgye-dong Janggobun
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Tteokgalbi，Naksamtang和Sundae Gukbap完成您的旅程
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   返回光州松井站，品尝矿山的特色菜。 Tteokgalbi街很久以前就在光山区办公室周围形成，吸引了旅行者的口味。 如果烘烤tteokgalbi的味道弥漫在巷子里，无论多么贪婪，您都无法放松。 如今，日本和中国游客也来听听这一谣言。 Songjeongri Tteokgalbi的房子之间的味道略有不同，因此您不必推荐房子。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;6&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;松亭里 - 韩国光州光山区 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/12f8958a-72eb-48ff-bf36-d845ebd7adb8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     松亭里
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Naksamtang也是光州的美味佳肴。 煮沸的绿豆粥加骨汤，放入人参，栗子和枣，再在章鱼中加一。 Usamtang是一种水煮鸡蛋而不是章鱼的样式。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;6&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;那空三 - 韩国光州光山区 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/8d5fd99c-b6c5-4184-a7f7-6eb398302745.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     那空三
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   矿山的开头有5到6个圣代汤店，就在Songjeong站的入口对面。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;6&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;松井站街市场 - 韩国光州光山区 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/e219acf6-393b-4493-8246-41ff3b59c163.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     松井站街市场
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   除了圣代凉拌面外，还有头汤，Naejang Gukbap，Seonji Gukbap和Ampoon Sundae可使较轻的旅行者的胃更轻。
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;6&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sundae Gukbap - 韩国光州光山区 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/58f2aec1-160e-4487-a499-f37b4c1ad57e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sundae Gukbap
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;7&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;15&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;山葵在市场上 - 韩国光州光山区 (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/f1b982b8-478e-4d38-9086-64a8c830ecf5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     山葵在市场上
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   旅游信息
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      龙宝宝
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     地址：光州广山区广川路46道街24号
     &lt;br/&gt;
     咨询处：矿山文化厅体育课062-960-8251
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      沃丰西旺
      &lt;br/&gt;
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     地址：光州市广山区区光谷街133号
     &lt;br/&gt;
     联络电话：062-432-1318
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.wolbong.org/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
      http://www.wolbong.org/
     &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1.附近的餐馆
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Jangan章鱼：Naksamtang /光山路30beon-gil 30光山区/光山区/ 062-942-4545
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Songjeong Tteokgalbi（1st Branch）：Tteokgalbi /光山区光山路29beon-gil 1，1，/ 062-944-1439
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Jangsu Gukbap：Sundae Gukbap /光山区矿山路1-1 / 062-945-8533
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2.住宿
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    桑塔莫旅游饭店：光山区216-beon-gil沙姆路10-11，062-956-5000
    &lt;br/&gt;
    电子汽车旅馆：光山区广域市231街木津大路13-12号/ 062-430-5707
    &lt;br/&gt;
    豪华汽车旅馆：光山区武进大路212街街13-20号/ 062-714-2110
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※以上信息为2015年2月的信息。之后可能发生变更，因此请在旅行前确认。
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※本文中使用的文字，照片和视频等信息受韩国旅游组织版权保护，因此禁止未经授权使用本文。
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, South Korea - Honam Line KTX to Naduya, Gwangju Mining Area</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/honam-line-ktx-to-naduya-gwangju-mining-area-42/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 20:44:16 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/honam-line-ktx-to-naduya-gwangju-mining-area-42/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-title=&#34;honam-line-ktx-to-naduya-gwangju-mining-area--42&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Gwangju Songjeong Station - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/acf39ebe-6300-4c75-b577-2546cf4ee2a3.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Gwangju Songjeong Station
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   Honam Line KTX to Naduya, Gwangju Mining Area
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, South Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The Honam Line KTX Express section has been extended to Gwangju Songjeong Station in Gwangju. KTX, which departed from Yongsan Station, arrived at Gwangju Songjeong Station in 1 hour 33 minutes, and it was possible to go out to Gwangju by taking a day trip in the metropolitan area. In the vicinity of Gwangju Songjeong Station, there are attractions such as Yonga Birthplace, Wolbong Seowon, Wolgye-dong Janggobun, Songjeong Park, and Sinchang-dong ruins.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Convenient for traveling by subway or city in front of Gwangju Songjeong Station
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Before the West Coast Highway was completed in 2001, it was convenient for tourists in the metropolitan area to use the Honam Highway Mine Tollgate to travel to Honam provinces such as Mokpo, Yeongam, and Naju. Since then, the emergence of the Gochang-Damyang Expressway followed the emergence of the West Coast Expressway, making the name “mining” faint in tourists&#39; heads. Then, with the recent opening of the Honam Line KTX, the mining district with Gwangju Songjeong Station was revived as a hot topic. Local residents expect that the number of visitors to Gwangju Songjeong Station will increase from 4,000 on average to 12,000.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;KTX at Gwangju Songjeong Station - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/a8d01ab7-1597-41ac-9729-c41f541ee3be.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     KTX at Gwangju Songjeong Station
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The name &#39;Gwangsan-gu&#39; was born in 1988 when Songjeong and Mining County were incorporated into Gwangju. Of the five districts that make up Gwangju, the area occupies 222.9㎢ (44.05%), the largest. There is a subway station with the same name right in front of the new station of Gwangju Songjeong Station. The subway in Gwangju runs between Okdong Station, Gwangju Songjeong Station, Gwangju Airport, Kimdaejung Convention Center, Geumnam-ro, Culture Hall, Hakdong and Jeungsimsa Entrance, and Yongsan Vehicle Station. Foreign travelers can take the Honam Line KTX and get off at Gwangju Songjeong Station and transfer to the subway for easy transportation around Gwangju.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Mugunghwa Lake stops at Gwangju Songjeong Station - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/8e923e82-af6f-4390-b796-dc64894bc9dc.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Mugunghwa Lake stops at Gwangju Songjeong Station
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Yong-A Park Enjoys Literary Journey at Birthplace
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   One of the most popular tourist attractions near Gwangju Songjeong Station in Gwangsan-gu is Yonga birthplace. &#39;Yong-ah&#39; is a child of Park Yong-cheol (1904 ~ 1938) who worked as a poet during the Japanese occupation. Born in Gwangsan-gu, he worked with Young-Rang Kim and Jung Ji-yong to publish Literary Literature. The poet published his leading works, Leaving Boats and Sending You in the Night Train, in The First of Poetry Literature. Here&#39;s a look at his poem Leaving Ship. The specialty is engraved on the granite fertilization of the flower bed of the dragon child.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     I&#39;m gonna go / my young age /
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     Are you going to send tears?
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Are these cozy harborers going to be easy?
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     Even the watery eyes like the fog
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Ripe beak shape on each foot of the valley /
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     Wrinkles also ripe eyes! Loved ones //
     &lt;br/&gt;
     I can&#39;t forget the one who throws it away /
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     What&#39;s different about being chased?
     &lt;br/&gt;
     The clouds look back, the wind is white /
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     Will there be hill climbers in front of us //
     &lt;br/&gt;
     I&#39;m so pretty / my young age /
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     Will you let go with tears?
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Fertilization set in the dragon birthplace - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/ddb73935-d6cc-4c49-864e-add053f35644.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Fertilization set in the dragon birthplace
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   It is probably because of the song of singer Kim Soo-chul that this poem comes close to us. Kim Soo-cheol quotes a part of the poet Park Yong-chul&#39;s poems in the song &amp;lt;Go To Me Too&amp;gt;. The desire to leave younger ages with tears and to find a dream was the independence of the country for the poet Park Yong-chul, and for the singer Kim Soo-chul. Even though the direction is different according to the times, the value is still so many people love their words and lyrics.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Portrait of poets guarding the yard - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/75ab670b-5ac5-47c2-993a-f500d165eb45.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Portrait of poets guarding the yard
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Unspoken conversations with poets
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Let&#39;s follow Yonga Park&#39;s literary life a little longer. He also published Literary Monthly and Literature, and translated and introduced foreign poems and plays. He also worked as a literary critic, but unfortunately he died in his mid-30s. The cause of death was tuberculosis. In addition to his birthplace, his fertilization, which engraves Leaving Boat, is also set up on the slope of Yangji, which leads to Songjeong Park.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   The poet&#39;s birthplace is surrounded by stone walls cleared with ocher. It is a thatched house with a wide yard, flower bed, and jangdokdae. Perhaps because of his literary activities with Jung Ji-yong and Kim Young-rang, looking at every corner of his birthplace naturally reminds him of poems such as &amp;lt;Perfume&amp;gt; and Kim Young-rang&#39;s &amp;lt;Sunshine on a Stone Wall&amp;gt;.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Another thing that catches your eye is the large paintbrush that painted the faces of six poets. It was used in the Yonga Literary Festival in 2014, and there is even a paint board in the yard, so it is less lively. Poetry poets such as Kim Yun-sik, Jung In-bo, Byun Young-ro, Jung Yong-yong, Park Yong-cheol, and Lee Ha-yun bloomed like flower wine. Their footprints can also be found in the Museum of Literature and Literature (opened in 2012) in Gangjin-eup, Gangjin-gun. Kang Jin is the birthplace of Kim Young Rang. Leaving Yong-Ah&#39;s birthplace, I recall Park Yong-chul&#39;s other representative film, Sending You to the Night Train.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Thatched house - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/17fcbc08-8b03-47ee-9313-e72b7ea6ccbf.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Thatched house
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     Now, in the distant winter, spring day
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     I&#39;ll look at it.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Laughing like a spring day, he rushes his train
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     I&#39;ll wait.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     “Forget” Meaners Laugh like this /
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     Let me learn
     &lt;br/&gt;
     While walking through the rough road,
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#036071&#34;&gt;
     Let&#39;s follow the example.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     At last he will be a follower.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Poet&#39;s face as seen from Songjeong Park fertilization - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/6793ad6d-7d7d-4a0d-a54c-f922b0bddfda.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Poet&#39;s face as seen from Songjeong Park fertilization
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Learned from Wolbongseowon, the high peak
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The footsteps of travelers who enjoyed literary journeys lead to exploration of their vows. Wolbongseowon, located in Gwangsan-gu, Gwangsan-gu, is quite old-fashioned from the way from the parking lot to the entrance of Seowon. This is because a low dirt wall, neatly tiled, passes through a village road. Wolbongseowon was founded in 1578, after the death of the teacher. It is now considered one of the eight scenes of Gwangju.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Gobong is famous as a scholar who exchanged the theory with Toegye Lee Hwang. The main auditorium of Seowon is called Bingwoldang. Chungjo bought Gobong&#39;s noble school virtues and gave the title of ‘Bingsim Snowwall’. The kindly reading of the jury with the Korean translation kindly adds to the enjoyment of the vow. The book begins with ‘Get a book and find a teacher and rise to a high hermit, &#39;and ends the middle section with‘ What will be lamented later divided into dragons and pigs? ’. &#39;Strive today&#39; contains lessons.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   “The foundation of the state is to make the people at ease. Only after the people are comfortable can enlightenment be made. It must be taught after the people have been strengthened first, and the people have been made rich. ”
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Wolbongseowon View - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/db196ed4-3eac-4115-b420-18d04fcf5c49.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Wolbongseowon View
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If you have plenty of time, let&#39;s walk the path of philosophers. This is a walking course from Wolbong Seowon to Baekwoojeong, Kyujeonam Ruins, Gobong Mausoleum and Khufujae.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;4&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The amount of Bingwoldang, the main lecture hall of Wolbong Seowon - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/0ec9602f-f344-483a-acce-20a9d9212d73.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The amount of Bingwoldang, the main lecture hall of Wolbong Seowon
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Ruins in downtown, Sinchang-dong ruins and Wolgye-dong Janggobun
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   After exploring the poet&#39;s birthplace and vows, he visits cultural remains that are not well known to foreign tourists, even though they are in the city center. Sinchang-dong ruins and Janggobun of Wolgye-dong are located near the Honam Expressway Mine Interchange.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Sinchang-dong ruins (Historic No. 375) may be disappointed because it is a field with no streets and no museums. However, according to the description of the Gwangju National Museum, there are many relics such as earthenware, wood, keel, and lacquerware that give a glimpse of the agricultural culture of the first century BC. Imagine the days when there would be no driveways or apartment complexes, and you can imagine that people were a very good place to live in groups. In particular, Shin Chang-dong was nicknamed the &#39;Ancient Textile Factory&#39; in that the oldest silk and burlap relics in Korea, bodies, thread bobbins and bone needles needed to produce these fabrics were excavated. In the main hall on the first floor of the Gwangju National Museum, a special exhibition will be held until May 25, &#39;The Silk Country, Textile Culture of Sinchang-dong, Gwangju&#39;.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;5&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sinchang-dong Historic Site - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/4e0190e6-2f28-430d-a7a6-8cae29027cf7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sinchang-dong Historic Site
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Janggobun, Wolgye-dong (Gwangju Metropolitan City Local Monument No. 20) is named after the tomb shape. It was discovered during the construction of Gwangju Advanced Science Park in the 1990s and is believed to have been built in the 5 ~ 6th centuries. A shopping mall and an apartment complex are built around the tomb and it is a cultural heritage that is loved as a place for citizens to stroll.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;5&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Wolgye-dong Janggobun - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/4839be3a-141d-484f-89f6-6cea258f06a3.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Wolgye-dong Janggobun
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Finish your trip with Tteokgalbi, Naksamtang, and Sundae Gukbap
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Go back to Gwangju Songjeong Station to taste the specialties of the mine. Tteokgalbi street was formed around Gwangsan-gu Office a long time ago, attracting travelers&#39; tastes. If the smell of baking tteokgalbi fills the alley, no matter how greedy, you can&#39;t help but relax. Nowadays, Japanese and Chinese tourists also come to hear the rumors. Songjeongri Tteokgalbi tastes slightly different from house to house, so you don&#39;t have to recommend a house.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;6&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Songjeong-ri Tteokgalbi - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/12f8958a-72eb-48ff-bf36-d845ebd7adb8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Songjeong-ri Tteokgalbi
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Naksamtang is also a delicacy in Gwangju. Boiled mung bean porridge with bone bone broth, put ginseng, chestnuts and jujube in it, and then add one to the octopus. Usamtang is a style of boiled boiled egg instead of octopus.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;6&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Naksamtang - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/8d5fd99c-b6c5-4184-a7f7-6eb398302745.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Naksamtang
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   There are five or six sundae soup restaurants at the beginning of the mine, opposite the entrance to the Songjeong station.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;6&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Songjeong station street market - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/e219acf6-393b-4493-8246-41ff3b59c163.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Songjeong station street market
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In addition to Sundae Gukbap, head soup, Naejang Gukbap, Seonji Gukbap, and Ampoon Sundae make the stomachs of lighter travelers lighter.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;6&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Sundae Gukbap - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/58f2aec1-160e-4487-a499-f37b4c1ad57e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Sundae Gukbap
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;7&#34; id2=&#34;1&#34; id3=&#34;15&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Wasabi on the market - Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, South Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/42/f1b982b8-478e-4d38-9086-64a8c830ecf5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Wasabi on the market
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel info
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Dragon Baby
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Address: 24 Sochon-ro 46beon-gil, Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Inquiries: Mine Culture Office, Sports Division 062-960-8251
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;strong&gt;
      Wolbong Seowon
      &lt;br/&gt;
     &lt;/strong&gt;
     Address: 133 Gwanggok-gil, Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju
     &lt;br/&gt;
     Contact: 062-432-1318
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#660000&#34;&gt;
     &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.wolbong.org/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
      http://www.wolbong.org/
     &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     1. Nearby restaurants
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Jangan Octopus: Naksamtang / 5, Gwangsan-ro 30beon-gil / Gwangsan-gu / 062-942-4545
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Songjeong Tteokgalbi (1st Branch): Tteokgalbi / 1, Gwangsan-ro 29beon-gil, Gwangsan-gu / 062-944-1439
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Jangsu Gukbap: Sundae Gukbap / 1-1, Mine-ro, Gwangsan-gu / 062-945-8533
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     2. Accommodation
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    Santamo Tourist Hotel: 10-11, Saam-ro 216beon-gil, Gwangsan-gu / 062-956-5000
    &lt;br/&gt;
    e-Motel: 13-12, Mujin-daero 231beon-gil, Gwangsan-gu / 062-430-5707
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Luxury Motel: 13-20, Mujin-daero 212beon-gil, Gwangsan-gu / 062-714-2110
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was made in February 2015. It may change afterwards, so please check before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ The information such as text, photos and videos used in this article is copyrighted by Korea Tourism Organization, so unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>