<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Eunpyeong-gu on Every Corner of Korea</title>
    <link>https://codecorea.github.io/tags/eunpyeong-gu/</link>
    <description>Every Corner of Korea (Eunpyeong-gu)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 16:04:32 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="https://codecorea.github.io/tags/eunpyeong-gu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>&#39;Garden of Mind&#39;, like the mother&#39;s arms - Eunpyeong-gu, Seoul, Korea</title>
      <link>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/garden-of-mind-like-the-mothers-arms-164/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 16:04:32 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codecorea.github.io/posts/garden-of-mind-like-the-mothers-arms-164/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div data-address=&#34;Eunpyeong-gu, Seoul, Korea&#34; data-title=&#34;garden-of-mind-like-the-mothers-arms--164&#34; id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
   &lt;button id=&#34;0&#34; id2=&#34;2&#34; id3=&#34;0&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;Monks sharing a conversation with visitors at Hyorimwon - Eunpyeong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/164/d85e7755-7b04-4c5b-98c0-ed325827fec7.jpg&#34;/&gt;
   &lt;/button&gt;
   &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
    Monks sharing a conversation with visitors at Hyorimwon
   &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;tit_cont&#34;&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;
   &#39;Garden of Mind&#39;, like the mother&#39;s arms
  &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;area_address&#34;&gt;
   &lt;h2 class=&#34;address&#34;&gt;
    Eunpyeong-gu, Seoul, Korea
   &lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- 팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
  &lt;!-- //팝업 메뉴 --&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&#34;box_txtPhoto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Jingwansa is a mother-like temple. It is near, so you can visit it often, and the temple that you embraced under the mountain of Bukhansan is also comfortable. In Jingwansa Temple, there is no monk&#39;s stern bamboo scolding his heart. Instead, there are garden-like temples, delicious and healthy temple foods like rice cooked by mothers, and programs to chat and learn while sipping tea with a graceful monk. It does not force the obsession of &#39;empty your heart&#39; or &#39;find me&#39;. Just as you came to your mother in your hometown, you can walk slowly through the temple like the back of my house.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Elegant Bhikkuni Temple, Jingwansa Temple
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Did you go 10km from Songchu IC on the Seoul Outer Ring Expressway? A mountain temple sits nicely beneath the ridge of the eagle, with its wings spread. Jin Gwan-sa, the successor of Sinhyeolsa Temple, was built in 1011 by King Hyunjong, the eighth king of Goryeo, who was built for the monk Jin Gwan who protected him from the fall of Queen Cheonchu.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;The Liberation Gate of Jingwansa Temple - Eunpyeong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/164/c5b9c99c-9b38-4cee-a610-e07821fca39e.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     The Liberation Gate of Jingwansa Temple
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Unlike any mountain temple where you have to drive into the parking lot for a long time, Jingwansa Temple is near the parking lot and the temple. The mother-like officer walks out to the front door and asks the visitor &#39;Come on&#39;. After passing through Iljumun, there is a Gukrak Bridge in front of Haetalmun, which raised the roof of Pajak. If you cross this bridge, you will be in the grounds of Jingwansa. There is a well-maintained wooden deck path next to the bridge. Although it is about 100m short, it is the treasure trail of Jingwansa where you can experience the cool greenery of Jingwansa Valley. Be sure to walk when entering or leaving the temple.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A wooden deck path leading to the temple along the Jingwansa Valley - Eunpyeong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/164/b5f2b580-5fb2-43b1-b99b-27d6fab9257f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A wooden deck path leading to the temple along the Jingwansa Valley
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The fact that Jin Gwan-sa, which was greatly lost in the Korean War, now looks like the work of Jin Gwan, who came to Governor of 1963 and Gho Ho, the current Governor of 2006, was appointed. As both are Bhikkhunis, Jingwansa is a graceful temple where 13-minute Bhikkuni monks care for the temple. Jingwansa&#39;s peculiar delicacy and coziness have this connection and karma.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Jingwansa Yeonjiwon. Anyone can go with a cup of tea - Eunpyeong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/164/9c028927-c0a2-458b-b5e2-47902c3af2aa.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Jingwansa Yeonjiwon. Anyone can go with a cup of tea
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   When you cross the Gukrak Bridge and go up to the center of Jingwansa Temple, you meet Sesimgyo Bridge, the bridge that washes your mind. There is a prison in front of the bridge, and the second floor of the prison is a bomunwon where you can chat with a monk. On the left side of the prison is Yeonjiwon, where you can taste traditional tea. With tea, people, and small laughter and stories, this is the cultural space of Jingwansa. By lowering the threshold of the temple, it was created as a place where anyone can come and drink a cup of fragrant tea. The meaning in the amount of annual support is valuable. &#39;Songpungja&#39;s name (松風 煮茗)&#39; means that the tea buds are brewed with a breeze.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;1&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;4&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Name of the annual supporter blower name (松風 煮茗) - Eunpyeong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/164/fa558a56-7a89-4da5-9199-ad72855bbd62.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Name of the annual supporter blower name (松風 煮茗)
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Jingwansa Temple Food
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Behind Yeonjiwon, there is the fragrance of Hyangjeokdang and Jeho. It is the pride of Jingwansa Temple, and it is a unique tourist item and a place where you can experience temple food, which is attracting attention as an alternative food. Do not use onions, such as green onions, garlic, leek, soy sauce, and onions in temple food. Then what taste do you eat? It seems that the difference in food between Jinhae Temple and Jingwansa Temple was analyzed. Jingwansa&#39;s intestines have a mellow taste and make the most of the unique texture of the ingredients.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;5&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Jindangsa Temple&#39;s Jangdok University - Eunpyeong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/164/e555fed2-5b14-453f-9da5-86a09d67059b.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Jindangsa Temple&#39;s Jangdok University
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The secret of Jingwansa Temple food is timing and mind rather than skill. Governor Gyeho Ho, who has been studying temple food for a long time, chose &#39;clean, flexible, and method&#39; as the three principles of temple food. It boils and boils seasonal vegetables as they are, making them carefully prepared according to the Buddha&#39;s teachings. Sam Kass, Senior Advisor and Vice-Chairman of the White House&#39;s Nutrition Policy, whether it was a fresh cultural stimulus for the Gentiles, will experience the food of the temple in Jingwansa in 2015. &#34;It is said.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;6&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Master Kyeho who studied temple food &amp;lt;Photo courtesy, Jingwansa&amp;gt; - Eunpyeong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/164/a0d3a03f-25c5-47cf-ac14-97d68cc35037.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Master Kyeho who studied temple food &amp;lt;Photo courtesy, Jingwansa&amp;gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   In fact, it is difficult to handle the profoundness and strictness of eating food at temples, that is, approaching &#39;gongyang&#39; as a Buddhist doctrine. Buddhism teaching in every act of preparing food and eating it is so heavy that it cannot be followed. &#34;The existence of one body is created by eating, and disappears through eating.&#34; &#34;Where did this food come from? I am ashamed to receive it by virtue of my virtues. I receive this offering to get rid of all kinds of greed in my heart and to make a profession by knowing it as a medicine that supports this body.&#34; Uneasy. Can you follow me with every meal? To do that, you will have to go home. From the pagan interpretation, the Buddhist temple food is an alternative to the paradox of abundance, and I think it is a message that Buddhism throws in this era. Isn&#39;t it a personalized missionary missionary for the modern people who are taking the price of human greed packed with richness such as high fat, high calorie, and high protein?
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;7&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Jingwansa Temple Food - Eunpyeong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/164/bce88de8-18cb-4178-8e47-8434c8bd50fb.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Jingwansa Temple Food
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The difference and competitiveness of Jingwansa Temple food is that it is &#39;good and delicious&#39;. It&#39;s not stimulating, it&#39;s not boring, it&#39;s definitely fresh, but it doesn&#39;t feel like it is lacking. It would be because it filled something empty with something else. Haphae Monk, the general secretary of Jin Gwan-sa, called it &#39;Jung Sung&#39; &#34;So the rice that my mother gave me is delicious,&#34; she said.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;8&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Jingwansa temple food experience &amp;lt;Photo courtesy, Jingwansa&amp;gt; - Eunpyeong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/164/092acfca-4103-4c81-ae86-ca12e68bb517.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Jingwansa temple food experience &amp;lt;Photo courtesy, Jingwansa&amp;gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   There is no reason why the &#39;heart&#39; provider is not necessarily a mother. On July 15th (Sat) and August 19th (Sat), Jingwansa will hold the &#39;Happy Sansa Food Learned by Dad&#39; program. The first experience was completed successfully in June. Dads who participated in feeding and experiencing good things for their children were hot. It consists of an experience where you can make and taste Sansa food yourself and share a conversation with a monk. Participation fee is free! Dad must participate and 2 people can participate. It is highly recommended as the best must-have item for children with this summer vacation.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;2&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;9&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Jingwansa temple food experience &amp;lt;Photo courtesy, Jingwansa&amp;gt; - Eunpyeong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/164/72834d03-7564-4090-808f-55cd7f73d05f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Jingwansa temple food experience &amp;lt;Photo courtesy, Jingwansa&amp;gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34;&gt;
   Jingwansa&#39;s Taegeukgi and National Amphibious Goods
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   From Jingwansa&#39;s cultural space, go past Jangdok University and go to Daeungjeon Hall. While most of the temples are located on a hillside, the space in front of the Buddhist temple is cramped, while Jingwansa has a large lawn yard in front of Daeungjeon and Myeongbujeon.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;3&#34; id3=&#34;10&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Jingwansa Temple under the Eungbong Ridge of Bukhansan Mountain - Eunpyeong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/164/8bb2be38-0621-4b50-8045-162281ce701c.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Jingwansa Temple under the Eungbong Ridge of Bukhansan Mountain
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Before entering the courtyard of Daeungjeon Hall, you can see the Buddhist temple and the grounds of Jingwansa Temple in harmony with the mountains of Bukhansan in front of Nagawon where the monk is located.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;5&#34; id3=&#34;11&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Jingwansa Daeungjeon Front Yard - Eunpyeong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/164/f5a883f4-b0d1-455e-a9d4-687f04f9bf8f.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Jingwansa Daeungjeon Front Yard
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Toxic and Chilseonggak are next to Daeungjeon and Myeongbujeon. This building avoided fire during the Korean War along with Nahanjeon. The description of Chilseonggak contains pictures of the faded Taegeukgi and Noh Seung, along with a fairly detailed explanation. When the Chilseonggak was dismantled and restored in 2008, an old Taegeukgi was found among the pillars along with several anti-Japanese newspapers. This is one of the monks Baekchowol (1878 ~ 1944), one of the most famous anti-Japanese monks along with Han Yongwoon Manhae.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;7&#34; id3=&#34;12&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Transcendence monk&#39;s Taegeukgi - Eunpyeong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/164/66daa68e-94e1-4aba-85db-b06d55f213d8.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Transcendence monk&#39;s Taegeukgi
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Jingwansa&#39;s National Amphibious Property (Important Intangible Cultural Heritage No. 126) is a representative Buddhist ritual and a great history and culture content. Amphibious is a Buddhist ritual that preaches and provides illegal food to lonely souls and devils who wander in water and water. Jingwansa&#39;s national amphibious material was led and sponsored by the royal family directly after the Joseon Dynasty established an amphibious company in Jingwansa and provided amphibious materials. In the Annals of the Joseon Dynasty, it is confirmed that the amphibious ash was carried out at Jingwansa until the Yeonsan army.
   &lt;br/&gt;
   Jingwansa&#39;s amphibious materials are the only two-day and nighttime materials. If you want to experience the formal beauty of the comprehensive arts of Buddhism, you may want to participate in the amphibious goods of Jingwansa held in October every year.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;9&#34; id3=&#34;13&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;A bridge that washes the heart - Eunpyeong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/164/0b8b9d96-8c3d-4501-bd3c-96400106c527.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     A bridge that washes the heart
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   After looking around Daeungjeon and Chilseonggak, we descend to Sesimgyo in front of the prison.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;11&#34; id3=&#34;14&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;When crossing Sesimgyo Bridge, you will see a temple stay space. - Eunpyeong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/164/d564778e-ce81-455c-bc9c-728ec3e813a1.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     When crossing Sesimgyo Bridge, you will see a temple stay space.
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Pursuing the mind of Sesim (洗 心), cross the bridge and head to Hamwoldang.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;13&#34; id3=&#34;15&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Seated at Hamwoldang Maru &amp;lt;Photo courtesy, Jingwansa&amp;gt; - Eunpyeong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/164/7018181e-bd1c-4122-a829-7b41019882ea.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Seated at Hamwoldang Maru &amp;lt;Photo courtesy, Jingwansa&amp;gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   Hamwoldang (含 月 堂) with the moon and Gil Sang-won, Gongdeok-won, and Hyorim-won connected to the hillside are the temple stay history halls of Jingwansa.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;15&#34; id3=&#34;16&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Jingwansa Templestay History Hall - Eunpyeong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/164/3dba87fd-db0c-4e2b-9106-42ecb0d4db92.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Jingwansa Templestay History Hall
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   If there is not enough just walking through the &#39;Heart Garden&#39;, stay at Jingwansa Temple for a day and take a comma in your mind.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;17&#34; id3=&#34;17&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Inside of Hamwoldang &amp;lt;Photo courtesy, Jingwansa&amp;gt; - Eunpyeong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/164/b84658ed-0f58-4268-98f0-889be4cb6af5.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Inside of Hamwoldang &amp;lt;Photo courtesy, Jingwansa&amp;gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   The Templestay History Hall, which shines at the top prize in Seoul&#39;s architectural award, is the best space that adds the elegance and the elegance of hanok with the basic and sophisticated modern interior for efficient space utilization.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;19&#34; id3=&#34;18&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;Jingwansa Temple Stay History Hall &#39;Gongdeokwon, Hyolimwon&#39; - Eunpyeong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/164/6fd4938e-2569-4227-a14b-a3aae0be88d3.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     Jingwansa Temple Stay History Hall &#39;Gongdeokwon, Hyolimwon&#39;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   There are various templestay programs at Jingwansa depending on the theme and time, so it is worth choosing a program that suits you.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;img_typeBox typeFix clfix&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;3&#34; id2=&#34;21&#34; id3=&#34;19&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;
     &lt;img alt=&#34;&#39;Hyorimwon&#39;, the deepest part of history - Eunpyeong-gu, Seoul, Korea (https://codecorea.github.io)&#34; src=&#34;https://codecorea.github.io/images/164/46a949f6-c75e-4872-b9d5-cf33f2114ec1.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;strong class=&#34;tit&#34;&gt;
     &#39;Hyorimwon&#39;, the deepest part of history
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;strong class=&#34;ar_title&#34; id=&#34;titTrableInfo&#34;&gt;
   Travel information
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;txt_p&#34;&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Jingwansa Temple
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Address: 73, Jingwan-gil, Eunpyeong-gu, Seoul
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Inquiries: 02-359-8410
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.jinkwansa.org/main.asp&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.jinkwansa.org/main.asp
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Happy Sansa Food that Dad Learns
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Date: July 15 (Sat), August 19 (Sat) 10: 30 ~ 14: 00
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Program: making Sansa food, tasting Sansa food, tea ceremony experience
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Experience fee: Experience fee free ※ Papa participation required
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Inquiries: 02-359-8410
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Jingwansa Temple Stay
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Type of experience
    &lt;br/&gt;
    * On the day: only groups
    &lt;br/&gt;
    * 2 days and 1 night: both individuals and groups
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Main program: temple food experience, Dadam
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Experience fee: 700,000 to 100,000 won (100,000 won for 2 people per room)
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Inquiries: 02-388-7999
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Restaurants near
    &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Qua Levy &amp;amp; Quare: Bakery &amp;amp; Book Cafe / 101, Jinheung-ro, Eunpyeong-gu, Seoul / 02-356-7886
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Songchu Goreul: Tteok Galbi / 17 Hoguk-ro 527beon-gil, Jangheung-myeon, Yangju-si, Gyeonggi-do / 031-826-1515
    &lt;br/&gt;
    -Pyeongyangmyeonok: Naengmyeon, Galbi / 515, Hoguk-ro, Jangheung-myeon, Yangju-si, Gyeonggi-do / 031-826-4231
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     Rooms
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Prime Seoul Hotel: 816 Tongil-ro, Eunpyeong-gu, Seoul / 02-3157-8000
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.primeinseoulhotel.com/gnuboard4/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.primeinseoulhotel.com/gnuboard4/
    &lt;/a&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Bukhansan Hanok Pension: 75, Junggaegae-gil, Deokyang-gu, Goyang-si, Gyeonggi-do / 02-386-5397
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    -Pill Hotel: 281-1, Gamaggol-ro, Jangheung-myeon, Yangju-si, Gyeonggi-do / 031-877-5965
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.philhotel.net/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;새창&#34;&gt;
     http://www.philhotel.net/
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
     &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;font color=&#34;#cc0000&#34;&gt;
     ※ The above information was created in July 2017, and may be changed later, so please check before you travel.
     &lt;br/&gt;
     ※ Information, such as text, photos, and videos used in this article, is copyrighted by the Korea Tourism Organization, and unauthorized use of the article is prohibited.
    &lt;/font&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
   &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>